<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="15293" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2020-04-05</startdate>
<enddate>2020-06-21</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Honzuki no Gekokujou: Shisho ni Naru Tame ni wa Shudan o Erande Iraremasen (2020)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Honzuki 2</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">本好きの下剋上 司書になるためには手段を選んでいられません (2020)</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Ascendance of a Bookworm (2020)</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">책벌레의 하극상: 사서가 되기 위해서라면 뭐든지 할 수 있어 (2020)</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="official">هيمنة عثة كتب (2020)</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="15300" type="Prequel">Honzuki no Gekokujou: Shisho ni Naru Tame ni wa Shudan o Erande Iraremasen - Eustachius no Shitamachi Sennyuu Daisakusen / Corinna-sama no Otaku Houmon</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="757481">2nd season still a gem

It not finished by this time, a little chewy-gum wacky due changes in story envirement. Still good for all family. Let`s hope we see not just only kidd`ish story in the future - serious drama, complex questions, optimism &amp; deep personages in simplified graphics - that all seems still strong points of this show.

It seems there some minor graphic improvements - like one plot hole: all now wandering with "washed hair" (even orphans from church, o why?))))

Well, let`s all hope that this series will return good storytelling in mass animation instead school-ecchi-harem fanservice clones.

For now - best anime of spring 2020</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://booklove-anime.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="5808" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kaiya Toshihisa</name>
<name id="26189" type="Chief Animation Direction">Endou Emiko</name>
<name id="4233" type="Chief Animation Direction">Yanagida Yoshiaki</name>
<name id="44779" type="Music">Michiru</name>
<name id="1548" type="Direction">Hongou Mitsuru</name>
<name id="57580" type="Original Work">Kazuki Miya</name>
<name id="49612" type="Original Work">Shiina Yuu</name>
<name id="9774" type="Series Composition">Kunisawa Mariko</name>
<name id="4233" type="Character Design">Yanagida Yoshiaki</name>
<name id="5808" type="Character Design">Kaiya Toshihisa</name>
<name id="960" type="Animation Work">Ajia-dou</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a fantasy light novel series written by http://anidb.net/cr57580 [Kazuki Miya] and illustrated by http://anidb.net/cr49612 [Shiina Yuu].
With her baptism ceremony complete, http://anidb.net/ch101309 [Myne] begins work in the temple as an apprentice shrine maiden. Awaiting within is what she always wanted: a room full of books! But her new life isn`t quite the dream she was hoping for; she`s surrounded by nobles who scorn her commoner origins, and even her own servants are causing her trouble. On top of that, she has to constantly battle the weakness of her own body. But with her love for books burning in her heart, she gives her all to her new apprentice duties.
Source: J-Novel Club</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="70">8.71</permanent>
<temporary count="71">7.97</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>244323.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>23026</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>40815</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://booklove-anime.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Ascendance_of_a_Bookworm</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>本好きの下剋上</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5600</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>370769</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22245</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>anime_booklove</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="26">
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=8BQs59MW7tA</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=4dlZlBHQceQ</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=bD53ze25S_E</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ascendance-of-a-bookworm</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2637" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>time travel</name>
<description>In time travel anime characters are transported through time either figuratively or literally to find themselves either in the past or the future</description>
<picurl>210068.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2876" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>religion</name>
<description>Religion is a collection of belief systems, cultural systems, and worldviews that relate humanity to spirituality and, sometimes, to moral values. Many religions have narratives, symbols, traditions and sacred histories that are intended to give meaning to life or to explain the origin of life or the universe. They tend to derive morality, ethics, religious laws or a preferred lifestyle from their ideas about the cosmos and human nature.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3150" parentid="4522" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>social class issues</name>
<description>A character`s standing in society is cause of many issues. More generally, the society`s class structure is the source of many problems in the anime.
A common example is class division; a strong and rigid class division between rich/elite and poor/commoners, with the elites having disproportionately more privilege than the common class.
This can be applied not only when royalty and nobility are present, but also dystopian societies display often these divisions.
Another example is a division between employees and management, with employees akin to the common class, and management akin to the elite class.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3217" parentid="2864" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-17">
<name>working life</name>
<description>The life of someone actually working on a often less than glamorous job is depicted in this anime. The job is taxing and the pay is low, not really the dream job one would choose to work in.
Examples: Working as salesperson in a department store, or as a waitress in a family restaurant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3797" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-01-13">
<name>trapped in the body of a child</name>
<description>For some reason, a character in this anime who is a late-teenager or an adult, has their mind trapped in the body of a child. E.g. a former late teenager or an adult is transformed into a child. This can be the result of magic, science, or otherwise.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4271" parentid="2876" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-29">
<name>corrupt church</name>
<description>An official religion (not cult or sect) has become evil or was evil to begin with, and tends to be highly influential with political leaders, to strengthen / enforce the church`s power over the people.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4522" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>social commentary</name>
<description>Social commentary is the act of rebelling against an individual, or a group of people by rhetorical means. This is most often done with the idea of implementing or promoting change by informing the general populace about a given problem and appealing to people’s sense of justice. (Source: Wikipedia)&#13;
&#13;
Since this is anime, usually, the mores of Japan and the Japanese society are scrutinised, but not restricted to that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5604" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-04">
<name>following one`s dream</name>
<description>No matter what the hardships may be, at least one of the protagonists in this anime is following her/his dream.
Examples: To become a professional athlete, a musician, a painter or the ruler of this world!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5768" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>intact family</name>
<description>The main character`s family is a so-called "nuclear family". Wherein both parents are alive and present in his or her life. This is actually relatively rare for anime, where "parental abandonment" is the norm.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6744" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-05">
<name>isekai</name>
<description>An isekai story is one in which the lead characters are transferred to and become stuck or trapped in another world, one completely different from the one they lived in up until the transfer. The new world is commonly a http://anidb.net/t2628 [fictional world], such as a http://anidb.net/t2838 [parallel world] or http://anidb.net/t2839 [virtual world] (other fictional world types can also apply). What defines the isekai genre is that the characters are sent to another world, often but not always a parallel one, and they generally cannot come back permanently without meeting a highly specific goal.
In order to adapt to their new environment, they must use the abilities and knowledge brought from their former world as well as any that may have been bestowed upon them by their brave new world. In some cases, they will seek and eventually find a way to return; in others, they will gleefully embrace their new life.
http://anidb.net/a144 [Inuyasha] is an example where isekai applies to a fictional world that is not also a parallel or virtual world. http://anidb.net/ch7246 [Higurashi Kagome] climbs down an ancient well at her grandfather`s shrine and is transported to feudal Japan (time travel). While she eventually gains the physical ability to travel back and forth between her time period and feudal Japan, her bonds and responsibilities to feudal Japan tie her there until they are ultimately resolved.
For clarity, below is an illustrative example where isekai is applied to a non-fictional, non-parallel, non-virtual world.

* The main characters are from Earth. One day, they are abducted by Nazis from Mars (alternate "world") are brought back to their Martian base. The main characters are trapped on Mars. Their only escape is to defeat the Nazis and steal their spaceship to return to Earth (specific goal required to escape); they are left to thier own devices, with no prospect of help from Earth, and no way to contact Earth.
</description>
<picurl>210952.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="101308" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-08-07">
<rating votes="4">9.60</rating>
<name>Ferdinand</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237056.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27" picture="26123.jpg">Hayami Shou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101309" type="main character in" update="2019-12-29">
<rating votes="26">8.45</rating>
<name>Myne</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237046.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="516" picture="34813.jpg">Iguchi Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104911" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-08-07">
<rating votes="4">6.28</rating>
<name>Eva</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237048.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="157" picture="42784.jpg">Orikasa Fumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104912" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-08-07">
<name>Otto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237051.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="315" picture="70740.jpg">Hino Satoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104913" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-08-07">
<rating votes="3">6.18</rating>
<name>Gunter</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237049.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="267" picture="25729.jpg">Koyama Tsuyoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104914" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-08-07">
<rating votes="2">6.18</rating>
<name>Gustav</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237054.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2340" picture="151335.jpg">Naka Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104915" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-11-03">
<rating votes="3">8.05</rating>
<name>Tuuli</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237047.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="423" picture="37799.jpg">Nakajima Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104916" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-08-07">
<rating votes="2">6.17</rating>
<name>Frida</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237055.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1614" picture="148394.jpg">Uchida Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104917" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-08-07">
<rating votes="1">9.47</rating>
<name>Benno</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237052.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104918" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-08-07">
<rating votes="3">6.18</rating>
<name>Marc</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237053.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="612" picture="79531.jpg">Maeno Tomoaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104919" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-18">
<rating votes="3">5.44</rating>
<name>Lutz</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237050.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3712" picture="240126.jpg">Tamura Mutsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106235" type="appears in" update="2020-02-12">
<name>Ralph</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244417.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="55" picture="33603.jpg">Nabatame Hitomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106702" type="appears in" update="2019-11-03">
<rating votes="3">1.40</rating>
<name>Carla</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240719.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2355" picture="223496.jpg">Tachibana Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106759" type="appears in" update="2019-11-07">
<name>Corinna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240836.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42697" picture="223257.jpg">Kinugawa Rika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106832" type="appears in" update="2019-11-11">
<rating votes="3">2.44</rating>
<name>Deed</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240979.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29684" picture="157183.jpg">Takeuchi Sou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107457" type="appears in" update="2019-12-14">
<name>Ilse</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>242074.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2069" picture="246996.jpg">Yamaguchi Mayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108294" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-04">
<name>Gil</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244326.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="81" picture="41282.jpg">Sanpei Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108295" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-04">
<name>Delia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244325.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39785" picture="223235.jpg">Tomaru Chiyo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108296" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-02-06">
<name>Furan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244324.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33502" picture="246104.jpg">Karino Shou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109097" type="appears in" update="2020-04-04">
<name>Zasha</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>245684.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32949" picture="243218.jpg">Hino Mari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109098" type="appears in" update="2020-04-04">
<name>Sieg</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>245685.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39928" picture="181237.jpg">Yaehata Yukine</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109102" type="appears in" update="2020-04-04">
<name>Jenny</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>245694.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="48909" picture="223240.jpg">Nagano Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109103" type="appears in" update="2020-04-04">
<rating votes="1">1.20</rating>
<name>Shindenchou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>245695.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2067" picture="186243.jpg">Hoshino Mitsuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109366" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-12">
<name>Rosina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>246102.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="44135" picture="185214.jpg">Suzuki Minori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109367" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-12">
<name>Vilma</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>246103.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27357" picture="75009.jpg">Yasuno Kiyono</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="226864" update="2020-02-12">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2020-02-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">TVアニメ『本好きの下剋上 司書になるためには手段を選んでいられません』第二部番宣CM</title>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 01 (0:15)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">TV Anime "Honzuki no Gekokujou: Shisho ni Naru Tame ni wa Shudan o Erande Iraremasen" Teaser PV Dai Ni Bu Bansen CM</title>
</episode>
<episode id="227334" update="2020-03-06">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2020-03-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">TVアニメ『本好きの下剋上 司書になるためには手段を選んでいられません』第二部 本PV</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 01 (1:57)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">TV Anime "Honzuki no Gekokujou: Shisho ni Naru Tame ni wa Shudan o Erande Iraremasen" Dai Ni Bu Hon PV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="227713" update="2020-05-08">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-04-05</airdate>
<rating votes="5">8.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">神殿の巫女見習い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Apprentice Priestess</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">الكاهنة المُتدرِّبة</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinden no Miko Minarai</title>
<summary>Main is now an apprentice priestess at the cathedral. How will she adapt to a new life in new surroundings, and how will they react to her?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>794551</identifier>
<identifier>ascendance-of-a-bookworm</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="227714" update="2020-05-08">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-04-12</airdate>
<rating votes="3">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">青い衣と異なる常識</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Blue Robes and Uncommon Sense</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">ذوو الرّداء الأزرق والمنطق غير المألوف</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aoi Koromo to Kotonaru Joushiki</title>
<summary>The stark contrast of the values at the church compared to life downtown continues to bewilder Main, as she butts heads with her retainers and her expected duties at the church.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>794552</identifier>
<identifier>ascendance-of-a-bookworm</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="227715" update="2020-05-08">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-04-19</airdate>
<rating votes="3">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">与えるべきもの</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Needs</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">حاجات</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ataerubeki Mono</title>
<summary>With Fran now fully on her team, Main must then get to work on winning Gil and Delia over.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>794553</identifier>
<identifier>ascendance-of-a-bookworm</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="227716" update="2020-05-08">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-04-26</airdate>
<rating votes="2">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">孤児院の大改革</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Orphanage Reforms</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">إصلاحات الميتَم</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kojiin no Dai Kaikaku</title>
<summary>Main is taken to the orphanage and collapses in shock when she sees the state it and its inhabitants are in. She wants to help the kids, but will she really be able to?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>794554</identifier>
<identifier>ascendance-of-a-bookworm</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="228394" update="2020-04-19">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-05-03</airdate>
<rating votes="2">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大掃除と星祭り</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cleanups and Star Festivals</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">مهرجان النّجوم والتّنظيف</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oosouji to Hoshimatsuri</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>794555</identifier>
<identifier>ascendance-of-a-bookworm</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="228395" update="2020-04-19">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-05-10</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ルッツの行く道</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Path Ahead of Lutz</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">الطريق أمام لوتز</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Lutz no Iku Michi</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>794556</identifier>
<identifier>ascendance-of-a-bookworm</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="228396" update="2020-04-19">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-05-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">新しい側仕え</title>
<title xml:lang="en">New Retainers</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Atarashii Sobazukae</title>
</episode>
<episode id="228397" update="2020-04-19">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-05-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 8</title>
</episode>
<episode id="228929" update="2020-05-04">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2020-04-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="228930" update="2020-05-04">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2020-04-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
