<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="10041" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2014-06-28</startdate>
<enddate>2014-09-21</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Sabagebu!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Survival Game Club!</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">さばげぶっ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Sabagebu! Survival Game Club!</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">生存游戏社</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="9620" approval="37" total="42">Stella Jogakuin Koutouka C3-bu</anime>
<anime id="10011" approval="9" total="15">D-Frag!</anime>
<anime id="8829" approval="8" total="14">Upotte!!</anime>
<anime id="10770" approval="1" total="5">Mahou Shoujo Ore</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="4">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="77972">Very hirarious. There`s nothing like boring C3. Every characters are funny expectialy the main girl Momoka you will love how bad girl she can be.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="572074">Some may be turned off by its less-than-stellar animation. However, if you want to have some silly fun, then by all means give "Sabagebu!" a watch.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="736643">The best part is the narration!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://sabagebu.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="17916" type="Animation Work">Pierrot Plus</name>
<name id="5806" type="Character Design">Kudou Masashi</name>
<name id="6742" type="Series Composition">Aoshima Takashi</name>
<name id="29305" type="Original Work">Matsumoto Hidekichi</name>
<name id="7852" type="Direction">Oota Masahiko</name>
<name id="5259" type="Chief Animation Direction">Sakurai Masaaki</name>
<name id="5806" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kudou Masashi</name>
<name id="7802" type="Music">Misawa Yasuhiro</name>
</creators>
<description>The 15-year-old http://anidb.net/ch65824 [Sonokawa Momoka] transfers to Aogiri Academy High, an all-girls high school, due to her father`s frequent job relocations. Looking for a club that is different, she follows the mysterious http://anidb.net/ch65828 [Ootori Miou] to a club house at the edge of the woods and gets tricked into signing a club admission form for Sabagebu!, a club that conducts survival games. Club president Miou has to use some underhanded methods to convince the less-than-trilled Momoka to actually join...
And so Momoka`s far-from-boring survival game life at the club, together with cosplaying http://anidb.net/ch65827 [Goutokuji Kayo], Miou`s childhood friend and masochist http://anidb.net/ch65825 [Kasugano Urara], and part-time model http://anidb.net/ch65826 [Kyoudou Maya], begins.
— written by foo2
Note: The first episode was streamed online on NicoNico Douga as part of a special preview event on June 28, 2014. The regular television broadcast started on July 6, 2014.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1206">5.49</permanent>
<temporary count="1208">6.79</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>156226.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15600</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20709</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>25647</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://sabagebu.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Sabagebu!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>さばげぶっ!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3433</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>348500</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>17297</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>sabagebu-survival-game-club-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="627" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-15">
<name>lingerie</name>
<description>Lingerie is a term for fashionable and alluring women`s undergarments.</description>
<picurl>238327.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1077" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shoujo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shoujo, literally meaning "girl", refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1482" parentid="2751" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-09-08">
<name>wrestling</name>
<description>Wrestling is a fight between two people without weapons, in which each person tries to beat their opponent. Wrestlers use clinching, holding, locking, and leverage. It resembles ritual fighting as it avoids things that will likely lead to serious injury. It is similar to military hand-to-hand combat or self-defence systems.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1761" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-11-23">
<name>hunter</name>
<description>Hunting is the practice of pursuing any living thing, usually wildlife or feral animals, by humans for food, recreation, or trade. Animals may also hunt other animal species but this is usually called predation. In present-day use, lawful hunting is distinguished from poaching, which is the killing, trapping or capture of the hunted species contrary to applicable law. The species that are hunted are referred to as game, and are usually mammals and migratory or non-migratory gamebirds.&#13;
&#13;
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2635" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-06">
<name>jungle</name>
<description>This show features jungle(s) as one of its settings.
This can either involve jungle adventures or shady business revolving around deforesting of jungles or forests.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2654" parentid="2853" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-13">
<name>medium awareness</name>
<description>Medium awareness is the situational and generally temporary awareness characters in works of fiction have and display of the very fact that they are characters in works of fiction. For example, they may comment about the background music, quip about the script or narration, complain about the roles given to them by the writer or their lack of screen time, see the subtitles that appear on screen, inform the audience about the arrival of the commercial break, and even use medium effects as tools. The most common form of medium awareness is known as breaking the fourth wall, in which characters speak directly to the audience, either to it as a whole or to specific members of it. The "fourth wall" is the imaginary "wall" at the front of the stage of a proscenium theatre through which the audience sees the play; it is a metaphor for the boundary between what happens inside the work, to the characters, and outside it, to the audience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2658" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>toilet humour</name>
<description>Everything leads back to poo.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2751" parentid="2881" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-27">
<name>combat</name>
<description>Combat involves a violent conflict with the goal to establish dominance over an opponent.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2775" parentid="2202" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>humanoid alien</name>
<description>Humanoids are aliens, intelligent beings who do not originate from Earth, but have a striking similarity to humans or at least show the basic body layout, i.e. two arms and legs, head with two eyes and ears, one nose and mouth. Though the latter - head-related features - may vary. As "DearS" shows some aliens actually exhibit super-human beauty, or as in the case of "Onegai Teacher" they are genetically compatible to humans for some strange reason.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2823" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>paper clothes</name>
<description>Worn clothing appears paper-thin and takes little abuse to be shredded or torn from the body. This is common in ecchi anime where the main storyline involves some type of fighting but consists primarily of dialogue and fanservice (Ikkitousen and Platonic Heart). Various girls’ clothing exploding as if made of rice paper is a very enticing prospect.</description>
<picurl>150776.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2836" parentid="7082" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Australia</name>
<description>Australia, officially the Commonwealth of Australia, is a sovereign country comprising the mainland of the Australian continent, the island of Tasmania and numerous smaller islands. It is the largest country in Oceania and the world`s sixth-largest country by total area. The neighbouring countries are Papua New Guinea, Indonesia and East Timor to the north; the Solomon Islands and Vanuatu to the north-east; and New Zealand to the south-east. Australia`s capital is Canberra, and its largest city is Sydney.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192049.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3741" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-25">
<name>bullying</name>
<description>Bullying is the use of force, threat, or coercion to abuse, intimidate, or aggressively dominate others. One who engages in bullying is known as a bully.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3751" parentid="6243" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-02">
<name>grandiose displays of wealth</name>
<description>Some of the characters in this anime come from very wealthy families. A huge estate with large mansion or castle, a flotilla of expensive cars, private jets or islands, and many servants will impress the viewer profoundly.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3813" parentid="6185" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-23">
<name>winter</name>
<description>Coldest season of the year with ice and snow, everything is covered in a blanket of white.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4055" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>facial distortion</name>
<description>The characters face are exaggerated into a misshape, deformed, and almost warped. Used as comedy element to express extreme mood swings.
Differing from "http://anidb.net/t2652 [Super Deformed]", here only the face changes to an extreme degree, not the whole body of the protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4176" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-05-14">
<name>OP and ED sung by characters</name>
<description>OP and/or ED in this anime is sung by the characters and animation shows them singing.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4614" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>narration</name>
<description>The most common example is that of a voice, either that of one of the characters or entirely unrelated, that appears at the beginning of an episode to offer a summary or introduction, and at the end of an episode for closure or for a preview to hint upon what to expect next.
Another use of narration comes in the form of a dominant voice belonging to one of the protagonists, intended only for the viewer and revealing the intimate thoughts to whom it belongs. This type of narration occurs frequently throughout the duration of the episode or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5518" parentid="7199" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-03">
<name>flat chest jokes</name>
<description>Jokes about the (supposedly or actually) flat chest of a character.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5697" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-02">
<name>randomness</name>
<description>The anime does not follow a predictable storyline. New, strange, obscure, or otherwise unexpected story elements are introduced at a whim.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5875" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-18">
<name>jealousy</name>
<description>A character is jealous of another character either due to love, or power, or wealth.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5910" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-27">
<name>diet</name>
<description>One or more of the characters in this anime go on a diet, to lose some weight. Typically a female character will be extremely distressed that her clothes no longer fit, or that her ideal weight has been exceeded. Ironically, normal growth is often the explanation.
Since diets do not work, this ends up as a comedy element, with many ridiculous attempts to get slim quickly.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5980" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-24">
<name>live-action imagery</name>
<description>This anime incorporates still images and/or video footage of real-world objects and locations into the animation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6034" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>Engrish</name>
<description>Engrish is actually a mispronunciation of English, as can be the result of someone, who does not have English as their primary language of origin (such as Japanese or Chinese). Occasionally characters in the original Japanese dialogue version of an anime will speak in English... however; this often still requires the assistance of subtitles, for while the words are meant to be said in English, the sentence structure and letter pronunciation may still be strongly related to the person’s primary language.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6243" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-29">
<name>money</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6349" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-13">
<name>multi-segment episodes</name>
<description>Multi-segment episodes are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t5852 [short episodes], which are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length (up to and including 10 minutes).
Also not to be confused with an OVA or music video with multiple (otherwise unrelated) full-length http://anidb.net/t7241 [bundled episodes] consolidated into a single episode video track.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6480" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-02-26">
<name>gun - TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>This character uses at least one type of gun, or this anime has one character that uses at least one type of gun. Please tag the characters with the appropriate gun type tags (e.g. pistol, revolver, assault rifle, etc) and remove this tag from them or their corresponding anime afterwards. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7082" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-07">
<name>Oceania</name>
<description>Oceania is a geographic region comprising Melanesia, Micronesia, Polynesia and Australasia. Situated in the southeast of the Asia Pacific region, Oceania is the smallest continental grouping in land area and the second smallest in population after Antarctica.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214397.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7199" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-12">
<name>sexual humour</name>
<description>Sexual humour is prevalent in this anime. It often involves cheeky or crude sexual language, with innuendos and jokes about the female or male genitalia. Often, such anime also have http://anidb.net/t2856 [ecchi] elements to them.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="65824" type="main character in" update="2014-09-24">
<rating votes="33">8.13</rating>
<name>Sonokawa Momoka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>152009.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30554" picture="81681.jpg">Oohashi Ayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65825" type="main character in" update="2014-09-24">
<rating votes="21">8.31</rating>
<name>Kasugano Urara</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>152006.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10973" picture="78574.jpg">Ookubo Rumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65826" type="main character in" update="2014-09-24">
<rating votes="21">7.44</rating>
<name>Kyoudou Maya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>152007.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34901" picture="130616.jpg">Lynn</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65827" type="main character in" update="2014-09-24">
<rating votes="17">7.04</rating>
<name>Goutokuji Kayo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>152005.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21312" picture="232438.jpg">Touyama Nao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65828" type="main character in" update="2014-09-24">
<rating votes="21">7.81</rating>
<name>Ootori Miou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>152008.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23686" picture="224554.jpg">Uchiyama Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65842" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-03-22">
<rating votes="7">7.08</rating>
<name>Kamo</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>152010.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="68375" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-07-11">
<rating votes="9">5.17</rating>
<name>Sakura Ena</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>157920.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="61" picture="58663.jpg">Horie Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68376" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-07-11">
<rating votes="13">7.32</rating>
<name>Sonokawa Kazue</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>157919.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="240" picture="17059.jpg">Inoue Kikuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68377" type="appears in" update="2014-07-11">
<rating votes="4">5.41</rating>
<name>Haguro Rozeria</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>157918.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="70" picture="171604.jpg">Kanai Mika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68508" type="appears in" update="2014-07-09">
<name>Chikan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>157793.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29961" picture="79252.jpg">Tezuka Hiromichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68509" type="appears in" update="2014-07-09">
<name>Tenchou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>157792.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="343" picture="140430.jpg">Genda Tesshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69216" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-08-05">
<rating votes="6">3.61</rating>
<name>Karaage Lemon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159199.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28672" picture="84423.jpg">Arai Souta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69217" type="appears in" update="2014-09-24">
<rating votes="5">6.04</rating>
<name>Isurugi Yayoi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159201.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34361" picture="127753.jpg">Matsui Eriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69572" type="appears in" update="2014-08-21">
<name>Juushoku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159954.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16987" picture="86303.jpg">Shimoyama Yoshimitsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69573" type="appears in" update="2014-08-21">
<name>Fukukaichou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159955.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10410" picture="223211.jpg">Izawa Shiori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69574" type="appears in" update="2014-08-21">
<name>Gakushoku no Oba-chan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159956.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3368" picture="132584.jpg">Kujira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69575" type="appears in" update="2014-08-21">
<name>Roujin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159957.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6942" picture="41078.jpg">Takaoka Binbin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69576" type="appears in" update="2014-08-21">
<name>Rouba</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159958.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40709" picture="159960.jpg">Makihara Chika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69860" type="appears in" update="2014-09-05">
<rating votes="1">6.25</rating>
<name>Yummy</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>160479.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1625" picture="226033.jpg">Yuuki Aoi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70142" type="appears in" update="2014-09-21">
<name>Solomon no Akai Tora</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>161372.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34417" picture="128012.jpg">Motohashi Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70143" type="appears in" update="2014-09-21">
<name>Model</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>161374.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33660" picture="92231.jpg">Takano Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70144" type="appears in" update="2014-09-21">
<name>Akatsuki no Gekitsui Ou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>161373.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29676" picture="188717.jpg">Shimotsuki Yukari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70145" type="appears in" update="2014-09-21">
<name>Shiro no Datenshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>161375.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40456" picture="181638.jpg">Hayashi Daichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70147" type="appears in" update="2014-09-21">
<name>Inugami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>161376.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="82" picture="216596.jpg">Asakawa Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70148" type="appears in" update="2014-09-21">
<name>Kuneo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>161378.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="468" picture="17383.jpg">Kikuchi Masami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70149" type="appears in" update="2014-09-21">
<name>Yakuza</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>161377.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32937" picture="89644.jpg">Kagami Riki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70221" type="appears in" update="2014-09-24">
<name>Kaichou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>161590.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6942" picture="41078.jpg">Takaoka Binbin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70222" type="appears in" update="2014-09-24">
<name>Ten`in</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>161589.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="70" picture="171604.jpg">Kanai Mika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70223" type="appears in" update="2014-09-24">
<name>Kurofuku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>161591.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32937" picture="89644.jpg">Kagami Riki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70224" type="appears in" update="2014-09-24">
<name>Taichou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>161592.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="220" picture="17038.jpg">Kosugi Juurouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70225" type="appears in" update="2014-09-24">
<name>Jijii</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>161593.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4731" picture="27599.jpg">Saitou Shirou</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="160854" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-07-13</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ツインテールのワナ / 精神トレーニング / 沈黙のKILL or DIE</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Twin Tail Trap / Mental Training / Silent Kill or Die</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le piège de la miss à couettes - Préparation mentale – Tué ou être tué... en silence</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Twintail no Wana / Seishin Training / Chinmoku no Kill or Die</title>
<summary>Urara expresses hostility towards Momoka during morning training. 
The natto-hating Maya is cast for a natto commercial. 
In the club room after school, Momoka ends up alone with the silent Kayo...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>656871</identifier>
<identifier>sabagebu-survival-game-club-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="160855" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-07-20</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヤツが来る! 嵐を呼ぶ女登場!! / ヤツも来る! ヘルズチルドレンの挑戦!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">She`s Coming! The Woman Who Summons Storms Appears!! / She`s Coming, Too! The Challenge of Hell`s Children!!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Elle arrive ! La catastrophe ambulante débarque ! - Elle arrive aussi ! Le défi de la petite diablesse !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yatsu ga Kuru! Arashi o Yobu Onna Toujou!! / Yatsu mo Kuru! Hell`s Children no Chousen!!</title>
<summary>Survival Game Club advisor Sakura-sensei, the teacher who summons storms, thoughtlessly promises to exterminate a hornet`s nest.
Cheeky grade school student Haguro challenges the girls to a survival game battle!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>656873</identifier>
<identifier>sabagebu-survival-game-club-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="160856" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-07-27</airdate>
<rating votes="10">3.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">運命(笑)のボーイミーツガールwww / 痩せる意志を嗤う豚よ / カモなマイハウス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Boy Meets Girl of Destiny (lol) / Pigs Who Mock the Will to Lose Weight / My Platy House</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Destined (LOL) boy meets girl – La truie qui veut maigrir – Kamo tape l`incruste</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Unmei (Warau) no Boy Meets Girl www / Yaseru Ishi o Warau Buta yo / Kamo na My House</title>
<summary>Japan`s shooting game champion Fried Chicken Lemons and Momoka battle over a two-shot photo!
Momoka becomes overweight after eating too many sweet rolls.
Momoka plots to rid her house of the mysterious creature Platy.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>656875</identifier>
<identifier>sabagebu-survival-game-club-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="160857" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-06-28</airdate>
<rating votes="12">5.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">入部! / 入部と言ったな? あれは嘘だ / 本当はリアルなサバゲをやるつもりでした</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Joining the Club! / You Said You`d Join? I Lied! / I Wanted to Play a Realistic Survival Game</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Intégration - J`ai dit que je m`inscrivais ? Mais c`est faux ! - En fait, je voulais faire un vrai jeu de survie !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nyuubu! / Nyuubu to Itta na? Are wa Uso Da / Hontou wa Real na Sabage o Yaru Tsumorideshita</title>
<summary>While heading to her first day of school, Momoka is rescued from a pervert by a girl wielding Desert Eagles. 
After becoming friends with the school`s charismatic Miou, the other students begin harassing Momoka. 
As a member of the Survival Game Club, Momoka prepares for her first battle.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>656869</identifier>
<identifier>sabagebu-survival-game-club-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="161026" update="2014-07-05">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-06-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="161284" update="2014-07-13">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-07-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="161425" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-08-24</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">純白防衛線 / 白銀の狩人たち. ーー麻耶, 散る</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pure White Defense Force / The Silvery White Hunters. Maya Falls.</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ligne de défense pure ! – Les chasseuses en ghillies blancs. Cours, Maya</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Junpaku Boueisen / Shirogane no Karibito-tachi. Maya, Chiru</title>
<summary>Momoka is excited to work part-time as a model until the Photographers of Death appear...
Will Momoka and Fried Chicken Lemon be able to protect her purity? In a battle against a girls university survival game club, the survival game club finds itself overwhelmed by their superior numbers. The girls fall one by one. As the last one standing, Maya...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>656883</identifier>
<identifier>sabagebu-survival-game-club-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="161426" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-08-17</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">しゅりょうぶ! / オトコってやつは / HENTAI</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Hunting Club! / To Be a Man / Hentai</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Club de chasse ! – Ce qu`on appelle un homme – HENTAI</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shuryou-bu! / Otoko-tte Yatsu wa / Hentai</title>
<summary>An old hunter fights to protect his village from vermin.
When Momoka dresses like a man at a girls high school, she suddenly becomes popular!
A suspicious person has entered school grounds!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>656881</identifier>
<identifier>sabagebu-survival-game-club-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="161427" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-08-10</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">生徒会長石動やよいの復讐! / 呆れるほど仁義なき戦い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Revenge of Isurugi Yayoi, Student Council President! / Disgustingly Immoral Battle</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La vengeance de Yaoi Isurugi, la présidente du Conseil des élèves – Pitoyable combat sans code d`honneur</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seito Kaichou Isurugi Yayoi no Fukushuu! / Akireru hodo Jinkinaki Tatakai</title>
<summary>Student council president Yayoi plots to destroy the Survival Game Club!
Influenced by a yakuza movie, the Survival Game Club members launch into a lawless battle for the boss` seat!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>656879</identifier>
<identifier>sabagebu-survival-game-club-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="161428" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-08-03</airdate>
<rating votes="9">3.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">昇天!? しずかなるサバイバル / 死にぞこないのツインテ / 聖戦--天使と悪魔のラグナロク</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ascension?! Silent Survival / The Unkillable Twin Tail / Crusade: Ragnarok of Angels and Demons</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`ascension ? Jeu de survie zen – La Miss à couettes veut mourir – Guerre sainte : Le Ragnrök de l`ange et du démon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shouten!? Shizuka Naru Survival / Shi ni Zokonai Twin Te / Seisen: Tenshi to Akuma no Ragnarok</title>
<summary>"The Survival Game Club is disbanded." Miou`s suden announcement has the members at a loss.
Urara ends up stuck to the outer wall of the third floor for certain reasons.
Momoka discovers a model gun worth a million yen in the club room.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>656877</identifier>
<identifier>sabagebu-survival-game-club-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="162016" update="2015-05-08">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2014-10-29</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">SPECIAL MISSION 2: さばよんっ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special Mission 2: Saba Shorts!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Special Mission 2: Sabayon!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="162017" update="2014-08-12">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2014-09-24</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">SPECIAL MISSION 1: そして誰かいなくなった</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special Mission 1: And Then Someone Was Gone</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Special Mission 1: Soshite Dareka Inakunatta</title>
</episode>
<episode id="162208" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-09-21</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さらば友よ! サバゲ部最後の日! / サバゲ部より愛を込めて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Farewell, Friends! The Last Day of the Survival Game Club! / With Love from the Survival Game Club</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Adieu, mes amis ! Le dernier jour du club Sabage - Chaleureusement, de la part du club</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saraba Tomo yo! Sabage Bu Saigo no Hi / Sabage Bu Yori Ai o Komete</title>
<summary>When Momoka becomes infected by an unknown virus, the government`s fearsome and secret National Survival Game Club moves to restrain her. Miou announces the Survival Game Club`s mission to throw a birthday party for Urara! While Momoka is normally cold to Urara, she decides she should at least be nice to her on this day and does her best to prepare.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>656891</identifier>
<identifier>sabagebu-survival-game-club-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="162209" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-09-14</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゴテゴテデコ / ぜったいシンデレラ / 赤い流星</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gaudy Decoration / Total Cinderella / The Red Shooting Star</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Déco flashy - Je serai Cendrillon - Étoile filante rouge</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gotegote Deko / Zettai Cinderella / Akai Ryuusei</title>
<summary>Momoka enjoys her first trip to Shibuya in a while. She stops by a decoration shop and accidentally has Miou`s gun decorated... Drawn by promises of a reward, Momoka tries on high heel shoes! After her hellish training, will she be able to master the heel? A high-quality organic crab escapes from the pot?! The clever crab beats the club members one after another.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>656889</identifier>
<identifier>sabagebu-survival-game-club-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="162210" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-09-07</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">トレジャーハンター / かなしみのアイドル / さVP</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Treasure Hunter / Idol of Sadness / Survival VP</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Chasseurs au trésor – L`Idole triste – SAVP</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Treasure Hunter / Kanashimi no Idol / Sa VP</title>
<summary>A broke Momoka discovers a treasure map?! How does the Survival Game Club`s treasure hunt end?! National idol Yammy suddenly gained weight?! The Survival Game Club helps her diet, but Momoka`s intentions... The Survival Game Club gets lost in the jungle. A mysterious creature watches them. A magnificent battle to the death begins between the Survival Game Club and their invisible enemy.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>656887</identifier>
<identifier>sabagebu-survival-game-club-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="162211" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-08-31</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">犬かも物語 / 天国に一番近いプール / MAD 爺婆X</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tale of the Doggypus / Pool Closest to Heaven / Mad Grannies X</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Histoire de chiens... ou pas... – La piscine la plus proche du paradis – Mad vieux</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Inu Kamo Monogatari / Tengoku ni Ichiban Chikai Pool / Mad Jijibaba X</title>
<summary>Momoka dresses Platy as a dog and infiltrates a dog cafe where she goes head to head with the owner`s pet in a contest of training...
Urara, Maya, and Kayo are trapped inside the indoor pool.
Miou suddenly drags the Survival Game Club to Australia where they battle against a decrepit team of old men and women burning with fury for young people!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>656885</identifier>
<identifier>sabagebu-survival-game-club-</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="167110" update="2015-05-08">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2015-02-20</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">SPECIAL MISSION 6: 王様ゲームっ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special Mission 6: King`s Game!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Special Mission 6: Ousama Game!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="167111" update="2015-05-08">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2015-01-28</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">SPECIAL MISSION 5: 戻ってきたさばよんっ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special Mission 5: Return of the Saba Shorts</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Special Mission 5: Modottekita Sabayon!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="167112" update="2015-05-08">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2014-12-25</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">SPECIAL MISSION 4: 生徒会長石動やよいの逆襲!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special Mission 4: Student Council President Yayoi Isurugi`s Counterattack!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Special Mission 4: Seitokaichou Isurugi Yayoi no Gyakushuu!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="167113" update="2015-05-08">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2014-11-21</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">SPECIAL MISSION 3: 部屋の中の懲りない面々</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special Mission 3: Nobody In That Room Ever Learns</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Special Mission 3: Heya no Naka no Korinai Hitobito</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
