<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="10110" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2014-01-09</startdate>
<enddate>2014-03-27</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Mikakunin de Shinkoukei</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">미확인으로 진행형</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">未確認で進行形</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Engaged to the Unidentified</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">未确认进行式</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="10572" type="Side Story">Mikakunin de Shinkoukei: Kamo Nikutte Midorippoi Aji ga Suru no ne.</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="5909" approval="3" total="13">Toradora!</anime>
<anime id="193" approval="2" total="6">Ranma 1/2 Nettou Hen</anime>
<anime id="12091" approval="1" total="7">Kobayashi-san Chi no Maidragon</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="7">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="423685">This one is a relaxing, cutesy show which made the right decision to play around with stereotypes rather than to abide blindly by them. By no means special or extraordinary, MdS will fail to tick you off when you expect it to and will succeed in making you smile when you least expect. Way better than most of its "glamorous" compatriots in the rom-com parody niche.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="194756">Surprisingly good. Am enjoying this show much more than I thought I would, good humour, very likeable characters and arguably the OP and ED of the season.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="560966">Hilarious rom-com with an interesting plot twist; the main character is engaged to someone from her past, but she suffers from amnesia and so has no recollection.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="557271">It`s a really beautiful, heartwarming story, with a lil comedy and overall a reall nice watch! Very nice to just spend a good chill time, forget your problems and put a smile on your face :D</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="436338">Just relax and enjoy!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="107202">It is a good heart-warming show. Good comedy and fantastic animation. The OP and ED are wonderful, lovable characters, really underrated. 

Perfect to watch when you need something to raise your morale.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="596323">Perfect school comedy, nuff said.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://mikakunin.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="27082" type="Original Work">Arai Cherry</name>
<name id="8071" type="Character Design">Kikuchi Ai</name>
<name id="535" type="Series Composition">Shimo Fumihiko</name>
<name id="30322" type="Direction">Fujiwara Yoshiyuki</name>
<name id="8071" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kikuchi Ai</name>
<name id="11086" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ojiri Shin`ya</name>
<name id="2469" type="Chief Animation Direction">Amasaki Manamu</name>
<name id="6673" type="Music">Ichikawa Jun</name>
<name id="1067" type="Animation Work">Doga Kobo</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch59905 [Yonomori Kobeni], an ordinary girl, finds out on her 16th birthday that she is betrothed to http://anidb.net/ch59903 [Mitsumine Hakuya], a boy the same age as her. Hakuya moves in from the countryside and starts living with her, bringing his younger sister, http://anidb.net/ch59902 [Mashiro], who is still a primary school student with him.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2232">6.10</permanent>
<temporary count="2242">7.14</temporary>
<review count="1">5.83</review>
</ratings>
<picture>151350.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15618</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20541</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>22071</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://mikakunin.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Engaged_to_the_Unidentified</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>未確認で進行形</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3225</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>347830</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16676</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>engaged-to-the-unidentified</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1157" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>horny nosebleed</name>
<description>In Japanese media, healthy young men who have no other sexual outlet will often suffer nosebleeds upon seeing the naked female body, or even just a pair of well-filled panties.
The nosebleed is, of course, a visual shorthand/euphemism for sexual arousal. It is commonly interpreted that way for males and females, with little trickles of blood indicating mild arousal, and gushing fountains of blood indicating erection/extreme arousal in both sexes. It can also be interpreted as shorthand strictly for erections in males. In that case, when blood shoots from the nose explosively, and in ridiculous quantity, the implication would be an ejaculation.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>233513.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1471" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-19">
<name>bad cooking</name>
<description>The character is hopelessly terrible at cooking, and any attempts he or she makes at making even the simplest dishes are spectacular failures.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2555" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-07-14">
<name>amnesia</name>
<description>The character suffers from some kind of amnesia (memory disturbance or loss). This may mean inability to memorize new information, or inability to recollect old memories. Since there are many types of memory, the person may e.g. forget who they are but still retain learned skills.
Amnesia is fairly common in fiction as a plot device. In fact, because it allows for major plot changes while requiring little creativity from the author, it may be subject to heavy overuse.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2634" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>countryside</name>
<description>The anime takes place far from the any densely populated areas like cities, i.e. out in the suburbs, in the countryside with many fields and forests.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2784" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>sudden girlfriend appearance</name>
<description>Sudden Girlfriend Appearance anime involve a sudden change in the main character`s life where (s)he suddenly gets confronted with an individual (s)he`s sexually attracted to, the two of them inevitably becoming a couple.</description>
<picurl>210066.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2805" parentid="2798" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>4-koma manga</name>
<description>Yonkoma manga (4コマ漫画, four cell manga, or 4-koma for short), a comic-strip format, generally consists of gag comic strips within four panels of equal size ordered from top to bottom. (They also sometimes run right-to-left horizontally or use a hybrid 2x2 style, depending on the layout requirements of the publication in which they appear.) Though the word yonkoma comes from the Japanese, the style also exists outside of Japan in other Asian countries as well as in the English-speaking market.</description>
<picurl>70558.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2855" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-03">
<name>under one roof</name>
<description>For some reason or another, the main protagonist (e.g. male in harem / female in reverse-harem) is living together with many other characters of the opposite-gender, all under the same roof (in the same dwelling unit).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3020" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-08-01">
<name>chibi ED</name>
<description>Some or all of the endings feature chibi versions of the characters.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3606" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-11">
<name>family without father</name>
<description>For some reason the protagonists father is no longer among the living. The much too early death was due to sickness or accident.
This plot device adds a certain degree of tragedy to the anime and usually has repercussions on the rest of the family: Possibly the grieve-stricken mother and children barely function as humans. Or adding emphasis to the overall financial predicament of the family, should the father have been the money earner.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3813" parentid="6185" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-23">
<name>winter</name>
<description>Coldest season of the year with ice and snow, everything is covered in a blanket of white.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5843" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>sibling yin yang</name>
<description>In real life, siblings hardly ever act the same. Fiction sometimes takes this to an extreme.
Enter Sibling Yin Yang, the occurrence of siblings that are nearly polar opposites. If he`s cool and reckless, she`s responsible and thoughtful. If she`s a spiky-haired hooligan, he`s the nerdy wimpy one. If he`s an immature brat, she`s... well, you get the picture.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5954" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-17">
<name>call my name</name>
<description>"TETSUOOOOOO!!" "KANEDAAAAAA!!"
"TAMAHOMEEEE!!" "MIAKAAAA!!"
Feelings of any kind towards other characters are best shown by calling each other`s name, loud, REALLY LOUD. For better effect at least twice or thrice. For lover`s couples and mortal enemies it is a requirement to run towards each other while calling each other`s name, unaware of the surroundings.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6186" parentid="6185" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-29">
<name>spring</name>
<description>During spring, the axis of the Earth is increasing its tilt relative to the Sun, and the length of daylight rapidly increases for the relevant hemisphere. The hemisphere begins to warm significantly causing new plant growth to spring forth, giving the season its name. Snow, if a normal part of winter, begins to melt, and streams swell with runoff. Frosts, if a normal part of winter, become less severe. In climates that have no snow and rare frosts, the air and ground temperatures increase more rapidly. Many flowering plants bloom this time of year, in a long succession sometimes beginning when snow is still on the ground, continuing into early summer. In normally snowless areas spring may begin as early as February (Northern Hemisphere) heralded by the blooming of deciduous magnolias, cherries and quince, or August (Southern Hemisphere) in the same way. Many temperate areas have a dry spring, and wet autumn (fall), which brings about flowering in this season more consistent with the need for water as well as warmth. Subarctic areas may not experience spring at all until May or even June.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>161969.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="59902" type="main character in" update="2014-05-10">
<rating votes="98">7.80</rating>
<name>Mitsumine Mashiro</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>143364.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38546" picture="228695.jpg">Yoshida Yuuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59903" type="main character in" update="2014-05-10">
<rating votes="50">6.59</rating>
<name>Mitsumine Hakuya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>143363.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29" picture="202917.jpg">Hatano Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59904" type="main character in" update="2014-05-10">
<rating votes="71">4.44</rating>
<name>Yonomori Benio</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>143365.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34361" picture="127753.jpg">Matsui Eriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="59905" type="main character in" update="2014-05-10">
<rating votes="91">7.96</rating>
<name>Yonomori Kobeni</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>143366.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28437" picture="77562.jpg">Terui Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62016" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-05-10">
<rating votes="16">2.56</rating>
<name>Oono Niko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>146671.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38963" picture="147735.jpg">Kakumoto Asuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62017" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-05-10">
<rating votes="25">5.02</rating>
<name>Suetsugi Konoha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>146669.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1673" picture="41835.jpg">Fujita Saki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62018" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-05-10">
<rating votes="16">5.46</rating>
<name>Momouchi Mayura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>146670.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="25107" picture="76467.jpg">Aimi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62019" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-05-10">
<rating votes="27">6.91</rating>
<name>Kashima Nadeshiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>146668.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20762" picture="131325.jpg">Sakura Ayane</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62637" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-05-10">
<rating votes="11">5.19</rating>
<name>Yonomori Akane</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147816.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="24615" picture="73810.jpg">Watanabe Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="62638" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-05-10">
<rating votes="35">6.19</rating>
<name>Mitsumine Shirayuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>147817.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34714" picture="216072.jpg">Komagata Yuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67243" type="appears in" update="2014-05-07">
<rating votes="5">5.79</rating>
<name>Tannin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>155289.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38704" picture="145173.jpg">Kouda Yumeha</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67284" type="appears in" update="2014-05-07">
<rating votes="2">4.56</rating>
<name>Tannin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>155308.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38704" picture="145173.jpg">Kouda Yumeha</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67351" type="appears in" update="2014-05-10">
<rating votes="2">5.12</rating>
<name>Suugaku Kyoushi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>155414.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34524" picture="128595.jpg">Maeda Kunihiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67411" type="appears in" update="2014-05-13">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Saru</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>155516.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38947" picture="157014.jpg">Nishimori Rika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67435" type="appears in" update="2014-05-14">
<rating votes="14">4.46</rating>
<name>Yonomori Benio</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Young Benio.</description>
<picture>155570.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34361" picture="127753.jpg">Matsui Eriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67436" type="appears in" update="2014-05-14">
<rating votes="3">5.61</rating>
<name>Mitsumine Hakuya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Young Hakuya.</description>
<picture>155571.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="67437" type="appears in" update="2014-05-14">
<rating votes="11">6.26</rating>
<name>Yonomori Kobeni</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Young Kobeni.</description>
<picture>155572.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28437" picture="77562.jpg">Terui Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="157161" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-01-09</airdate>
<rating votes="18">5.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">何事も最初が肝心です</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It`s Important to Start Off on the Right Foot</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nanigoto mo Saisho ga Kanjin Desu</title>
<summary>Yonomori Kobeni is a whiz at housework, has a curvy figure, and is otherwise a completely ordinary high school student. On her 16th birthday, she is suddenly greeted by a fiancee, Mitsumine Hakuya (who is nearly invisible), and his little sister Mitsumine Mashiro (who appears to be a little girl). The two move in with her with little warning. Her sister Yonomori Benio is a pervert with a sister complex. Will Kobeni`s life be turned upside down or not?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648831</identifier>
<identifier>engaged-to-the-unidentified</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="157168" update="2014-11-14">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-01-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="157169" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-01-30</airdate>
<rating votes="15">6.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あれはただのへんたいです</title>
<title xml:lang="en">That`s Just Being a Pervert</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Are wa Tada no Hentai Desu</title>
<summary>Benio reveals information about Kobeni`s past. The sudden revelation causes a short in Kobeni`s mind and the shock leaves her bedridden. Benio takes over in the kitchen, and after a progression of nightmarish meals, Mashiro comes to appreciate what she`s lost in Kobeni.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648837</identifier>
<identifier>engaged-to-the-unidentified</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="157170" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-01-23</airdate>
<rating votes="15">6.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ラブコメの波動を感じる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Can Feel the Love Comedy Waves</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Love Come no Hadou o Kanjiru</title>
<summary>In gym class, Kobeni struggles with the vault. Her classmate Mayura claims "she does have a handicap, after all." Eventually Sunday rolls around, and while Kobeni busies herself with housework, Benio offers to help.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648835</identifier>
<identifier>engaged-to-the-unidentified</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="157171" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-01-16</airdate>
<rating votes="15">4.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ロリ小姑ってのも悪くないわ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It`s Not Bad Having a Loli Sister-in-Law</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Loli Kojuuto tte no mo Warukunai wa</title>
<summary>The sudden arrival of a fiancee and a sister-in-law has Kobeni at a loss, with. Her fiancee Hakuya is one thing, but despite her sister-in-law Mashiro definitely being a little girl, she somehow ends up in the same class at school.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648833</identifier>
<identifier>engaged-to-the-unidentified</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="157596" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-02-27</airdate>
<rating votes="15">5.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">妹の悲しみをいやすのは, 妹</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Only a Little Sister Can Soothe Sadness over a Little Sister</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Imouto no Kanashimi o Iyasu no wa, Imouto</title>
<summary>There`s nothing wrong with having a big butt. There`s nothing wrong with having big breasts, either. It`s actually a good thing. Setting that aside, the battle between Mashiro and Konoha continues. They go to the roof to have it out.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648845</identifier>
<identifier>engaged-to-the-unidentified</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="157597" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-02-20</airdate>
<rating votes="15">5.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">それはそれ, これはこれ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">That`s One Thing, This Is Another</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sore wa Sore, Kore wa Kore</title>
<summary>Suetsugi Konoha is the student council secretary and a devout Benio disciple. She has a friend, Ohno Niko. When Konoha burns with jealousy towards Mashiro, Niko agrees to help her investigate. She says she`ll do it "secretly," but doesn`t seem very good about that part.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648843</identifier>
<identifier>engaged-to-the-unidentified</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="157598" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-02-13</airdate>
<rating votes="15">7.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">そうだ, 小姑でうめよう</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Know! I`ll Fill It with a Sister-in-Law</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sou Da, Kojuuto de Umeyou</title>
<summary>It`s all about chocolate. Kobeni is worried. Hakuya is worried. Mashiro is worried. Mayura is laughing. "Valentine`s Day comes with all kinds of interesting human drama!" Nessie. Mongolian Death Worm. Yeti. Nessie. Nessie. Nessie. They say "Nessie" a lot in this episode.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648841</identifier>
<identifier>engaged-to-the-unidentified</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="157599" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-02-06</airdate>
<rating votes="15">7.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">これが経産婦だと</title>
<title xml:lang="en">This Woman Has Given Birth?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kore ga Keisanpu Da to</title>
<summary>A lovely young girl in Japanese clothing arrives. Although she seems too young for it to be true, she is apparently Mashiro`s mother, Shirayuki. Kobeni is nervous while Mashiro is tense. Benio is in anguish over Shirayuki`s youthful appearance, but eventually decides that "she`s got it." Meanwhile, a shocking truth comes from Shirayuki`s lips. Kobeni is distraught, uncertain of whether what she`s been told is the truth or not.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648839</identifier>
<identifier>engaged-to-the-unidentified</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="158190" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-03-27</airdate>
<rating votes="13">6.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">わかってる? わかってる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">You Understand? I Understand</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wakatteru? Wakatteru</title>
<summary>Hakuya and Mashiro have disappeared. Their things are gone. They`ve fallen out of contact. The house is quiet. Kobeni is worried and nervous. Mayura convinces her to head for the Mitsumine household.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648853</identifier>
<identifier>engaged-to-the-unidentified</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="158191" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-03-20</airdate>
<rating votes="14">4.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ハンカチを楽しんでるのよ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`m Enjoying My Handkerchief</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hankachi o Tanoshinderu no yo</title>
<summary>It appears that handkerchiefs are made to be enjoyed. Hakuya`s troubles continue from last week. Niko spots a UMA. It`s important to stay on guard even in the evening hours. Meanwhile, Kobeni and Hakuya grow closer. They go on a date (with a child along). The first step to delinquency is made.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648851</identifier>
<identifier>engaged-to-the-unidentified</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="158192" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-03-13</airdate>
<rating votes="14">5.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">デレ期という単語を調べたら</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Looked Up the Term "Time of Dere"</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dereki to Iu Tango o Shirabetara</title>
<summary>Hakuya is concerned about White Day. Mashiro takes him to task. Benio swoons. Kobeni is mai waifu. The lovey-dovey deepens. Kobeni is a good girl. Konoha is also a good girl. Niko is a good girl, but she`s also on the rampage.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648849</identifier>
<identifier>engaged-to-the-unidentified</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="158193" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-03-06</airdate>
<rating votes="14">4.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">くつじょくです, はずかしめをうけました</title>
<title xml:lang="en">How Humiliating, I`m So Embarrassed</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kutsujoku Desu, Hazukashime o Ukemashita</title>
<summary>Mashiro breaks the news to Konoha about Kobeni and Kaguya`s engagement.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>648847</identifier>
<identifier>engaged-to-the-unidentified</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="158523" update="2015-04-29">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2014-03-19</airdate>
<rating votes="12">4.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">見て. あれが私たちの泊まっている旅館よ.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Look. It`s the Inn Where We Are Staying.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mite. Are ga Watashitachi no Tomatte Iru Ryokan yo.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="158641" update="2014-11-14">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-01-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="158859" update="2015-11-14">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2014-03-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">とまどい→レシピ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Video Clips Opening</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tomadoi - Recipe</title>
</episode>
<episode id="161750" update="2014-12-28">
<epno type="4">T21</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 11 PV2 (16 sec)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="161751" update="2014-12-28">
<epno type="4">T20</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 11 PV1 (16 sec)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="161752" update="2014-12-28">
<epno type="4">T19</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 10 PV2 (16 sec)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="161753" update="2014-12-28">
<epno type="4">T18</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 10 PV1 (16 sec)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="161754" update="2014-12-28">
<epno type="4">T17</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 9 PV2 (16 sec)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="161755" update="2014-12-28">
<epno type="4">T16</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 9 PV1 (16 sec)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="161756" update="2014-12-28">
<epno type="4">T15</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 8 PV2 (16 sec)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="161757" update="2014-12-28">
<epno type="4">T14</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 8 PV1 (16 sec)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="161758" update="2014-12-28">
<epno type="4">T13</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 7 PV2 (16 sec)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="161759" update="2014-12-28">
<epno type="4">T12</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 7 PV1 (16 sec)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="161760" update="2014-12-28">
<epno type="4">T11</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 6 PV2 (16 sec)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="161761" update="2014-12-28">
<epno type="4">T10</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 6 PV1 (16 sec)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="161762" update="2014-12-28">
<epno type="4">T9</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 5 PV2 (16 sec)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="161763" update="2014-12-28">
<epno type="4">T8</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 5 PV1 (16 sec)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="161764" update="2014-12-28">
<epno type="4">T7</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 4 PV2 (16 sec)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="161765" update="2014-12-28">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 4 PV1 (16 sec)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="161766" update="2014-12-28">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 3 PV2 (16 sec)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="161767" update="2014-12-28">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 3 PV1 (16 sec)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="161768" update="2014-12-28">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 2 PV2 (16 sec)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="161769" update="2014-12-28">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 2 PV1 (16 sec)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="164947" update="2014-12-28">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-12-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">TVアニメ『未確認で進行形』PV第1弾 - プロモーションムービー第1弾(確認済みVer.)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 01 (1 min 43 sec)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="165009" update="2014-12-30">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2013-12-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">未確認で進行形: ぜんたい的にセンセーション MUSIC VIDEO</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Music Video: Zentaiteki ni Sensation - Long OAD Version</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mikakunin de Shinkoukei: Zentaiteki ni Sensation Music Video</title>
</episode>
<episode id="165010" update="2014-12-30">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2013-12-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">未確認で進行形: ぜんたい的にセンセーション MUSIC VIDEO (半分くらいの尺で歌詞付のVer.)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Music Video: Zentaiteki ni Sensation - Short Web Version with Lyrics</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mikakunin de Shinkoukei: Zentaiteki ni Sensation Music Video (Hanbun Kurai no Shaku de Kashitsuki no Ver.)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="217927" update="2019-06-09">
<epno type="4">T22</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 12 PV1 (16 sec)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="217928" update="2019-06-09">
<epno type="4">T23</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 12 PV2 (16 sec)</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
