<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="10542" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2014-07-07</startdate>
<enddate>2014-09-22</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Gekkan Shoujo Nozaki-kun</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">월간순정 노자키 군</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">gsnk</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Nozaki-kun</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">月刊少女野崎くん</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Monthly Girls` Nozaki-kun</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">月刊少女野崎君</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="2165" approval="15" total="26">School Rumble</anime>
<anime id="4148" approval="12" total="22">Ouran Koukou Host Club</anime>
<anime id="10295" approval="8" total="8">Mangaka-san to Assistant-san to: The Animation</anime>
<anime id="13293" approval="4" total="10">Otaku ni Koi wa Muzukashii</anime>
<anime id="7238" approval="2" total="10">Arakawa Under the Bridge</anime>
<anime id="10619" approval="2" total="8">Denki-gai no Hon`ya-san</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="12">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="433112">If you are into shoujo manga/anime or at least know some of their clichés, you`ll enjoy them being parodied and inverted here. Or maybe just pat yourself on the shoulder for recognizing them, since the jokes themselves are often predictable and not very funny.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="784472">This show has shoujo comedy in spades. Charming and delightful characters mismatch in all sorts of ways in an attempt to help their classmate write his romance manga.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="750045">Even if you don`t like shoujos, I`m pretty sure you`ll enjoy this anime. I think I`ve never laughed as much since I watched Nichijou.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="170697">Hilarious!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="626835">If your genre is Comedy,this anime is for you</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="79717">I really enjoyed this series! I loved all of the characters and LAUGHED at something for each episode.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://nozakikun.tv/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1067" type="Animation Work">Doga Kobo</name>
<name id="11055" type="Direction">Yamazaki Mitsue</name>
<name id="7866" type="Character Design">Taniguchi Jun`ichirou</name>
<name id="22911" type="Series Composition">Nakamura Yoshiko</name>
<name id="39667" type="Original Work">Tsubaki Izumi</name>
<name id="16512" type="Chief Direction">Takeshita Ryouhei</name>
<name id="7866" type="Chief Animation Direction">Taniguchi Jun`ichirou</name>
<name id="3073" type="Music">Hashimoto Yukari</name>
</creators>
<description>High school student http://anidb.net/ch65813 [Sakura Chiyo] has a crush on schoolmate http://anidb.net/ch65812 [Nozaki Umetarou], but when she confesses her love to him, he mistakes her for a fan and gives her an autograph. When she says that she always wants to be with him, he invites her to his house, but has her help on some drawings. Chiyo discovers that Umetarou is actually a renowned shoujo manga artist named Yumeno Sakiko, and agrees to be his assistant. As they work on his manga Let`s Love, they encounter other schoolmates who assist them or serve as inspirations for characters in the stories.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="3283">7.70</permanent>
<temporary count="3301">7.77</temporary>
<review count="1">8.50</review>
</ratings>
<picture>224612.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16036</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>23289</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>27633</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tv-tokyo.co.jp/anime/nozakikun/index2.html</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://nozakikun.tv/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Gekkan_Shōjo_Nozaki-kun</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>月刊少女野崎くん</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3424</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>348718</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>17272</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>nozaki_anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="26">
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=-tHbKBCTDFQ</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=HlEuSVbu3Pw</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=6pF_mAi28HY</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=y0X4wc_sahQ</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=lWQQOd6L4UE</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=BOjdanNLFAI</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>monthly-girls-nozaki-kun</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18505</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>19915</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1298" parentid="2883" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-02">
<name>drawing</name>
<description>The art or technique of representing an object or outlining a figure, plan, or sketch by means of lines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1760" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-23">
<name>bishounen</name>
<description>Young man whose beauty (and sexual appeal) transcends the boundary of gender or sexual orientation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2760" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>basketball</name>
<description>Basketball is Netball for men, the real game that encourages dribbling and other such uncouth behaviour that was sanitised out of the ladies` version. However, it is itself woozy compared to Ulama, as the losing side are seldom publicly sacrificed.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2779" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>multiple couples</name>
<description>More than one couple is developed in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2793" parentid="2883" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>performance</name>
<description>The song performance on stage or acting in a theatre is a central part of the character`s life in this anime type.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2805" parentid="2798" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>4-koma manga</name>
<description>Yonkoma manga (4コマ漫画, four cell manga, or 4-koma for short), a comic-strip format, generally consists of gag comic strips within four panels of equal size ordered from top to bottom. (They also sometimes run right-to-left horizontally or use a hybrid 2x2 style, depending on the layout requirements of the publication in which they appear.) Though the word yonkoma comes from the Japanese, the style also exists outside of Japan in other Asian countries as well as in the English-speaking market.</description>
<picurl>70558.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3848" parentid="6348" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-04-02">
<name>preview in ed</name>
<description>For some reason the director decided to show the preview during the ending sequence.
In some cases the preview might be after the ending animation, but still during the ending theme.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4223" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>running gag</name>
<description>(Bit) character(s) play out a short skit several times during the course of the anime. The skit may or may not be exactly the same but does tend to have the same theme throughout.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5943" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-06-14">
<name>misunderstanding</name>
<description>Suggests that a large portion of storyline revolves around a rather large misunderstanding between two or more characters, usually forming long lasting situations of separation or hostility between all those involved.
A large portion of the story may be dedicated to gradually working all parties into a mutual understanding to true intentions or changes of heart.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6021" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>gender bender</name>
<description>Term used to refer to a person who takes on the role of their opposite gender. This often only reaches to the extent of cross-dressing (involving physical appearance and clothing only), but in rarer cases, involves a total gender swap (which seems to be more common in anime) - where the willing or unwilling victim receives a body opposite of their original gender (either permanently or temporarily), with all natural parts per their new body fully (or just all-out amply) included.
Example of cross-dressing gender bender: "Maria+Holic"
Examples of body-swap gender bender: "Kashimashi: Girl meets Girl", "Birdy the Mighty Decode"</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6030" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-22">
<name>otaku culture</name>
<description>Otaku (おたく/オタク) is a Japanese term used to refer to people with obsessive interests, particularly anime, manga, and video games. A female otaku is occasionally referred to as a fujoshi. (Source: Wikipedia)
Here certain aspects of this "fandom" are presented in more detail, e.g. the creation of doujinshi (self-published amateur manga).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6348" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2015-02-19">
<name>old animetags - OP ED</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="65812" type="main character in" update="2015-08-03">
<rating votes="39">7.87</rating>
<name>Nozaki Umetarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A normal highschool student at first glance but actually posseses another identity as Yumeno Sakiko (夢野咲子), creator of shoujo manga Let`s Love~ (恋しよっ Koishiyo~) in magazine Monthly Shoujo Romance (月刊少女ロマンス). Despite making a romance-oriented manga, he has absolutely no experience in love. His ideas for storyline is often delusional and ridiculous. Asks Sakura, who is a member of art club, to be his assistant. During middle school, he was a captain of the school basketball team. He is now in class 2-B.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>152123.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="345" picture="84834.jpg">Nakamura Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65813" type="main character in" update="2015-03-22">
<rating votes="76">7.18</rating>
<name>Sakura Chiyo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Has a crush on Nozaki and confessed, but misinterpreted by Nozaki as a fan. She became Nozaki`s ink work assistant afterwards. Petite with two big ribbons on head is her trademark. She is in class 2-A and is a member of the school art club.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>152124.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39007" picture="148258.jpg">Ozawa Ari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65814" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-05-29">
<rating votes="28">7.41</rating>
<name>Mikoshiba Mikoto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nozaki`s assistant in charge of effects. He was hired before Sakura. He is icemen on the outside but timid and tsundere on the inside which leads to Nozaki calling him Mikorin (みこりん). He is the model of Nozaki`s manga heroine. He is in class 2-G.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>152125.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="390" picture="33609.jpg">Okamoto Nobuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65946" type="appears in" update="2015-02-07">
<rating votes="2">4.77</rating>
<name>Mamiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Heroine of Nozaki`s ongoing manga. Modeled after Mikoshiba.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>168487.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12598" picture="74984.jpg">Miyake Marie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65947" type="appears in" update="2015-02-07">
<rating votes="2">4.77</rating>
<name>Suzuki Saburou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hero of Nozaki`s ongoing manga. Mamiko`s love interest.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>168488.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="255" picture="40713.jpg">Miyano Mamoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65948" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-05-29">
<rating votes="24">5.60</rating>
<name>Wakamatsu Hirotaka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nozaki`s middle school basketball club junior who attends the same high school. Currently a member of school basketball club. He is the latest assistant joined in Nozaki`s team and is in charge of tone work. Has an indescribable relationship with Seo. He is in class 1-D.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>152122.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2225" picture="192115.jpg">Kimura Ryouhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65949" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-05-29">
<rating votes="55">8.11</rating>
<name>Seo Yuzuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sakura`s classmate and friend. She lacks of self-awareness and blind to the situation happen around her. Despite her rude tomboyish demeanor, she has an angelic singing voice thus giving her the nickname Vocal Club`s Lorelei (声楽部のローレライ). Lorelei`s identity is a secret known to Sakura and Nozaki only. She is often asked for help on various extracurricular activities.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>152121.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38" picture="171532.jpg">Sawashiro Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65950" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-05-29">
<rating votes="40">6.92</rating>
<name>Kashima Yuu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Together with Hori, she is a member of school drama club. Her tall figure, tomboyish appearance, and prince-like personality make girls go crazy about her. She is in class 2-G.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>152120.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6" picture="171987.jpg">Nakahara Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="65951" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-05-29">
<rating votes="28">7.28</rating>
<name>Hori Masayuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>President of the school drama club and Nozaki`s assistant in charge of background work. He is no longer performs on stage but instead, works on stage properties. His short figure makes him feels somewhat inferior to Kashima. He is in class 3-C.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>152119.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3155" picture="24137.jpg">Ono Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67646" type="appears in" update="2014-08-08">
<rating votes="8">1.79</rating>
<name>Maeno Mitsuya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159335.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="250" picture="157976.jpg">Ono Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67647" type="appears in" update="2014-08-08">
<rating votes="7">7.03</rating>
<name>Miyamae Ken</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159333.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="178" picture="228660.jpg">Miyake Kenta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67648" type="appears in" update="2014-08-08">
<rating votes="15">7.73</rating>
<name>Miyako Yukari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159334.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12" picture="184301.jpg">Kawasumi Ayako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69505" type="appears in" update="2014-08-19">
<rating votes="2">5.76</rating>
<name>Tomoda</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159818.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="315" picture="70740.jpg">Hino Satoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69506" type="appears in" update="2014-08-19">
<rating votes="2">3.34</rating>
<name>Asuka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159819.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20762" picture="131325.jpg">Sakura Ayane</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69507" type="appears in" update="2014-08-19">
<rating votes="2">3.34</rating>
<name>Sayuri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>159820.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28602" picture="131381.jpg">Uesaka Sumire</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="160619" update="2018-03-05">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-06-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">PV第2弾</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">PV Dai 2 Dan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="160620" update="2018-03-04">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-06-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">PV ver.1.5</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 1.5</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">PV Ver. 1.5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="160621" update="2018-03-04">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-03-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">PV(キャスト公開ver.)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 1 (Complete cast)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">PV (Cast Koukai Ver.)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="160622" update="2018-03-04">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-03-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">PV(キャスト未公開ver.)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">PV (Cast Mikoukai Ver.)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="160777" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-07-14</airdate>
<rating votes="12">6.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">新[ニュー]ヒロインをよろしくね♪</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Say Hello to the New Heroine</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">New Heroine o Yoroshiku ne</title>
<summary>Chiyo is introduced to Nozaki`s other assistant, who he calls Mikorin, Mikoshiba Mikoto. Chiyo was expecting someone who was the healing type, but instead finds out that he is the exact opposite. Mikorin tries to act tough as Chiyo`s senpai assistant, but he ends up having a rather surprising side to him...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>656981</identifier>
<identifier>monthly-girls-nozaki-kun</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="160778" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-07-07</airdate>
<rating votes="13">7.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">その恋は, 少女漫画化されてゆく.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">This Love... Is Being Turned Into a Shojo Manga.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sono Koi wa, Shoujo Manga Kasarete Yuku.</title>
<summary>Sakura Chiyo, age 16, falls in love with a boorish classmate named Nozaki Umetaro. One day, she gathers her courage and confesses her feelings to him... but somehow there is a misunderstanding, and he gives her his autograph. Upon further misunderstanding, Nozaki invites Chiyo to his house, where she suddenly becomes a manga artist`s assistant.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>656979</identifier>
<identifier>monthly-girls-nozaki-kun</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="161066" update="2018-03-05">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2014-06-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">番宣映像</title>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 1 (30s)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bansen Eizou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="161067" update="2018-03-05">
<epno type="4">T7</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2014-07-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">[月刊少女野崎くん]創刊号「その恋は, 少女漫画家されていく」予告15秒ver.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 15s</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Gekkan Shoujo Nozaki-kun" Soukan Gou "Sono Koi wa, Shoujo Mangaka Sarete Iku" Yokoku 15 Byou Ver.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="161068" update="2018-03-05">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2014-07-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">期間限定[月刊少女野崎くん]創刊号「その恋は, 少女漫画家されていく」予告30秒ver.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 2 (30s) / Preview of Episode 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kikan Gentei "Gekkan Shoujo Nozaki-kun" Soukan Gou "Sono Koi wa, Shoujo Mangaka Sarete Iku" Yokoku 30 Byou Ver.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="161111" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-07-28</airdate>
<rating votes="9">8.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">男には, 戦わねばならない, 時がある.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">There Are Times When Men Must Fight.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Otoko ni wa, Tatakawanebanaranai, Toki ga Aru.</title>
<summary>Nozaki, Chiyo, and Mikorin are all at Nozaki`s house working on manga, as usual. They finish a day`s worth of work, and Mikorin says he`s going to stay the night at Nozaki`s. Chiyo can`t help but be a bit jealous of Mikorin, and asks them what they usually do when they have sleepovers. Mikorin says that he asks Nozaki for advice about girls, but that ends up being...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>656985</identifier>
<identifier>monthly-girls-nozaki-kun</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="161112" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-07-21</airdate>
<rating votes="11">5.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">バイオレンスVSプリンス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Violence vs. the Prince</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Violence VS Prince</title>
<summary>Chiyo introduces Nozaki to her friend Seo Yuzuki since he wanted a model for a new character in "Let`s Fall in Love." She also asks Mikoshiba if he happens to know anyone that would be a good fit. Mikoshiba then introduces Chiyo to the Prince of the School.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>656983</identifier>
<identifier>monthly-girls-nozaki-kun</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="161148" update="2014-07-07">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-07-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="161149" update="2014-07-07">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2014-07-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="161542" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-08-25</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">学園の王子様(女子)の悩み</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Prince (Girl) of the School`s Problems</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gakuen no Ouji-sama (Joshi) no Nayami</title>
<summary>Kashima feels that Hori is being cold to her recently, and Mikoshiba tells her that it`s because she lacks appeal. Mikoshiba tells Kashima to push and push hard, so she does, and one day, she finds a copy of "Let`s Fall in Love" in Hori`s bag. Of course, she doesn`t know that he has it in his bag because he`s helping out with the manga, so her imagination starts to run wild on why he has it...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>656993</identifier>
<identifier>monthly-girls-nozaki-kun</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="161543" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-08-18</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">マンガ家脳野崎くん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Manga Artist`s Brain, Nozaki-kun</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Manga-ka Nou Nozaki-kun</title>
<summary>Nozaki finishes up a deadline early for once, and then realizes that he has absolutely no hobbies. Chiyo sees this, and tries to invite him to do something that people would do on their day off. After he agrees, Chiyo realizes that this seems like they`re on a date, which excites her. However, they go to the mall to go shopping and...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>656991</identifier>
<identifier>monthly-girls-nozaki-kun</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="161544" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-08-11</airdate>
<rating votes="11">8.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔法をかけて, あ・げ・る♥</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`ll Cast a Spell on You</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mahou o Kakete, A-ge-ru</title>
<summary>Nozaki passes by the gymnasium to find his underclassman, Wakamatsu, being pummeled by Yuzuki. As the basketball team`s helper, Yuzuki seemed rather overzealous about going after just Wakamatsu, which causes him a lot of stress, which had turned into insomnia.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>656989</identifier>
<identifier>monthly-girls-nozaki-kun</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="161545" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-08-04</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">恋を「思い」「描く」男子.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Man Who Envisions Love</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koi o "Omoi" "Egaku" Danshi.</title>
<summary>One day, Chiyo drops in on Nozaki`s house and finds it cleaner than usual. Chiyo gets delusional and thinks that he cleaned up for her, but apparently that wasn`t the case. Nozaki then gets a phone call and starts panicking and tries to clean up even more. Apparently, the person on the phone is his editor, but...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>656987</identifier>
<identifier>monthly-girls-nozaki-kun</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="162125" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-09-22</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">この気持ちが恋じゃないなら, きっと世界に恋はない.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">If This Feeling Isn`t Love, Then There Is No Love in the World.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kono Kimochi ga Koi ja Nai nara, Kitto Sekai ni Koi wa Nai.</title>
<summary>Chiyo finds the Valentine`s chocolates she meant to give to Nozaki, but failed to, in the back of her fridge. Despite Valentine`s being long over, she knows that her feelings of love are still left in the chocolates... She realizes how her life has changed for the better since she became his assistant, and she decides to give it one more try...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>657001</identifier>
<identifier>monthly-girls-nozaki-kun</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="162126" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-09-15</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">米しよっ♡</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let`s Rice</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kome Shiyo</title>
<summary>Fearing that the love story between Suzuki and Mamiko is lacking something exciting, Nozaki asks Chiyo for some ideas when she visits. Chiyo suggests doing something that`ll surprise or shock, so Nozaki tells her that he`ll try that out on her and that he wants her honest opinion. He then starts doing things that are meant to shock and surprise her at school, but...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>656999</identifier>
<identifier>monthly-girls-nozaki-kun</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="162127" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-09-08</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">強まるのは, 絆と手綱.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">What`s Strengthened Is Our Bond and Our Reins</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsuyomaru no wa, Kizuna to Tazuna.</title>
<summary>Ken-san asks about doing a story with the sub characters that are based on Yuzuki and Wakamatsu. Wakamatsu then visits Nozaki, telling him that Yuzuki gave him movie tickets and he doesn`t know what to do. Nozaki then tells Wakamatsu that he should totally go with Yuzuki, despite his obvious reservations, and so Wakamatsu ends up on a date with Yuzuki.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>656997</identifier>
<identifier>monthly-girls-nozaki-kun</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="162128" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2014-09-01</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ドキドキ, たりてる?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Do You Have Enough Excitement?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dokidoki, Tariteru?</title>
<summary>One rainy day after school, both Nozaki and Chiyo forget their umbrellas and decide to try out a solution used in shojo manga... and using a jacket as cover... but they quickly realize that doesn`t work, and rush back. Despite being drenched, Nozaki still tries to think of other solutions to this problem that he can think of from shojo mangas and...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>656995</identifier>
<identifier>monthly-girls-nozaki-kun</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="163081" update="2015-01-22">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2014-09-24</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あの美男子, 男友達?? それとも彼氏??</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Is That Handsome Guy a Friend?? Or a Boyfriend??</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ano Bidanshi, Otoko Tomodachi?? Soretomo Kareshi??</title>
</episode>
<episode id="164017" update="2015-01-22">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2014-10-29</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">続・あの美男子, 男友達?? それとも彼氏??</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Is That Handsome Guy a Friend?? Or a Boyfriend?? Continued</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zoku. Ano Bidanshi, Otoko Tomodachi?? Soretomo Kareshi??</title>
</episode>
<episode id="164749" update="2015-01-22">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2014-11-26</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">全てが繋がる相関図</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Comprehensive Relationship Chart</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Subete ga Tsunagaru Soukanzu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="165539" update="2015-01-22">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2014-12-24</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夏だ! 海だ! 合宿だ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Summer Time! Beach Time! Trip Time!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Natsu Da! Umi Da! Gasshuku Da!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="165600" update="2016-06-30">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2015-02-25</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">その事件は少女漫画化されてゆく.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Making That Accident for Shoujo Manga.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sono Jiken wa Shoujo Manga Kasareteyuku.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="165601" update="2015-01-24">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2015-01-28</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">俺と太陽, どっちが眩しい?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Which Shines Brighter, Me or the Sun?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ore to Taiyou, Docchi ga Mabushii?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="196895" update="2018-03-04">
<epno type="4">T18</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview of Episode 12</title>
</episode>
<episode id="196896" update="2018-03-04">
<epno type="4">T17</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview of Episode 11</title>
</episode>
<episode id="196897" update="2018-03-04">
<epno type="4">T16</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview of Episode 10</title>
</episode>
<episode id="196898" update="2018-03-04">
<epno type="4">T15</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview of Episode 9</title>
</episode>
<episode id="196899" update="2018-03-04">
<epno type="4">T14</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview of Episode 8</title>
</episode>
<episode id="196900" update="2018-03-04">
<epno type="4">T13</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview of Episode 7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="196901" update="2018-03-04">
<epno type="4">T12</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview of Episode 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="196902" update="2018-03-04">
<epno type="4">T11</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview of Episode 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="196903" update="2018-03-04">
<epno type="4">T10</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview of Episode 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="196904" update="2018-03-04">
<epno type="4">T9</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview of Episode 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="196905" update="2018-03-04">
<epno type="4">T8</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview of Episode 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="196906" update="2018-03-04">
<epno type="4">T22</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Airing Announcement</title>
</episode>
<episode id="196907" update="2018-03-04">
<epno type="4">T21</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 1 (Post-Air) (15s)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="196908" update="2018-03-04">
<epno type="4">T20</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 1 (Post-Air) (30s)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="196909" update="2018-03-04">
<epno type="4">T19</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 1 (15s)</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
