<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="109" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2001-10-06</startdate>
<enddate>2001-12-29</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Mahoromatic: Automatic Maiden</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Automatic Maiden</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">마호로매틱</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">마호로매틱: Automatic Maiden</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">魔力女仆真幌</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">MM</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">まほろまてぃっく Automatic Maiden</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Mahoromatic: Automatic Maiden</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Mahoromatic - Automatic Maiden</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Mahoromatic</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Махороматик: Автоматическая девушка</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="201" type="Sequel">Mahoromatic: Automatic Maiden - Motto Utsukushii Mono</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="1431" approval="23" total="37">Kono Minikuku mo Utsukushii Sekai</anime>
<anime id="88" approval="17" total="19">Koutetsu Tenshi Kurumi</anime>
<anime id="5278" approval="14" total="22">Koharu Biyori</anime>
<anime id="10854" approval="14" total="20">Plastic Memories</anime>
<anime id="13500" approval="10" total="17">Beatless</anime>
<anime id="526" approval="7" total="9">Bannou Bunka Nekomusume (1998)</anime>
<anime id="12091" approval="4" total="10">Kobayashi-san Chi no Maidragon</anime>
<anime id="10609" approval="1" total="4">Majimoji Rurumo</anime>
<anime id="13363" approval="1" total="4">Kimi no Suizou o Tabetai</anime>
<anime id="2842" approval="1" total="2">Hotori: Tada Saiwai o Koinegau</anime>
<anime id="6271" approval="1" total="2">Kowarekake no Orgel</anime>
<anime id="223" approval="1" total="1">Seihou Tenshi Angel Links</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="1"/>
<url>http://www.mahoro-matic.com</url>
<creators>
<name id="2341" type="Music">Masuda Toshio</name>
<name id="8456" type="Original Work">Nakayama Bunjuurou</name>
<name id="718" type="Animation Work">Gainax</name>
<name id="792" type="Animation Work">Shaft</name>
<name id="582" type="Original Work">Ditama Bow</name>
<name id="3594" type="Chief Animation Direction">Takamura Kazuhiro</name>
<name id="3584" type="Direction">Yamaga Hiroyuki</name>
<name id="3594" type="Character Design">Takamura Kazuhiro</name>
</creators>
<description>In the hushed-up war against Saint, mankind has been saved countless times by an android named http://anidb.net/ch6594 [Andou Mahoro]. After her last battle, Mahoro discovers that if she stays in her full battle mode, she only has a limited lifespan left to her. If her armaments are removed, Mahoro has a new lease on life and the freedom to live it as she pleases — for another 398 days at least. So what should an android with a little over a year left do?
http://anidb.net/ch6595 [Misato Suguru], a 14-year-old orphan, hires Mahoro on as a maid. Poor Suguru has no idea of Mahoro`s past life, or her deep connection to him. But he is not one to complain as Mahoro moves in. His friends find this suspicious though, and his homeroom teacher http://anidb.net/ch6597 [Shikijou Saori] becomes rather jealous. Now Suguru just has to come to terms with the fact that his beautiful maid is actually only 9 years old and an android!</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="4121">6.23</permanent>
<temporary count="4150">7.51</temporary>
<review count="6">6.58</review>
</ratings>
<picture>221931.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>428</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>632</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>276</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>254</identifier>
<identifier>cjnqfr</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.mahoro-matic.com</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Mahoromatic</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>まほろまてぃっく</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>72</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>234835</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4956</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7642</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1018" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-25">
<name>middle school</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1157" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>horny nosebleed</name>
<description>In Japanese media, healthy young men who have no other sexual outlet will often suffer nosebleeds upon seeing the naked female body, or even just a pair of well-filled panties.
The nosebleed is, of course, a visual shorthand/euphemism for sexual arousal. It is commonly interpreted that way for males and females, with little trickles of blood indicating mild arousal, and gushing fountains of blood indicating erection/extreme arousal in both sexes. It can also be interpreted as shorthand strictly for erections in males. In that case, when blood shoots from the nose explosively, and in ridiculous quantity, the implication would be an ejaculation.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>233513.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1278" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>android</name>
<description>An android is a robot or synthetic organism designed to look and act like a human.</description>
<picurl>223943.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1282" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>pet</name>
<description>A domestic animal kept for pleasure or companionship.</description>
<picurl>221616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1760" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-23">
<name>bishounen</name>
<description>Young man whose beauty (and sexual appeal) transcends the boundary of gender or sexual orientation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2008" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-05">
<name>small breasts</name>
<description>This character has a bust size that is considered small. 
The small size is usually a bust that would use a bra which is A or B. In anime, C may rarely enter this category.</description>
<picurl>162720.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2072" parentid="2608" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>maid</name>
<description>A maid is a female employed in domestic service. They usually wear uniforms. Since their nature is to be obedient and serve their goshujin-sama (master), they are one of the most desired types of women in Japan, a dream of every Japanese man, particularly http://anidb.net/t1133 [otaku]. Often seen in so-called Maid Cafes in Akihabara, where male customers can for a little time enjoy the feeling of being served by a woman. The male gender opposite is the butler.</description>
<picurl>4954.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2396" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-08">
<name>swimsuit</name>
<description>A swimsuit is one of several kinds of garments designed to be worn by people engaging in water-based activities or sports or during certain activities under sunlight. Most kinds of swimsuit reveal a large portion of the body surface area, but exceptions exist. The more revealing kinds may also be worn as undergarment in sports that require wetsuits, or when there is a need to display the body, as in the case of beauty pageants or bodybuilding contests.
There is a very wide range of styles of modern swimsuits, which vary in relation to body coverage and materials. The choice of style of swimsuit is dependent on current fashions, community standards of modesty, and plain personal preference. Swimsuits for men usually expose the chest, while those for women do not usually do so; however, many women prefer to engage in water or sun activities with their torso uncovered, in a practice commonly described as toplessness or topfreedom. Since the early twentieth century a naturist movement has developed in western countries that seeks a return to non-sexual nakedness when swimming and during other appropriate activities; in some places around the world, nude beaches have been set aside for people who choose to engage in normal beach activities in the nude, and such beaches may or may not enforce nudity onto their goers.
In anime, it is common for at least one episode to feature the characters in swimsuits, usually as an excuse for gratuitous fanservice; when that happens, the episode is usually labeled a pool or beach episode, after the place the characters went to. Swimsuits, and in particular one-piece swimsuits, are a very common fetish in Japan; while the reason for that is uncertain, a common folk explanation is the fact that boys throughout their entire adolescence are commonly exposed to their female classmates wearing them, in what might be called an experiment in sexual discovery waiting to happen.</description>
<picurl>149786.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2775" parentid="2202" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>humanoid alien</name>
<description>Humanoids are aliens, intelligent beings who do not originate from Earth, but have a striking similarity to humans or at least show the basic body layout, i.e. two arms and legs, head with two eyes and ears, one nose and mouth. Though the latter - head-related features - may vary. As "DearS" shows some aliens actually exhibit super-human beauty, or as in the case of "Onegai Teacher" they are genetically compatible to humans for some strange reason.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2815" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>boobs in your face</name>
<description>Boobs in your face: the character`s face is pressed into a female`s cleavage. This may be accidental or actually intended by the female character, or even a result of a device by the other character. This action is generally seen as sexually charged by the viewers and often also by the cast, so it will usually happen in an ecchi context; as such, something such as a mother hugging her child won`t generally count.</description>
<picurl>230160.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2816" parentid="2856" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>sexual fantasies</name>
<description>One or more characters in this anime let their imaginations run wild thinking about another character.
Yes, they are thinking about sex, and in an ecchi anime these thoughts are often perverted, leading to a nosebleed. But it may also be romanticising simply being husband and wife, and everything that implies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2829" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-21">
<name>shower scene</name>
<description>The anime contains a shower scene, obligatory for ecchi anime. The person under the shower will most likely be female — providing "fanservice".</description>
<picurl>208635.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2830" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>furo scene</name>
<description>Furo (polite: Ofuro) is Japanese for bath, specifically a type of bath which originated as a short, steep-sided wooden bathtub. Baths of this type are found all over Japan in houses, apartments and traditional Japanese inns (Ryokans).
Furo are part of the Japanese ritual of bathing, not used for washing but for relaxing and warming oneself. Washing is carried out separately outside the furo, and only when completely clean does the bather enter the water. Generally Japanese bathrooms are small, so the bathroom is set up much like a walk-in shower area but containing the ofuro.
The cheapest and shortest way to show naked skin on TV, at least as much as allowed. It usually only takes up few minutes at most and as such it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in the nude and raise the DVD sales while still maintaining a "non-filler" episode.
Compare to the big brothers http://anidb.net/t4290 [sentou episode] and http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode].
See also http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode], and http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].</description>
<picurl>160785.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2865" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-16">
<name>summer festival</name>
<description>The summer festival is used to show off the female protagonists in traditional Japanese clothing — the yukata — a casual form of kimono.
The festivities include food stalls (cotton candy, candy apples, choco bananas, taiyaki), various games (scoop goldfishes), and a fireworks display.</description>
<picurl>161023.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2879" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>alcohol</name>
<description>Alcohol (or more scientifically, ethanol), is one of the world`s oldest psychoactive substances. It is traditionally found in the form of a beverage such as beer, wine, or liquor, although in some contexts it can be inhaled to produce similar or intoxication, and some people prefer another way of consuming beverage-form alcohol.
Alcoholic beverages are many and varied, due to production methods (fermentation or distillation), source materials (grains, fruits, vegetables, other plants), added substances such as flavorings, and many more ways of defining different forms of alcoholic beverages.
Alcoholic beverages are divided into three general classes: beers, wines, and spirits. They are legally consumed in most countries, and over 100 countries have laws regulating their production, sale, and consumption. In particular, such laws specify the minimum age at which a person may legally buy or drink them. This minimum age varies between 16 and 25 years, depending upon the country and the type of drink. Most nations set it at 18 years of age.</description>
<picurl>70749.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2893" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>female teacher</name>
<description>Any kind of female teacher will do, even if she only does home visits. Female teachers imply mature women (even if they sometimes look like schoolgirls) dressed in what women would typically wear when doing official business (like a blouse, pinstripe dress with side front slit), but of course, not limited to that. Furthermore, school nurses also count as female teachers unless they`re actually wearing a nurse outfit, which they almost never are.
Almost completely exclusive to hentai animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3237" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-16">
<name>test of courage</name>
<description>As part of a summer excursion or festival, an anime with school setting may also have a test of courage (or kimodameshi in Japanese), where the male and female students are paired up (by lottery) to retrieve a "charm" by passing though a "haunted house" or a scary forest at night.
The teachers usually disguise themselves as monsters or ghosts, scaring the students out of their socks.
This seems to be some sort of Japanese "coming of age" ritual, providing a certain level of excitement under controlled and safe circumstances.
Frequently seen in the Festival Episode.</description>
<picurl>38866.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3378" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true">
<name>redemption</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3444" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>hot springs visit</name>
<description>An onsen is a term for hot springs in the Japanese language, though the term is often used to describe the bathing facilities and inns around the hot springs. Often the cast of a show somehow ends up going to an onsen because of various reasons, such as winning a lottery ticket. 
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters nude and raise the DVD sales.
Another cheap variant is the http://anidb.net/t4290 [sentou episode].
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode], and http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].</description>
<picurl>160784.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3569" parentid="1278" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-17">
<name>human-android love</name>
<description>There is a romance going on between a human (often male) and an android (usually female).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3702" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-12">
<name>swimsuit shopping</name>
<description>To provide additional, potentially ecchi moments, the usually female character(s) go shopping for a new, often quite revealing, swimsuit — as preparation for an upcoming pool or beach episode.</description>
<picurl>166999.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3834" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-11-24">
<name>impending death -- TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>At least one character in this show is going to or very likely to die soon because of a http://anidb.net/t2574 [terminal illness], of a http://anidb.net/t2874 [disaster] such a http://anidb.net/t2925 [war], an http://anidb.net/t5466 [epidemic] (including the zombie apocalypse), or of other life-threatening reasons. Please assign the appropriate disaster tags to the anime, the terminal illness tag to the relevant characters, and any other relevant or necessary replacement tags to the corresponding entities, and then remove this tag from the anime in question. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4290" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>bath house visit</name>
<description>A sentou is a type of Japanese communal bath house where customers pay for entrance. Some Japanese find social importance in going to public baths, out of the theory that physical intimacy brings emotional intimacy, which is termed skinship in Japanese. Traditionally it is gender-segregated — men usually bathe only with men, and women with women. 
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in the nude and raise the DVD sales.
See also http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode], http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode], and http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].</description>
<picurl>160783.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4323" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-04">
<name>spacing out</name>
<description>A comedy element: The character starts to daydream or fantasize about some topic. The typical complete lack of reality makes the spacing out funny. Especially when the protagonist mumbles to himself / herself and friends hear this. Promptly teasing the possibly lovestruck and very embarrassed protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4389" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-14">
<name>amusement park visit</name>
<description>Plot device: All or part of the cast visit an amusement park. 
Added to show the characters in a more leisurely environment (i.e. other than school or at home). Often used in school settings to "develop" and "further" the relations between the male and female leads in this anime. Can also set the stage for comedic misunderstandings, or private moments with possibly ecchi undertones. 
Furthermore, it gives the anime creators a chance to show off their characters in non-uniforms (e.g. school uniforms). Also see "pool episode".</description>
<picurl>160897.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4440" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>boy meets girl</name>
<description>A classical type of plot in story writing, where the story begins with a boy meeting a girl leading to romantic development between the two. More often than not the boy loses the girl later on and has to find her again.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4479" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-03">
<name>sense of foreboding</name>
<description>The anime starts off quietly, everything seems to be fine, but from episode to episode the signs that something ominous is about to happen increase. E.g. a typical mystery setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4570" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-07">
<name>watercolour style</name>
<description>A watercolour or aquarelle is a painting method in which the paints are made of pigments suspended in a water-based solution. Some anime are created in the style of watercolour paintings, the watercolour style, usually with faded pastels that often give the show a warm and friendly visual presentation. In modern anime, this is generally achieved via computer effects that create an imitation of watercolour, rather than by creating real-life watercolour art. While the watercolour style is more commonly used for backgrounds, it is possible to create the entire anime in such a style.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4612" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>Do Androids Dream of Electric Sheep?</name>
<description>The title of Philip K. Dick`s SF novel (movie: Blade Runner). 
The phrase implies a set of existential questions: Do artificial beings (e.g. Replicants, Bioroids, or other AI constructs) dream, feel, or have a soul? If memories can be implanted, what makes real memories real? By contrast — what makes humans human? What is reality? 
These are central themes e.g. in all of the Ghost in the Shell and Appleseed series / movies.</description>
<picurl>210067.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5826" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-12">
<name>rivalry</name>
<description>Quite broadly used term describing a conflict, contest, struggle, or opposition of some sort.
Typical examples: The mostly comedic rivalry for the love of a protagonist in a harem anime (love polygon), the more "mindless" battles between wannabe delinquents in a school fighting anime, or the struggle between good &amp; evil in an epic conflict for world domination.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5846" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-26">
<name>beach visit</name>
<description>Every anime has to have them, episodes in which the characters for whatever reason end up going to the sea, ocean, random island or the local pond.
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in swimsuits and raise the DVD sales.
The cheap version is the http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].
Other marginally less used variants of this are the http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode] and the http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], used when it is too cold for a beach/pool episode.
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene].</description>
<picurl>160805.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="6594" type="main character in" update="2009-06-13">
<rating votes="225">8.43</rating>
<name>Andou Mahoro</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mahoro is an android created by VESPER to fight an alien invasion by Saint in the 1980s. She is immensely powerful and fast, and is considered to be a formidable opponent by her enemies.
Being an android, she has a limited life span. At the beginning of the story, she has just 398 days to live, and is given the choice to do anything she wants by VESPER. She chooses to become a maid for Suguru Misato: his father was her superior commander, and she was forced to kill both him and an alien when the alien took him hostage.
Mahoro has a very sunny disposition and is friendly to just about everyone — she becomes a welcome regular at the market and becomes famous at Suguru`s school for working for him. She also quickly becomes an excellent cook, able to emulate and recreate dishes from the best restaurants. She is also quite devoted to Suguru, with feelings for him reminiscent of both doting mother and shy girlfriend.</description>
<picture>28703.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12" picture="184301.jpg">Kawasumi Ayako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6595" type="main character in" update="2010-01-07">
<rating votes="39">3.13</rating>
<name>Misato Suguru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Suguru Misato is a junior high school student living in Tokyo. He lost both his parents earlier — his mother, and years later, his father. While he believed his father was killed in an accident during a business trip, he was actually a commander (and Mahoro`s commanding officer) in VESPER and was killed-in-action during the alien war. Although relatives offered to take him in, he refused and lived alone prior to Mahoro`s arrival.
He is smart and has an IQ of 130. He makes a favorable impression on members of the opposite sex.
Suguru hired a maid because of the filthy state of his house. He was expecting an older woman, and Mahoro`s arrival completely surprised him.</description>
<picture>2274.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="2438" picture="156420.jpg">Takimoto Fujiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6596" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-13">
<rating votes="11">6.47</rating>
<name>Slash</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Slash is known as a "support mecha" and assists Mahoro during combat. He has the form of a panther and can be summoned at any time by Mahoro. Although he can speak, his mouth never moves except during times when he expresses emotions. Although used for combat in the past, he often now acts as a guard dog around the Misato residence and a friend to the Misato`s dog — a role he was not thrilled to take in the beginning.
He is friendly but tough and will lend a helping paw when asked. Although Mahoro is Slash`s master, he will now take commands from Suguru: since Suguru is Mahoro`s employer, he is also her master and thus Slash`s master as well.</description>
<picture>2275.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="2981" picture="23711.jpg">Noda Keiichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6597" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-22">
<rating votes="41">6.98</rating>
<name>Shikijou Saori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Saori Shikijo, or Shikijo-sensei, is Suguru`s teacher in junior high school and is extremely attracted to him. She has an extreme shota complex, or an attraction to young boys. Many of the jokes stem from her attempts to openly physically seduce Suguru, and the ways in which her attempts are foiled by Mahoro.
She is a heavy drinker and as a result is often broke and unable to afford food. Soon after Mahoro arrives at the Misato household, Shikijo starts inviting herself for dinner on a daily basis despite Mahoro`s protests.
Shikijo and Mahoro often compete with each other, usually with Mahoro emerging victorious except when it comes to insults. She has much larger breasts than Mahoro, which she flaunts when comparing herself to Mahoro or in taunting her. Her large breasts are also a focus of her many attempts to seduce Suguru.</description>
<picture>28708.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="557" picture="228659.jpg">Takada Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6598" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-13">
<rating votes="10">6.17</rating>
<name>Sakura Miyuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Miyuki is the daughter of the public bath`s owner in Hiryuu. She is very tomboyish by contrast with her friends and sisters.</description>
<picture>2270.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="3288" picture="25521.jpg">Kikuchi Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6599" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-13">
<rating votes="17">5.34</rating>
<name>Todoroki Rin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Todoriki Rin is the most ladylike of the trio, but is also a skilled martial artist.
Rin has also the most physically developed breasts of the Triomatic, which at times causes Miyuki and Chizuko consternation. For the most part Rin seems almost embarrassed when the other two complain about her breasts, but as the series goes on she becomes more and more comfortable with her "advantage."
Rin`s family is wealthy (coming from a long military line), and lives in a palatial estate filled with numerous pieces of art and wealth.</description>
<picture>2272.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="3294" picture="223278.jpg">Mizuno Manabi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6606" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-13">
<rating votes="16">7.02</rating>
<name>Ooe Chizuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ooe Chizuko, often comes at Suguru`s home to eat meals, cooked by Mahoro, which she seems to like quite a lot. The scream she does when she tastes Mahoro`s food can scare at first, but you get used to it rather quickly.
Her father is a ecchi movie producer.</description>
<picture>2269.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="359" picture="65537.jpg">Sanada Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6607" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-13">
<rating votes="3">3.43</rating>
<name>Hamaguchi Toshiya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>2271.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="3295" picture="38451.jpg">Ogihara Hideki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6608" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-13">
<rating votes="3">3.43</rating>
<name>Kawahara Kiyomi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of Suguru`s male friends who also enjoys looking at dirty magazines. He is a kendo student, and is usually with Suguru`s other friend Toshiya.</description>
<picture>2276.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="484" picture="17476.jpg">Kisaichi Atsushi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6610" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-08">
<rating votes="4">5.36</rating>
<name>Ryuuga Tou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ryuuga is one of the best Saint` androids. He is a powerful warrior, against whom Mahoro can show all her potential, but his warrior spirit is so strong that it obsesses him.
He arrives under the fake identity of a teacher at Suguru`s school.</description>
<picture>28722.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6611" type="appears in" update="2009-06-13">
<rating votes="2">5.25</rating>
<name>Vesper</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>A secret agency fighting an army of alien invaders.</description>
<picture>28719.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6612" type="appears in" update="2009-05-02">
<rating votes="2">3.43</rating>
<name>Saint</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="6615" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-13">
<rating votes="2">5.25</rating>
<name>Guri</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>2273.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="2438" picture="156420.jpg">Takimoto Fujiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6616" type="appears in" update="2010-01-08">
<rating votes="3">5.91</rating>
<name>Sera</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>24328.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="230" picture="238938.jpg">Tanaka Kahori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="24739" type="appears in" update="2010-11-04">
<rating votes="1">3.43</rating>
<name>Daimon Hayato</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>58481.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="339" picture="79312.jpg">Ishizuka Unshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="24741" type="appears in" update="2010-11-04">
<rating votes="1">3.43</rating>
<name>Hokaze Minato</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>58483.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="60" picture="171602.jpg">Kawada Shinji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25003" type="appears in" update="2010-11-10">
<rating votes="1">5.25</rating>
<name>Misato Ryou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>59079.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42809" picture="223789.jpg">Nakata Kazuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25005" type="appears in" update="2010-11-10">
<rating votes="1">5.25</rating>
<name>Sakura Natsuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>59081.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="230" picture="238938.jpg">Tanaka Kahori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25006" type="appears in" update="2010-11-10">
<rating votes="1">3.43</rating>
<name>Sakura Akimi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>59082.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="19677" picture="76719.jpg">Kobayashi Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25007" type="appears in" update="2010-11-10">
<rating votes="1">5.25</rating>
<name>Sakura Yukie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>59083.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="603" picture="223012.jpg">Jou Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50204" type="appears in" update="2014-04-20">
<rating votes="1">3.47</rating>
<name>Andou-san</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154562.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4715" picture="223209.jpg">Imai Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50205" type="appears in" update="2012-10-29">
<name>Shiina Eimi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>58484.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="13061" picture="43055.jpg">Shimazaki Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50206" type="appears in" update="2014-04-20">
<name>Mizutani-kun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154563.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="60" picture="171602.jpg">Kawada Shinji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50207" type="appears in" update="2012-10-29">
<name>Gunji Yoshihiko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>58482.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6855" picture="238933.jpg">Endou Akifumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50212" type="appears in" update="2012-10-29">
<name>Sakura Harune</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>59080.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10192" picture="37551.jpg">Yonekura Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="50221" type="appears in" update="2012-10-29">
<name>Sakura Taizou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>59084.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="7432" picture="69009.jpg">Horikawa Jin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66927" type="appears in" update="2014-04-20">
<name>Nobu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154564.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4749" picture="27700.jpg">Katsuragi Masanori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66928" type="appears in" update="2014-04-20">
<name>Machi Kaichou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>154565.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6854" picture="216700.jpg">Tani Atsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="3568" update="2011-11-16">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-12-08</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">戦士としての宿命</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Fate As a Warrior</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Schicksal eines Kriegers</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le destin du guerrier</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Senshi to Shite no Shukumei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="3569" update="2011-11-16">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-11-03</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">8ノ634ハ元気デス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">8-634 Is Doing Fine</title>
<title xml:lang="de">8-634 macht sich gut</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">8/634, c`est la forme</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">8-no-634 wa Genki Desu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="3570" update="2011-11-16">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-10-27</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ハート撃ち抜きます</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shoot Me Straight Through the Heart</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ich treff ihn mitten ins Herz</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Pénétrer ton cœur</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Heart Uchinukimasu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="3571" update="2011-11-16">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-10-20</airdate>
<rating votes="5">8.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">墓ありて儚く</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Grave So Transient</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ein Grab, so vergänglich</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une tombe éphémère</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Haka Arite Hakanaku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="3572" update="2011-11-16">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-10-13</airdate>
<rating votes="4">9.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">女教師沙織二十五歳</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Woman Teacher Saori, 25 Years Old</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Fräulein Shikijo, Alter: 25</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Mademoiselle le professeur Shikijo, 25 ans</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onna Kyoushi Saori Nijuugosai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="3573" update="2011-11-16">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-10-06</airdate>
<rating votes="7">8.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">紫陽花の咲く庭で</title>
<title xml:lang="en">In the Garden Where the Hydrangeas Bloom</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Im Garten der blühenden Hortensien</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Dans le jardin où fleurissent les hortensias</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ajisai no Saku Niwa de</title>
</episode>
<episode id="3574" update="2011-11-16">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-12-01</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ライムライト ~LimeLight~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Limelight</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Rampenlicht</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Limelight</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Limelight</title>
</episode>
<episode id="3575" update="2011-11-16">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-11-24</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">完璧な心の持ち主</title>
<title xml:lang="en">One Who Has a Perfect Heart</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ich besitze ein wahres Herz</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Celle qui a des sentiments parfaits</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanpeki na Kokoro no Mochinushi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="3576" update="2011-11-16">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-12-29</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">いつか夢見た風景に</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To the Scenery I Once Dreamt Of</title>
<title xml:lang="de">An dem Ort, wo ich einen Traum hatte</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ce paysage dont je rêve parfois</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Itsuka Yumemita Fuukei ni</title>
</episode>
<episode id="3577" update="2011-11-16">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-11-17</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">過去に追われるメイドさん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Maid Chased by Her Past</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das von der Vergangenheit verfolgte Hausmädchen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une maid poursuivie par son passé</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kako ni Owareru Maid-san</title>
</episode>
<episode id="3578" update="2011-11-16">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-12-22</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ぼくの大切な人間</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Person Precious to Me</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Mensch den ich schätze</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Quelqu`un d`important pour moi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Boku no Taisetsu na Ningen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="3579" update="2011-11-16">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-11-10</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">月花愁色</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Moon Flower Design</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Mond, Blumen, Herbstgefühle</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Air mélancolique des fleurs sous la lune</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekka Shuushoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6977" recap="true" update="2019-11-10">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-12-15</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Year End Special</title>
</episode>
<episode id="6991" update="2011-09-17">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>20</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Mahoromatic News Flash!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="21316" update="2009-11-27">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Automatic Maiden Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="22700" update="2010-04-12">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2001-10-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46290" recap="true" update="2011-09-17">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>6</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Reviewspecial Collection of Singingscenes</title>
</episode>
<episode id="96174" update="2009-01-06">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD Extras</title>
</episode>
<episode id="106414" update="2010-04-12">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2001-10-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="110745" update="2009-10-17">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo 1</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
