<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="11568" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2016-04-02</startdate>
<enddate>2016-06-27</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Sansha San`you</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Sansha Sanyou</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="synonym">三者三葉</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">三者三葉</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Three Leaves, Three Colors</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">三者三叶</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="11139" approval="6" total="8">Wakaba Girl</anime>
<anime id="8107" approval="5" total="5">A Channel: The Animation</anime>
<anime id="5910" approval="3" total="5">Hyakko</anime>
<anime id="14156" approval="0" total="5">Watashi ni Tenshi ga Maiorita!</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="3">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="730868">Wow, I really took one for the team by watching this thing.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="345228">Simple, relaxed comedy with smile here, laugh there, and random over-dramatization over there. Sonobe`s voice is interesting and was awaiting for more Teru`s remarks eagerly. And, of course, Teru`s "Mi-ru-fii-yu! ♥" is pure cuteness overload ^_^</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://sansyasanyou.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="17239" type="Character Design">Yamazaki Jun</name>
<name id="6898" type="Series Composition">Koyasu Hideaki</name>
<name id="27082" type="Original Work">Arai Cherry</name>
<name id="1067" type="Animation Work">Doga Kobo</name>
<name id="17701" type="Direction">Kimura Yasuhiro</name>
<name id="17239" type="Chief Animation Direction">Yamazaki Jun</name>
<name id="7900" type="Chief Animation Direction">Taniguchi Motohiro</name>
<name id="40490" type="Music">Mutsuki Shuuhei</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on http://anidb.net/cr27082 [Arai Cherry]`s Sansha Sanyou 4-panel seinen manga.
http://anidb.net/ch79405 [Odagiri Futaba] is the new transfer student with a super energetic personality; http://anidb.net/ch79406 [Hayama Teru] is the class president with a surprisingly mean personality contrary to her innocent looks; and http://anidb.net/ch79407 [Nishikawa Youko] is a girl from a formerly rich, now extremely poor family who still holds on to her princess attitude. These three unlikely students with clashing personalities become good friends and survive the day-to-day teenage life.
Source: MangaHelpers
Note: The first episode received an early screening at a special event on 02.04.2016. The regular TV broadcast started later on April 11, 2016.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="586">5.38</permanent>
<temporary count="587">6.67</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>183658.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>17908</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>31564</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>33173</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://sansyasanyou.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Sansha_San'yō</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>三者三葉</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4083</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>354060</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18983</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B073JZWVZH</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1471" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-19">
<name>bad cooking</name>
<description>The character is hopelessly terrible at cooking, and any attempts he or she makes at making even the simplest dishes are spectacular failures.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2805" parentid="2798" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>4-koma manga</name>
<description>Yonkoma manga (4コマ漫画, four cell manga, or 4-koma for short), a comic-strip format, generally consists of gag comic strips within four panels of equal size ordered from top to bottom. (They also sometimes run right-to-left horizontally or use a hybrid 2x2 style, depending on the layout requirements of the publication in which they appear.) Though the word yonkoma comes from the Japanese, the style also exists outside of Japan in other Asian countries as well as in the English-speaking market.</description>
<picurl>70558.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3217" parentid="2864" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-17">
<name>working life</name>
<description>The life of someone actually working on a often less than glamorous job is depicted in this anime. The job is taxing and the pay is low, not really the dream job one would choose to work in.
Examples: Working as salesperson in a department store, or as a waitress in a family restaurant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4614" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>narration</name>
<description>The most common example is that of a voice, either that of one of the characters or entirely unrelated, that appears at the beginning of an episode to offer a summary or introduction, and at the end of an episode for closure or for a preview to hint upon what to expect next.
Another use of narration comes in the form of a dominant voice belonging to one of the protagonists, intended only for the viewer and revealing the intimate thoughts to whom it belongs. This type of narration occurs frequently throughout the duration of the episode or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4729" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-07-06">
<name>colour coded</name>
<description>Every single character on the main cast has a unique hair colour to help less perceptive viewers distiguish between them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5518" parentid="7199" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-03">
<name>flat chest jokes</name>
<description>Jokes about the (supposedly or actually) flat chest of a character.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7146" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-14">
<name>cute girls doing cute things</name>
<description>Cute girls doing cute things with each other (CGDCT): when girls are super friendly with each other and do all sorts of http://anidb.net/t798 [cute/moe] things with each other, but there is no yuri or shoujo ai subtext -- more specifically, there is no romantic subtext.

* CGDCT applies where the main focus is on moe/cute girls and their interactions with each other. Good examples include http://anidb.net/a9722 [Non Non Biyori] (600 weight / 3.0 stars) and http://anidb.net/a9579 [Kin`iro Mosaic] (600 weight / 3.0 stars).
* Generally, CGDCT is applicable only if the anime is also tagged predominantly female cast or all female cast.
* CGDCT does not apply if girls doing cute things is incidental to a larger motive/theme/meta. For example, in http://anidb.net/a8168 [Nichijou] the focus is comedy, using cute girls; the tag would not apply.

CGDCT is often mistaken as low level yuri or shoujo ai. If there is also actual romantic subtext, use the http://anidb.net/t2695 [yuri (18+)] and http://anidb.net/t2782 [shoujo ai] tags as well. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>223153.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7199" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-12">
<name>sexual humour</name>
<description>Sexual humour is prevalent in this anime. It often involves cheeky or crude sexual language, with innuendos and jokes about the female or male genitalia. Often, such anime also have http://anidb.net/t2856 [ecchi] elements to them.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="79405" type="main character in" update="2016-02-08">
<rating votes="16">8.33</rating>
<name>Odagiri Futaba</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>182544.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43784" picture="181317.jpg">Kanazawa Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79406" type="main character in" update="2016-02-08">
<rating votes="10">5.73</rating>
<name>Hayama Teru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>182545.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40344" picture="181316.jpg">Imamura Ayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79407" type="main character in" update="2016-02-08">
<rating votes="13">7.92</rating>
<name>Nishikawa Youko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>182543.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="44400" picture="181318.jpg">Wakui Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79925" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-02-08">
<rating votes="12">8.33</rating>
<name>Sonobe Shino</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>182547.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43485" picture="223364.jpg">Momokawa Rika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79926" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-02-08">
<rating votes="13">7.17</rating>
<name>Nishiyama Serina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>182548.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="41848" picture="166347.jpg">Machico</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="79927" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-02-08">
<rating votes="8">5.61</rating>
<name>Kondou Asako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>182546.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="41296" picture="177392.jpg">Suzuki Aina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80654" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-03-05">
<rating votes="4">3.26</rating>
<name>Yamaji Mitsugu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>183709.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2487" picture="23183.jpg">Akabane Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80655" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-03-05">
<rating votes="3">2.18</rating>
<name>Takezono Yuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>183707.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43267" picture="204146.jpg">Watanabe Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80656" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-03-05">
<rating votes="5">5.94</rating>
<name>Usuda Sakura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>183710.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45089" picture="224099.jpg">Natsuno Nao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80657" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-03-05">
<rating votes="10">6.91</rating>
<name>Hayama Kou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>183708.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4616" picture="170439.jpg">Nishi Asuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80658" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-03-05">
<rating votes="3">3.80</rating>
<name>Tsuji Hajime</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>183711.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42733" picture="223921.jpg">Kuwayama Kotone</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80659" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-03-05">
<rating votes="5">7.57</rating>
<name>Tsuji Sasame</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>183712.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45090" picture="185899.jpg">Tanaka Chiemi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95565" type="appears in" update="2018-05-14">
<name>Futaba no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>217603.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43494" picture="224097.jpg">Fujita Shizuku</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95592" type="appears in" update="2018-05-15">
<name>Manpuku Tenchou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>217639.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37937" picture="223928.jpg">Yagi Takanori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95593" type="appears in" update="2018-05-16">
<name>Eternal</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>217646.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43372" picture="175176.jpg">Yoshikai Tomomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95594" type="appears in" update="2018-05-17">
<name>Ichiyanagi Hiyori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>217662.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16804" picture="224734.jpg">Kurosawa Tomoyo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95595" type="appears in" update="2018-05-17">
<name>Osakabe Sei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>217663.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34361" picture="127753.jpg">Matsui Eriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95596" type="appears in" update="2018-05-17">
<name>Sekiguchi Nonoka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>217664.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36368" picture="224755.jpg">Mao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95597" type="appears in" update="2018-05-17">
<name>Beel</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>217665.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40885" picture="224096.jpg">Katsuta Shiori</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="176376" update="2017-10-17">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-04-02</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">パンの耳ですわ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">These Are Bread Crusts</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Pan no Mimi Desu wa</title>
<summary>Yoko Nishikawa is a former rich girl struggling to understand her new reduced circumstances. The loneliness is getting to be too much when carefree glutton Futaba Odagiri and scary class rep No-First-Name Hayama crash into her life and change everything.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="176475" update="2017-10-17">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-05-02</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">むしろ生きがいです</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Actually, This Is What I Live For</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mushiro Ikigai Desu</title>
<summary>Yoko, Futaba, and Hayama learn about each others` hobbies and childhoods. They also encounter Yu and Sakura, who stir up a little trouble.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="176476" update="2017-10-17">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-04-25</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">メイドの味がした</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Taste of Maid</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maid no Aji ga Shita</title>
<summary>Yoko and Futaba are in a pinch and need to find part-time jobs to earn money. Along the way, the three girls meet Shino Sonobe, Yoko`s eccentric former maid.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="176477" update="2017-10-17">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-04-18</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">カラダにいいのはおいしくないものだよ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nothing Good for You Is Tasty</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Karada ni Ii no wa Oishikunai Mono Da yo</title>
<summary>Yoko, Futaba, and Hayama learn more about each other as they continue to eat lunch together. They encounter a rival, a sibling, and cats. All the while,Yoko is deciding whether Hayama is kind-hearted or black-hearted.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="176836" update="2016-04-10">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-04-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="176837" update="2016-04-10">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-04-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="177268" update="2017-10-17">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-05-30</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">たくさん釣れてる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">You`ve Got Them Hooked</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Takusan Tsureteru</title>
<summary>Hayama goes to a cat cafe with her sister and sees Nishiyama there! Futaba has a free ticket for the petting zoo. Then, Futaba wants to start up a band.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="177269" update="2017-10-17">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-05-23</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">十円足りない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ten Yen Short</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Juuen Tarinai</title>
<summary>Fall is here, and we meet two siblings who seem to hate Futaba for no reason. Who are they, and why do they have something against her?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="177270" update="2017-10-17">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-05-16</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">野菜肉肉肉肉肉肉魚</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Veggies, Meat, Meat, Meat, Meat, Meat, Meat, and Fish</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yasai Niku Niku Niku Niku Niku Niku Sakana</title>
<summary>It`s time for the beach! Yoko, Futaba, and Hayama help out Sonobe at her beach hut.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="177271" update="2017-10-17">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-05-09</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">もうこはんはもうないんですね</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Your Birthmarks Have Faded</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Moukohan wa Mou Naindesu ne</title>
<summary>An accident temporarily puts Yoko out of commission, so Futaba and Hayama help out at the patisserie. While Miss Sonobe is certainly grateful for the help, she won`t stop until she`s acquired one more part-time employee.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="177498" update="2017-10-17">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-06-27</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">もうパンの耳は卒業しますわ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Am Graduating from Bread Crusts</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mou Pan no Mimi wa Sotsugyou Shimasuwa</title>
<summary>It starts as a normal day for Yoko, but everybody is acting strange! What has gotten into them?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="177499" update="2017-10-17">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-06-20</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">チョコを食べまくる日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Day to Gorge on Chocolate</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Choko o Tabe Makuru Hi</title>
<summary>Join Yoko, Hayama, and Futaba as they prepare for and celebrate Valentine`s Day.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="177500" update="2017-10-17">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-06-13</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">鶏肉とケーキを食べまくる日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Day to Gorge on Chicken and Cake</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Keiniku to Cake o Tabe Makuru Hi</title>
<summary>It`s Christmas and it also happens to be someone`s birthday. Then, the end of the year approaches, and it`s almost New Year`s. How will Hayama, Futaba, and Yoko celebrate these holidays?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="177501" update="2017-10-17">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-06-06</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">カレーは二日目</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Curry Tastes Better on the Second Day</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Curry wa Futsukame</title>
<summary>The school is having its cultural festival. Hayama and Futaba`s class is doing a curry shop, and Miss Yoko`s class will be doing some haunting!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="182654" update="2016-11-28">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2016-06-29</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">キノコはからだにいいんだよ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mushrooms Are Good for You</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kinoko wa Karada ni Iinda yo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="182655" update="2017-03-22">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2016-07-13</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">高級和牛の試食会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">High Grade Wagyuu Taste Testing</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koukyuu Wagyuu no Shishoku-kai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="182656" update="2017-03-22">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2016-08-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">できる女は目分量</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Smart Girls Measure by Eyes</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dekiru Onna wa Mebunryou</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
