<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="11981" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2017-04-09</startdate>
<enddate>2017-06-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Eromanga-sensei</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">色情漫画老师</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">エロマンガ先生</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Eromanga Sensei</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">EroManga Sensei</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">에로망가 선생</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">埃罗芒阿老师</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="13580" type="Sequel">Eromanga-sensei OVA</anime>
<anime id="7525" type="Same Setting">Ore no Imouto ga Konna ni Kawaii Wake ga Nai</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="4">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="164713">You will definitely like it if you are into this stuff. Characters are super cute. Harem setting is a little bit over the top. Screen time is pretty evenly distributed between the girls. There is a lot of fanservice in form of cameo characters/manga from other titles.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="477606">Your typical Harem Trash anime, but "Very Good" kind of trash,

all characters are cute, care of everyone feeling, and have happy together,
once you get used to it you want it to keep continue forever and want season 2 season 3 more.

Strongly Recommend for Novelist Artist or wannabe and siscon who want/need daily happy life~
Character cuteness is 1000000/100 points</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="540059">the first 2 ep`s i wasnt feeling it; nonsense. but then it started to pick up. i like to feel there is some depth in a ecchi/harem title, this totally has it, if only implied. only got better as it went on. i didnt care for Oreimo at all, couldn`t watch it</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://eromanga-sensei.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="18152" type="Series Composition">Takahashi Tatsuya</name>
<name id="16512" type="Direction">Takeshita Ryouhei</name>
<name id="12860" type="Character Design">Oda Hiroyuki</name>
<name id="1303" type="Work">A-1 Pictures</name>
<name id="17862" type="Original Work">Fushimi Tsukasa</name>
<name id="21412" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kobayashi Shinpei</name>
<name id="3399" type="Music">Kikuya Tomoki</name>
<name id="9087" type="Chief Animation Direction">Oka Yuuichi</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a Japanese light novel series written by http://anidb.net/cr17862 [Fushimi Tsukasa] and illustrated by http://anidb.net/cr17314 [Kanzaki Hiro].
http://anidb.net/ch85258 [Izumi Masamune] is a high school student who loves writing light novels. Having no artistic skill himself, Masamune always gets his novels illustrated by an anonymous partner using the pen name Eromanga-sensei who, like the name suggests, draws questionably perverted images despite being extremely reliable. In addition to balancing his passion and school, Masamune is also stuck with taking care of his only family member, his younger sister http://anidb.net/ch80893 [Izumi Sagiri]. A hikikomori by nature, Sagiri shut herself in her room for over a year and constantly bosses Masamune around despite his attempts to get her to leave her room. However, when Masamune inadvertently discovers that his anonymous partner has been Sagiri all along, their sibling relationship quickly leaps to new levels of excitement, especially when a beautiful popular light novel author enters the fray.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2016">4.20</permanent>
<temporary count="2033">6.28</temporary>
<review count="1">5.33</review>
</ratings>
<picture>199481.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18142</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>32901</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://eromanga-sensei.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Eromanga_Sensei</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>エロマンガ先生</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4506</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>355961</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20043</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>oreimo_eromanga</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>eromanga-sensei</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B06Y459QJ6</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2008" parentid="2891" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-05">
<name>small breasts</name>
<description>This character has a bust size that is considered small. 
The small size is usually a bust that would use a bra which is A or B. In anime, C may rarely enter this category.</description>
<picurl>162720.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3867" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>ED variety</name>
<description>Several ED sequences in this anime have either a different song or different animation, maybe even to the point of having a unique ED for each episode.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4431" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-04-06">
<name>love at first sight</name>
<description>Plot device: When two characters meet for the first time, at least one party, supposedly, immediately falls in love with the other party, and from then on tries to get to know that party better.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5485" parentid="7199" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-28">
<name>penis jokes</name>
<description>A penis or other phallic object is used as a device to elicit laughter from the viewer. This also includes indirect references to such objects provided the intent is clearly the same.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5916" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-26">
<name>product placement</name>
<description>Otherwise known as a "plug" or "writing commercials right into a show". The practice of prominently displaying or talking about a recognizable product in a program, in exchange for some consideration from the manufacturer, usually monetary. (Source: TV Tropes)
Particularly notorious example, Pizza Hut for the involvement with Code Geass, Darker than Black and other series.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6073" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-11-23">
<name>age difference romance</name>
<description>A romance between individuals of significantly different ages is featured. Depending on how big the age gap is and on the society featured, that may be considered taboo.
While the terms "lolicon" and "shotacon", often used in relation to anime and its fandom, are limited to a physical or erotic attraction to sexually precocious girls or boys respectively, this tag expands into platonic romances and other age ranges.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7199" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-12">
<name>sexual humour</name>
<description>Sexual humour is prevalent in this anime. It often involves cheeky or crude sexual language, with innuendos and jokes about the female or male genitalia. Often, such anime also have http://anidb.net/t2856 [ecchi] elements to them.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="29" type="cameo appearance in" update="2017-12-29">
<rating votes="2250">9.19</rating>
<name>Holo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Holo is a wolf harvest deity originally from a land in the north known as Yoitsu. She made a promise with men from a town called Pasroe where she would ensure the town would have good wheat harvests year after year. However, as time went on, the townspeople slowly started to forsake Holo and did not rely on her as they once did. As such, Holo escapes from town in Lawrence`s wagon and started traveling with him to see how much the world has changed since she has been in Pasroe. Holo has chosen the form of a girl younger than Lawrence, though she still retains her large white-tipped wolf tail, and ears. Her true form is that of a very large wolf which many people revered and feared.
She refers to herself as the "Wise Wolf of Yoitsu" (ヨイツの賢狼, Yoitsu no Kenrou). She is typically very haughty and self-sufficient, though due to her isolation for hundreds of years in Pasroe, she came to feel very lonely, and sometimes shows a more fragile side of herself. She relies on Lawrence for company as she fears loneliness, which is something that Lawrence is very aware of and tries to comfort her in his own way. Holo is also very aware of the different time spans that she and Lawrence have, as a human lifespan is like a blink of an eye for her kind. Holo is shown to be quite scared of that fact but hides it with jokes. She has a peculiar way of speaking, modeled after that of the oiran high-class courtesans. She is fond of delicious food and alcohol, but especially loves apples. She takes pride in her tail and takes special care of it, constantly combing and maintaining it.</description>
<picture>209420.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="51" picture="39247.jpg">Koshimizu Ami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1009" type="cameo appearance in" update="2011-08-22">
<rating votes="737">7.54</rating>
<name>Aisaka Taiga</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A girl in Ryuuji`s class. She has a well-regulated and beautiful appearance though is unable to stomach company from others. Due to her often snapping at others in brutal ways and her short stature at 143.6 cm, she is given the nickname "Palmtop Tiger". Her under-developed body and the added nickname has given her a complex which in turn serves to give her a negative attitude and facial expression. Essentially, Taiga gets upset easily and is considerably clumsy. Due to her cute looks (described as a doll by Ryuuji), she often gets confessions by boys her age, but she turns down every one of them. She comes from a rich family but due to bad family relations, she has taken to living on her own. However, since she came from a privileged household, she does not know how to do any domestic chores. When she meets Ryuuji and learns of his domestic talents, she ends up relying on Ryuuji to clean up after her. Aside from sleeping in her own house, and going to school, she spends most of her time at Ryuuji`s house; so much so that she is almost considered a member of his family. At the beginning of the story, she is infatuated with his best friend Kitamura Yuusaku to the point that she drools at her picture collection of him and gets nervous every time he appears. Due to this, Taiga and Ryuuji team up to help each other get into a relationship with each other`s best friend. However, as the story goes on, she too develops feelings for Ryuuji, commenting once how even though they are in a big room, they still sit so close together like at his cramped apartment.</description>
<picture>25133.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="1015" type="cameo appearance in" update="2008-12-28">
<rating votes="398">7.75</rating>
<name>Enpatsu Shakugan no Uchite</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Enpatsu Shakugan no Uchite is Shana`s former name, which she got when she became a flame haze. When transforming, her hair and eyes turn crimson red.</description>
<picture>15374.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="17521" type="cameo appearance in" update="2013-10-03">
<rating votes="135">4.70</rating>
<name>Kurusu Kanako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kurusu Kanako is a friend to Kirino and Ayase, and like them also works as a model, but is also a budding idol and can sing and dance very well. Like Ayase she is also biased against otaku culture, but Ayase manages to trick her into cosplaying as the main character in Kirino`s favorite anime Stardust Witch Meruru for a contest, whose prize is a limited edition Stardust Witch Meruru figurine. She manages to win the contest because of her uncanny resemblance to the main character, and her ability to sing the anime`s main theme so well despite never having sung it before.</description>
<picture>143826.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="17522" type="cameo appearance in" update="2012-10-14">
<rating votes="195">5.56</rating>
<name>Saori Vageena</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Saori Vageena is one of the active female members of the anime forum that Kirino wound up frequenting, and organized the get-together in Akihabara where she met Kirino and Kuroneko for the first time. She is the peacemaker of the group, and her friendly disposition helps to defuse tensions between Kirino and Kuroneko, keeping their arguments about each other`s tastes from getting out of hand. She tends to speak in a very quirky way, always using a very polite and antiquated mode of Japanese generally heard today only in samurai movies. Not much is known about her for certain, not even her real name (Saori Vageena is her handle on the anime board and evidently a pseudonym), but brief scenes of her at home show her in what looks a large mansion, attended by maids and butlers, implying that she is very wealthy, although neither the Kousaka siblings nor Kuroneko seem to be aware of this.</description>
<picture>55757.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="55" picture="33603.jpg">Nabatame Hitomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17524" type="cameo appearance in" update="2011-12-18">
<rating votes="354">4.22</rating>
<name>Kousaka Kyousuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kousaka Kyousuke is the main protagonist of the series, and acts as the narrator. He is a fairly ordinary second-year high school student who wishes for nothing more than a peaceful life until he accidentally discovers his little sister Kirino`s otaku hobbies. Even though Kirino is mean and disrespectful to him, he tries to be a good elder brother to her, giving her advice as best he can, and helping her to continue in her hobbies and make new friends. He is a responsible and reliable person who cares deeply about the welfare of his sister and of his friends.</description>
<picture>55755.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="345" picture="84834.jpg">Nakamura Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17525" type="cameo appearance in" update="2011-12-17">
<rating votes="921">4.89</rating>
<name>Kousaka Kirino</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kousaka Kirino is the main heroine of the series. She is a 14-year old girl who seems normal on the outside, but is in secret a hardcore otaku obsessed with anime and visual novel eroges, especially those involving little sisters. She works part-time as a model, which is how she managed to purchase her most impressive collection of figurines, visual novels, and anime DVDs. She has a talent for writing, and loves track and field.
She is initially cold and disrespectful towards her brother Kyousuke, but after he discovers her secret hobby and he supports her in it, they gradually grow closer.</description>
<picture>53292.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="590" picture="242467.jpg">Taketatsu Ayana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17526" type="cameo appearance in" update="2013-04-21">
<rating votes="1020">8.54</rating>
<name>Gokou Ruri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kuroneko (a.k.a. Gokou Ruri) was one of the anime otaku girls Kirino had met in a gathering organized by Saori. Though their tastes in anime and games greatly differ, they nevertheless began to be good friends. She also became a good friend to Kyousuke, and it is hinted that she may have feelings for him. As befits the Kuroneko epithet, she is usually seen wearing a black Gothic Lolita-style dress, and is sharp-tongued and antisocial.
She enters Kyousuke`s high school later in the series, and joins the Game Club at his urging, displaying her considerable talents at writing and graphic design.</description>
<picture>55756.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="176" picture="192484.jpg">Hanazawa Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="25426" type="cameo appearance in" update="2013-11-28">
<rating votes="24">6.74</rating>
<name>Gokou Tamaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gokou Tamaki is Kuroneko`s younger sister. She is in 1st grade.</description>
<picture>146454.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="37273" type="cameo appearance in" update="2014-04-05">
<rating votes="395">5.83</rating>
<name>Kirito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The main protagonist of the series. He is the protagonist and is a "solo" player, a player who hasn`t joined a guild and usually works alone. When it is announced that the players of Sword Art Online can no longer logout, he is surprised like everyone else, but unlike everyone else he quickly gets over it and accepts it, to an extent. He mainly uses a one-handed sword and usually wears all black in game, as it adds to stealth. He can also use two blades at once, a unique skill to him and he only uses it in emergencies to avoid attention for being one out of the two people to have unique skills. His game alias is Kirito, which is created by taking the syllables of the first and last Kanji of his real last and first names respectively: (Kirigaya Kazuto). In the real world, he lives with his mother and younger sister in a family of 3.</description>
<picture>83186.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20249" picture="186289.jpg">Matsuoka Yoshitsugu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="56133" type="cameo appearance in" update="2013-11-28">
<rating votes="18">8.83</rating>
<name>Gokou Hinata</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gokou Hinata is Kuroneko`s younger sister. She is in 5th grade.</description>
<picture>146453.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="176" picture="192484.jpg">Hanazawa Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60239" type="cameo appearance in" update="2017-07-03">
<rating votes="195">7.48</rating>
<name>Shiba Tatsuya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>149874.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="345" picture="84834.jpg">Nakamura Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80893" type="main character in" update="2019-01-27">
<rating votes="64">6.01</rating>
<name>Izumi Sagiri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>229653.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34976" picture="188448.jpg">Fujita Akane</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85257" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-01-27">
<rating votes="33">6.46</rating>
<name>Senju Muramasa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>229655.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34449" picture="171791.jpg">Oonishi Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85258" type="main character in" update="2019-01-27">
<rating votes="17">4.64</rating>
<name>Izumi Masamune</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>229652.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20249" picture="186289.jpg">Matsuoka Yoshitsugu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85259" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-01-27">
<rating votes="62">7.94</rating>
<name>Yamada Elf</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>229654.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33633" picture="151771.jpg">Takahashi Minami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85260" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-01-27">
<rating votes="34">6.34</rating>
<name>Jinno Megumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>229656.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32738" picture="88323.jpg">Kido Ibuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85261" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-01-27">
<rating votes="31">7.06</rating>
<name>Takasago Tomoe</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>229657.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="443" picture="145927.jpg">Ishikawa Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88150" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-01-28">
<rating votes="10">3.41</rating>
<name>Shidou Kunimitsu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>229710.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10776" picture="77627.jpg">Shimazaki Nobunaga</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88151" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-01-28">
<rating votes="21">3.49</rating>
<name>Kagurazaka Ayame</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>229712.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16085" picture="178446.jpg">Komatsu Mikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88806" type="appears in" update="2017-06-18">
<rating votes="2">4.88</rating>
<name>Masamune no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203997.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="345" picture="84834.jpg">Nakamura Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88807" type="appears in" update="2017-06-18">
<rating votes="8">6.41</rating>
<name>Sagiri no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203999.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="516" picture="34813.jpg">Iguchi Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89217" type="appears in" update="2017-06-10">
<rating votes="5">3.68</rating>
<name>Yamada Chris</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203789.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37882" picture="173035.jpg">Yamashita Seiichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="186437" update="2017-04-30">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-04-30</airdate>
<rating votes="19">5.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">エロマンガ先生</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Eromanga Sensei</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Maître Eromanga</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Eromanga-sensei</title>
<summary>After observing the younger and more popular author, Elf Yamada, work on her novel, Masamune and Elf become a little closer. Sagiri notices this, and gets suspicious of their relationship, despite Masamune saying that he and Yamada-san don’t get along at all.  Regardless of their argument over this matter, Masamune begins working on his “ultimate light novel”!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>734161</identifier>
<identifier>eromanga-sensei</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="186438" update="2017-04-22">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-04-23</airdate>
<rating votes="17">5.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">全裸の館と堕落の主[あるじ]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Buck Naked Mansion and the Fallen Master</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le manoir de la nudité et l`adepte de la dépravation</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zenra no Kan to Daraku no Aruji</title>
<summary>The Izumi House`s empty mansion next door has rumors of being cursed because of continuous misfortunes.  But what happens when Sagiri starts hearing piano music coming from the supposed empty mansion?!  And how will Masamune handle this Fallen Master?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>734159</identifier>
<identifier>eromanga-sensei</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="186439" update="2017-04-15">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-04-16</airdate>
<rating votes="21">5.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">リア充委員長と不敵な妖精</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Class Rep with a Normie Life, and a Fearless Fairy</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La déléguée extravertie et la fée intrépide</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Reajuu Iinchou to Futeki na Yousei</title>
<summary>Megumi Jinno, the class representative for Sagiri`s class, shows up at the Izumi residence with no prior warning. Her mission is to "take Sagiri to school". How will Sagiri and Masamune handle the situation? Afterwards, Masamune runs into a mystical fairy in a pink dress...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>734157</identifier>
<identifier>eromanga-sensei</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="186440" update="2017-04-08">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-04-09</airdate>
<rating votes="20">5.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">妹と開かずの間</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My Little Sister, and the Sealed Room</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ma petite sœur, et la chambre isolée</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Imouto to Akazu no Ma</title>
<summary>Masamune Izumi is a high school student also working as a light novel author.  He works with a mysterious illustrator who draws really erotic art for his light novels.  In the midst of trying to deal with school and his shut-in sister, he discovers the identity behind this Eromanga-sensei!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>734155</identifier>
<identifier>eromanga-sensei</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="186654" update="2017-04-03">
<epno type="2">S9</epno>
<length>115</length>
<airdate>2017-03-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アニメ『エロマンガ先生』 最近 (もっとも近い) のアニメをみんなで作ります - 9</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S9</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Anime "Eromanga Sensei" Saikin (Mottomo Chikai) no Anime o Minna de Tsukurimasu - 9</title>
</episode>
<episode id="186655" update="2017-04-03">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>145</length>
<airdate>2017-02-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アニメ『エロマンガ先生』 最近 (もっとも近い) のアニメをみんなで作ります - 8</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S8</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Anime "Eromanga Sensei" Saikin (Mottomo Chikai) no Anime o Minna de Tsukurimasu - 8</title>
</episode>
<episode id="186656" update="2017-04-03">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>95</length>
<airdate>2017-01-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アニメ『エロマンガ先生』 最近 (もっとも近い) のアニメをみんなで作ります - 7</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S7</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Anime "Eromanga Sensei" Saikin (Mottomo Chikai) no Anime o Minna de Tsukurimasu - 7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="186657" update="2017-04-03">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>100</length>
<airdate>2016-12-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アニメ『エロマンガ先生』 最近 (もっとも近い) のアニメをみんなで作ります - 6</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S6</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Anime "Eromanga Sensei" Saikin (Mottomo Chikai) no Anime o Minna de Tsukurimasu - 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="186658" update="2017-04-03">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>85</length>
<airdate>2016-11-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アニメ『エロマンガ先生』 最近 (もっとも近い) のアニメをみんなで作ります - 5</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S5</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Anime "Eromanga Sensei" Saikin (Mottomo Chikai) no Anime o Minna de Tsukurimasu - 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="186659" update="2017-04-03">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>95</length>
<airdate>2016-10-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アニメ『エロマンガ先生』 最近 (もっとも近い) のアニメをみんなで作ります - 4</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Anime "Eromanga Sensei" Saikin (Mottomo Chikai) no Anime o Minna de Tsukurimasu - 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="186660" update="2017-04-03">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>85</length>
<airdate>2016-09-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アニメ『エロマンガ先生』 最近 (もっとも近い) のアニメをみんなで作ります - 3</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Anime "Eromanga Sensei" Saikin (Mottomo Chikai) no Anime o Minna de Tsukurimasu - 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="186661" update="2017-04-03">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>90</length>
<airdate>2016-08-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アニメ『エロマンガ先生』 最近 (もっとも近い) のアニメをみんなで作ります - 2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Anime "Eromanga Sensei" Saikin (Mottomo Chikai) no Anime o Minna de Tsukurimasu - 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="186662" update="2017-04-03">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>85</length>
<airdate>2016-07-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アニメ『エロマンガ先生』 最近 (もっとも近い) のアニメをみんなで作ります - 1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Anime "Eromanga Sensei" Saikin (Mottomo Chikai) no Anime o Minna de Tsukurimasu - 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="187028" update="2018-02-23">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-04-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="187029" update="2018-02-23">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-04-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="187030" update="2020-02-11">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-04-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="187286" update="2017-05-27">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-05-28</airdate>
<rating votes="16">5.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夢見る紗霧と夏花火</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dreaming Sagiri and Summer Fireworks</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les rêveries de Sagiri et les feux d`artifices d`été</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yumemiru Sagiri to Natsu Hanabi</title>
<summary>Sagiri finds out what happened between Masamune and Muramasa. It’s not like Sagiri was happy about it or anything.  In the midst of this, it’s crunch time at the editorial office as Masamune begins to turn his short story into a long novel.  Elf-sensei also suggests having a wrap party at Masamune’s house as they celebrate summer in yukata outfits!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>734169</identifier>
<identifier>eromanga-sensei</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="187287" update="2017-05-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-05-21</airdate>
<rating votes="16">5.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">妹と世界で一番面白い小説</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Little Sister and the Most Interesting Novel in the World</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Écrire le meilleur roman au monde avec sa petite sœur</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Imouto to Sekai no Ichiban Omoshiroi Shousetsu</title>
<summary>Masamune, who is sparing no effort to publish his new title faster, immediately signs up for the light-novel competition, “Light-novel Tenkaichi Budoukai.” However, the super-popular author, Senju Muramasa, also signs up for the competition and declares to Masamune that she will crush his pointless dream! Why would she even do that?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>734167</identifier>
<identifier>eromanga-sensei</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="187288" update="2017-05-13">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-05-14</airdate>
<rating votes="16">5.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">和泉マサムネと一千万部の宿敵</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Masamune Izumi and the Nemesis of Ten Million Copies</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Izumi Masamune et l`adversaire aux 10 millions d’exemplaires</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Izumi Masamune to Issenmanbu no Shukuteki</title>
<summary>To find a clue for becoming friends with Sagiri, Megumi tries to gain an affinity for light-novels. Masamune suggests dropping by and asking if she could borrow books from Sagiri.  At first, Sagiri vehemently rejects the encounter, but later presents Masamune with a certain condition…
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>734165</identifier>
<identifier>eromanga-sensei</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="187289" update="2017-05-06">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-05-07</airdate>
<rating votes="17">5.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">妹とラノベ企画を創ろう</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let`s Plan a Light-Novel with Your Little Sister</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Écrire un projet de light novel avec sa petite sœur</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Imouto to Linove Kigaku o Tsukurou</title>
<summary>Motivated by Masamune’s manuscript, Sagiri puts effort into getting a little closer to Masamune, despite the awkwardness.  Both of them are now working towards making the manuscript into a book, starting with the project proposal. In the midst of all this, Elf sends an emergency text message to Masamune!?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>734163</identifier>
<identifier>eromanga-sensei</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="187541" update="2017-05-07">
<epno type="2">S10</epno>
<length>75</length>
<airdate>2017-05-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アニメ『エロマンガ先生』 最近 (もっとも近い) のアニメをみんなで作ります - 10</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S10</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Anime "Eromanga Sensei" Saikin (Mottomo Chikai) no Anime o Minna de Tsukurimasu - 10</title>
</episode>
<episode id="187888" update="2017-06-25">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-06-25</airdate>
<rating votes="16">5.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">エロマンガフェスティバル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Eromanga Festival</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Eromanga festival</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Eromanga Festival</title>
<summary>Masamune and Sagiri`s new work, "Sekaimo: The World`s Cutest Little Sister" is now on sale. Sagiri continues to stream from her room wearing a mask as always, and declares the curtain rising on a "Festival".
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>734177</identifier>
<identifier>eromanga-sensei</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="187889" update="2017-06-17">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-06-18</airdate>
<rating votes="15">7.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">二人の出会いと未来の兄妹[ふたり]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">How the Two Met and Future Siblings</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Notre première rencontre et notre avenir en commun</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Futari no Deai to Mirai no Futari</title>
<summary>Masamune comes home from his trip, and Sagiri is happy to see him return.  They now await their new novel to go on sale.  On the day of, an “Izumi Masamune Faire” is held in a store in Akihabara. While Masamune and Sagiri “explore” the area, they share their stories of how they got into writing novels and illustrating.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>734175</identifier>
<identifier>eromanga-sensei</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="187890" update="2017-06-11">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-06-11</airdate>
<rating votes="15">4.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">和泉マサムネと年下の先輩</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Masamune Izumi and the Younger Senpai</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Izumi Masamune et sa jeune aînée</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Izumi Masamune to Toshishita no Senpai</title>
<summary>At the Yamada Family’s vacation house, Muramasa enthusiastically reads Masamune’s “shelved” stories. Even Masamune can’t hide his happiness when he sees someone reading his novels so passionately. However, within Muramasa’s heart filled with unhidden love towards Masamune, there was indeed a change occurring, and so Muramasa makes a certain decision.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>734173</identifier>
<identifier>eromanga-sensei</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="187891" update="2017-06-05">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-06-04</airdate>
<rating votes="15">7.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">妹と妖精の島</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Little Sister and the Fairy Island</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ma petite sœur et l`île féerique</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Imouto to Yousei no Shima</title>
<summary>"I`ll call it the `Summer Data Collection and Writing Camp`!" As a result of one of Elf`s ideas, the light-novel authors end up heading to a vacation house on an island in the “South Seas”. How far can Elf push the "Data Collection" card?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>734171</identifier>
<identifier>eromanga-sensei</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="188105" update="2017-06-04">
<epno type="2">S12</epno>
<length>60</length>
<airdate>2017-06-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アニメ『エロマンガ先生』 最近 (もっとも近い) のアニメをみんなで作ります - 12</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S12</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Anime "Eromanga Sensei" Saikin (Mottomo Chikai) no Anime o Minna de Tsukurimasu - 12</title>
</episode>
<episode id="188106" update="2017-06-04">
<epno type="2">S11</epno>
<length>115</length>
<airdate>2017-05-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アニメ『エロマンガ先生』 最近 (もっとも近い) のアニメをみんなで作ります - 11</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S11</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Anime "Eromanga Sensei" Saikin (Mottomo Chikai) no Anime o Minna de Tsukurimasu - 11</title>
</episode>
<episode id="193694" update="2020-02-12">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-06-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="193695" update="2020-02-12">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-06-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2c</title>
</episode>
<episode id="196609" update="2020-02-11">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-05-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="196610" update="2020-02-12">
<epno type="3">C8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-06-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2d</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198113" update="2018-04-17">
<epno type="4">T8</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198114" update="2018-04-17">
<epno type="4">T7</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198115" update="2018-04-17">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198116" update="2018-04-17">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198117" update="2018-04-17">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198118" update="2018-04-17">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198119" update="2018-04-17">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198120" update="2018-04-17">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="226834" update="2020-02-12">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-05-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
