<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="12023" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>6</episodecount>
<startdate>2018-06-03</startdate>
<enddate>2018-07-07</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Furi Kuri Progressive</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Fooly Cooly Progressive</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Фури-кури 2</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">フリクリ プログレ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">FLCL Progressive</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">FLCL: прог</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="13258" type="Sequel">Furi Kuri Alternative</anime>
<anime id="117" type="Prequel">Furi Kuri</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="758462">Earnestly trying to avoid ripping off the original series, Progressive manages to become something in and of itself, even if that `something` is not that much to write home about.

Overall it`s a pleasant show, which doesn`t stand a chance against the 2000s OVA. But it doesn`t try to, so it`s all good. 

Oh, and the protagonist is such a cutie.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://flcl-anime.com/progre/</url>
<creators>
<name id="671" type="Character Design">Kubota Chikashi</name>
<name id="21989" type="Chief Direction">Motohiro Katsuyuki</name>
<name id="27345" type="Direction">Hiroshi Ikehata</name>
<name id="32756" type="Direction">Ogawa Yuuki</name>
<name id="27520" type="Direction">Suezawa Kei</name>
<name id="721" type="Animation Work">Production I.G</name>
<name id="7062" type="Music">RON</name>
<name id="43312" type="Animation Work">Signal MD</name>
<name id="44522" type="Animation Work">Production Good Book</name>
<name id="29133" type="Direction">Ibata Yoshihide</name>
<name id="45020" type="Direction">Arai Kazuto</name>
<name id="5808" type="Direction">Kaiya Toshihisa</name>
</creators>
<description>Many years have passed since http://anidb.net/ch10129 [Naota] and http://anidb.net/ch5487 [Haruhara Haruko] shared their adventure together. Meanwhile, the war between the two entities known as Medical Mechanica and Fraternity rages across the galaxy. Enter http://anidb.net/ch94691 [Hidomi], a young teenaged girl who believes there is nothing amazing to expect from her average life, until one day when a new teacher named Haruko arrives at her school. Soon enough, Medical Mechanica is attacking her town and Hidomi discovers a secret within her that could save everyone, a secret that only Haruko can unlock.
But why did Haruko return to Earth? What happened to her Rickenbacker 4001 she left with Naota? And where did the human-type robot http://anidb.net/ch10207 [Canti] go?
Source: Adult Swim
Note: The anime first aired in the US on Adult Swim`s Toonami block in June. In Japan it was released in a movie format on 28.09.2018.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="493">4.12</permanent>
<temporary count="495">5.85</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>257709.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20791</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>19820</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>33010</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://flcl-anime.com/progre/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>FLCL#Sequel_series</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>フリクリ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5226</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>361117</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21028</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>FLCL_JAPAN/</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="26">
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=Ix7mDEclKxU</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>flcl</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B07D9T14CN</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="28" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-16">
<name>baseball</name>
<description>Baseball is like a complicated version of Rounders. It involves hitting a ball with a stick, then running around several bases placed in the form of a diamond on a field. Big in the US, and also in Japan.</description>
<picurl>29801.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1152" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-23">
<name>undead</name>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2257" parentid="1152" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-12">
<name>zombie</name>
<description>A zombie is asserted to be a reanimated corpse, or a human who is being controlled by someone else by use of magic with some media renditions using a pandemic illness to explain their existence.
Stories of zombies originated in the West African spiritual belief system of voodoo, which told of the people being controlled as laborers by a powerful wizard.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>36563.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2644" parentid="2274" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-14">
<name>transforming craft</name>
<description>A transforming craft is an object built by humans or other intelligent lifeforms, usually a robot but sometimes also a vehicle of some sort, that can rearrange its parts in order to switch between a minimum of two forms.</description>
<picurl>224142.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2654" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-13">
<name>medium awareness</name>
<description>Medium awareness is the situational and generally temporary awareness characters in works of fiction have and display of the very fact that they are characters in works of fiction. For example, they may comment about the background music, quip about the script or narration, complain about the roles given to them by the writer or their lack of screen time, see the subtitles that appear on screen, inform the audience about the arrival of the commercial break, and even use medium effects as tools. The most common form of medium awareness is known as breaking the fourth wall, in which characters speak directly to the audience, either to it as a whole or to specific members of it. The "fourth wall" is the imaginary "wall" at the front of the stage of a proscenium theatre through which the audience sees the play; it is a metaphor for the boundary between what happens inside the work, to the characters, and outside it, to the audience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2775" parentid="2202" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>humanoid alien</name>
<description>Humanoids are aliens, intelligent beings who do not originate from Earth, but have a striking similarity to humans or at least show the basic body layout, i.e. two arms and legs, head with two eyes and ears, one nose and mouth. Though the latter - head-related features - may vary. As "DearS" shows some aliens actually exhibit super-human beauty, or as in the case of "Onegai Teacher" they are genetically compatible to humans for some strange reason.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2821" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>sudden naked girl appearance</name>
<description>A character or group of characters are simply minding their own business, when suddenly, a naked girl appears. It does not matter how or why, but a naked someone is there. Sometimes the naked girl is not happy about this. 
Usually this is a fanservice element, but not always.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2823" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>paper clothes</name>
<description>Worn clothing appears paper-thin and takes little abuse to be shredded or torn from the body. This is common in ecchi anime where the main storyline involves some type of fighting but consists primarily of dialogue and fanservice (Ikkitousen and Platonic Heart). Various girls’ clothing exploding as if made of rice paper is a very enticing prospect.</description>
<picurl>150776.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2851" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>horror</name>
<description>The horror cinematic genre is characterized by the attempt to make the viewer experience dread, fear, terror, or horror. Often their plots involve the intrusion of an evil force, event or personage, sometimes of supernatural origin, on the mundane world and the consequences thereof.</description>
<picurl>214682.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3277" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-28">
<name>bendy lasers</name>
<description>Lasers — of all things — bend at strange angles, are profusely in effect in this anime. Usually seen in a space setting, as part of a weapon system on spaceships.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3546" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-01-08">
<name>experimental animation</name>
<description>This anime uses distinct, alternative animation — much unlike other contemporary anime — either throughout or in individual episodes/sequences.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4083" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-04">
<name>drastic change of life</name>
<description>One or more characters in this series go through an event that makes them change their way of life drastically and permanently. This change might be voluntary, or against the character`s will.
Some examples might be an accident, the gaining of superpowers, or simply graduating.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4096" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>gore</name>
<description>A Splatter film or Gore film is a sub-genre of horror film that deliberately focuses on graphic portrayals of gore and graphic violence. These films, through the use of special effects and excessive blood and guts, tend to display an overt interest in the vulnerability of the human body and the theatricality of its mutilation. Due to their willingness to portray images society might consider shocking, splatter films share some ideological grounds with the transgressive art movement. The term "splatter cinema" was coined by George A. Romero to describe his film Dawn of the Dead, though Dawn of the Dead is generally considered by critics to have higher aspirations, such as social commentary, than to be simply exploitative for its own sake.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>32491.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4131" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-05-11">
<name>cultural references</name>
<description>The plot of this anime shows signs of cultural references, these are often jokes that make reference to a certain custom, habit or history that is specifically attributed to that culture. Knowledge of the culture itself is needed in order to properly understand these jokes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4167" parentid="2841" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-08-24">
<name>air combat</name>
<description>Dogfight refers to combat engagement between aircraft (or space craft), often one on one. So in short: jets, planes, missiles, machine guns and maybe a kamikaze or two.
Not to be confused with the `bark-bark` or `woof-woof` sort of dogfight.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4193" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-03-23">
<name>improbable physics</name>
<description>The physics in this anime have little to do with real-world physics, and are actually very much exaggerated.
Examples: Cars hitting a tiny obstacle, but then flying through the air for no apparent reason, or flimsy bullets slamming heavy characters clear across the room.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4217" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-02-11">
<name>nightmares</name>
<description>One or more characters in the anime are plagued by bad dreams.
Possible causes: A traumatic experience in the past or induced by an external "presence".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4225" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-02-16">
<name>symbolism</name>
<description>Representation of a more complex concept by a simple thing. Like a red flower for love or a flag for a nation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4280" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-06-02">
<name>surreal</name>
<description>Refers to things or occurrences that are generally bizarre or dreamlike, with the relentless capability of replacing reality through the eyes of the beholder. Surrealism is boundless, limited only by thought itself.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4499" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-07-28">
<name>some weird shit goin` on</name>
<description>Scenes of this show point to insanely strange events which seem to be taking place; throughout its episodes, the show may or may not explain what is going on. Either way, many viewers will find that a succinct and accurate way to describe the show is "WTF?", and the show`s explanations (or lack thereof) to the events will often be subject of heated debate.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4588" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-20">
<name>fast-paced</name>
<description>Hold onto your hats, this anime`s storyline is relentless.
The characters don`t get time to take a breath as events keep both them and the viewer on a roller coaster ride of revelation and excitement!
Hopefully it all makes sense...</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5095" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2022-04-21">
<name>slum</name>
<description>A slum is a highly populated urban residential area consisting of densely packed housing units of weak build quality and often associated with poverty. The infrastructure in slums is often deteriorated or incomplete, and they are primarily inhabited by impoverished people. Although slums are usually located in urban areas, in some countries they can be located in suburban areas where housing quality is low and living conditions are poor. While slums differ in size and other characteristics, most lack reliable sanitation services, supply of clean water, reliable electricity, law enforcement, and other basic services. Slum residences vary from shanty houses to professionally built dwellings which, because of poor-quality construction or lack of basic maintenance, have deteriorated.
Source: wikipedia</description>
<picurl>272197.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5227" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-04-26">
<name>alternating animation style</name>
<description>The animation style in this show may change between scenes, usually making the anime experimental in a way. This may be a form of artistic visualisation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5417" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-22">
<name>mind fuck</name>
<description>A `mind fuck` is a slang term which describes a work that uses literary devices such as nonlinear storytelling and plot twists in order to present convoluted, yet not conflicting, themes.
A creation is usually considered a mind fuck when a casual observer is not able to discern the true meaning of a work without making a serious attempt to unravel the themes presented or when the plot is incredibly difficult to follow.
Special examples of mind fucks involve a single plot twist which completely changes the viewer`s understanding of the events in a film or novel as well as the ideas it presents.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5459" parentid="6243" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-10">
<name>poverty</name>
<description>It refers to the condition of not having the means to afford basic human needs.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5697" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-02">
<name>randomness</name>
<description>The anime does not follow a predictable storyline. New, strange, obscure, or otherwise unexpected story elements are introduced at a whim.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6019" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2021-03-19">
<name>brainwashing</name>
<description>Brainwashing, the application of coercive techniques to change the values and beliefs, perceptions and judgements, and subsequent mindsets and behaviours of one or more people, usually for political, financial, personal, or religious purposes. The victim is left http://anidb.net/t91 [brainwashed]. Often featured in dark anime or pornography.</description>
<picurl>258585.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6034" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>Engrish</name>
<description>Engrish is actually a mispronunciation of English, as can be the result of someone, who does not have English as their primary language of origin (such as Japanese or Chinese). Occasionally characters in the original Japanese dialogue version of an anime will speak in English... however; this often still requires the assistance of subtitles, for while the words are meant to be said in English, the sentence structure and letter pronunciation may still be strongly related to the person’s primary language.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>origin</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6243" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-29">
<name>money</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7885" parentid="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2021-11-07">
<name>Japanese production</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="10207" type="appears in" update="2010-11-05">
<rating votes="32">7.39</rating>
<name>Canti</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>Canti is a robot with what looks like a television set for a head. After having his head broken by Haruko, he is recruited by her as an assistant; however, he proves to be no good for much other than washing dishes and fetching drinks for the family.
He was manufactured by Medical Mechanica, but taken over by Atomsk as a way to escape them. Atomsk can manifest through Canti, with Naota being the catalyst. Atomsk`s symbol appears on Canti`s screen when he absorbs Naota; the symbol is a corruption of the kanji characters for "adult" (大人). This symbol also appears on him when Naota "swings the bat" in Full Swing. The symbol that appears when Canti is absorbed by the terminal core in FLCLimax is similar, but he uses the characters for "child" (小人) instead. When Naota is absorbed, Canti`s physical strength is increased and he gains the ability to transform into a canon, that utilizes pilot as a munition.
The emotions of Canti are very human-like, despite his looks. He is embarrassed about his broken head (where Haruko hit him) and is looking for the pieces to glue back together in episode two. He wears the box on the back of his head for the same reason. Canti seems to like porn, as he was reading it in the 7-11. It is also stated in the novel, that Canti spends 3 hours at a time looking through `perverted magazines.` He is also extremely polite, extending a helping hand to Lieutenant Kitsurubami even after she attempted to destroy him.
Canti also dons a halo and fake wings which Haruko puts on him earlier in the episode. Mamimi is convinced that Canti is an angel. She calls him "Canti-sama" after "The Lord of Black Flames" in a video game she plays. The rest of the cast call him by this title throughout the rest of the series.</description>
<picture>30635.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="94681" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-06-20">
<rating votes="4">2.26</rating>
<name>Aiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>219370.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16804" picture="224734.jpg">Kurosawa Tomoyo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94682" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-06-20">
<rating votes="4">3.01</rating>
<name>Eyepatch</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>219371.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="464" picture="11019.jpeg">Sugou Takayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94683" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-06-20">
<rating votes="4">6.54</rating>
<name>Julia Jinyu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>219365.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38" picture="11310.jpeg">Sawashiro Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94684" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-07-16">
<rating votes="5">3.66</rating>
<name>Haruha Raharu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>220476.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="13" picture="16583.jpg">Hayashibara Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94685" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-07-16">
<rating votes="4">2.68</rating>
<name>Masurao</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>220478.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5891" picture="30453.jpg">Ookura Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94686" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-06-24">
<rating votes="4">3.01</rating>
<name>Marco Nogata</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>219367.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="13644" picture="236301.jpg">Nakazawa Masatomo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94687" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-06-24">
<rating votes="5">4.70</rating>
<name>Ide Kou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>219372.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="14" picture="265667.jpg">Fukuyama Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94688" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-06-28">
<rating votes="4">2.68</rating>
<name>Tonkichi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>219669.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9288" picture="34149.jpg">Urayama Jin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94689" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-06-24">
<rating votes="4">2.38</rating>
<name>Mori Gorou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>219368.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32035" picture="151695.jpg">Muranaka Tomo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94690" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-05-29">
<rating votes="3">2.65</rating>
<name>Hanae Tami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>247867.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2040" picture="186173.jpg">Suzuki Reiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94691" type="main character in" update="2018-06-19">
<rating votes="9">7.29</rating>
<name>Hibajiri Hidomi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66223.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="21013" picture="201781.jpg">Minase Inori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94692" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-07-16">
<rating votes="4">6.67</rating>
<name>Hibajiri Hinae</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>220477.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="240" picture="265340.jpg">Inoue Kikuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96233" type="appears in" update="2018-09-30">
<rating votes="2">5.85</rating>
<name>Haruko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>219433.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="195975" update="2018-02-11">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2017-07-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">劇場版フリクリ2&amp;3 超特報</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 1 (0:39): Furi Kuri Movie 2 &amp; 3: Super Special</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekijouban Furi Kuri 2 &amp; 3: Chou Tokuhou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="197249" update="2018-11-21">
<epno type="6">O1</epno>
<length>135</length>
<airdate>2018-09-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="200085" update="2019-05-26">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-06-03</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">サイスタ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">RE: Start</title>
<summary>Hidomi’s Dream – white ash covers the entire ruins, behind which a row of humongous irons comes thundering after Hidomi who is now a zombie.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>786438</identifier>
<identifier>flcl</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="200229" update="2019-05-26">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-06-10</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">フリハニ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Freebie Honey</title>
<summary>Hidomi wakes up from yet another dream of her becoming a Zombie. At school, Raharu gives her a handout to bring over to Ide, who didn’t show up to class.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>786441</identifier>
<identifier>flcl</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="200331" update="2019-05-26">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-06-17</airdate>
<rating votes="5">2.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ミズキリ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Stone Skipping</title>
<summary>Crazy things happen during Hidomi’s NO activation, and she is now left with a cheerful and happy personality, which is the total opposite of her real self. The only way to bring her back to normal is to destroy the cables of the giant iron.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>786439</identifier>
<identifier>flcl</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="200720" update="2019-05-26">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-06-24</airdate>
<rating votes="4">2.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ラリルレ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">LooPQR</title>
<summary>Marco is the only one that seems to think that happy Hidomi is attractive. While he’s aware that Ide is in love with her, he works part time to buy her a charm. Meanwhile, Jinyu and Raharu scheme to go up to the plant in her Bel Aire.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>786443</identifier>
<identifier>flcl</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="201847" update="2019-05-26">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-06-30</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">フルブラ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fool on the Planet</title>
<summary>Having made damage to the plant, the iron now stands up straight. Raharu tells the class that she’s happily married and now pregnant. The only way to become happy is to go to the amusement park (run by Tonkichi).
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>786444</identifier>
<identifier>flcl</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="202122" update="2019-05-26">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-07-07</airdate>
<rating votes="6">2.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アワラン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Our Running</title>
<summary>Trying to get Ide back, Hidomi attacks Raharu physically first then verbally. She tells Raharu that she is acting immature because she knows that she is using Hidomi because Raharu is in love with Atomsk.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>786440</identifier>
<identifier>flcl</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="217906" update="2019-06-08">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-06-03</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
