<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="12280" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2016-10-05</startdate>
<enddate>2016-12-21</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Nazotokine</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ナゾトキネ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Nazotokine</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">解谜之音</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="12716" type="Sequel">Kaito x Ansa</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://nazotokine.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="20731" type="Original Work">Fukushi Naoya</name>
<name id="20731" type="Direction">Fukushi Naoya</name>
<name id="46386" type="Animation Work">Tengu Koubou</name>
<name id="50982" type="Character Design">Takano Hitomi</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch84196 [Amino Tokine] is the CEO`s secretary at the advertising agency TEN2. But only her best friends at the company, http://anidb.net/ch84193 [Yamazumi Yoshie] and http://anidb.net/ch84195 [Minakami Kyouka], both working the front desk, know that the much admired Amino is secretly a huge http://anidb.net/t1133 [otaku] and also loves tokusatsu.
One day, while putting in order conference room G, just before a meeting with a important animation company, she finds herself bathed in intense light, and transported to a strange parallel world. Here a small "inter-dimensional pig" named http://anidb.net/ch84192 [Hacchin] greats the seemingly unfazed Amino, explaining that she will not be able to leave this world called Quizun unless she solves riddles within a time limit.
As it turns out Amino has been chosen, and is given the power to unlock the truth, while wearing a tight-fitting suit, that releases her full reasoning potential. Solving a riddle, releases a crystal called Q-Stone from Amino`s body, that Hacchin collects.
And so she vows to "solve the riddles, then think about them!"
— written by foo2</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="218">1.86</permanent>
<temporary count="218">4.19</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>188851.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18634</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>33690</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://nazotokine.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Nazotokine</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ナゾトキネ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4323</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>358285</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19658</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>nazotokine</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1482" parentid="2751" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-09-08">
<name>wrestling</name>
<description>Wrestling is a fight between two people without weapons, in which each person tries to beat their opponent. Wrestlers use clinching, holding, locking, and leverage. It resembles ritual fighting as it avoids things that will likely lead to serious injury. It is similar to military hand-to-hand combat or self-defence systems.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2751" parentid="2881" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-27">
<name>combat</name>
<description>Combat involves a violent conflict with the goal to establish dominance over an opponent.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2838" parentid="2628" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>parallel world</name>
<description>A parallel world, parallel universe, or alternative reality is a self-contained separate reality coexisting with our own. Because "alternative reality" sometimes implies that the reality is a variant of our own, like for example a mirror world, we use the term "parallel world/universe" which is more general, without any connotations implying a relationship (or lack thereof) with our own world/universe (meaning a fictional world can just as well have an alternative reality, it doesn`t need to be our reality). To put it more simply, this category is to show if more than 1 world/universe/reality is present in the anime.
Multiple timelines of the same world/universe/reality are NOT considered parallel worlds. For example, in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate] the cast travels through multiple "World Lines", which are defined as parallel timelines of the same universe had various events occurred with differing outcomes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2854" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>henshin</name>
<description>Japanese for "transformation" (metamorphosis or disguise).
A "henshin anime" is any anime, where the characters or their costumes transform, such as Sailor Moon. The henshin switches on the character`s special powers, and is frequently accompanied by a costume change. Often the change of clothing is the only outward indicator that the character has changed and yet nobody seems to notice the hero`s true self.
Most henshin heroes have a special item which they use to change into their heroic form. These items are usually activated by a command phrase (which is often in Engrish, for some reason), triggering a transformation sequence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3217" parentid="2864" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-17">
<name>working life</name>
<description>The life of someone actually working on a often less than glamorous job is depicted in this anime. The job is taxing and the pay is low, not really the dream job one would choose to work in.
Examples: Working as salesperson in a department store, or as a waitress in a family restaurant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3842" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-31">
<name>TV censoring</name>
<description>The TV version is censored and later DVD/BD releases are uncensored, so the money-grubbing capitalists can make a couple more bucks at our expense.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3977" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-29">
<name>dialogue driven</name>
<description>A dialogue driven show has its story advanced by dialogue, with action being of much lower priority, and relies heavily on conversations between characters.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5697" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-02">
<name>randomness</name>
<description>The anime does not follow a predictable storyline. New, strange, obscure, or otherwise unexpected story elements are introduced at a whim.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5852" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>short episodes</name>
<description>Short episodes are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length. This means up to and including 10 minutes; shows with episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length are http://anidb.net/t6494 [half-length episodes] instead.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6349 [multi-segment episodes], which are regular episodes that are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6018" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-27">
<name>predominantly adult cast</name>
<description>This show features mostly adults. That means children and teenagers are relatively rare and unlikely to hold significance to the plot.
That is a rare trait in anime, as most shows spin around children or teenagers.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="84192" type="main character in" update="2017-06-03">
<rating votes="1">1.23</rating>
<name>Hacchin</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203402.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21805" picture="169875.jpg">Tokui Sora</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84193" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-06-03">
<name>Yamazumi Yoshie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203407.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45197" picture="232225.jpg">Yashima Sarara</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84194" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-06-03">
<name>Yanagisawa Natsuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203408.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21806" picture="186701.jpg">Sasaki Mikoi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84195" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-06-03">
<name>Minakami Kyouka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203406.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34361" picture="127753.jpg">Matsui Eriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84196" type="main character in" update="2017-06-03">
<rating votes="2">6.53</rating>
<name>Amino Tokine</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203400.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43627" picture="176871.jpg">Hara Natsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89734" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-06-03">
<name>Takaragawa Hinata</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203401.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="22170" picture="226837.jpg">Nitta Emi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="111823" type="appears in" update="2020-07-29">
<name>Sanazawa Mamori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="61606" picture="250717.jpg">Tosaki Nanami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="111824" type="appears in" update="2020-07-29">
<name>Minakami Kyouko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="43190" picture="173204.jpg">Kageyama Akari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="111825" type="appears in" update="2020-07-29">
<name>Tsukiyono Mine</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="61607" picture="250723.jpg">Arino Iku</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="111826" type="appears in" update="2020-07-29">
<name>Mukouyama Hotaru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="46899" picture="191168.jpg">Fujisaki Yuzu</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="180784" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2016-10-26</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">自分以外はクイズ?!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">There Are Other People in the Quiz?!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jibun Igai wa Quiz?!</title>
<summary>The riddle of the commuters continues! Tokine had better think fast if she wants to solve it and escape Quizun with all innocent bystanders safe!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>721521</identifier>
<identifier>nazotokine</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="180785" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2016-10-19</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">の・り・も・の</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Vehicle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Norimono</title>
<summary>Tokine is pulled into Quizun during her late-night commute home, which brings her fellow commuters with her into the riddle. Can she solve it and save them all?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>721519</identifier>
<identifier>nazotokine</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="180786" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2016-10-12</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ねらわれたQストーン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">They`re After the Q-Stone</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Warawareta Q Stone</title>
<summary>Trapped in the Quizun dimension, Tokine has only five minutes to solve a riddle... and she`s already wasted two! Will she have her eureka moment?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>721517</identifier>
<identifier>nazotokine</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="180787" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2016-10-05</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">解いてから考える!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Solve It, Then Think About It!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toite kara Kangaeru!</title>
<summary>On the verge of an exciting meeting with an anime company, Amino Tokine finds herself trapped in an extradimensional space where she`ll have to solve riddles to escape!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>721515</identifier>
<identifier>nazotokine</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="180832" update="2016-10-06">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2016-10-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="180833" update="2016-10-06">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-10-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="181330" update="2016-11-24">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2016-11-23</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">泉極志って何ですか?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">What`s Sengokushi?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sengokushitte Nan Desuka?</title>
<summary>Tokine`s back in the world of Quizun with her friends from the bath. But how well can she solve a riddle with a dragon breathing fire at her?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>721529</identifier>
<identifier>nazotokine</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="181331" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2016-11-16</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ハラハラわくわく社員旅行</title>
<title xml:lang="en">An Exciting, Fantastic Company Trip</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Harahara Wakuwaku Shainryouko</title>
<summary>Tokine and her friends go to an amazing hot springs resort... which, naturally, triggers a trip to Quizun!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>721527</identifier>
<identifier>nazotokine</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="181332" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2016-11-09</airdate>
<rating votes="3">1.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">クイズンは突然に</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Quizun Is Suddenly...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Quizun wa Totsuzen ni</title>
<summary>Tokine solves the riddle of the boxes with a little help from her English skills.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>721525</identifier>
<identifier>nazotokine</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="181333" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2016-11-02</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">タクロスにお引越し</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Moving to Takros</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Takros ni Ohikkoshi</title>
<summary>While helping a friend move into her new apartment, Tokine is sucked into Quizun once more.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>721523</identifier>
<identifier>nazotokine</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="182168" update="2016-12-22">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2016-12-21</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ん?! どうなる最終回!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hmm?! What Happens in the Last Episode?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">N?! Dou Naru Saishuukai!</title>
<summary>Tokine solves Quizun`s most complicated riddle yet. But is it really the end, or the beginning of something new?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>721537</identifier>
<identifier>nazotokine</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="182169" update="2016-12-15">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2016-12-14</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">カンドウの最終問題!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Amazing Final Problem!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kandou no Saishuu Mondai!</title>
<summary>Tokine gets sucked into Quizun once more during a winter illumination display at the park. What will the final puzzle be?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>721535</identifier>
<identifier>nazotokine</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="182170" update="2016-12-08">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2016-12-07</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">育ち始めた?! Qストーン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Q Stone Starts to Grow?!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sodachi Hajimeta?! Q Stone</title>
<summary>Tokine`s trapped in Quizun with a crowd of people... and another solver! Can they work together to solve an especially tricky mystery?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>721533</identifier>
<identifier>nazotokine</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="182171" update="2016-12-01">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2016-11-30</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">体が震える「極爆」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Earth-Shattering Sound</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Karada ga Furueru "Kyokubaku"</title>
<summary>Tokine goes with her friends to see a monster movie in an extra-loud theater, where she has an awkward run-in with a co-worker... and another trip to Quizun!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>721531</identifier>
<identifier>nazotokine</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="183331" recap="true" update="2016-12-28">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-12-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S1</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
