<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="12526" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2017-04-02</startdate>
<enddate>2017-06-25</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Alice to Zouroku</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Alice and Zoroku</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Alice &amp; Zouroku</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">a&amp;z</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">アリスと蔵六</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Alice &amp; Zoroku</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Alice &amp; Zôroku</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">앨리스와 조로쿠</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">爱丽丝与藏六</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="13434" approval="23" total="46">Hinamatsuri (2018)</anime>
<anime id="1544" approval="1" total="4">Elfen Lied</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="198548">This was actually nice and cute.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="440498">A breath of fresh air.
I really liked the story and it kept the mysterious and somehow atrocious atmosphere going right to the end. It reminded me of Elfen Lied at times. But. Because of that last ep was a bit of a bummer. Still... it was good. 

It`s amazing that while not leaving the fantasy and /cute girls/ genre it focused a lot on family relations(and kinda social relations in general). Grandads rule!
 
Some might not be so fond of the animation style, but I assure you the backgrounds are of good quality.
I looked forward to fight scenes, but in the second half of the anime they weren`t "the best". Maybe fight scenes are not its profile. And oh well, you can`t have everything in one anime!

I give it a must see, regardless of small things I didn`t like.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.alicetozouroku.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="47672" type="Original Work">Imai Tetsuya</name>
<name id="720" type="Animation Work">J.C.Staff</name>
<name id="2175" type="Character Design">Iwakura Kazunori</name>
<name id="2290" type="Series Composition">Takayama Fumihiko</name>
<name id="4648" type="Direction">Sakurabi Katsushi</name>
<name id="3430" type="Chief Animation Direction">Sasaki Takahiro</name>
<name id="3744" type="Chief Animation Direction">Fujii Masahiro</name>
<name id="46864" type="Music">To-Mas Soundsight Fluorescent Forest</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the seinen manga by http://anidb.net/cr47672 [Imai Tetsuya].
A group of young girls possesses a mysterious power which gives them the ability to materialize their thoughts. Detained and experimented upon, these youths are locked away in secret until one of them manages to escape. Her name is http://anidb.net/ch87531 [Sana] — a girl with the power to ignore the very laws of physics. When this wilful powerhouse crosses paths with a stubborn old man named http://anidb.net/ch87530 [Zouroku], his carefully-ordered life will never be the same again!
Source: crunchyroll</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="917">5.72</permanent>
<temporary count="918">6.77</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>221214.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19024</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>34350</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.alicetozouroku.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Alice_to_Zouroku</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>アリスと蔵六</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4504</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>358761</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20074</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>alicetozouroku</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>alice-zoroku</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B07F4B6ZQ1</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2676" parentid="2672" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo</name>
<description>Tokyo, officially Tokyo Metropolis, is the capital city of Japan and one of its 47 prefectures. The Greater Tokyo Area is the most populous metropolitan area in the world. It is the seat of the Emperor of Japan and the Japanese government. Tokyo is in the Kantou region on the southeastern side of the main island Honshu and includes the Izu Islands and Ogasawara Islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214311.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2773" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-18">
<name>magic circles</name>
<description>A magic circle is circle or sphere of space marked out by practitioners of many branches of ritual magic. It may be marked physically, drawn in salt or chalk, for example, or merely visualised.
Traditionally, circles have been used by ritual magicians to form a protective barrier between themselves and what they summoned. Nowadays, circles often have the more benign function of containing and concentrating the energy raised during a ritual. Circles can also be used as barriers for non-magical work such as meditation.
Generally, as with most magical practices, an incantation is recited stating the purpose and nature of the circle, often repeating an assortment of divine and angelic names.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>32800.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2952" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-06">
<name>rotten world</name>
<description>A rotten world is a setting or situation where the jaded notion that "anything that can go wrong will go horribly wrong" almost always applies. Oppression, perpetual warfare, lawlessness, despair or other forms of mental instability, and other highly undesirable factors tend to be rampant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3028" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-17">
<name>real-world location</name>
<description>Places seen in the show exist in reality.
Note: This could be sometime in the future, though names and certain places will still be recognizable.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3037" parentid="2676" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo Skytree</name>
<description>Tokyo Skytree is a broadcasting, restaurant, and observation tower in Sumida, Tokyo, Japan. It became the tallest structure in Japan in 2010 and reached its full height of 634.0 metres in March 2011, making it the tallest tower in the world, displacing the Canton Tower, and the second tallest structure in the world after Burj Khalifa (829.8 m).
Source: Wikipedia
Note: Not to be confused with the very much older http://anidb.net/t3667 [Tokyo Tower].</description>
<picurl>161122.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3191" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-14">
<name>ohanami</name>
<description>Hanami (花見, lit. "flower viewing") is the Japanese traditional custom of enjoying the beauty of flowers, "flower" in this case almost always meaning cherry blossoms or ume blossoms. 
From the end of March to early May, sakura bloom all over Japan, and around the first of February on the island of Okinawa. The blossom forecast (桜前線 sakurazensen, literally cherry blossom front) is announced each year by the weather bureau, and is watched carefully by those planning hanami as the blossoms only last a week or two. 
In modern-day Japan, hanami mostly consists of having an outdoor party beneath the sakura during daytime or at night. Hanami at night is called yozakura (夜桜, literally night sakura). 
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
<picurl>160895.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3436" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>human experimentation</name>
<description>Genetic, biological, chemical or psychological experimentation on human beings are portrayed or their aftermath is shown.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3457" parentid="6397" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-17">
<name>Alice`s Adventures in Wonderland</name>
<description>Alice`s Adventures in Wonderland (often shortened to Alice in Wonderland,) is an 1865 novel written by English author Charles Lutwidge Dodgson under the pseudonym Lewis Carroll. It tells of a girl named Alice falling through a rabbit hole into a fantasy world populated by peculiar, anthropomorphic creatures. The tale plays with logic, giving the story lasting popularity with adults as well as with children. It is considered to be one of the best examples of the literary nonsense genre. Its narrative course and structure, characters and imagery have been enormously influential in both popular culture and literature, especially in the fantasy genre.
The anime or an episode features important elements of the novel. This could mean that the main character is portrayed as Alice (with another name), accompanied by somebody portraying the white rabbit (possibly as a human). While the world can be a Wonderland, it does not have to be.</description>
<picurl>169452.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3898" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-11-11">
<name>science and magic coexist</name>
<description>In this anime science and magic do not exclude each other. Magic here is actually very advanced, artefact- and/or ritual-based science.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3993" parentid="2872" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-28">
<name>kidnapping</name>
<description>In criminal law, kidnapping is the taking away or transportation of a person against that person`s will, usually to hold the person in false imprisonment, a confinement without legal authority. This may be done for ransom or in furtherance of another crime, or in connection with a child custody dispute.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>10583.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4083" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-04">
<name>drastic change of life</name>
<description>One or more characters in this series go through an event that makes them change their way of life drastically and permanently. This change might be voluntary, or against the character`s will.
Some examples might be an accident, the gaining of superpowers, or simply graduating.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4498" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-20">
<name>heart-warming</name>
<description>The story and its characters give off good vibes — includes elevated feelings of affection such as tenderness, sympathy and love, all in one package.
The kind of anime which leaves you with a warm feeling inside and you can not stop smiling while watching it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4499" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-07-28">
<name>some weird shit goin` on</name>
<description>Scenes of this show point to insanely strange events which seem to be taking place; throughout its episodes, the show may or may not explain what is going on. Either way, many viewers will find that a succinct and accurate way to describe the show is "WTF?", and the show`s explanations (or lack thereof) to the events will often be subject of heated debate.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4522" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>social commentary</name>
<description>Social commentary is the act of rebelling against an individual, or a group of people by rhetorical means. This is most often done with the idea of implementing or promoting change by informing the general populace about a given problem and appealing to people’s sense of justice. (Source: Wikipedia)&#13;
&#13;
Since this is anime, usually, the mores of Japan and the Japanese society are scrutinised, but not restricted to that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4570" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-07">
<name>watercolour style</name>
<description>A watercolour or aquarelle is a painting method in which the paints are made of pigments suspended in a water-based solution. Some anime are created in the style of watercolour paintings, the watercolour style, usually with faded pastels that often give the show a warm and friendly visual presentation. In modern anime, this is generally achieved via computer effects that create an imitation of watercolour, rather than by creating real-life watercolour art. While the watercolour style is more commonly used for backgrounds, it is possible to create the entire anime in such a style.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4614" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>narration</name>
<description>The most common example is that of a voice, either that of one of the characters or entirely unrelated, that appears at the beginning of an episode to offer a summary or introduction, and at the end of an episode for closure or for a preview to hint upon what to expect next.
Another use of narration comes in the form of a dominant voice belonging to one of the protagonists, intended only for the viewer and revealing the intimate thoughts to whom it belongs. This type of narration occurs frequently throughout the duration of the episode or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4669" parentid="6249" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-27">
<name>parenting</name>
<description>This anime is about parenting and its many challenges.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5773" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-14">
<name>secret organisation</name>
<description>A secret organisation or secret society is an organisation whose activities and inner functioning are concealed from non-members. The society may or may not attempt to conceal its existence itself. Examples of historical and existing secret societies include Freemasonry, the Knights Templar, the Rosicrucians, Skull and Bones, the Thule Society, and the Illuminati.</description>
<picurl>192876.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5790" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-30">
<name>family without mother</name>
<description>For some reason, the protagonist`s mother is no longer among the living. The much-too-early death was due to sickness or accident.
This plot device adds a certain degree of tragedy to the anime, and usually has repercussions on the rest of the family. For example: the grief-stricken father and children barely function as humans; the oldest daughter has an extra burden of raising the other children, additional emphasis is given to the only female child in the family, i.e. with bishounen brother and dad in a shoujo setting.
In rare cases the mother may still be alive, just not living with the rest of the family presently, i.e. on some quest or job and gone for a long time.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5916" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-26">
<name>product placement</name>
<description>Otherwise known as a "plug" or "writing commercials right into a show". The practice of prominently displaying or talking about a recognizable product in a program, in exchange for some consideration from the manufacturer, usually monetary. (Source: TV Tropes)
Particularly notorious example, Pizza Hut for the involvement with Code Geass, Darker than Black and other series.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5965" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2015-02-10">
<name>incomplete story</name>
<description>The show does not cover all of the original work (if present) or was cancelled prematurely, leaving plot lines unresolved or aborting character development. Sometimes the show runs through all its initially slotted episodes and adapts all of the original work (if applicable) but fails to present a proper ending, leaving viewers wondering whether they`re missing the final episodes.
In some cases, this may overlap with the studio forging an anime-original ending. Such an ending normally manages to allow the show to "finish", but may still suffer from incomplete story issues.
An incomplete storyline is not to be confused with the sequel bait, which is when the story presented by the show is finished but leaves enough room for a sequel to be produced. Sometimes this goes as far as to present a new potential problem in the last few minutes; that is usual for after-credits footage in movies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6186" parentid="6185" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-29">
<name>spring</name>
<description>During spring, the axis of the Earth is increasing its tilt relative to the Sun, and the length of daylight rapidly increases for the relevant hemisphere. The hemisphere begins to warm significantly causing new plant growth to spring forth, giving the season its name. Snow, if a normal part of winter, begins to melt, and streams swell with runoff. Frosts, if a normal part of winter, become less severe. In climates that have no snow and rare frosts, the air and ground temperatures increase more rapidly. Many flowering plants bloom this time of year, in a long succession sometimes beginning when snow is still on the ground, continuing into early summer. In normally snowless areas spring may begin as early as February (Northern Hemisphere) heralded by the blooming of deciduous magnolias, cherries and quince, or August (Southern Hemisphere) in the same way. Many temperate areas have a dry spring, and wet autumn (fall), which brings about flowering in this season more consistent with the need for water as well as warmth. Subarctic areas may not experience spring at all until May or even June.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>161969.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6397" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-02">
<name>tales</name>
<description>Tales are stories told time and again and passed down from generation to generation, and some of those show up in anime not just once or twice, but several times.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="87530" type="main character in" update="2017-04-02">
<rating votes="9">8.17</rating>
<name>Kashimura Zouroku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199235.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="286" picture="17117.jpg">Ootsuka Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="87531" type="main character in" update="2017-03-05">
<rating votes="16">8.05</rating>
<name>Kashimura Sana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199234.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37977" picture="226053.jpg">Oowada Hitomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88127" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-03-11">
<rating votes="10">2.91</rating>
<name>"Minnie C" Tachibana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199425.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88128" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-03-11">
<rating votes="2">3.09</rating>
<name>Kureo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199433.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="49189" picture="199359.jpg">Uchida Shuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88129" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-03-11">
<rating votes="11">7.07</rating>
<name>Ichijou Shizuku</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199431.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="51" picture="39247.jpg">Koshimizu Ami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88130" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-03-11">
<rating votes="3">2.24</rating>
<name>Naitou Ryuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199434.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="297" picture="233915.jpg">Ootsuka Houchuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88131" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-03-11">
<rating votes="7">6.85</rating>
<name>Yamada Noriko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199435.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="47407" picture="235753.jpg">Hirose Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88132" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-03-11">
<rating votes="11">7.40</rating>
<name>Kashimura Sanae</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199430.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1438" picture="69192.jpg">Toyosaki Aki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88133" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-03-11">
<rating votes="6">6.14</rating>
<name>Hinagiri Asahi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199426.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45121" picture="225365.jpg">Fujiwara Natsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88134" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-03-11">
<rating votes="7">6.61</rating>
<name>Hinagiri Yonaga</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199428.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="41766" picture="242448.jpg">Kitou Akari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88135" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-03-11">
<rating votes="2">3.09</rating>
<name>Kitou Kouichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199432.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="263" picture="186711.jpg">Matsukaze Masaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89255" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-05-27">
<rating votes="7">3.73</rating>
<name>Shikishima Hatori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>202999.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="49189" picture="199359.jpg">Uchida Shuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89256" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-06-25">
<rating votes="4">6.02</rating>
<name>Miho Ayumu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>204235.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33633" picture="151771.jpg">Takahashi Minami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90871" type="appears in" update="2017-08-10">
<rating votes="2">4.78</rating>
<name>Kakkoii Onee-san</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>205996.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="350" picture="20063.jpg">Tamura Yukari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90875" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-08-10">
<rating votes="2">3.09</rating>
<name>Hayashi Ichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>205999.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45234" picture="186846.jpg">Sugawara Shinsuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90876" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-08-10">
<rating votes="2">5.88</rating>
<name>Nakanishi Chinatsu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>206000.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23647" picture="202378.jpg">Takakura Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92555" type="appears in" update="2017-11-30">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Hatori no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mother of Hatori Shikishima, she appears to become spiteful towards Hatori for failing to get into a prestigious school.</description>
<picture>210030.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="56427" picture="225344.jpg">Oomori Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92556" type="appears in" update="2017-11-30">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Hatori no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hatori`s father. He`s seen constantly arguing with his wife which adds more stress and anxiety to Hatori.</description>
<picture>210031.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="25026" picture="70111.jpg">Nosaka Naoya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94703" type="appears in" update="2018-03-21">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Chika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>215198.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45708" picture="246632.jpg">Sasaki Hitomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94704" type="appears in" update="2018-03-21">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Kirk Herschel</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>215207.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="373" picture="191382.jpg">Hamada Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94705" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-03-22">
<rating votes="5">7.24</rating>
<name>Ichijou Shizuku</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>215209.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="51" picture="39247.jpg">Koshimizu Ami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94723" type="appears in" update="2018-03-22">
<rating votes="1">4.13</rating>
<name>Miho Daiki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>215234.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42872" picture="171894.jpg">Tsuzuki Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="185594" update="2017-11-28">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-03-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">PV (01:16)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="186177" update="2017-05-02">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-04-23</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">人でないモノ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Something Not Human</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Non humaine</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hito de Nai Mono</title>
<summary>Minnie C and her group took advantage of a moment`s negligence to kidnap Sana. Left behind at his office, Zoroku demands answers from Naito as to just what Sana really is. Meanwhile, the giant "arms" controlled by Minnie C have Sana completely trapped, and Minnie C asks her, "Did you think that you were human?" Just when it seems all hope is lost, Sana`s powerful thoughts take the situation in an unexpected direction...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>733431</identifier>
<identifier>alice-zoroku</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="186178" update="2017-04-23">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-04-16</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">トランプ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cards</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Cartes à jouer</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Trump</title>
<summary>Kashimura Floral is in an uproar after Sana uses her Dream of Alice, suddenly landing herself and Sanae in the shop. Even after things quiet down, Zoroku scolds Sana for breaking her promise not to use her power. Then Naito, an old acquaintance of Zoroku`s, enters the scene with a proposal for Zoroku. Meanwhile, Kito and his team in pursuit of Sana are steadily closing in...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>733429</identifier>
<identifier>alice-zoroku</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="186179" update="2017-04-12">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-04-09</airdate>
<rating votes="6">2.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アリスの夢</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dreams of Alice</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les rêves d`Alice</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Alice no Yume</title>
<summary>Since Sana had nowhere to go, Zoroku decided to let her stay in his own home for the time being. After he finds out that the previous day`s incident isn`t being covered by any media, he makes a call to an old friend. Meanwhile, Sana awakens to find Zoroku`s granddaughter, Sanae, watching over her. Sanae says her grandpa asked her to keep an eye on Sana while he went to work. Sana was untrusting at first, but they eventually warm up to each other. Then Sana recalls her time spent at the research facility...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>733427</identifier>
<identifier>alice-zoroku</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="186180" update="2017-04-12">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>45</length>
<airdate>2017-04-02</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">赤の女王, 逃げる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Red Queen Escapes</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La Reine Rouge s`échappe</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aka no Joou, Nigeru</title>
<summary>In a deep, remote forest, a blond-haired girl runs amidst heavy rain and wind. Some pursue her, while others extend a hand to help her. As various motives tangle together, the girl, named Sana, makes her flight to the outside world for the first time in her life. In the end, Sana arrives at the bustling district of Kabukicho in Tokyo`s Shinjuku Ward. In a convenience store there, she meets Kashimura Zoroku, the quintessential "stubborn old man."
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>733425</identifier>
<identifier>alice-zoroku</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="186620" update="2017-04-09">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-04-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="186919" update="2017-04-09">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-04-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="187096" update="2017-06-07">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-05-28</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">悪い魔女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Evil Witch</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La méchante sorcière</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Warui Majo</title>
<summary>Shikishima Hatori is a completely ordinary grade school girl. Then, one day, she develops a "Dream of Alice" power. Hurt by the sight of her parents constantly fighting over her future schooling, Hatori prays that they`ll go back to being her kind mom and dad again... and that dream is realized in a way she never expected. Meanwhile, Sana is helping out at the flower shop as usual, waiting excitedly for Asahi and Yonaga to come for a visit...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>733441</identifier>
<identifier>alice-zoroku</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="187097" update="2017-06-01">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-05-21</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ともだち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Friends</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Amies</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tomodachi</title>
<summary>Zoroku is making a trip to Yokohama to meet a client, so he takes Sana with him. Accompanied by Ichijo, Sana is impressed by the sight of the ocean and the robot-operated factory that she visits, and enjoys her day out to the fullest. Rejoined by Zoroku, the trio visits Chinatown, but then Asahi and Yonaga suddenly appear after being unseen ever since the research facility incident was resolved. The twins run away as Sana and Ichijo chase after them...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>733439</identifier>
<identifier>alice-zoroku</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="187098" update="2017-06-01">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-05-14</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">樫村家</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Kashimura Family</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La famille Kashimura</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kashimura-ke</title>
<summary>The seasons have quickly turned to winter. The matter of the research facility has been resolved, and life is normal again in Zoroku`s household. Sana seems to have fully adjusted to being a member of the Kashimura family, as well. After seeing Sanae off on her way to school, she heads for the flower shop with Zoroku, where she sometimes helps with his work. She still has some trouble with stamina, but she has adapted well to the outside world. Then, one day, Sana  goes out with Zoroku to get her overgrown hair cut...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>733437</identifier>
<identifier>alice-zoroku</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="187099" update="2017-05-16">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-04-30</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">帰るところ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Home to Return To</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un endroit où rentrer</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaeru Tokoro</title>
<summary>When Sana and Zoroku are loaded onto a cargo ship, the one who appears to rescue them is Cabinet Information Research Office agents Ichijo Shizuku and Yamada Noriko. As they all plan their escape, Minnie C stand before them once again. As she attacks with the invisible arms that she can control freely, Ichijo links with Yamada to unleash various abilities of her own. As this battle between Dreams of Alice rages on, Sana tells Zoroku what she truly wishes for.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>733433</identifier>
<identifier>alice-zoroku</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="187484" recap="true" update="2018-12-06">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-05-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アリスと蔵六 第2部放送直前特番</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Alice and Zoroku Special: Looking Ahead to Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Alice to Zouroku: Dai 2 Bu Housou Chokuzen Tokuban</title>
<summary>Recap Special
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>733435</identifier>
<identifier>alice-zoroku</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="187908" update="2017-10-09">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-06-25</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ただいま</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`m Home</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Je suis de retour</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tadaima</title>
<summary>Ten days have passed in the outside world since Sana and Hatori got trapped in Wonderland. Ayumu, remembering a promise they once made, begins to worry that Hatori won`t ever come back. As he and Sanae search, Zoroku looks back on on all the things that have happened since they met Sana. Meanwhile, Sana and Hatori finally find an exit out of Wonderland, but it has already begun expanding at an accelerated rate, to the point that it`s affecting the outside world...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>733449</identifier>
<identifier>alice-zoroku</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="187909" update="2017-07-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-06-18</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">女王と魔女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Queen and the Witch</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La Reine et la Sorcière</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Joou to Majo</title>
<summary>Ten days have passed in the outside world since Sana and Hatori got trapped in Wonderland. Ayumu, remembering a promise they once made, begins to worry that Hatori won`t ever come back. As he and Sanae search, Zoroku looks back on on all the things that have happened since they met Sana. Meanwhile, Sana and Hatori finally find an exit out of Wonderland, but it has already begun expanding at an accelerated rate, to the point that it`s affecting the outside world...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>733447</identifier>
<identifier>alice-zoroku</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="187910" update="2017-07-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-06-11</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">小さな女王</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Little Queen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La Petite Reine</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chiisana Joou</title>
<summary>A collision with a "Dream of Alice" power has left Sana and Hatori trapped in the deepest part of Wonderland. They wander all over this world so unlike their own, but there`s no sign of an exit anywhere. Meanwhile. after learning what`s happened to Sana, Zoroku and Sanae head to Wonderland with Ichijo. They can`t help gazing with wonder at their first sight of Wonderland, the place where Sana was born. But they`ve barely begun the search before Ichijo...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>733445</identifier>
<identifier>alice-zoroku</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="187911" update="2017-06-13">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-06-04</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">チェシャ猫の笑う場所</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Where the Cheshire Cat Smiles</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Là où sourit le chat du Cheshire</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Cheshire Neko no Warau Basho</title>
<summary>Sana collapsed after meeting Hatori and Ayumu, and Asahi and Yonaga brought her back to Zoroku`s house. The three girls are now having a great time playing together for the first time in so long. Then Sana comes up with a plan to teach Hatori a lesson for doing something so awful to Zoroku. Meanwhile, Hatori`s emotional state has changed yet again after her encounter with Sana. She tells her best friend, Ayumu, that she`s used her power too much and can`t go to school again. So a concerned Ayumu returns to Harajuku to search for Sana.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>733443</identifier>
<identifier>alice-zoroku</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="193511" recap="true" update="2017-11-27">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>8</length>
<airdate>2017-10-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">第1部振り返り動画</title>
<title xml:lang="en">First Half Summary</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dai 1 Bu Furikaeri Douga</title>
</episode>
<episode id="193512" update="2017-11-27">
<epno type="4">T11</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">BD CM 6 (00:15)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="193513" update="2017-11-27">
<epno type="4">T10</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">BD CM 5 (00:15)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="193514" update="2017-11-27">
<epno type="4">T9</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">BD CM 4 (00:15)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="193515" update="2017-11-27">
<epno type="4">T8</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">BD CM 3 (00:15)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="193516" update="2017-11-27">
<epno type="4">T7</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">BD CM 2 (00:15)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="193517" update="2017-11-27">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">BD CM 1 (00:30)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="193518" update="2017-11-27">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 2 (00:15)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="193519" update="2017-11-27">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 1 (00:15)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="193520" update="2017-11-27">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 3 (00:30)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="193521" update="2017-11-27">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 2 (01:45)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="193522" update="2017-11-27">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2017-06-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 12 Part B</title>
</episode>
<episode id="193523" update="2017-11-27">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>10</length>
<airdate>2017-04-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 1 Part A</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
