<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="12819" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2017-06-29</startdate>
<enddate>2017-09-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">New Game!!</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">NEW GAME!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">New Game!!</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">뉴 게임!!</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">NEW GAME!!</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="11736" type="Prequel">New Game!</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="3">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="140505">Although still thoroughly entertaining, the second season of New Game! ditches the somewhat realistic `office atmosphere` of the original, including a look at the arduous process of making a game and as a result loses the pay-off and ends up being much less relatable than the first season.
Regardless, for people who enjoyed New Game! this second season is a no-brainer. For newcomers, it`s definitely better to fall in love with the characters by watching the first season first.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="279344">More of the same glittering moe studio in game industry, with additional cast of two and the famous "clone" in another few occupations.
Now end it with a full-length movie and I will be fully satisfied.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="317942">Another awesome season introducing new rivals, a new game and some other interesting twists. Totally worth the time. Also... I totally want to play PECO.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://newgame-anime.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1067" type="Animation Work">Doga Kobo</name>
<name id="8071" type="Character Design">Kikuchi Ai</name>
<name id="535" type="Series Composition">Shimo Fumihiko</name>
<name id="45308" type="Original Work">Tokunou Shoutarou</name>
<name id="30322" type="Direction">Fujiwara Yoshiyuki</name>
<name id="8071" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kikuchi Ai</name>
<name id="2469" type="Chief Animation Direction">Amasaki Manamu</name>
<name id="18610" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kikunaga Chisato</name>
<name id="10944" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kinoshita Sumie</name>
<name id="2424" type="Music">Hyakkoku Hajime</name>
</creators>
<description>After graduating from high school, http://anidb.net/ch81305 [Suzukaze Aoba] starts work at the game company, Eagle Jump where she ends up working on the third installment of the game she loved as a child, "Fairies` Story." Aoba then meets http://anidb.net/ch81303 [Yagami Kou], who inspired her to become a character designer in the first place, and other senpai at her new job who help her grow along the way.
"Fairies` Story 3" launched with no problem and now it`s been about a year since Aoba first joined Eagle Jump. The season to welcome in new employees has arrived.
Aoba reflects upon how nervous she was when she first started and gets excited about the fact that she was now going to be the senpai.
She repeats, "I`m your senpai, Suzukaze Aoba. Nice to meet you!" in front of the entrance of Eagle Jump, but...
A working life comedy about the daily lives of girls working at a gaming company begins its new chapter!
Source: crunchyroll
Note: The first episode received an early distribution on Abema TV on June 29, 2017. The regular broadcast started on July 11, 2017.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1153">7.07</permanent>
<temporary count="1157">7.46</temporary>
<review count="1">5.83</review>
</ratings>
<picture>200463.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19593</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>34914</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://newgame-anime.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>New_Game!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>NEW_GAME!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4596</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>359697</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20249</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>nganime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>new-game</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B07GL9YRTC</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="627" parentid="2856" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-15">
<name>lingerie</name>
<description>Lingerie is a term for fashionable and alluring women`s undergarments.</description>
<picurl>238327.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1157" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>horny nosebleed</name>
<description>In Japanese media, healthy young men who have no other sexual outlet will often suffer nosebleeds upon seeing the naked female body, or even just a pair of well-filled panties.
The nosebleed is, of course, a visual shorthand/euphemism for sexual arousal. It is commonly interpreted that way for males and females, with little trickles of blood indicating mild arousal, and gushing fountains of blood indicating erection/extreme arousal in both sexes. It can also be interpreted as shorthand strictly for erections in males. In that case, when blood shoots from the nose explosively, and in ridiculous quantity, the implication would be an ejaculation.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>233513.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1298" parentid="2883" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-02">
<name>drawing</name>
<description>The art or technique of representing an object or outlining a figure, plan, or sketch by means of lines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2056" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-09-13">
<name>cosplaying</name>
<description>This character likes to cosplay.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2676" parentid="2672" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo</name>
<description>Tokyo, officially Tokyo Metropolis, is the capital city of Japan and one of its 47 prefectures. The Greater Tokyo Area is the most populous metropolitan area in the world. It is the seat of the Emperor of Japan and the Japanese government. Tokyo is in the Kantou region on the southeastern side of the main island Honshu and includes the Izu Islands and Ogasawara Islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214311.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2793" parentid="2883" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>performance</name>
<description>The song performance on stage or acting in a theatre is a central part of the character`s life in this anime type.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2805" parentid="2798" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>4-koma manga</name>
<description>Yonkoma manga (4コマ漫画, four cell manga, or 4-koma for short), a comic-strip format, generally consists of gag comic strips within four panels of equal size ordered from top to bottom. (They also sometimes run right-to-left horizontally or use a hybrid 2x2 style, depending on the layout requirements of the publication in which they appear.) Though the word yonkoma comes from the Japanese, the style also exists outside of Japan in other Asian countries as well as in the English-speaking market.</description>
<picurl>70558.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2879" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>alcohol</name>
<description>Alcohol (or more scientifically, ethanol), is one of the world`s oldest psychoactive substances. It is traditionally found in the form of a beverage such as beer, wine, or liquor, although in some contexts it can be inhaled to produce similar or intoxication, and some people prefer another way of consuming beverage-form alcohol.
Alcoholic beverages are many and varied, due to production methods (fermentation or distillation), source materials (grains, fruits, vegetables, other plants), added substances such as flavorings, and many more ways of defining different forms of alcoholic beverages.
Alcoholic beverages are divided into three general classes: beers, wines, and spirits. They are legally consumed in most countries, and over 100 countries have laws regulating their production, sale, and consumption. In particular, such laws specify the minimum age at which a person may legally buy or drink them. This minimum age varies between 16 and 25 years, depending upon the country and the type of drink. Most nations set it at 18 years of age.</description>
<picurl>70749.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3020" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-08-01">
<name>chibi ED</name>
<description>Some or all of the endings feature chibi versions of the characters.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3092" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-03-02">
<name>important haircut</name>
<description>When a character cuts off his or her hair, it often symbolizes a rite of passage or bout of character growth. A princess striking out on an adventure, or a new recruit at boot camp, for instance. Hair is something that takes time and effort to grow, so parting with it voluntarily can be a powerful act.
This is particularly a big deal when women get haircuts. Yet in fiction, even an accidental hair slicing can leave a character with a surprisingly even cut.
In many religions (Western Christianity, Ancient Egyptian religion, and others) priests and/or monks cut/shave their hair. Roman Catholic nuns also tend to cut and mantain their hair short under their veils when they enter the nunneries. The cutting of one`s own hair is also a part of Buddhist mythology, specifically something done by Siddhartha himself early on in his path to enlightenment, so anime examples might draw from this as an allusion. There are also some cultures, including Native American and many Asians, where a person would cut his or her hair as an act of grief, disgrace, or even rebellion. In the Confucian tradition, hair (like the rest of your body) is considered a gift from your parents and may not be damaged without a very good reason. Furthermore, prisoners and psychiatric patients commonly have their heads shaved, often to prevent the spread of lice, but sometimes also as a demeaning measure.
Source: TVTRope</description>
<picurl>169641.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3170" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-10">
<name>occupation and career</name>
<description>The kind of anime which shows the career of a character, usually from the beginning.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3217" parentid="2864" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-17">
<name>working life</name>
<description>The life of someone actually working on a often less than glamorous job is depicted in this anime. The job is taxing and the pay is low, not really the dream job one would choose to work in.
Examples: Working as salesperson in a department store, or as a waitress in a family restaurant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3610" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-12-19">
<name>game references</name>
<description>Be it the sound of a 1-up being grabbed, three golden triangles appearing on someones shirt or a blatant parody portraying a monkey throwing barrels down a poorly constructed facility, this anime contains characteristics dedicated to the remembrance/worship of an actual video game.</description>
<picurl>166123.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3759" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-11">
<name>teamwork</name>
<description>A cooperative effort by the members of a group or team to achieve a common goal.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3867" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>ED variety</name>
<description>Several ED sequences in this anime have either a different song or different animation, maybe even to the point of having a unique ED for each episode.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3971" parentid="3170" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-07-04">
<name>entertainment industry</name>
<description>The show depicts how the entertainment industry works and how the main protagonists strive to cope with the sudden change to fame. At times this can be a very ugly sight indeed.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3977" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-29">
<name>dialogue driven</name>
<description>A dialogue driven show has its story advanced by dialogue, with action being of much lower priority, and relies heavily on conversations between characters.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4222" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>walls of text</name>
<description>Walls of text refers to Japanese text that appears in large quantities within the anime itself. This text is most likely vital to the storyline and may come in the form of charts and diagrams or pieces of paper, notes or even thoughts that are only partially or entirely unspoken.
May also be taken as a fair warning to viewers unable to translate Japanese text on their own, suggesting that thorough subtitle support may be required as well as making use of the pause button on their media players so that all text can be read.
Normally, tags don`t refer to physical translations of text, subtitle appearances and karaoke styling added by 3rd parties. But those who seek to describe an anime that is heavy on SPOKEN dialogue (which may tend to create a large quantity of natural subtitling to read for those not fluent in the language being used) could consider this tag but may make clearer reference with the dialogue driven tag.</description>
<picurl>32534.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4498" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-20">
<name>heart-warming</name>
<description>The story and its characters give off good vibes — includes elevated feelings of affection such as tenderness, sympathy and love, all in one package.
The kind of anime which leaves you with a warm feeling inside and you can not stop smiling while watching it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5515" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>faceless background characters</name>
<description>Unimportant random/extra characters that appear mostly as part of the background are often drawn without much facial details, normally to save money, effort and manpower for more important parts of the show. Sometimes, they have almost or no facial details, meaning their heads only have indications of the presence of parts such as hair or mouth, or not even that. This can go as far as only drawing an abstracted silhouette of the whole body.</description>
<picurl>233515.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5604" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-04">
<name>following one`s dream</name>
<description>No matter what the hardships may be, at least one of the protagonists in this anime is following her/his dream.
Examples: To become a professional athlete, a musician, a painter or the ruler of this world!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5640" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-16">
<name>video game development</name>
<description>Part of the anime`s story relates to creating video games.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5826" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-12">
<name>rivalry</name>
<description>Quite broadly used term describing a conflict, contest, struggle, or opposition of some sort.
Typical examples: The mostly comedic rivalry for the love of a protagonist in a harem anime (love polygon), the more "mindless" battles between wannabe delinquents in a school fighting anime, or the struggle between good &amp; evil in an epic conflict for world domination.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6018" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-27">
<name>predominantly adult cast</name>
<description>This show features mostly adults. That means children and teenagers are relatively rare and unlikely to hold significance to the plot.
That is a rare trait in anime, as most shows spin around children or teenagers.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6030" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-22">
<name>otaku culture</name>
<description>Otaku (おたく/オタク) is a Japanese term used to refer to people with obsessive interests, particularly anime, manga, and video games. A female otaku is occasionally referred to as a fujoshi. (Source: Wikipedia)
Here certain aspects of this "fandom" are presented in more detail, e.g. the creation of doujinshi (self-published amateur manga).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6184" parentid="6185" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-29">
<name>autumn</name>
<description>Autumn, interchangeably known as fall in the US and Canada, is one of the four temperate seasons. Autumn marks the transition from summer into winter, in September (Northern Hemisphere) or March (Southern Hemisphere), when the arrival of night becomes noticeably earlier and the temperature cools considerably. One of its main features is the shedding of leaves from deciduous trees.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>161967.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6186" parentid="6185" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-29">
<name>spring</name>
<description>During spring, the axis of the Earth is increasing its tilt relative to the Sun, and the length of daylight rapidly increases for the relevant hemisphere. The hemisphere begins to warm significantly causing new plant growth to spring forth, giving the season its name. Snow, if a normal part of winter, begins to melt, and streams swell with runoff. Frosts, if a normal part of winter, become less severe. In climates that have no snow and rare frosts, the air and ground temperatures increase more rapidly. Many flowering plants bloom this time of year, in a long succession sometimes beginning when snow is still on the ground, continuing into early summer. In normally snowless areas spring may begin as early as February (Northern Hemisphere) heralded by the blooming of deciduous magnolias, cherries and quince, or August (Southern Hemisphere) in the same way. Many temperate areas have a dry spring, and wet autumn (fall), which brings about flowering in this season more consistent with the need for water as well as warmth. Subarctic areas may not experience spring at all until May or even June.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>161969.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="81303" type="main character in" update="2016-07-14">
<rating votes="45">7.99</rating>
<name>Yagami Kou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188370.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1799" picture="156027.jpg">Hikasa Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81304" type="main character in" update="2016-07-14">
<rating votes="37">4.79</rating>
<name>Sakura Nene</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188374.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="44228" picture="222798.jpg">Asahina Madoka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81305" type="main character in" update="2017-09-02">
<rating votes="60">7.70</rating>
<name>Suzukaze Aoba</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188366.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40353" picture="225072.jpg">Takada Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81306" type="main character in" update="2018-07-14">
<rating votes="98">8.17</rating>
<name>Takimoto Hifumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A character designer. She is shy talking to others and prefers to speak via e-mail. She has a pet hedgehog named Soujirou and secretly enjoys cosplay.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>188367.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="8935" picture="239412.jpg">Yamaguchi Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81307" type="main character in" update="2016-07-14">
<rating votes="43">6.56</rating>
<name>Shinoda Hajime</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188369.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33959" picture="203633.jpg">Toda Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81308" type="main character in" update="2016-07-14">
<rating votes="33">6.24</rating>
<name>Hazuki Shizuku</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188373.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="401" picture="223216.jpg">Kitamura Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81309" type="main character in" update="2016-07-14">
<rating votes="43">7.16</rating>
<name>Tooyama Rin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188371.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20497" picture="62433.jpg">Kayano Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81310" type="main character in" update="2016-07-14">
<rating votes="41">7.44</rating>
<name>Ahagon Umiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188372.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40739" picture="186144.jpg">Morinaga Chitose</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81311" type="main character in" update="2016-07-14">
<rating votes="41">6.97</rating>
<name>Iijima Yun</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>188368.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40755" picture="205013.jpg">Takeo Ayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89402" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-05-31">
<rating votes="18">6.14</rating>
<name>Yamato Christina Wako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203272.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="308" picture="44975.jpg">Nazuka Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89403" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-05-31">
<rating votes="8">6.32</rating>
<name>Hoshikawa Hotaru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203271.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="49536" picture="228921.jpg">Iwami Manaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89404" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-05-31">
<rating votes="18">7.44</rating>
<name>Mochizuki Momiji</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203270.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42903" picture="172026.jpg">Suzuki Arisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89405" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-05-31">
<rating votes="16">3.30</rating>
<name>Narumi Tsubame</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203269.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37977" picture="226053.jpg">Oowada Hitomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92144" type="appears in" update="2020-04-18">
<rating votes="4">6.99</rating>
<name>Mozuku</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>246380.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="401" picture="223216.jpg">Kitamura Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92146" type="appears in" update="2017-11-04">
<rating votes="2">7.45</rating>
<name>Soujirou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>209259.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="8935" picture="239412.jpg">Yamaguchi Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92156" type="appears in" update="2017-11-05">
<rating votes="2">7.45</rating>
<name>Ren</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>209311.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="41504" picture="178543.jpg">Matsuda Risae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92157" type="appears in" update="2017-11-05">
<rating votes="2">7.45</rating>
<name>Miu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>209312.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37003" picture="171788.jpg">Kawakami Chihiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104015" type="appears in" update="2019-10-14">
<rating votes="2">7.45</rating>
<name>Yamada</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>239664.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1673" picture="41835.jpg">Fujita Saki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104017" type="appears in" update="2019-06-30">
<name>Dandy Max</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>235564.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="178" picture="228660.jpg">Miyake Kenta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105250" type="appears in" update="2019-08-31">
<rating votes="1">7.45</rating>
<name>Okada</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237875.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="47010" picture="223717.jpg">Nukui Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106131" type="appears in" update="2019-10-12">
<name>Waitress</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>239587.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37003" picture="171788.jpg">Kawakami Chihiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106171" type="appears in" update="2019-10-14">
<rating votes="1">7.45</rating>
<name>Akki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>239666.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="44400" picture="181318.jpg">Wakui Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106184" type="appears in" update="2019-10-15">
<name>Kaijin Sacchuuzai Otoko</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>239701.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="68" picture="16675.jpg">Yasumura Makoto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106185" type="appears in" update="2019-10-15">
<name>Spider Red</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>239698.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="50489" picture="208406.jpg">Batori Shougo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106186" type="appears in" update="2019-10-15">
<name>Ant Black</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>239699.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34070" picture="130103.jpg">Furukawa Makoto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106187" type="appears in" update="2019-10-15">
<name>Butterfly Pink</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>239700.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39068" picture="204958.jpg">Sekine Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="188518" update="2017-08-22">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-08-01</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">この... にぶちんめ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">How Dense... Can You Be?</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Elle est aveugle, ou quoi ?</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">이...둔탱이!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kono... Nibuchinme!</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant">這個…遲鈍的傢伙！</title>
<summary>“Moon Ranger” started off as a girls’ anime series, but because of its high quality, it was highly regarded by adults and was made into theatrical releases as well as live shows. After it’s 2 and a half year run, the protagonist in the “Moon Ranger” series was going to change. And because of that, a final live show was going to take place. Hajime, a huge “Moon Ranger” fan, wants to do anything possible to get her hands on the tickets and tries to get into the ticket site, but...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742157</identifier>
<identifier>new-game</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="188519" update="2017-07-25">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-07-25</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">......うー, 恥ずかしい!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ooh, I`m So Embarrassed!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Hum... La honte...</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">......으... 부끄러워!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">......Uu, Hazukashii!</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant">……嗚，好丟臉喔！</title>
<summary>Aoba’s dream of becoming a character designer comes true, though she has to touch up on the designs with Ko, and has to get everything finalized by Ko. Aoba sees that her designs that won at the character design competition had already been made into 3D by Hifumi, and she tells Hifumi to ask her if she has any questions about the designs. Ko warns Aoba to hurry up and keep working on the designs, but when she sees her senpais discussing something about 3D, she is unable to voice her own opinions. Aoba then starts wondering if it’s actually okay for her to be character designer...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742155</identifier>
<identifier>new-game</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="188520" update="2017-07-23">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-07-18</airdate>
<rating votes="10">8.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">これじゃあただのコスプレだにゃー!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">This Is Just Turning Into Cos-purr-lay!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ah mais non, on dirait juste un déguisement !</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">이래선 그냥 코스프레다냥~!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kore Jaa Tada no Cosplay Da Nyaa!</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant">這只是單純的Cosplay啊！</title>
<summary>The character design competition gets announced at their flower viewing. Just like Ko’s designs for “Fairies’ Stories” was chosen right after she had joined the company after graduating high school, everyone has a chance to enter. Aoba reads the proposal that Shizuku and the other members of the design team comes up with, and ends up going through a lot of trial and error. Aoba can’t seem to get the designs just right. She goes to visit Ko and sees that she has already completed numerous sketches that are all high quality and Aoba is amazed. Aoba uses her feelings of frustration from this to try to motivate her and enters the character design competition.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742153</identifier>
<identifier>new-game</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="188521" update="2017-07-23">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-06-29</airdate>
<rating votes="11">6.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">恥ずかしいところを見られてしまいました......</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Of All the Embarrassing Things to Be Caught Doing...</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Bravo, j`ai réussi à me ridiculiser devant vous...</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">부끄러운 모습을 보이고 말았다......</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hazukashii Tokoro o Mirarete Shimaimashita......</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant">被看到丟臉的樣子了……</title>
<summary>It has been a year since Aoba had graduated from high school and joined the game production company, Eagle Jump, and now, the season to welcome new employees has arrived. Aoba is very excited about the fact that she’s now in the position of Ko and her other senpais who had helped her out when she first started and didn’t know left from right. She rehearses her greeting in front of the entrance of the Eagle Jump building, but then Rin tells her the shocking truth...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742151</identifier>
<identifier>new-game</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="188740" update="2017-06-29">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>60</length>
<airdate>2017-06-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">このあと!!「NEW GAME!!」第2期先行配信するよSP</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kono Ato!! "New Game!!" Dai 2 Ki Senkou Haishin Suru yo SP</title>
</episode>
<episode id="188987" update="2017-07-11">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-06-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="189198" update="2017-07-19">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-07-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="189452" update="2017-10-09">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-08-29</airdate>
<rating votes="9">8.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">メイド喫茶がいいと言ったんだよ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`m Telling You, I Want a Maid Cafe</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Je dis juste qu`un bar à soubrettes, c`est mieux</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">메이드카페가 좋다고 말했어</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maid Kissa ga Ii to Ittanda yo</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant">我推薦女僕咖啡廳</title>
<summary>Aoba and the other members of the character team are put in charge of figuring out where to have the welcoming party for the two new interns, Momiji and Tsubame. According to Hajime, this is a very important role and if they don’t do well, their reputation may go down. Aoba is visibly nervous now, but then Hajime also tells her that if they do too well, it’s also troublesome because they’d get asked to do it again. But then Aoba wonders if it’s okay for them to be an employee that doesn’t get remembered if they don’t do too well or too badly.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742165</identifier>
<identifier>new-game</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="189453" update="2017-08-22">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-08-22</airdate>
<rating votes="8">8.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">凄く熱い視線を感じる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`m Sensing a Very Intense Gaze</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Je sens qu`on me dévisage, là...</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">굉장히 뜨거운 시선이 느껴져</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sugoku Atsui Shisen o Kanjiru</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant">感覺有股強烈的視線</title>
<summary>Aoba is asked by Umiko to sit in on an interview for a new programmer. Aoba asks Umiko if it’s really okay for her to sit in on this interview, since she knows nothing about programming, but Umiko tells her that the skills of the programmer had already been acknowledged and that she’d just like her to watch how she behaves. Aoba still doesn’t fully grasp the situation, when there’s a knock on the door as it slowly opens. The person on the other side happens to be someone that Aoba is rather familiar with...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742163</identifier>
<identifier>new-game</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="189454" update="2017-08-22">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-08-15</airdate>
<rating votes="9">9.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あぁ...... すごいなあ......</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wow... It`s So Amazing..</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ah... C`est magnifique...</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">아...굉장해...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aa....... Sugoi naa......</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant">啊……真厲害……</title>
<summary>Things are going well for Aoba and her job as the character designer, as her desk piles up with a ton of prints that need to be checked or redone. Seeing the giant pile of papers on her desk, Aoba can’t help but smile, as it confirms the fact that she is actually doing her dream job. Yun and Hajime start talking about the key visuals for the game that’ll appear in gaming magazines, and Ko tells Aoba that as the character designer, she’d be in charge of doing those as well. After realizing that, Aoba starts to get nervous, but...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742161</identifier>
<identifier>new-game</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="189455" update="2017-08-22">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-08-08</airdate>
<rating votes="8">8.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">や, 変なとこ触らないでよ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hey! Don`t Touch Me There!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Hé, bas les pattes</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">앙~ 이상한 곳 건들지 말아!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ya, Hen na Toko Sawaranaide yo!</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant">不要摸奇怪的地方！</title>
<summary>Hifumi is now the character team leader and uses all of her courage to ask Aoba and Yun about their progress on their 3D models. Both Aoba and Yun are used to Ko being the leader, and end up lying about their deadlines. However, Hifumi doesn’t seem to suspect anything from their deadlines, which makes Aoba panic and tell her the truth. Meanwhile, Yun knew she wouldn’t make it in time, but ended up telling Hifumi she would, ends up being even later than she thought. This makes her stress, wondering if Hifumi would become depressed once she tells her...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742159</identifier>
<identifier>new-game</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="189905" update="2017-08-09">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>60</length>
<airdate>2017-08-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">夏コミお疲れさまです! みんなで振り返ろう『NEW GAME!!』生放送SP!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Natsu Comi Otsukaresama Desu! Minna de Furikaerou "New Game!!" Namahousou SP!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="190295" update="2017-10-09">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-09-26</airdate>
<rating votes="7">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ぜひ買ってくださいね!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Make Sure You Buy It</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">J`espère que vous l`achèterez</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">제발 사주세요!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zehi Katte Kudasai ne!</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant">請務必購買！</title>
<summary>PECO’s master has finally been upped and an event was held, honoring its completion. The anticipation for PECO is pretty high, and a decent-sized crowd showed up for the event. Aoba and the other staff is seated up front and watch Ko and Shizuku talk about the project onstage. The event includes a little unplanned surprise, and ends in success. Afterwards, they all meet in the greenroom, where they are told some shocking news...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742173</identifier>
<identifier>new-game</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="190296" update="2017-10-09">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-09-19</airdate>
<rating votes="7">9.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">心に闇を抱えてるのか</title>
<title xml:lang="en">What`s Hidden in Your Heart</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">T`aurais pas un côté obscur, en fait ?</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">마음속에 어둠을 품고 있는가?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kokoro ni Yami o Kakaeteru no ka</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant">內心是懷有什麼東西嗎</title>
<summary>Tsubame gets done with her work early and is praised by Umiko about how fast she is. Nene is annoyed by how this is making Tsubame act, and while reading some of Tsubame’s code while doing her debug work, points out the fact that the code could’ve been shorter. Tsubame panics, thinking this could bring down her reputation with Umiko, and angrily tells Nene to mind her own business The air gets a bit tense in the programming department, so Nene decides to go visit the character team, where Momiji tells her something rather surprising about Tsubame...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742171</identifier>
<identifier>new-game</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="190297" update="2017-10-09">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-09-12</airdate>
<rating votes="7">8.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">どんどんリアリティが薄くなっていくんだよ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It`s Gonna Really Break the Immersion</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Si on laisse passer ce genre de détails, on va perdre le réalisme de l`univers</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">점점 리얼리티가 떨어지기 시작했어</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dondon Reality ga Usuku Natte Ikunda yo</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant">真實感漸漸減少了</title>
<summary>Tsubame creates the red light green light mini game that Hajime thought up in PECO. However, Aoba sees the mini game and comments that something is lacking. However, Hajime sees the finished product and says something is lacking. Hajime isn’t able to figure out exactly what is lacking, and asks Aoba and Yun for help, but they still aren’t able to figure it out. Hajime asks Tsubame if she thought the mini game was fun when she was making it, and her answer makes Hajime realize what’s missing, but Tsubame then worries about how the extra work is going to reflect on her...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742169</identifier>
<identifier>new-game</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="190298" update="2017-10-09">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-09-05</airdate>
<rating votes="8">4.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">シャツくらい着なよ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">At Least Put a Shirt On!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Mets au moins une chemise !</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">셔츠정도는 입으란 말야!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shirt Kurai Kina yo!</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant">至少穿件襯衫！</title>
<summary>Hajime and Yun go to see an Insect Five hero show at an amusement park. After the show, Hajime gets in line for a handshaking event with the cast members, when her friend from high school, Akki finds her. Akki asks Hajime what she’s doing in Tokyo, and Hajime tells her that she works as a designer. On top of that, she gets embarrassed for being in line for a handshake in front of Akki, so she gets out of line. Yun pokes fun at Hajime for the way she’s acting, and Hajime tells her that she actually kept her love for anime and tokusatsu a secret when she was in school.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742167</identifier>
<identifier>new-game</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="190713" update="2017-09-10">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-08-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="197097" update="2018-03-18">
<epno type="4">T12</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview 12</title>
</episode>
<episode id="197098" update="2018-03-18">
<epno type="4">T11</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview 11</title>
</episode>
<episode id="197099" update="2018-03-18">
<epno type="4">T10</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview 10</title>
</episode>
<episode id="197100" update="2018-03-18">
<epno type="4">T9</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview 9</title>
</episode>
<episode id="197101" update="2018-03-18">
<epno type="4">T8</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview 8</title>
</episode>
<episode id="197102" update="2018-03-18">
<epno type="4">T7</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview 7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="197103" update="2018-03-18">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="197104" update="2018-03-18">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="197105" update="2018-03-18">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="197106" update="2018-03-18">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="197107" update="2018-03-18">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="197108" update="2018-03-18">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview 1</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
