<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="13099" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2017-07-12</startdate>
<enddate>2017-09-27</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Teekyuu (2017)</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">てーきゅう (2017)</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Teekyu 9</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="12321" type="Prequel">Teekyuu (2016)</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://te-kyu.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="40269" type="Animation Work">Millepensee</name>
<name id="2338" type="Character Design">Itagaki Shin</name>
<name id="34736" type="Original Work">Piyo</name>
<name id="30935" type="Original Work">Roots</name>
<name id="2338" type="Direction">Itagaki Shin</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on http://anidb.net/cr34736 [Piyo]`s sports comedy manga by the same name, serialised in Comic Earth Star.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="228">5.28</permanent>
<temporary count="228">6.32</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>201910.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19543</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>35370</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://te-kyu.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>てーきゅう</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4632</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>360358</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15486</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>te_kyu/</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>teekyu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1049" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-03-06">
<name>cycling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2654" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-13">
<name>medium awareness</name>
<description>Medium awareness is the situational and generally temporary awareness characters in works of fiction have and display of the very fact that they are characters in works of fiction. For example, they may comment about the background music, quip about the script or narration, complain about the roles given to them by the writer or their lack of screen time, see the subtitles that appear on screen, inform the audience about the arrival of the commercial break, and even use medium effects as tools. The most common form of medium awareness is known as breaking the fourth wall, in which characters speak directly to the audience, either to it as a whole or to specific members of it. The "fourth wall" is the imaginary "wall" at the front of the stage of a proscenium theatre through which the audience sees the play; it is a metaphor for the boundary between what happens inside the work, to the characters, and outside it, to the audience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2752" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tennis</name>
<description>Tennis is yet another sport involving hitting a ball. Were it not for the copious amounts of grass involved in certain varieties, it seems hard to imagine that people would pay it any attention at all.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2805" parentid="2798" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>4-koma manga</name>
<description>Yonkoma manga (4コマ漫画, four cell manga, or 4-koma for short), a comic-strip format, generally consists of gag comic strips within four panels of equal size ordered from top to bottom. (They also sometimes run right-to-left horizontally or use a hybrid 2x2 style, depending on the layout requirements of the publication in which they appear.) Though the word yonkoma comes from the Japanese, the style also exists outside of Japan in other Asian countries as well as in the English-speaking market.</description>
<picurl>70558.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3568" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-02-07">
<name>gambling</name>
<description>Gambling is the wagering of money or something of value (referred to as "the stakes") on an event with an uncertain outcome with the primary intent of winning additional money and/or material goods. Gambling thus requires three elements be present: consideration, chance and prize. The outcome of the wager is often immediate, such as a single roll of dice or a spin of a roulette wheel, but longer time frames are also common, allowing wagers on the outcome of a future sports contest or even an entire sports season.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4570" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-07">
<name>watercolour style</name>
<description>A watercolour or aquarelle is a painting method in which the paints are made of pigments suspended in a water-based solution. Some anime are created in the style of watercolour paintings, the watercolour style, usually with faded pastels that often give the show a warm and friendly visual presentation. In modern anime, this is generally achieved via computer effects that create an imitation of watercolour, rather than by creating real-life watercolour art. While the watercolour style is more commonly used for backgrounds, it is possible to create the entire anime in such a style.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4588" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-20">
<name>fast-paced</name>
<description>Hold onto your hats, this anime`s storyline is relentless.
The characters don`t get time to take a breath as events keep both them and the viewer on a roller coaster ride of revelation and excitement!
Hopefully it all makes sense...</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5697" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-02">
<name>randomness</name>
<description>The anime does not follow a predictable storyline. New, strange, obscure, or otherwise unexpected story elements are introduced at a whim.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5852" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>short episodes</name>
<description>Short episodes are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length. This means up to and including 10 minutes; shows with episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length are http://anidb.net/t6494 [half-length episodes] instead.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6349 [multi-segment episodes], which are regular episodes that are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="47679" type="main character in" update="2016-08-12">
<rating votes="43">6.90</rating>
<name>Bandou Marimo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>94531.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="176" picture="192484.jpg">Hanazawa Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47680" type="main character in" update="2016-08-12">
<rating votes="37">4.68</rating>
<name>Oshimoto Yuri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>94528.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="24615" picture="73810.jpg">Watanabe Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47681" type="main character in" update="2016-08-12">
<rating votes="41">6.41</rating>
<name>Shinjou Kanae</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>94527.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20025" picture="132938.jpg">Mimori Suzuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47682" type="main character in" update="2016-08-12">
<rating votes="46">5.74</rating>
<name>Takamiya Nasuno</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>94530.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34225" picture="127053.jpg">Narumi Kyouko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="188502" update="2017-08-19">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2017-08-02</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">先輩と300</title>
<title xml:lang="en">300 with Senpai</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Senpai to 300</title>
<summary>Thanks to the love of our viewers, "Tekyu" has finally reached its 100th episode!!
We`ll be announce the results of the character popularity poll! Who will have the honor of being #1?! Don`t miss the 100th episode featuring the entire cast!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742319</identifier>
<identifier>teekyu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="188503" update="2017-08-19">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2017-07-26</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">先輩とピッチ・パーフェクト</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pitch Perfect with Senpai</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Senpai to Pitch Perfect</title>
<summary>Kanae suddenly announces that the tennis club is going to be an idol group! Tennis club first-year Oshimoto Yuri is about to respond with a witty remark, but for some reason she`s stopped by another member. The curtains have risen on the most brutal day of Yuri`s life...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742317</identifier>
<identifier>teekyu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="188504" update="2017-07-23">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2017-07-19</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">先輩とホームアローン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Home Alone with Senpai</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Senpai to Home Alone</title>
<summary>The birthday of the Kameido High School Tennis Club`s rich girl Takamiya Nasuno is coming up! Shinjo Kanae and the rest of the tennis club head to Nasuno`s house, each bringing their own surprise. Who will be able to surprise Nasuno the most?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742315</identifier>
<identifier>teekyu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="188505" update="2017-07-23">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2017-07-12</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">先輩とスピーシーズ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Species with Senpai</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Senpai to Species</title>
<summary>Alien Tomarin looks like a little girl, but she`s from outer space. In this episode we get a closer look at her life shrouded in mystery. After eating breakfast with Marimo, who she lives with, where will she head next...?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742313</identifier>
<identifier>teekyu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="189065" update="2017-07-14">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2017-07-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="189066" update="2017-07-14">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2017-07-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="189522" update="2017-10-07">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2017-08-30</airdate>
<rating votes="2">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">先輩とシェフ 三ツ星フードトラック始めました</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Chef with Senpai</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Senpai to Chef: Mitsu Hoshi Food Truck Hajimemashita</title>
<summary>Alien girl Tomarin lives at Marimo`s house. When Tomarin asks Marimo if she`d rather have dinner or her first, naturally she chooses Tomarin... *cough cough*. Will Marimo enjoy the meal Tomarin so painstakingly made?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742327</identifier>
<identifier>teekyu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="189523" update="2017-10-07">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2017-08-23</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">先輩と貞子vs伽椰子</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sadako vs Kayako with Senpai</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Senpai to Sadako vs Kayako</title>
<summary>One of the Takamiya family`s homes has become haunted! Nasuno, the dolls Natalia and Kazuko haunting her, and her mother go to check it out. There they find a house that has become fully haunted! Will Nasuno make it home safe and sound?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742325</identifier>
<identifier>teekyu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="189524" update="2017-08-19">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2017-08-16</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">先輩と茄子 アンダルシアの夏</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nasu: Summer in Andalusia with Senpai</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Senpai to Nasu: Andalusia no Natsu</title>
<summary>The tennis club goes cycling together. Nasuno rides up on a rather unusual bicycle, and Marimo shows up on that might be pretty difficult to ride. And Kanae... is that even a bicycle?!
Once the four of them begin riding, it`s questionable whether the path they`re taking is suitable for cycling at all...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742323</identifier>
<identifier>teekyu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="189525" update="2017-08-19">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2017-08-09</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">先輩と101</title>
<title xml:lang="en">101 Dalmatians with Senpai</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Senpai to 101</title>
<summary>Yuri and Tomarin accompany the newspaper club`s Kondo Udonko as she gathers information for an article.
There are apparently no decent clubs at Kameido High School, with the tennis club at the top of the list, and naturally, the girls must cover the tennis club as well.
Kanae and the others don`t waste this opportunity! The tennis club`s introduction hell has begun!!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742321</identifier>
<identifier>teekyu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="190373" update="2017-08-24">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2017-09-27</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">先輩とサウンド・オブ・ミュージック</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Sound of Music with Senpai</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Senpai to Sound of Music</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742335</identifier>
<identifier>teekyu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="190374" update="2017-10-07">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2017-09-20</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">先輩とドクター・ドリトル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dr. Dolittle with Senpai</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Senpai to Dr. Dolittle</title>
<summary>Welcome to the Kameido Zoo! However, the zoo the tennis club has arrived at is awfully quiet, and the exhibits are divided into animal and raw categories, making it a hardly satisfying experience. The zoo curator who holds the key to the situation explains to the girls what`s going on...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742333</identifier>
<identifier>teekyu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="190375" update="2017-10-07">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2017-09-13</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">先輩と仁義無き戦い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Battles Without Honor and Humanity with Senpai</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Senpai to Jingi Naki Tatakai</title>
<summary>Whistle, whistle. As festival music sounds in the background, the members of the tennis club change into shrine maiden outfits and help out at the shrine`s festival!
The four of them help out in earnest.
Kanae uses her ability to operate heavy machinery she learned in a past life to put together the stage! Wait, this isn`t a traditional music festival! It`s a music festival!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742331</identifier>
<identifier>teekyu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="190376" update="2017-10-07">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2017-09-06</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">先輩とデッドプール</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Deadpool with Senpai</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Senpai to Deadpool</title>
<summary>Upon hearing voices behind her, Yuri turns around to find there`s something wrong with Kanae and Marimo`s dimensions. It seems to be an illusion. This episode features such illusions. For the next three minutes, you`ll experience strange sensations... probably.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742329</identifier>
<identifier>teekyu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
