<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="13753" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2018-04-10</startdate>
<enddate>2018-06-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Fumikiri Jikan</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Railroad Crossing Time</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">踏切時間</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Crossing Time</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">건널목 시간</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">道口时间</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="9286" approval="2" total="2">Kyou no Asuka Show</anime>
</similaranime>
<url>http://fumikirijikan.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="14083" type="Character Design">Takamura Kaoru</name>
<name id="46815" type="Series Composition">Chiba Misuzu</name>
<name id="11282" type="Direction">Suzuki Yoshio</name>
<name id="53487" type="Animation Work">Ekachi Epilka</name>
<name id="53482" type="Original Work">Sato Yoshimi</name>
<name id="42509" type="Music">Houno Satoshi</name>
<name id="54806" type="Music">Tani Naoki</name>
<name id="54807" type="Music">Yamazaki Hibiki</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on http://anidb.net/cr53482 [Sato Yoshimi]`s slice of life manga.
Short stories about conversations young women have while waiting at railroad crossings.
Source: ANN
Note: The first two episodes received an early screening at a special event held at United Cinemas Toyosu on 24.03.2018.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="354">4.60</permanent>
<temporary count="355">6.15</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>213483.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20578</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>37188</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://fumikirijikan.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Fumikiri_Jikan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>踏切時間</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4924</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>363168</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21081</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>fumikiri_anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>crossing-time</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3007" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-07-16">
<name>monologues</name>
<description>This show features a noticeable amount of screen time during which characters talk to themselves. That is usually a way to display to the viewers what the characters are thinking. When used in excess, it may be a sign of poor storytelling, but when done skillfully, it may be excellent comedy fuel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3185" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-27">
<name>wordplay</name>
<description>The characters play with words. 
E.g. purposely or accidentally use similar-sounding but wrongly applied words in the Japanese original, leading to supposedly funny misunderstandings and confusion.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3813" parentid="6185" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-23">
<name>winter</name>
<description>Coldest season of the year with ice and snow, everything is covered in a blanket of white.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3977" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-29">
<name>dialogue driven</name>
<description>A dialogue driven show has its story advanced by dialogue, with action being of much lower priority, and relies heavily on conversations between characters.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4522" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>social commentary</name>
<description>Social commentary is the act of rebelling against an individual, or a group of people by rhetorical means. This is most often done with the idea of implementing or promoting change by informing the general populace about a given problem and appealing to people’s sense of justice. (Source: Wikipedia)&#13;
&#13;
Since this is anime, usually, the mores of Japan and the Japanese society are scrutinised, but not restricted to that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4576" parentid="6185" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-03">
<name>summer</name>
<description>At least one of the episodes takes place in summer. Think oppressively warm weather, summer vacation, summer school, summer festival, or a visit to the beach.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4588" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-20">
<name>fast-paced</name>
<description>Hold onto your hats, this anime`s storyline is relentless.
The characters don`t get time to take a breath as events keep both them and the viewer on a roller coaster ride of revelation and excitement!
Hopefully it all makes sense...</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5852" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>short episodes</name>
<description>Short episodes are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length. This means up to and including 10 minutes; shows with episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length are http://anidb.net/t6494 [half-length episodes] instead.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6349 [multi-segment episodes], which are regular episodes that are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6029" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-04-08">
<name>mundane made awesome</name>
<description>Sometimes normal just doesn`t cut it. Eating: you put food in your mouth and chew. Playing sports: you throw a ball around. You need to make it awesome, no matter how mundane it is.
Let`s throw in some gripping orchestral music, lighting changes, different camera angles, something! Don`t write like a man, write like an evil overlord! Exaggerate your expressions and gestures, speak with excessive intonation, and if all else fails, throw in some close-ups, slow motion, and ominous Latin chanting! With practice, even you can turn something like eating chips into an epic battle of light and dark, blinding the viewer with sheer awesomeness.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>149443.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6073" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-11-23">
<name>age difference romance</name>
<description>A romance between individuals of significantly different ages is featured. Depending on how big the age gap is and on the society featured, that may be considered taboo.
While the terms "lolicon" and "shotacon", often used in relation to anime and its fandom, are limited to a physical or erotic attraction to sexually precocious girls or boys respectively, this tag expands into platonic romances and other age ranges.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6088" parentid="2785" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-01-29">
<name>unrequited shoujo ai</name>
<description>At least one female character has a romantic or sexual interest in another female character, but the feelings are not returned.
This can be because the recipient is oblivious, straight, or simply not interested.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6093" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-08">
<name>short story collection</name>
<description>An anthology is a collection of literary works chosen by the compiler. It may be a collection of poems, short stories, plays, songs, or excerpts by different authors.
An omnibus format release is not just one continuous story, but several short stories. They may feature a different cast between each story, and the authors may differ.
In genre fiction, anthology is used to categorize collections of shorter works such as short stories and short novels, by different authors, each featuring unrelated casts of characters and settings, and usually collected into a single volume for publication. The complete collections of works are often called complete works or Opera Omnia (Latin language equivalent).
Source: EN Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6184" parentid="6185" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-29">
<name>autumn</name>
<description>Autumn, interchangeably known as fall in the US and Canada, is one of the four temperate seasons. Autumn marks the transition from summer into winter, in September (Northern Hemisphere) or March (Southern Hemisphere), when the arrival of night becomes noticeably earlier and the temperature cools considerably. One of its main features is the shedding of leaves from deciduous trees.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>161967.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6186" parentid="6185" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-29">
<name>spring</name>
<description>During spring, the axis of the Earth is increasing its tilt relative to the Sun, and the length of daylight rapidly increases for the relevant hemisphere. The hemisphere begins to warm significantly causing new plant growth to spring forth, giving the season its name. Snow, if a normal part of winter, begins to melt, and streams swell with runoff. Frosts, if a normal part of winter, become less severe. In climates that have no snow and rare frosts, the air and ground temperatures increase more rapidly. Many flowering plants bloom this time of year, in a long succession sometimes beginning when snow is still on the ground, continuing into early summer. In normally snowless areas spring may begin as early as February (Northern Hemisphere) heralded by the blooming of deciduous magnolias, cherries and quince, or August (Southern Hemisphere) in the same way. Many temperate areas have a dry spring, and wet autumn (fall), which brings about flowering in this season more consistent with the need for water as well as warmth. Subarctic areas may not experience spring at all until May or even June.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>161969.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6399" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-25">
<name>episodic</name>
<description>An episodic anime consists of many successive short arcs that are generally 1-2 episodes in length, with strong plot continuity within each arc but generally little continuity from one arc to the next. For long shows (well upwards of 50 episodes), the episode count constraint is less tight; for example, a show with close to 250 episodes would also be considered episodic if it consisted of a majority of arcs of up to 3 or maybe 4 episodes and possibly also very few slightly longer arcs.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="94491" type="main character in" update="2018-03-12">
<rating votes="8">7.04</rating>
<name>Ai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>214728.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38108" picture="172027.jpg">Senbongi Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94492" type="main character in" update="2018-03-12">
<rating votes="6">7.93</rating>
<name>Tomo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>214729.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16794" picture="214757.jpg">Ogura Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94493" type="main character in" update="2018-03-12">
<rating votes="4">6.57</rating>
<name>Sensei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>214721.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6919" picture="223669.jpg">Mamiya Yasuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94494" type="main character in" update="2018-03-12">
<rating votes="4">4.38</rating>
<name>Tanishi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>214724.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="54158" picture="223274.jpg">Matsunaga Kazuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94495" type="main character in" update="2018-03-12">
<rating votes="5">8.40</rating>
<name>Majima Eriko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>214725.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34714" picture="216072.jpg">Komagata Yuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94496" type="main character in" update="2018-03-12">
<rating votes="6">5.04</rating>
<name>Utako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>214726.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36620" picture="134995.jpg">Ayase Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94497" type="main character in" update="2018-03-12">
<rating votes="4">4.98</rating>
<name>Komaba Takashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>214722.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="71" picture="171537.jpg">Ichiki Mitsuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94498" type="main character in" update="2018-03-12">
<rating votes="6">6.81</rating>
<name>Komaba Misaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>214723.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10853" picture="232196.jpg">Kinoshita Suzuna</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94499" type="main character in" update="2018-03-12">
<rating votes="5">6.14</rating>
<name>Kurobe</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>214727.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9511" picture="35179.jpg">Honda Mariko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96204" type="main character in" update="2019-12-14">
<rating votes="6">5.17</rating>
<name>Fukutome</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>219271.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="55780" picture="66332.png">Haruki Nazuna</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96205" type="main character in" update="2018-06-17">
<rating votes="4">3.76</rating>
<name>Saito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>219272.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="26645" picture="171630.jpg">Hatanaka Tasuku</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96206" type="main character in" update="2018-06-17">
<rating votes="5">3.27</rating>
<name>Hassaku-ojisan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>219273.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2" picture="16471.jpg">Wakamoto Norio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96207" type="main character in" update="2018-06-17">
<rating votes="6">5.54</rating>
<name>Akemi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>219274.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10080" picture="235712.jpg">Aranami Kazusa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96208" type="main character in" update="2018-06-17">
<rating votes="4">8.51</rating>
<name>Saiki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>219277.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="387" picture="17233.jpg">Narita Ken</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96209" type="appears in" update="2018-06-17">
<rating votes="2">6.05</rating>
<name>Saiki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>219278.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="387" picture="17233.jpg">Narita Ken</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96210" type="appears in" update="2018-06-17">
<rating votes="4">7.68</rating>
<name>Yukiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>219279.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="96211" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-06-17">
<rating votes="5">6.77</rating>
<name>Yukiko no Musume</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>219280.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="350" picture="20063.jpg">Tamura Yukari</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="197505" update="2018-05-14">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-05-01</airdate>
<rating votes="11">5.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">SNS兄妹</title>
<title xml:lang="en">SNS Siblings</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">SNS Kyoudai</title>
<summary>Siblings, Takashi and Misaki, text each other while waiting at the railroad crossing.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>769209</identifier>
<identifier>crossing-time</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="197506" update="2018-04-24">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-04-24</airdate>
<rating votes="11">6.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">先生といっしょ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Together with Sensei</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sensei to Issho</title>
<summary>Sensei bumps into Kurobe while waiting at the railroad crossing.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>769207</identifier>
<identifier>crossing-time</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="197507" update="2018-04-24">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-04-17</airdate>
<rating votes="11">5.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">真島さんはエロい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Majima-san Is Sexy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Majima-san wa Eroi</title>
<summary>Tanishi secretly observes Majima while waiting at the railroad crossing.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>769205</identifier>
<identifier>crossing-time</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="197508" update="2018-04-24">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-04-10</airdate>
<rating votes="11">6.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">二人の青春</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Their Youth</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Futari no Seishun</title>
<summary>Ai and Tomo discuss their youth while waiting at the railroad crossing.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>769203</identifier>
<identifier>crossing-time</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="197897" update="2018-04-10">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2018-04-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198478" update="2018-06-09">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-05-29</airdate>
<rating votes="10">5.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">SNS兄妹②</title>
<title xml:lang="en">SNS Siblings 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">SNS Kyoudai 2</title>
<summary>The Komaba siblings returns! Takashi and Misaki continues to text each other while waiting at the railroad crossing
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>769217</identifier>
<identifier>crossing-time</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="198479" update="2018-05-22">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-05-22</airdate>
<rating votes="10">2.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">踏切のポエト</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Railroad Crossing Poet</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fumikiri no Poet</title>
<summary>A poet writes haiku`s at the railroad crossing.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>769215</identifier>
<identifier>crossing-time</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="198480" update="2018-05-14">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-05-15</airdate>
<rating votes="9">5.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">私とはっさくおじさん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mr. Hassaku and I</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Watashi to Hassaku Ojisan</title>
<summary>Akemi finds an old man in trouble at the railroad crossing.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>769213</identifier>
<identifier>crossing-time</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="198481" update="2018-05-14">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-05-08</airdate>
<rating votes="10">4.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゴス受難</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Goth Ordeals</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Goth Junan</title>
<summary>A girl dressed with Gothic outfit visits home, but bumps into an old friend of hers at the railroad crossing.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>769211</identifier>
<identifier>crossing-time</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="200081" update="2018-07-24">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-06-26</airdate>
<rating votes="10">4.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">二人の青春②</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Their Youth Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Futari no Seishun 2</title>
<summary>Ai and Tomo stand next to each other in silence at the railroad crossing.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>769225</identifier>
<identifier>crossing-time</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="200082" update="2018-06-18">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-06-19</airdate>
<rating votes="10">3.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">真島さんはエロい②</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Majima Eriko Is Sexy Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Majima-san wa Eroi 2</title>
<summary>Tanishi secretly observes Mashima while waiting at the railroad crossing. Yet again.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>769223</identifier>
<identifier>crossing-time</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="200083" update="2018-06-18">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-06-12</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">都電こころ状 後編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Heart of the City Train Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toden Kokoro Jou: Kouhen</title>
<summary>Saiki talks to the girl that looks like his first love at the railroad crossing.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>769221</identifier>
<identifier>crossing-time</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="200084" update="2018-06-09">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-06-05</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">都電こころ状 前編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Heart of the City Train Part 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toden Kokoro Jou: Zenpen</title>
<summary>Saiki reminisces about his past at the railroad crossing.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>769219</identifier>
<identifier>crossing-time</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
