<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="13869" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>11</episodecount>
<startdate>2019-04-12</startdate>
<enddate>2019-06-21</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Sarazanmai</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">さらざんまい</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Sarazanmai</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">皿三昧</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="8421" approval="15" total="15">Mawaru Penguindrum</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="778494">"This is the sarcastic fantasy of three boys who don`t feel connected to their important ones, getting to realize the real meaning of bonds." - in a flashy way!
1st  episode: "Nani?"
2nd episode: "Nani? Nani?
3-6th episode: "Really, I don`t get it!"
7-9th episode: "What`s wrong with you???"
10-11th episode: "Ohhhh that it?! Not so much waste of time as I thought half the way".
(Sorry for this, but thats what it discribed it the best.)</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://sarazanmai.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="3648" type="Direction">Ikuhara Kunihiko</name>
<name id="13304" type="Character Design">Ishikawa Kayoko</name>
<name id="13304" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ishikawa Kayoko</name>
<name id="3073" type="Music">Hashimoto Yukari</name>
<name id="3648" type="Series Composition">Ikuhara Kunihiko</name>
<name id="30794" type="Series Composition">Utsumi Teruko</name>
<name id="2835" type="Chief Direction">Takeuchi Nobuyuki</name>
<name id="21503" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kawatsuma Tomomi</name>
<name id="741" type="Work">Fuji TV</name>
<name id="805" type="Work">Dentsu</name>
<name id="3513" type="Work">Animax Broadcast Japan</name>
<name id="802" type="Work">Movic</name>
<name id="46626" type="Work">Gentosha Comics</name>
<name id="762" type="Work">Aniplex</name>
<name id="45418" type="Animation Work">Lapintrack</name>
<name id="31375" type="Animation Work">MAPPA</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch99005 [Yasaka Kazuki], an 8th grader living in Asakusa, is turned into a http://anidb.net/ch100446 [Kappa] along with his classmates http://anidb.net/ch99003 [Tooi] and http://anidb.net/ch99007 [Enta] by a mysterious creature named http://anidb.net/ch99002 [Keppi], after they break inadvertently a statue of a Kappa, the guardian god of the city.
They are then ordered by Keppi, who claims to be the first heir to the throne of Kappa Kingdom, to fight against the Kapa-zombies, bioarms created by his enemies, if they want to return to their human form.
In order to kill them, they have to make a specific sound called "Sarazanmai" which is produced only when the three of them are united, but the three boys cannot connect at first.
In addition, one of their secrets is revealed to each other every time they emit the sound!
They finally accept to take risks to collect the "Plates of Hope", given by Keppi when they defeat the Kapa-zombies, and which can make their wishes come true. However, some trouble occurs over the plates...!
Along the course of the fights against the Kapa-zombies, their fierce past and inner conflicts keep getting revealed. This is the sarcastic fantasy of three boys who don`t feel connected to their important ones, getting to realize the real meaning of bonds.
Source: Fuji TV</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="352">5.56</permanent>
<temporary count="356">6.49</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>230454.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21544</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>37426</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://sarazanmai.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Sarazanmai</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>さらざんまい</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5283</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>363568</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21839</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>sarazanmai</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>sarazanmai</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B07SQ9S1V4</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="55" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-11">
<name>awards</name>
</tag>
<tag id="997" parentid="2881" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>association football</name>
<description>Football is a sport that involves kicking a ball in order to score a goal, while the other team tries to stop you by kicking the ball in the other direction to score a goal of their own. In the United States, this sport is known as soccer; the inappropriately titled "American" football (which in fact is played with the egg-shaped "ball" being carried around) is some kind of rugby for babies.</description>
<picurl>40031.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1651" parentid="2883" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>photography</name>
<description>Photography is the art or process of producing images by the action of radiant energy and especially light on a sensitive surface (such as film or an optical sensor).
Source: Merriam-Webster</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1955" parentid="2925" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-05-18">
<name>child soldier</name>
<description>Untrained and as yet immature, children are expediently thrust into the role of warriors to protect god, king, and country. Not having even finished school, they are inexplicably designated to elite status or roles, typically requiring months of training and years of experience. All the more so with "experimental" equipment or weapons of mass destruction.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2565" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-14">
<name>cross-dressing</name>
<description>This character sometimes wears clothes traditionally worn by and associated with the opposite sex.
Cross-dressers often hide their cross-dressing identity for a long period of time and thus tend to become adept in accurately portraying the opposite sex in terms of voice, movement, behaviour, temperament, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2676" parentid="2672" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo</name>
<description>Tokyo, officially Tokyo Metropolis, is the capital city of Japan and one of its 47 prefectures. The Greater Tokyo Area is the most populous metropolitan area in the world. It is the seat of the Emperor of Japan and the Japanese government. Tokyo is in the Kantou region on the southeastern side of the main island Honshu and includes the Izu Islands and Ogasawara Islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214311.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2783" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>shounen ai</name>
<description>Shounen Ai means boys love, and thus explores what happens when two boys (or men) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2723 [Yaoi] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphical sex.
The female version is http://anidb.net/t2782 [Shoujo Ai].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2820" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>wardrobe malfunction</name>
<description>A euphemistic term for an embarrassing display of a body part when clothing droops, falls, or is torn. Wikipedia: "Super Bowl XXXVIII half-time show" for more details.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2857" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>anthropomorphism</name>
<description>Anthropomorphism is the attribution of uniquely human characteristics to non-human beings, inanimate objects, or natural or supernatural phenomena. If it`s an animal or an object (AI excluded) and it speaks and/or does other human-like things (dresses up) then we`re dealing with anthropomorphism.
Anthropomorphism leans more on the animal-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t7 [juujin], which leans more on the human-looking side.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2877" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>revenge</name>
<description>A primary factor that drives the plot forward, is the almost obsessive desire of one of the characters to get back at someone else.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3013" parentid="55" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-10">
<name>Newtype Anime Award</name>
<description>This anime has won 1 or more Newtype Anime Award(s)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3037" parentid="2676" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo Skytree</name>
<description>Tokyo Skytree is a broadcasting, restaurant, and observation tower in Sumida, Tokyo, Japan. It became the tallest structure in Japan in 2010 and reached its full height of 634.0 metres in March 2011, making it the tallest tower in the world, displacing the Canton Tower, and the second tallest structure in the world after Burj Khalifa (829.8 m).
Source: Wikipedia
Note: Not to be confused with the very much older http://anidb.net/t3667 [Tokyo Tower].</description>
<picurl>161122.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3103" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-07-11">
<name>first love</name>
<description>Ah… first love. The love that is remembered the most fondly by the participant, as this is commonly what people experience when they first have a first crush, but it is also the love before the Second Love, if that should ever happen, and for a guy, he usually holds her memory very close to him if he is a widower whereas for young girls, the memory of the First Love they ever had is a special memory to them, especially if he later becomes the boyfriend they`ve longed for.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>204995.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3411" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>fighting</name>
<description>For some reason or other one faction has to take it out on some opponent via fight or battle. Typical examples of this are all the anime with "endless pointless fighting" tag.</description>
<picurl>211266.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3606" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-11">
<name>family without father</name>
<description>For some reason the protagonists father is no longer among the living. The much too early death was due to sickness or accident.
This plot device adds a certain degree of tragedy to the anime and usually has repercussions on the rest of the family: Possibly the grieve-stricken mother and children barely function as humans. Or adding emphasis to the overall financial predicament of the family, should the father have been the money earner.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3759" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-11">
<name>teamwork</name>
<description>A cooperative effort by the members of a group or team to achieve a common goal.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3843" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-26">
<name>saving the world</name>
<description>While villains love to take over the world or cause the end of the world as we know it, the heroes are most likely motivated by the polar opposite, saving the world. A fairly simple plot/motivation related to for great justice and what not, this trope is pretty broad and very common for many stories not focused on character interaction only.
Source: TV Trope</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3863" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-07-05">
<name>competition</name>
<description>Some sort of confrontation occurs in this show. The protagonists "duke it out" via various competitions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3865" parentid="6153" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-08-07">
<name>noitaminA</name>
<description>noitaminA (ノイタミナ) – Animation written backwards – is a Fuji Television programming block, devoted to anime, broadcast each Thursday night from 00:45 to 1:15. It was launched with the intention of expanding the target audience beyond the typical young male demographic.
The timeslot was expanded from half an hour to a full hour in 2010, and now airs Thursday nights from 00:45 to 1:45.
noitaminA aired its first non-anime series in 2010, with the premiere of the live-action adaptation of Moyashimon. On April 15, 2010, Fuji TV and FUNimation announced an agreement that allows FUNimation to simulcast series from the noitaminA block in North America within an hour of their airing in Japan.</description>
<picurl>36897.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4048" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-17">
<name>Japanese mythology</name>
<description>Japanese mythology is a system of beliefs that embraces Shinto and Buddhist traditions as well as agriculture-based folk religion. The Shinto pantheon alone consists of an uncountable number of kami (Japanese for "gods" or "spirits").
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4052" parentid="2850" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-23">
<name>treasure hunting</name>
<description>A significant part of the anime centres on the protagonists` search for some obscure artefact or other treasure, an epic adventure and wild goose chase for something unusual and quite valuable.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4083" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-04">
<name>drastic change of life</name>
<description>One or more characters in this series go through an event that makes them change their way of life drastically and permanently. This change might be voluntary, or against the character`s will.
Some examples might be an accident, the gaining of superpowers, or simply graduating.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4203" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>rebellion</name>
<description>Rebellion, uprising, or insurrection is a refusal of obedience or order. It may, therefore, be seen as encompassing a range of behaviors aimed at destroying or taking over the position of an established authority such as a government, governor, president, political leader, financial institution, or person in charge. On the one hand the forms of behaviour can include non-violent methods such as the (overlapping but not quite identical) phenomena of civil disobedience, civil resistance and nonviolent resistance. On the other hand it may encompass violent campaigns. Those who participate in rebellions, especially if they are armed rebellions, are known as "rebels".&#13;
&#13;
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>163803.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4251" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-20">
<name>ensemble cast</name>
<description>A show with an ensemble cast focuses on a larger group of main characters in a single plot narrative; anime containing several segmented plot narratives (such as episodic or arc-based plots) are excluded. As such, it doesn`t really have a "main" or "lead" character; instead, every member of the central main character group plays an important part in the show`s grander scheme; no single character is more important or prominent than the others (equality of importance). Further, subplots (if any) lead by each character in the ensemble have equal weighting in importance (or lack of weight).

* In a show where no single main character is more important or prominent than the others, 4+ main characters is almost always an ensemble cast.
* A show with 3 main characters of equal importance is likely also an ensemble cast; equality of importance must be considered carefully.
* A show with 2 main characters of equal importance is generally not an ensemble cast situation; however, on an exception basis where neither main character is considered an antagonist, a 2-main-character anime may be considered an ensemble (e.g. http://anidb.net/a11829 [Kimi no Na wa.]).

Pictured: http://anidb.net/a9043 [K (anime)]</description>
<picurl>94914.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4387" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-07-04">
<name>good vs evil</name>
<description>A theme often used to relay lessons of morality. The fight between two entities, with one side representing all that is good and right and the other one all that is evil and wrong.
It’s one of the most conventional themes in literature, and sometimes considered to be a universal part of the human condition.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4499" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-07-28">
<name>some weird shit goin` on</name>
<description>Scenes of this show point to insanely strange events which seem to be taking place; throughout its episodes, the show may or may not explain what is going on. Either way, many viewers will find that a succinct and accurate way to describe the show is "WTF?", and the show`s explanations (or lack thereof) to the events will often be subject of heated debate.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4729" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-07-06">
<name>colour coded</name>
<description>Every single character on the main cast has a unique hair colour to help less perceptive viewers distiguish between them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5515" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>faceless background characters</name>
<description>Unimportant random/extra characters that appear mostly as part of the background are often drawn without much facial details, normally to save money, effort and manpower for more important parts of the show. Sometimes, they have almost or no facial details, meaning their heads only have indications of the presence of parts such as hair or mouth, or not even that. This can go as far as only drawing an abstracted silhouette of the whole body.</description>
<picurl>233515.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5697" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-02">
<name>randomness</name>
<description>The anime does not follow a predictable storyline. New, strange, obscure, or otherwise unexpected story elements are introduced at a whim.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5790" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-30">
<name>family without mother</name>
<description>For some reason, the protagonist`s mother is no longer among the living. The much-too-early death was due to sickness or accident.
This plot device adds a certain degree of tragedy to the anime, and usually has repercussions on the rest of the family. For example: the grief-stricken father and children barely function as humans; the oldest daughter has an extra burden of raising the other children, additional emphasis is given to the only female child in the family, i.e. with bishounen brother and dad in a shoujo setting.
In rare cases the mother may still be alive, just not living with the rest of the family presently, i.e. on some quest or job and gone for a long time.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5823" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-09-01">
<name>predominantly male cast</name>
<description>The anime features a mostly male cast, i.e. female characters are rare.
Example: Reverse harem setting with a plethora of bishounen.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5859" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-30">
<name>monster of the week</name>
<description>On a pretty much regular basis — weekly or episodic — the protagonists engage in some kind of conflict. This can be an actual showdown between mecha, or the all-out fight against an enemy, or a (car) race that needs to be won.
This can make the anime quite repetitive.</description>
<picurl>60013.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6021" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>gender bender</name>
<description>Term used to refer to a person who takes on the role of their opposite gender. This often only reaches to the extent of cross-dressing (involving physical appearance and clothing only), but in rarer cases, involves a total gender swap (which seems to be more common in anime) - where the willing or unwilling victim receives a body opposite of their original gender (either permanently or temporarily), with all natural parts per their new body fully (or just all-out amply) included.
Example of cross-dressing gender bender: "Maria+Holic"
Examples of body-swap gender bender: "Kashimashi: Girl meets Girl", "Birdy the Mighty Decode"</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6248" parentid="2872" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>thievery</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="99002" type="main character in" update="2019-01-21">
<name>Keppi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>229455.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="200" picture="17015.jpg">Suwabe Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99003" type="main character in" update="2019-01-21">
<rating votes="1">9.65</rating>
<name>Kuji Tooi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>229451.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2588" picture="153507.jpg">Uchiyama Kouki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99004" type="main character in" update="2019-01-21">
<name>Niiboshi Reo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>229456.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="255" picture="40713.jpg">Miyano Mamoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99005" type="main character in" update="2019-01-21">
<rating votes="1">6.18</rating>
<name>Yasaka Kazuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>229449.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30656" picture="153750.jpg">Murase Ayumu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99006" type="main character in" update="2019-01-21">
<rating votes="1">6.18</rating>
<name>Akutsu Mabu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>229457.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3709" picture="84359.jpg">Hosoya Yoshimasa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99007" type="main character in" update="2019-01-21">
<rating votes="1">6.18</rating>
<name>Jinnai Enta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>229453.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43410" picture="225078.jpg">Horie Shun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100446" type="main character in" update="2019-01-21">
<name>Yasaka Kazuki (Henshin-go)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>229450.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30656" picture="153750.jpg">Murase Ayumu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100447" type="main character in" update="2019-01-21">
<rating votes="1">8.17</rating>
<name>Kuji Tooi (Henshin-go)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>229452.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2588" picture="153507.jpg">Uchiyama Kouki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100448" type="main character in" update="2019-01-21">
<name>Jinnai Enta (Henshin-go)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>229454.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43410" picture="225078.jpg">Horie Shun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101086" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-04-12">
<rating votes="2">6.38</rating>
<name>Azuma Sara</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>232555.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="57514" picture="230626.jpg">Teiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102092" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-04-11">
<name>Zombie</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="54711" picture="216708.jpg">Katou Ryou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102093" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-04-12">
<rating votes="1">6.18</rating>
<name>Kuji Chikai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>232556.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="592" picture="170729.jpg">Tsuda Kenjirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102094" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-04-11">
<name>Haruka</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="3" picture="44969.jpg">Kugimiya Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102095" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-04-11">
<name>Jinnai Otone</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="101" picture="16709.jpg">Ise Mariya</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="213959" update="2019-05-14">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-04-12</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">つながりたいけど偽りたい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Want to Be Connected, but I Want to Lie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsunagaritai kedo Itsuwaritai</title>
<summary>Three middle schoolers, Yasaka Kazuki, Kuji Toi and Jinnai Enta encounter Keppi of the Kappa Kingdom. Butt stuff happens, and the three are enlisted to fight kappa zombies.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>783102</identifier>
<identifier>sarazanmai</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="213960" update="2019-05-14">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-04-19</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">つながりたいけど奪いたい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Want to Connect, but I Want to Take</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsunagaritai kedo Ubaitai</title>
<summary>Kazuki goes to unthinkable lengths to make his kid brother, Haruka, happy, including deception and theft.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>783103</identifier>
<identifier>sarazanmai</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="213961" update="2019-05-14">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-04-26</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">つながりたいけど報われない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Want to Connect, but It`s Not Meant to Be</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsunagaritai kedo Mukuwarenai</title>
<summary>Having no way to express his feelings for Kazuki, all Enta can do is to try to get him back in the soccer club.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>783104</identifier>
<identifier>sarazanmai</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="213962" update="2019-05-28">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-05-03</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">つながりたいけどそばにいない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Want to Connect, but You`re So Far Away</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsunagaritai kedo Soba ni Inai</title>
<summary>Kazuki needs Toi’s help to take over Sara’s fan meet. Meanwhile, Toi has his own demons to fight.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>783105</identifier>
<identifier>sarazanmai</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="214986" update="2019-10-08">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-04-12</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="214987" update="2019-10-09">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-04-12</airdate>
<rating votes="2">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="216089" update="2019-05-28">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-05-10</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">つながりたいけど許されない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Want to Connect, but I Can`t Be Forgiven</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsunagaritai kedo Yurusarenai</title>
<summary>Kazuki’s plot to highjack Sara’s fan meet goes sideways when it turns out there’s more to her than meets the eye.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>783106</identifier>
<identifier>sarazanmai</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="216090" update="2019-06-06">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-05-17</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">つながりたいから諦めない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Want to Connect, So I`m Not Giving Up</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsunagaritai kara Akiramenai</title>
<summary>Having failed to defeat the previous kappa zombie, the three are stuck as kappa. Meanwhile, Reo and Mabu become more desperate for kappa zombies.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>783107</identifier>
<identifier>sarazanmai</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="216091" update="2019-06-06">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-05-24</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">つながりたいけど裏切りたい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Want to Connect, but I Want to Betray</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsunagaritai kedo Uragiritai</title>
<summary>With things returning to normal for the three, they begin playing soccer together, but someone seems not to be happy with that.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>783108</identifier>
<identifier>sarazanmai</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="216092" update="2019-06-16">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-05-31</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">つながりたいけどもう会えない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Want to Connect, but We`ll Never Meet Again</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsunagaritai kedo Mou Aenai</title>
<summary>Chikai wants Toi to leave town with him. He bumps into Enta, and they go on a walk around as they share their predicaments.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>783109</identifier>
<identifier>sarazanmai</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="216639" update="2019-06-16">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-06-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">つながりたいけど伝わらない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Want to Connect, but I Can`t Express It</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsunagaritai kedo Tsutawaranai</title>
<summary>Enta and Keppi are both in critical condition. Meanwhile, Toi and Chikai flee from town, only to run into even more trouble.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>783110</identifier>
<identifier>sarazanmai</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="216640" update="2019-07-15">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-06-14</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">つながりたいけどつながれない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Want to Connect, but I Can`t</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsunagaritai kedo Tsunagarenai</title>
<summary>Enta has four hours left to live. The only way to save him is with the Dishes of Hope, but Reo also needs them to bring back the real Mabu.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>783111</identifier>
<identifier>sarazanmai</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="216641" update="2019-07-15">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-06-21</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">つながりたいからさらざんまい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Want to Connect, So Sarazanmai</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsunagaritai kara Sarazanmai</title>
<summary>Enta and Kazuki follow Toi, who is going into the past to remove himself from existence.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>783112</identifier>
<identifier>sarazanmai</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="222159" update="2019-10-09">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-04-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="222160" update="2019-10-08">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-05-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="222161" update="2019-10-08">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-06-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1c</title>
</episode>
<episode id="222162" update="2019-10-08">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-06-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
