<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="13925" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2018-10-06</startdate>
<enddate>2018-12-29</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Irozuku Sekai no Ashita kara</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">So Many Colors in the Future What a Wonderful World</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Iroduku Sekai no Ashita kara</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Irodzuku Sekai no Ashita kara</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">色づく世界の明日から</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Iroduku: The World in Colors</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">С завтрашнего дня в разноцветном мире</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">물드는 세계의 내일로부터</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">来自多彩世界的明天</title>
</titles>
<recommendations total="3">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="96490">Series has much to commend it. Great use of color to advance the story, and as a plot device. The plot is both touching and intriguing, but the characters advance the story more than the plot. You root for our MC to grow into her future. But it does not end the way you hope it might, it has a twist ending. Great for romance fans, and fans of excellent art and animation.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="311037">A beautiful, beautiful story that tugs on just the right heartstrings... It isn`t about love, so don`t expect that, but there is a lot of romance and the main heroine is just emanating purity and innocence in every scene she`s in. Cannot recommend this one enough!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://iroduku.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1385" type="Animation Work">P.A. Works</name>
<name id="124" type="Direction">Shinohara Toshiya</name>
<name id="24630" type="Character Design">Akiyama Yuki</name>
<name id="5071" type="Series Composition">Kakihara Yuuko</name>
<name id="24630" type="Chief Animation Direction">Akiyama Yuki</name>
<name id="8977" type="Music">Dewa Yoshiaki</name>
</creators>
<description>In a world in the future where magic is still a part of everyday life, 17-year-old http://anidb.net/ch94780 [Tsukishiro Hitomi], a descendant of a family of mages, lost the ability to see colors when young and has grown up into a girl devoid of emotion. Her grandmother http://anidb.net/ch98439 [Kohaku], a great mage, sends Hitomi to the past, to the year 2018. There, she spends time with a 17-year-old http://anidb.net/ch94779 [Kohaku] and her friends from club activities.
Source: amazon &amp; ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="956">6.28</permanent>
<temporary count="959">7.07</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>224636.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20794</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>37497</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://iroduku.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Iroduku_Sekai_no_Ashita_kara</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>色づく世界の明日から</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5060</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>363826</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21448</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>iroduku_anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B07J1VC599</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="165" parentid="2883" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>painting</name>
<description>Painting is the practice of applying paint, pigment, color or other medium[1] to a surface (support base). The medium is commonly applied to the base with a brush but other implements, such as knives, sponges, and airbrushes, can be used.
In art, the term painting describes both the act and the result of the action. Paintings may have for their support such surfaces as walls, paper, canvas, wood, glass, lacquer, clay, leaf, copper or concrete, and may incorporate multiple other materials including sand, clay, paper, gold leaf as well as objects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1298" parentid="2883" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-02">
<name>drawing</name>
<description>The art or technique of representing an object or outlining a figure, plan, or sketch by means of lines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1651" parentid="2883" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>photography</name>
<description>Photography is the art or process of producing images by the action of radiant energy and especially light on a sensitive surface (such as film or an optical sensor).
Source: Merriam-Webster</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2637" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>time travel</name>
<description>In time travel anime characters are transported through time either figuratively or literally to find themselves either in the past or the future</description>
<picurl>210068.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2642" parentid="2624" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-09-28">
<name>alternative present</name>
<description>Anime that fit in the alternative present category usually have technology and society that is very similar to ours, but with differences in both, history and culture, which sometimes are blatantly obvious, but sometimes harder to place; this one can at times be very subjective.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2680" parentid="2672" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Nagasaki</name>
<description>Nagasaki Prefecture is a prefecture of Japan located on the island of Kyushu. The capital is the city of Nagasaki.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214378.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2774" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>spellcasting</name>
<description>The magic version of “call your attacks”. The protagonist will explicitly call out the magical incantation for the spells.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3103" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-07-11">
<name>first love</name>
<description>Ah… first love. The love that is remembered the most fondly by the participant, as this is commonly what people experience when they first have a first crush, but it is also the love before the Second Love, if that should ever happen, and for a guy, he usually holds her memory very close to him if he is a widower whereas for young girls, the memory of the First Love they ever had is a special memory to them, especially if he later becomes the boyfriend they`ve longed for.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>204995.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3191" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-14">
<name>ohanami</name>
<description>Hanami (花見, lit. "flower viewing") is the Japanese traditional custom of enjoying the beauty of flowers, "flower" in this case almost always meaning cherry blossoms or ume blossoms. 
From the end of March to early May, sakura bloom all over Japan, and around the first of February on the island of Okinawa. The blossom forecast (桜前線 sakurazensen, literally cherry blossom front) is announced each year by the weather bureau, and is watched carefully by those planning hanami as the blossoms only last a week or two. 
In modern-day Japan, hanami mostly consists of having an outdoor party beneath the sakura during daytime or at night. Hanami at night is called yozakura (夜桜, literally night sakura). 
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
<picurl>160895.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3263" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>fashion</name>
<description>Fashion is a popular aesthetic expression in a certain time and context, especially in clothing, footwear, lifestyle, accessories, makeup, hairstyle and body proportions.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3369" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-06-23">
<name>human psyche</name>
<description>How that grey mass inside the skulls of us earthlings works.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3546" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-01-08">
<name>experimental animation</name>
<description>This anime uses distinct, alternative animation — much unlike other contemporary anime — either throughout or in individual episodes/sequences.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3809" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-05-24">
<name>character driven</name>
<description>The main appeal of the show is the way the characters are portrayed and interact, focusing on dialogue, spending time together or getting to know each other. These anime are not "story-less" but story is secondary to character development and the characters themselves and what they experience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3898" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-11-11">
<name>science and magic coexist</name>
<description>In this anime science and magic do not exclude each other. Magic here is actually very advanced, artefact- and/or ritual-based science.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3931" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-27">
<name>magical realism</name>
<description>Magical realism is fiction that portrays magical or unreal elements as a natural part in an otherwise realistic or mundane environment, in particular when a highly detailed, realistic setting is invaded by something too strange to believe. Magical realism is often associated with Latin American literature, particularly authors including Gabriel García Márquez and Isabel Allende.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3977" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-29">
<name>dialogue driven</name>
<description>A dialogue driven show has its story advanced by dialogue, with action being of much lower priority, and relies heavily on conversations between characters.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4440" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>boy meets girl</name>
<description>A classical type of plot in story writing, where the story begins with a boy meeting a girl leading to romantic development between the two. More often than not the boy loses the girl later on and has to find her again.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4614" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>narration</name>
<description>The most common example is that of a voice, either that of one of the characters or entirely unrelated, that appears at the beginning of an episode to offer a summary or introduction, and at the end of an episode for closure or for a preview to hint upon what to expect next.
Another use of narration comes in the form of a dominant voice belonging to one of the protagonists, intended only for the viewer and revealing the intimate thoughts to whom it belongs. This type of narration occurs frequently throughout the duration of the episode or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5529" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-11-05">
<name>black and white</name>
<description>Some or all of this anime is in black and white, typical of older anime made before ~1960. Some modern anime may intentionally shift to black and white for certain scenes or episodes as an artistic effect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5790" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-30">
<name>family without mother</name>
<description>For some reason, the protagonist`s mother is no longer among the living. The much-too-early death was due to sickness or accident.
This plot device adds a certain degree of tragedy to the anime, and usually has repercussions on the rest of the family. For example: the grief-stricken father and children barely function as humans; the oldest daughter has an extra burden of raising the other children, additional emphasis is given to the only female child in the family, i.e. with bishounen brother and dad in a shoujo setting.
In rare cases the mother may still be alive, just not living with the rest of the family presently, i.e. on some quest or job and gone for a long time.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5884" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-03-22">
<name>slow-paced</name>
<description>The story — including its characters and events — develop slowly.
May contain a weak continuity of plot and/or character development. 
Or may be a story telling device to increase the "sense of foreboding" in an anime with thriller or horror setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5984" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-09-10">
<name>girly tears</name>
<description>Usually girly tears are the ones not shed by men (duh). 
Like when a (stereotypical) girl watches something and cries her makeup out, a (stereotypical) dude just says, proclaiming his masculinity: "Meh, yet another soap opera bulls..t, I`ll be in my garage fixing my ride while playing heavy metal on a burning guitar ...with my teeth! And where`s my beer, woman?".
So that`s how it goes: girly tears are for girls and sissies! Chuck Norris forbid a guy would weep watching something that has this tag! Now 20 push-ups!
P.S. The opposite of "manly tears". Or is it? Let`s face it - it`s all subjective (and relative, and context-dependent).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6086" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-17">
<name>the power of love</name>
<description>The power of love is not only the strongest power known to mankind, it is the strongest power in the universe. The power of love conquers all things. It makes people cry, it makes people laugh, it can make them sing and occasionally it even brings dead people back to life, just so.
More so than the power of friendship, the power of true love gives boundless strength and resolution; by the power of love every hardship can be overcome, every issue can be resolved and it does make people resistant to food poisoning (caused by the bad cooking of their loved ones). Even the big bad evil doesn`t stand a chance against the power of true love and often ends up redeemed.
Even when the power of love is not literally and directly responsible, the scene is often set so that the audience is left with the impression that it was "really responsible".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="94779" type="main character in" update="2019-05-18">
<rating votes="21">8.04</rating>
<name>Tsukishiro Kohaku</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>223525.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43552" picture="179144.jpg">Hondo Kaede</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94780" type="main character in" update="2019-05-11">
<rating votes="18">6.12</rating>
<name>Tsukishiro Hitomi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>223524.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16763" picture="45795.jpg">Ishihara Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94781" type="main character in" update="2019-05-18">
<rating votes="6">1.94</rating>
<name>Aoi Yuito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>223526.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="24335" picture="192864.jpg">Chiba Shouya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97928" type="main character in" update="2019-05-18">
<rating votes="6">2.93</rating>
<name>Yamabuki Shou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>223527.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="55877" picture="222023.jpg">Maeda Seiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97929" type="main character in" update="2019-05-18">
<rating votes="6">5.91</rating>
<name>Kawai Kurumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>223528.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21312" picture="232438.jpg">Touyama Nao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97930" type="main character in" update="2019-05-18">
<rating votes="4">4.62</rating>
<name>Fukazawa Chigusa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>223530.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30656" picture="153750.jpg">Murase Ayumu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97931" type="main character in" update="2019-05-18">
<rating votes="12">7.52</rating>
<name>Kazano Asagi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>223529.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="52537" picture="225050.jpg">Ichinose Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98437" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-22">
<name>Tsukishiro Gen</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240148.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="341" picture="52370.jpg">Morikawa Toshiyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98438" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-22">
<name>Tsukishiro Yuzuha</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240151.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="364" picture="202614.jpg">Han Keiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98439" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-22">
<name>Tsukishiro Kohaku (60 Nengo)</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240149.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="508" picture="140061.jpg">Shimamoto Sumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98440" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-22">
<name>Tsukishiro Ruri</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240150.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="74" picture="84835.jpg">Oohara Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98441" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-22">
<name>Aoi Haru</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240147.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="442" picture="187043.jpg">Honda Takako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101603" type="appears in" update="2019-10-22">
<name>Kyoutou-sensei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240154.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3098" picture="248136.jpg">Ugaki Hidenari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101698" type="appears in" update="2019-10-22">
<name>Asakawa Sanami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240152.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="53526" picture="242924.jpg">Hasegawa Ikumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101699" type="appears in" update="2019-10-22">
<name>Kawai Ichika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240153.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="49728" picture="201172.jpg">Tachibana Emiri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101710" type="appears in" update="2019-03-30">
<name>Ichiyanagi Shuusei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67331.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="200" picture="17015.jpg">Suwabe Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="207949" update="2018-10-05">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-10-06</airdate>
<rating votes="14">8.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">キミノイクベキトコロ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Where You Belong</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kimi no Ikubeki Tokoro</title>
<summary>Hitomi Tsukishiro, a girl from a family of mages who lost the ability to see color when young, gets sent 60 years into the past when her grandmother Kohaku tells her one night to go back in time and visit her when she was a 2nd-year student in high school.
Source: amazon</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="207950" update="2018-09-17">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-10-13</airdate>
<rating votes="13">7.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔法なんて大キライ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Can`t Stand Magic</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mahou Nante Daikirai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="207951" update="2018-09-17">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-10-20</airdate>
<rating votes="11">6.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">No Rain,No Rainbow</title>
<title xml:lang="en">No Rain, No Rainbow</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">No Rain, No Rainbow</title>
</episode>
<episode id="207952" update="2018-09-17">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-10-27</airdate>
<rating votes="11">7.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">おばあちゃんはヤメテ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Stop Calling Me "Granny"!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Obaa-chan wa Yamete!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="209142" update="2018-10-12">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-10-13</airdate>
<rating votes="3">9.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="209143" update="2019-11-30">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-10-13</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="209364" update="2018-10-18">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-11-03</airdate>
<rating votes="9">7.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ささやかなレシピ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Modest Recipe</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sasayaka na Recipe</title>
</episode>
<episode id="209365" update="2018-10-18">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-11-10</airdate>
<rating votes="10">8.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">金色のサカナ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Golden Fish</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kin`iro no Sakana</title>
</episode>
<episode id="209366" update="2018-10-18">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-11-17</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヴィーナスの重荷</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Burden of Venus</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Venus no Omoni</title>
</episode>
<episode id="209367" update="2018-10-18">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-11-24</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほころびのカケラ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fragile Fragments</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hokorobi no Kakera</title>
</episode>
<episode id="209896" update="2019-01-05">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-11-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">特別編 石原夏織が行く, 色づく長崎の旅</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tokubetsu Hen: Ishihara Kaori ga Yuku, Irozuku Nagasaki no Tabi</title>
<summary>A live action travelog about Nagasaki.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="210156" update="2018-11-15">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-12-01</airdate>
<rating votes="9">5.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さまよう言葉</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wandering Words</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Samayou Kotoba</title>
</episode>
<episode id="210157" update="2018-11-15">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-12-08</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">モノクロのクレヨン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Monochromatic Crayon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Monochro no Crayon</title>
</episode>
<episode id="210158" update="2018-11-15">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-12-15</airdate>
<rating votes="9">7.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">欠けていく月</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Waning Moon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kakete Iku Tsuki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="210159" update="2018-11-15">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-12-22</airdate>
<rating votes="9">7.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">光る光るこの一日が光る</title>
<title xml:lang="en">On This Bright, Shining Day</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hikaru Hikaru Kono Tsuitachi ga Hikaru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="210160" update="2018-11-15">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-12-29</airdate>
<rating votes="10">8.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">色づく世界の明日から</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The World in Colors</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Irozuku Sekai no Ashita kara</title>
</episode>
<episode id="224833" update="2019-11-30">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-12-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="224834" update="2019-11-30">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-12-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="224835" update="2019-11-30">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-10-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1a</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
