<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="14397" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2019-06-15</startdate>
<enddate>2019-06-15</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Seishun Buta Yarou wa Yumemiru Shoujo no Yume o Minai</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Rascal Does Not Dream of a Dreaming Girl</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">청춘 돼지는 꿈꾸는 소녀의 꿈을 꾸지 않는다</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">青春ブタ野郎はゆめみる少女の夢を見ない</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">青春猪头少年不会梦到怀梦美少女</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="13900" type="Prequel">Seishun Buta Yarou wa Bunny Girl Senpai no Yume o Minai</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="96490">This is  movie on the one thread left undone, that of Makinohara. She has a huge part to play and explains a lot of other things throughout the series. It also is a story of first love, futures, and taking responsibility. I recommend it to anyone who enjoyed the series, and because it really presumes you know the characters and prior conflict(s), you should see this at the conclusion of the series.
On a 10 scale, it i an 8. Not because the animation is a wow but because it gives us a real ending to the series.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="338163">If you watched the series, you`ll want to watch this because it`s one of those rare times where an anime gets a solid conclusion.

Enjoyed it a lot, but wasn`t ready for it to get as heavy as it did. Maybe make sure you`re emotionally stable first.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>https://ao-buta.com/themovie/</url>
<creators>
<name id="21210" type="Character Design">Tamura Satomi</name>
<name id="54910" type="Work">Clover Works</name>
<name id="32834" type="Original Work">Kamoshida Hajime</name>
<name id="6192" type="Direction">Masui Souichi</name>
<name id="55636" type="Music">Fox Capture Plan</name>
<name id="21210" type="Chief Animation Direction">Tamura Satomi</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the 6th and 7th light novel volumes from Seishun Buta Yarou light novel series written by http://anidb.net/cr32834 [Kamoshida Hajime] and illustrated by http://anidb.net/cr28844 [Mizoguchi Keiji].
In Fujisawa, where the skies are bright and the seas glisten, http://anidb.net/ch94422 [Azusagawa Sakuta] is in his second year of high school. His blissful days with his girlfriend and upperclassman, http://anidb.net/ch94420 [Sakurajima Mai], are interrupted with the appearance of his first crush, Makinohara Shouko. For reasons unknown, he encounters two Shoukos: one in http://anidb.net/ch96611 [middle school] and another who has become an http://anidb.net/ch98161 [adult].
As Sakuta finds himself helplessly living with Shouko, the adult Shouko leads him around by the nose, causing a huge rift in his relationship with Mai. In the midst of all of this, he discovers that the middle school Shouko is suffering from a grave illness and his scar begins to throb...
Source: Aniplex of America</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="370">7.97</permanent>
<temporary count="376">7.80</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>232818.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21406</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>38329</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://ao-buta.com/themovie/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>青春ブタ野郎シリーズ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>365515</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22075</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="55" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-11">
<name>awards</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3013" parentid="55" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-10">
<name>Newtype Anime Award</name>
<description>This anime has won 1 or more Newtype Anime Award(s)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3813" parentid="6185" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-23">
<name>winter</name>
<description>Coldest season of the year with ice and snow, everything is covered in a blanket of white.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4576" parentid="6185" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-03">
<name>summer</name>
<description>At least one of the episodes takes place in summer. Think oppressively warm weather, summer vacation, summer school, summer festival, or a visit to the beach.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5384" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-15">
<name>put right what once went wrong</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="94420" type="main character in" update="2018-10-21">
<rating votes="154">6.61</rating>
<name>Sakurajima Mai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sakurajima Mai is a 3rd year student at Minegahara High School—well known, famous actress, who is currently on hiatus. Because her life had always revolved around her work in entertainment, she remains isolated at school. She`s serious and polite, but has a strong will.
Source: Official site</description>
<picture>224429.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21733" picture="152476.jpg">Seto Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94421" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-10-21">
<rating votes="56">6.76</rating>
<name>Azusagawa Kaede</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Azusagawa Kaede is http://anidb.net/ch94422 [Sakuta]`s younger sister. As a result of bullying in the past, she`s unable to leave the house and always house-sitting. She loves pandas and her older brother, while consistently striving to become the ideal little sister. Her daily routine includes waking up Sakuta every morning.
Source: Official site</description>
<picture>224430.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28392" picture="224735.jpg">Kubo Yurika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94422" type="main character in" update="2018-10-21">
<rating votes="75">6.15</rating>
<name>Azusagawa Sakuta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Azusagawa Sakuta is a strange 2nd year student in high school, who doesn`t have a cellphone in this day and age. He`s currently an outcast at school due to rumors of a violent past... but he doesn`t seem to care.
Source: Official site</description>
<picture>224428.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34296" picture="225238.jpg">Ishikawa Kaito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96609" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-10-21">
<rating votes="68">6.73</rating>
<name>Futaba Rio</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Futaba Rio is http://anidb.net/ch94422 [Sakuta]`s classmate who is always cool and calm, the sole member of the Science Club and known as an eccentric person at the school. She`s actually one of the Sakuta`s only friends, and is always willing to give various advice on the Puberty Syndrome.
Source: Official site</description>
<picture>224431.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32751" picture="157891.jpg">Tanezaki Atsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96610" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-10-21">
<rating votes="121">7.86</rating>
<name>Koga Tomoe</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Koga Tomoe is a 1st year student at Minegahara High School, a typical high-school girl who can take hints, but is slightly scatterbrained. Being overly concerned about how people look at her, she hides here Hakata accent, which comes out when she panics or is relaxed.
Source: Official site</description>
<picture>224432.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21312" picture="232438.jpg">Touyama Nao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96611" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-12-01">
<rating votes="20">7.19</rating>
<name>Makinohara Shouko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Makinohara Shouko is a shy middle school girl, but reliable and kind. She bumps into http://anidb.net/ch94422 [Sakuta], while holding an umbrella over an abandoned cat in the rain.
Source: Official site</description>
<picture>224433.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21013" picture="201781.jpg">Minase Inori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97309" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-10-21">
<rating votes="24">5.18</rating>
<name>Toyohama Nodoka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Toyohama Nodoka is http://anidb.net/ch94420 [Mai]`s half-sister, related through her father, a member of the idol group Sweet Palette and designated as the most fashionable within the group. Despite her flashy looks, she attends an elite all girls` high school. She`s confident and can be competitive.
Source: Official site</description>
<picture>224434.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="22366" picture="217303.jpg">Uchida Maaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98161" type="main character in" update="2019-12-01">
<rating votes="17">7.68</rating>
<name>Makinohara Shouko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Makinohara Shouko is http://anidb.net/ch94422 [Sakuta]`s first crush. He met her at the Shichirigahama beach back when he was in middle school. She claims to be an alum of Minegahara High School but there is no record that she ever was a student. Little of her origins other than her name are known, clouding her in a veil of mystery.
Source: Official site</description>
<picture>224435.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21013" picture="201781.jpg">Minase Inori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98525" type="appears in" update="2018-11-14">
<rating votes="5">6.91</rating>
<name>Kunimi Yuuma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>226773.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38579" picture="225249.jpg">Uchida Yuuma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99463" type="appears in" update="2018-11-25">
<rating votes="2">6.86</rating>
<name>Nasuno</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>227122.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="99464" type="appears in" update="2018-11-25">
<rating votes="2">5.87</rating>
<name>Hayate</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>227123.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="99775" type="appears in" update="2018-12-12">
<rating votes="4">4.34</rating>
<name>Sakuta Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>227613.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="78" picture="16686.jpg">Shimura Tomoyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100147" type="appears in" update="2019-01-01">
<rating votes="4">5.37</rating>
<name>Hanawa Ryouko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>228586.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37377" picture="188508.jpg">Aikawa Natsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="212488" update="2019-06-13">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>90</length>
<airdate>2019-06-15</airdate>
<rating votes="2">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="224811" update="2019-11-29">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-11-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">初日舞台挨拶</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening Day Stage Greeting</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shonichi Butai Aisatsu</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
