<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="14512" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2019-07-06</startdate>
<enddate>2019-09-21</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Araburu Kisetsu no Otome-domo yo.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">araoto</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">荒ぶる季節の乙女どもよ.</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">O Maidens in Your Savage Season</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">거친 계절의 소녀들이여</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">骚动时节的少女们啊。</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="12906" approval="4" total="11">Koi wa Ameagari no You ni</anime>
<anime id="5909" approval="1" total="9">Toradora!</anime>
<anime id="2165" approval="1" total="8">School Rumble</anime>
<anime id="191" approval="1" total="7">GTO</anime>
<anime id="16" approval="1" total="5">Onegai Teacher</anime>
<anime id="227" approval="1" total="4">Princess Nine: Kisaragi Joshikou Yakyuubu</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="395002">Feeling down? Don`t know what to watch next? Life`s not treating ya well today? Then this anime is RIGHT for you!!

I am quite STUNNED at how much I enjoyed this one!!

It`s about the story of young girls, who are coming of age and happen to think A LOT about sex. 

It`s much more cleaner than you might think! Yes! It is a reminder that women also think about such things! But done in a tasteful, mature, and yet somewhat childish way!

BE WARNED!

It will TUG on the old HEART STRINGS! Be prepared for a fuzzy and fun time! I HIGHLY recommend this if you need a pick-me-up. Perfect for  anime romance fans!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="446680">I`m amazed by the rating this show has. It`s a masterpiece from a legendary author about youth and figuring out your feelings and ways to translate them from the other person.
Characters, dialogues, development - everything is perfect. 
I`m a huge fan of Toradora, and this isn`t inferior in any aspect (except there are now tsunderes). I`ve never seen character being so realistic and believable, this is just perfect.
10/10 without a second thought.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://araoto-anime.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="42709" type="Animation Work">Lay-duce</name>
<name id="18497" type="Character Design">Ishii Kaori</name>
<name id="27375" type="Direction">Tsukada Takurou</name>
<name id="141" type="Direction">Andou Masahiro</name>
<name id="122" type="Original Work">Okada Mari</name>
<name id="18497" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ishii Kaori</name>
<name id="54197" type="Music">Hyuuga Moe</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a romantic school life shounen manga by author http://anidb.net/cr122 [Okada Mari] and artist http://anidb.net/cr56764 [Emoto Nao].
The girls in a high school literature club do a little icebreaker to get to know each other: answering the question, "What`s one thing you want to do before you die?" One of the girls blurts out, "Sex." Little do they know, the whirlwind unleashed by that word pushes each of these girls, with different backgrounds and personalities, onto their own clumsy, funny, painful, and emotional paths toward adulthood.
Source: Kodansha Comics</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="628">6.66</permanent>
<temporary count="631">7.22</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>234057.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21874</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>38753</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://araoto-anime.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>O_Maidens_in_Your_Savage_Season</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>荒ぶる季節の乙女どもよ。</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5358</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>366354</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22085</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>araotoproject</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="34">
<externalentity>
<url>https://www.hidive.com/tv/o-maidens-in-your-savage-season</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2069" parentid="2869" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-15">
<name>delinquent</name>
<description>Delinquents - Every school has them, but not all anime with school setting make delinquents a central topic. There are several versions of these delinquents, though some are grounded on a misunderstanding:
* The student with a really bad image and attitude, based on his real criminal actions outside of the school and is even feared by teachers.
* The primitive "class bully" that pushes around ("clobbers") his classmates for no apparent reason, possibly extorting lunch money.
* The student with an sinister complexion or "evil eye", but is actually a "good" student (unfoundedly feared character).
* The rebellious student, who does not care for studying, but is otherwise docile. Called a "delinquent" as a joke.</description>
<picurl>243713.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2706" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-13">
<name>masturbation</name>
<description>Manual erotic stimulation of the genitals or other erogenous regions, often to orgasm, either by oneself or a partner.</description>
<picurl>210612.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>sex</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%27Origine_du_monde).
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2779" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>multiple couples</name>
<description>More than one couple is developed in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2787" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-08-28">
<name>teacher x student</name>
<description>Suggests a relationship involving a teacher and their student, often times sexual in nature.</description>
<picurl>206646.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2816" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>sexual fantasies</name>
<description>One or more characters in this anime let their imaginations run wild thinking about another character.
Yes, they are thinking about sex, and in an ecchi anime these thoughts are often perverted, leading to a nosebleed. But it may also be romanticising simply being husband and wife, and everything that implies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2828" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-26">
<name>borderline porn</name>
<description>Breaks the bounds of "excessive fanservice".
While the physical interactions and dialogue between characters may be extremely sexual, the most sexual situations do *not* have sex itself take place.
Specifically descriptive of containing all the plentiful features of (excessive) fanservice in addition to the interactions between characters being quite sexual — at most, sexual in NATURE only. This means physical touching such as groping, molesting, or bondage will focus primarily on the revealed (i.e. nude) upper portion of the body or through/over clothing on the lower half of the body. This is all WITHOUT actual sex acts (penetration, etc.) taking place.</description>
<picurl>214855.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2845" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-04-30">
<name>blackmail</name>
<description>In general usage, blackmail is a crime involving unjustified threats against a person or organization in order to make a gain or harm or cause material loss to them unless a demand is met. It may be considered similar to or a form of extortion, although some jurisdictions will consider them as separate crimes. Most often, blackmail involves the threat of revealing some secret to a given third party, which may be another person, a rival organization, or a state institution such as the police, or to the general public. In anime and related media, and more specifically in pornographic works, blackmail is also a device used to coerce people, generally female and often schoolgirls, into having sex with another or others; in such cases, it may be considered similar to or a form of rape.</description>
<picurl>136031.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3047" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>feminism</name>
<description>Women or girls fighting against the social stereotyping of females.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3103" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-07-11">
<name>first love</name>
<description>Ah… first love. The love that is remembered the most fondly by the participant, as this is commonly what people experience when they first have a first crush, but it is also the love before the Second Love, if that should ever happen, and for a guy, he usually holds her memory very close to him if he is a widower whereas for young girls, the memory of the First Love they ever had is a special memory to them, especially if he later becomes the boyfriend they`ve longed for.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>204995.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3185" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-27">
<name>wordplay</name>
<description>The characters play with words. 
E.g. purposely or accidentally use similar-sounding but wrongly applied words in the Japanese original, leading to supposedly funny misunderstandings and confusion.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3227" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-06-24">
<name>introspection</name>
<description>The characters in this anime do not walk through life simply accepting how they are, but quite on the contrary constantly try to understand their own motives, feelings and reactions to the other protagonists. 
This self-searching included the questions: "Who am I?", "What makes me tick?", "What do I want?", "What do others expect of me?", etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3684" parentid="2883" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-04-28">
<name>literature</name>
<description>Works of literature are featured. Likely, a prominent character in this anime likes to read books, or the books themselves play a role. They might be specific, named works of literature or books in general.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3718" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true">
<name>love between enemies</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3741" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-25">
<name>bullying</name>
<description>Bullying is the use of force, threat, or coercion to abuse, intimidate, or aggressively dominate others. One who engages in bullying is known as a bully.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3977" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-29">
<name>dialogue driven</name>
<description>A dialogue driven show has its story advanced by dialogue, with action being of much lower priority, and relies heavily on conversations between characters.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4055" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>facial distortion</name>
<description>The characters face are exaggerated into a misshape, deformed, and almost warped. Used as comedy element to express extreme mood swings.
Differing from "http://anidb.net/t2652 [Super Deformed]", here only the face changes to an extreme degree, not the whole body of the protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4222" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>walls of text</name>
<description>Walls of text refers to Japanese text that appears in large quantities within the anime itself. This text is most likely vital to the storyline and may come in the form of charts and diagrams or pieces of paper, notes or even thoughts that are only partially or entirely unspoken.
May also be taken as a fair warning to viewers unable to translate Japanese text on their own, suggesting that thorough subtitle support may be required as well as making use of the pause button on their media players so that all text can be read.
Normally, tags don`t refer to physical translations of text, subtitle appearances and karaoke styling added by 3rd parties. But those who seek to describe an anime that is heavy on SPOKEN dialogue (which may tend to create a large quantity of natural subtitling to read for those not fluent in the language being used) could consider this tag but may make clearer reference with the dialogue driven tag.</description>
<picurl>32534.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4394" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-21">
<name>defeat means friendship</name>
<description>In a series based around an endless series of one-on-one fights, defeating a Worthy Opponent or The Rival will sometimes convert them to the hero`s side, if not always to his cause. 
Furthermore, no matter how many people the Worthy Opponent has killed, how much grief he has caused, even if he slaughtered helpless children or the hero`s own family, as soon as he shows a bit of remorse or goes out of his way to help the hero even once, he will be welcomed into the hero`s circle of True Companions with open arms.
(Source: TVTropes)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4498" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-20">
<name>heart-warming</name>
<description>The story and its characters give off good vibes — includes elevated feelings of affection such as tenderness, sympathy and love, all in one package.
The kind of anime which leaves you with a warm feeling inside and you can not stop smiling while watching it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4570" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-07">
<name>watercolour style</name>
<description>A watercolour or aquarelle is a painting method in which the paints are made of pigments suspended in a water-based solution. Some anime are created in the style of watercolour paintings, the watercolour style, usually with faded pastels that often give the show a warm and friendly visual presentation. In modern anime, this is generally achieved via computer effects that create an imitation of watercolour, rather than by creating real-life watercolour art. While the watercolour style is more commonly used for backgrounds, it is possible to create the entire anime in such a style.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4614" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>narration</name>
<description>The most common example is that of a voice, either that of one of the characters or entirely unrelated, that appears at the beginning of an episode to offer a summary or introduction, and at the end of an episode for closure or for a preview to hint upon what to expect next.
Another use of narration comes in the form of a dominant voice belonging to one of the protagonists, intended only for the viewer and revealing the intimate thoughts to whom it belongs. This type of narration occurs frequently throughout the duration of the episode or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4712" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-02-01">
<name>childhood ties</name>
<description>At least two of the characters share a childhood experience together that plays a part in the plot of the anime. The experience can be anything that ties them together, be it a memory, friendship, promise, tragedy, etc. Something happened to them in their childhood which binds them in a way that is unique.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5485" parentid="7199" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-28">
<name>penis jokes</name>
<description>A penis or other phallic object is used as a device to elicit laughter from the viewer. This also includes indirect references to such objects provided the intent is clearly the same.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5875" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-18">
<name>jealousy</name>
<description>A character is jealous of another character either due to love, or power, or wealth.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5984" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-09-10">
<name>girly tears</name>
<description>Usually girly tears are the ones not shed by men (duh). 
Like when a (stereotypical) girl watches something and cries her makeup out, a (stereotypical) dude just says, proclaiming his masculinity: "Meh, yet another soap opera bulls..t, I`ll be in my garage fixing my ride while playing heavy metal on a burning guitar ...with my teeth! And where`s my beer, woman?".
So that`s how it goes: girly tears are for girls and sissies! Chuck Norris forbid a guy would weep watching something that has this tag! Now 20 push-ups!
P.S. The opposite of "manly tears". Or is it? Let`s face it - it`s all subjective (and relative, and context-dependent).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6075" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-12">
<name>educational</name>
<description>The entire series (at least a major part of it) is centred on a particular subject. Information is fed to the audience in a sublime manner. Most of the time an on-screen written comment by the narrator (or translator) can be seen, e.g. biological specimen, medicine, process, etc. Sometimes at the end of every episode’s closing song, a 20 seconds educational clip is presented.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6088" parentid="2785" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-01-29">
<name>unrequited shoujo ai</name>
<description>At least one female character has a romantic or sexual interest in another female character, but the feelings are not returned.
This can be because the recipient is oblivious, straight, or simply not interested.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6840" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-07">
<name>social media</name>
<description>Social media are computer-mediated technologies that allow the creating and sharing of information, ideas, career interests and other forms of expression via virtual communities and networks.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7199" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-12">
<name>sexual humour</name>
<description>Sexual humour is prevalent in this anime. It often involves cheeky or crude sexual language, with innuendos and jokes about the female or male genitalia. Often, such anime also have http://anidb.net/t2856 [ecchi] elements to them.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="103158" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-06-02">
<rating votes="8">2.81</rating>
<name>Saegusa Hisashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>234197.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="144" picture="16904.jpg">Sakuya Shunsuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103159" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-06-02">
<rating votes="12">5.53</rating>
<name>Norimoto Izumi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>234194.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="46764" picture="204863.jpg">Tsuchiya Shinba</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103160" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-09-27">
<rating votes="5">6.86</rating>
<name>Juujou Sonoe</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238860.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5" picture="233827.jpg">Tomatsu Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103161" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-06-02">
<rating votes="11">5.65</rating>
<name>Amagi Shun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>234195.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43500" picture="235807.jpg">Hirose Yuuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103162" type="main character in" update="2019-06-02">
<rating votes="47">8.18</rating>
<name>Onodera Kazusa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>234189.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="51410" picture="223259.jpg">Kouno Hiyori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103163" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-06-02">
<rating votes="8">7.53</rating>
<name>Yamagishi Tomoaki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>234196.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="14" picture="75503.jpg">Fukuyama Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103164" type="main character in" update="2019-06-02">
<rating votes="27">6.21</rating>
<name>Sonezaki Rika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>234193.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28602" picture="131381.jpg">Uesaka Sumire</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103165" type="main character in" update="2019-06-02">
<rating votes="26">6.08</rating>
<name>Hongou Hitoha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>234192.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16804" picture="224734.jpg">Kurosawa Tomoyo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103166" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-09-27">
<rating votes="3">1.11</rating>
<name>Sugimoto Satoru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238859.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="31313" picture="84218.jpg">Hanae Natsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103167" type="main character in" update="2019-06-02">
<rating votes="41">2.19</rating>
<name>Sugawara Niina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>234190.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10759" picture="38748.jpg">Anzai Chika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103168" type="main character in" update="2019-06-02">
<rating votes="31">2.52</rating>
<name>Sudou Momoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>234191.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37985" picture="175206.jpg">Asakura Momo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105558" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-09-27">
<rating votes="4">6.94</rating>
<name>Tomita Emi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238862.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38296" picture="228671.jpg">Aoyama Yoshino</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105566" type="appears in" update="2019-09-23">
<rating votes="2">6.97</rating>
<name>Youshouki Izumi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238683.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="57152" picture="228647.jpg">Shibata Mei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105567" type="appears in" update="2019-09-27">
<rating votes="2">5.93</rating>
<name>Izumi Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238863.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="160" picture="30490.jpg">Kaida Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105568" type="appears in" update="2019-09-23">
<rating votes="1">7.63</rating>
<name>Kazusa Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238685.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="253" picture="222833.jpg">Yuzuki Ryouka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105569" type="appears in" update="2019-09-27">
<rating votes="1">2.39</rating>
<name>Asada Emi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238861.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39890" picture="161176.jpg">Oomori Nichika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105570" type="appears in" update="2019-09-23">
<rating votes="2">2.53</rating>
<name>Henshuusha</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238689.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40436" picture="186230.jpg">Hamada Youhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105571" type="appears in" update="2019-09-23">
<rating votes="2">2.01</rating>
<name>Kouchou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238690.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17167" picture="170235.jpg">Fujiyoshi Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105572" type="appears in" update="2019-09-23">
<rating votes="1">7.63</rating>
<name>Kazusa Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238691.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38116" picture="223784.jpg">Kitada Masamichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105573" type="appears in" update="2019-09-23">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Takeyama Yuuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238693.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43627" picture="176871.jpg">Hara Natsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105574" type="appears in" update="2019-09-23">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Hongou Ane</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238695.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42697" picture="223257.jpg">Kinugawa Rika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105618" type="appears in" update="2019-09-27">
<rating votes="2">1.52</rating>
<name>Yamagishi Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238864.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1683" picture="223030.jpg">Kanemitsu Nobuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105619" type="appears in" update="2019-09-27">
<rating votes="2">6.92</rating>
<name>Yamagishi Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238865.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="54272" picture="223458.jpg">Kowaka Wakana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105620" type="appears in" update="2019-09-27">
<rating votes="1">2.39</rating>
<name>Josei Henshuusha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238840.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42022" picture="224286.jpg">Ishii Misa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105632" type="appears in" update="2019-09-27">
<rating votes="1">1.04</rating>
<name>Kyoutou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238856.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38116" picture="223784.jpg">Kitada Masamichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105633" type="appears in" update="2019-09-27">
<rating votes="1">1.56</rating>
<name>Sonezaki Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238857.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42022" picture="224286.jpg">Ishii Misa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105634" type="appears in" update="2019-09-27">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Sonezaki Sobo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238858.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="55796" picture="223635.jpg">Mikajiri Nozomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105635" type="appears in" update="2019-09-27">
<rating votes="1">4.14</rating>
<name>Onodera Kazusa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238866.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="51410" picture="223259.jpg">Kouno Hiyori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105636" type="appears in" update="2019-09-27">
<name>Sugawara Niina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238867.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10759" picture="38748.jpg">Anzai Chika</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="218017" update="2019-07-07">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-07-06</airdate>
<rating votes="12">6.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">豚汁の味</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Taste of Her Pork Miso Soup</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tonjiru no Aji</title>
</episode>
<episode id="218018" update="2019-06-13">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-07-13</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">えすいばつ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Es-Ee-Ecks</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Esuibatsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="218019" update="2019-06-13">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-07-20</airdate>
<rating votes="9">7.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">バスガス爆発</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Willy`s Rear Rear Wheel</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bus Gas Bakuhatsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="218020" update="2019-06-13">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-07-27</airdate>
<rating votes="8">8.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">本という存在</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Purpose of Books</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hon to Iu Sonzai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="218595" update="2020-02-10">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-07-06</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="218596" update="2020-02-10">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-07-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="218873" update="2019-07-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-08-03</airdate>
<rating votes="9">8.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">私を知らぬ間に変えたもの</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Things That Changed Before We Knew It</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Watashi o Shirazu Aida ni Kaeta Mono</title>
</episode>
<episode id="218874" update="2019-07-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-08-10</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">乙女は森のなか</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Maidens in the Woods</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Otome wa Mori no Naka</title>
</episode>
<episode id="218875" update="2019-07-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-08-17</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">揺れ, の, その先</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Jiggling, Then, After</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yure, no, Sono Saki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="218876" update="2019-07-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-08-24</airdate>
<rating votes="10">9.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Legend of Love</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Legend of Love</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Legend of Love</title>
</episode>
<episode id="219374" update="2019-08-16">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-08-31</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">キツネノカミソリ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Orange Fox`s Lilies</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kitsune no Kamisori</title>
</episode>
<episode id="219375" update="2019-08-16">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-09-07</airdate>
<rating votes="10">9.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">穴</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Holes</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ana</title>
</episode>
<episode id="219376" update="2019-08-16">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-09-14</airdate>
<rating votes="7">8.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">男女交際禁止令</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Inappropriate Conduct Between the Sexes Is Now Forbidden</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Danjo Kousai Kinshi Ryou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="219377" update="2019-08-16">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-09-21</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">乙女心のいろいろは</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Colors of the Hearts of Maidens</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Otomegokoro no Iroiro wa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="221523" update="2020-02-10">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-08-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="221524" update="2020-02-10">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-08-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1c</title>
</episode>
<episode id="221525" update="2020-02-10">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-07-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="221526" update="2020-02-10">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-07-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1c</title>
</episode>
<episode id="221527" update="2020-02-10">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2019-09-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
