<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="14602" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2020-01-12</startdate>
<enddate>2020-03-29</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Kyokou Suiri</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">虚構推理</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">In/Spectre</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">허구추리</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="official">المنطق الخيالي</title>
</titles>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="498162">It is just ok, somewhat engaging after the first episode, but story is thin and slow, over half of the season is talking about a single story.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="748358">This one could have been really good. The premise was hooking and both main leads appeared interesting at first. Animation and voice acting were decent, complete with a dark, night city setting and vibe. However, right from the second episode, it became clear that the anime was just going to focus on exposition, and I mean tons, and tons, of exposition. Entire episodes were spent just on the female lead literally telling the story, with little to no action involved. The last four episodes were pure exposition galore. This imbalance between storytelling and action made the anime generally unexciting, boring and repetitive. I also found the female lead to be somewhat annoying at times, but that`s a personal preference anyway. In short, I didn`t quite enjoy this one.

However, I know there are many fans out there who like this technique on mystery animes, and I respect that, it just wasn`t for me. So is recommended for yokai mystery fans who value storytelling over action.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://kyokousuiri.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="54454" type="Music">Manabe Akihiro</name>
<name id="29579" type="Chief Animation Direction">Honda Takatoshi</name>
<name id="1725" type="Direction">Gotou Keiji</name>
<name id="3559" type="Original Work">Shirodaira Kyou</name>
<name id="783" type="Work">NAS</name>
<name id="7428" type="Series Composition">Takagi Noboru</name>
<name id="29579" type="Character Design">Honda Takatoshi</name>
<name id="982" type="Animation Work">Brain`s Base</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a mystery thriller novel series written by http://anidb.net/cr3559 [Shirodaira Kyou] since 2011. A manga adaptation by http://anidb.net/cr57239 [Katase Chashiba] started in 2015.
When she was still just a girl, http://anidb.net/ch106551 [Kotoko] was kidnapped by yokai. These spirits made her into a powerful intermediary between the spirit and human worlds, but this power came at a price: an eye and a leg. Now, years later, she watches out for dangerous yokai while developing feelings for a young man named http://anidb.net/ch106553 [Kurou], who is also special: an incident with a yokai has given him healing powers. He`s surprised when Kotoko asks him to team up to handle renegade yokai, preserving the thin line between reality and the supernatural.
Source: Kodansha Comics</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="471">4.91</permanent>
<temporary count="472">6.55</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>241405.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22256</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>40894</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>39017</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://kyokousuiri.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>In/Spectre</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>虚構推理</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5536</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>366818</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22445</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>kyokou_suiri/status/1218095614182948864</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>kyokou_suiri</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>kyokou_suiri/status/1223169047744745477</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>kyokou_suiri/status/1225705761269059585</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>kyokou_suiri/status/1220632329229492224</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="26">
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=CEQ56-P9L9c</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=O47qukJbNHc</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=JDfepuIF9ow</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=idrQVPdrw3g</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>inspectre</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="34">
<externalentity>
<url>https://kyokousuiri.jp/movie/minianime/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="308" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>detective</name>
<description>A detective is an investigator, generally either a member of a law enforcement agency or as an individual working in the capacity of private investigators, tasked with solving crimes and other mysteries, such as disappearances, by examining and evaluating clues and records in order to solve the mystery; for a crime, this would mean uncovering the criminal`s identity and/or whereabouts. In some police systems, a detective position is achieved by passing a written test after a person completes the requirements for being a police officer; in others, detectives are college graduates who join directly from civilian life without first serving as uniformed officers.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210906.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1152" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-23">
<name>undead</name>
</tag>
<tag id="2438" parentid="2794" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-16">
<name>idol</name>
<description>In Japanese culture, idols (アイドル) are media personalities in their teens and early twenties who are considered particularly cute and cuddly and who will, for a period ranging from several months to a few years, regularly appear in the mass media, e.g. as singers for J-pop groups, bit-part actors, TV personalities, models in photo spreads published in magazines, advertisements, etc.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>63097.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2535" parentid="1152" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-18">
<name>ghost</name>
<description>In traditional belief, a ghost is the soul or spirit of a deceased person or animal that can appear, in visible form or other manifestation, to the living. Descriptions of the apparition of ghosts vary widely: The mode of manifestation can range from an invisible presence to translucent or wispy shapes, to realistic, life-like visions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2566" parentid="2608" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-31">
<name>loli</name>
<description>Lolita (often also just abbreviated to loli) refers originally to a novel by Vladimir Nabokov. The book is internationally famous for its controversial subject: the narrator and protagonist, middle aged Humbert Humbert, becomes obsessed and sexually involved with a 12-year-old girl named Dolores Haze.
Nowadays the name "Lolita" describes a sexually precocious young girl.
Related to this is http://anidb.net/t2415 [lolicon], the Japanese abbreviation of the English phrase "Lolita Complex". Sometimes written as "roricon" or "rorikon" due to the inexact mapping between Japanese and English phonemes. This is the term used to describe the fetish/fascination some mature people have for underage girls. There is an entire industry in Japan devoted to providing legal but schoolgirl-themed pornography, taking advantage of the cute childlike appearance some Japanese women maintain well into their twenties.
Because the characters in anime are often young by convention, many fans think that a character can only be Lolicon if she is twelve or younger. Exceptions are granted if the other character in the relationship is a lot older.
One particular device used to skirt the boundaries of taste and legality is the exotic being (alien, creature of magic, robot or the like) which takes the form of an underage human girl, but is in fact for all other practical purposes an adult.
Another reason why lolicon is fetishized by people may be because some of them just view it as a substitute for their fetish for flat-chested, but otherwise well-developed, women.
Source: Wikipedia / TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32760.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2568" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-06">
<name>deity</name>
<description>Some religions say that there is a supernatural being called God. Other religions say there is more than one god. A supernatural being is also sometimes called a deity. Many religions believe that a deity created everything that exists. In most religions, a god is believed to be immortal (cannot die), and to have powers to control nature far beyond the powers of humans.</description>
<picurl>32415.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2679" parentid="2672" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Kyoto</name>
<description>Kyoto Prefecture is a prefecture of Japan in the Kansai region of the island of Honshu. The capital is the city of Kyoto.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214383.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2851" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>horror</name>
<description>The horror cinematic genre is characterized by the attempt to make the viewer experience dread, fear, terror, or horror. Often their plots involve the intrusion of an evil force, event or personage, sometimes of supernatural origin, on the mundane world and the consequences thereof.</description>
<picurl>214682.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2878" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>conspiracy</name>
<description>The conspiracy thriller (or paranoid thriller) is a sub-genre of the thriller which flourished in the 1970s in the US (and was echoed in other parts of the world) in the wake of a number of high-profile scandals and controversies (most notably Vietnam, the assassination of President Kennedy, Chappaquiddick and Watergate), and which exposed what many people regarded as the clandestine machinations and conspiracies beneath the orderly fabric of political life.
The protagonists of conspiracy thrillers are often journalists or amateur investigators who find themselves (often inadvertently) pulling on a small thread which unravels a vast conspiracy that ultimately goes "all the way to the top".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2897" parentid="2885" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>police</name>
<description>The police (civil servants) are the good guys in the battle against crime. Though they try hard, they are usually outclassed by super-criminals or criminal organizations in anime, requiring the help of special units or some lone hero.</description>
<picurl>238615.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2952" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-06">
<name>rotten world</name>
<description>A rotten world is a setting or situation where the jaded notion that "anything that can go wrong will go horribly wrong" almost always applies. Oppression, perpetual warfare, lawlessness, despair or other forms of mental instability, and other highly undesirable factors tend to be rampant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2979" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-18">
<name>mutilation</name>
<description>Mutilation is an act of physical injury that degrades the appearance or function of any living body. Some ethnic groups practice ritual mutilation, e.g. scarification, burning, flagellation(whipping), tattooing, or wheeling, as part of a rite of passage. In some cases, the term may apply to treatment of dead bodies, such as soldiers mutilated after they have been killed by an enemy. Maiming, or mutilation which involves the loss of, or incapacity to use, a bodily member, is and has been practised by many societies with various cultural and religious significances, and is also a customary form of physical punishment, especially applied on the principle of "an eye for an eye".
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3088" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-10-31">
<name>manipulation</name>
<description>When someone else is pulling the strings.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3092" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-03-02">
<name>important haircut</name>
<description>When a character cuts off his or her hair, it often symbolizes a rite of passage or bout of character growth. A princess striking out on an adventure, or a new recruit at boot camp, for instance. Hair is something that takes time and effort to grow, so parting with it voluntarily can be a powerful act.
This is particularly a big deal when women get haircuts. Yet in fiction, even an accidental hair slicing can leave a character with a surprisingly even cut.
In many religions (Western Christianity, Ancient Egyptian religion, and others) priests and/or monks cut/shave their hair. Roman Catholic nuns also tend to cut and mantain their hair short under their veils when they enter the nunneries. The cutting of one`s own hair is also a part of Buddhist mythology, specifically something done by Siddhartha himself early on in his path to enlightenment, so anime examples might draw from this as an allusion. There are also some cultures, including Native American and many Asians, where a person would cut his or her hair as an act of grief, disgrace, or even rebellion. In the Confucian tradition, hair (like the rest of your body) is considered a gift from your parents and may not be damaged without a very good reason. Furthermore, prisoners and psychiatric patients commonly have their heads shaved, often to prevent the spread of lice, but sometimes also as a demeaning measure.
Source: TVTRope</description>
<picurl>169641.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3276" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-02">
<name>plot twists</name>
<description>The plot and story of this anime may seem to be going along a quite predictable path, when suddenly there is a jarring unexpected twist in the plot, taking the viewer by surprise.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3278" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false">
<name>deception</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3581" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-23">
<name>tactics</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3597" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-26">
<name>mythology</name>
<description>The anime gets inspirations from many forms of mythologies (either Greek, Egyptian, Nord, etc.) to form its story and setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3759" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-11">
<name>teamwork</name>
<description>A cooperative effort by the members of a group or team to achieve a common goal.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3772" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-09-03">
<name>library</name>
<description>In a traditional sense, a library is a large collection of books, and can refer to the place in which the collection is housed.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3809" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-05-24">
<name>character driven</name>
<description>The main appeal of the show is the way the characters are portrayed and interact, focusing on dialogue, spending time together or getting to know each other. These anime are not "story-less" but story is secondary to character development and the characters themselves and what they experience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3842" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-31">
<name>TV censoring</name>
<description>The TV version is censored and later DVD/BD releases are uncensored, so the money-grubbing capitalists can make a couple more bucks at our expense.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3876" parentid="3597" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>folklore</name>
<description>Folklore, or simply Lore, are the traditions of a culture, subculture, or group, in the form of legends, music, proverbs, jokes, popular beliefs, fairy tales, stories, tall tales and customs. In usage, there is a continuum between folklore and mythology.
Folklore is generally divided into four areas of study: physical artifacts, transmissible entities and stories, culture and technologies, and behaviors and rituals.
[From Wikipedia]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3898" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-11-11">
<name>science and magic coexist</name>
<description>In this anime science and magic do not exclude each other. Magic here is actually very advanced, artefact- and/or ritual-based science.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3977" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-29">
<name>dialogue driven</name>
<description>A dialogue driven show has its story advanced by dialogue, with action being of much lower priority, and relies heavily on conversations between characters.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4030" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-04-13">
<name>mental cinema</name>
<description>The ability to imagine all kinds of things, as if they were real.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4085" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-02-17">
<name>unlikely duo</name>
<description>Comedy element: There is usually not only a difference in gender but also in appearance, character, and background concerning the main characters of this anime. Making it very unlikely for them to appear in the same context. Non-the-less they share the same adventure, as in "opposites attract".
These differences are exploited to come up with all sorts of wacky situations.
Examples: A demon-killer or Hero and the daughter of the Demon King. A girl from a normal family and a very intelligent and attractive boy from a very rich background (Shoujo). A very energetic outgoing girl and her very calm almost introverted best friend.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4096" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>gore</name>
<description>A Splatter film or Gore film is a sub-genre of horror film that deliberately focuses on graphic portrayals of gore and graphic violence. These films, through the use of special effects and excessive blood and guts, tend to display an overt interest in the vulnerability of the human body and the theatricality of its mutilation. Due to their willingness to portray images society might consider shocking, splatter films share some ideological grounds with the transgressive art movement. The term "splatter cinema" was coined by George A. Romero to describe his film Dawn of the Dead, though Dawn of the Dead is generally considered by critics to have higher aspirations, such as social commentary, than to be simply exploitative for its own sake.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>32491.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4131" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-05-11">
<name>cultural references</name>
<description>The plot of this anime shows signs of cultural references, these are often jokes that make reference to a certain custom, habit or history that is specifically attributed to that culture. Knowledge of the culture itself is needed in order to properly understand these jokes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4227" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-03">
<name>detailed landscapes</name>
<description>An amazing view of nature, of artificially sculpted landscapes (i.e. gardens), or of a cityscape.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4251" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-20">
<name>ensemble cast</name>
<description>A show with an ensemble cast focuses on a larger group of main characters in a single plot narrative; anime containing several segmented plot narratives (such as episodic or arc-based plots) are excluded. As such, it doesn`t really have a "main" or "lead" character; instead, every member of the central main character group plays an important part in the show`s grander scheme; no single character is more important or prominent than the others (equality of importance). Further, subplots (if any) lead by each character in the ensemble have equal weighting in importance (or lack of weight).

* In a show where no single main character is more important or prominent than the others, 4+ main characters is almost always an ensemble cast.
* A show with 3 main characters of equal importance is likely also an ensemble cast; equality of importance must be considered carefully.
* A show with 2 main characters of equal importance is generally not an ensemble cast situation; however, on an exception basis where neither main character is considered an antagonist, a 2-main-character anime may be considered an ensemble (e.g. http://anidb.net/a11829 [Kimi no Na wa.]).

Pictured: http://anidb.net/a9043 [K (anime)]</description>
<picurl>94914.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4274" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-02-01">
<name>hidden agenda</name>
<description>Someone or some organization/government/etc. is misrepresenting themselves by doing/saying one thing while hoping/striving for something else.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4340" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-09-26">
<name>suicide</name>
<description>One or several characters in this anime commit suicide.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4455" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>dysfunctional family</name>
<description>When the nuclear family (Mother, Father and child(ren)) goes boom due to conflicts between family members, sometimes resulting in the breakup of the family or even violence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4479" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-03">
<name>sense of foreboding</name>
<description>The anime starts off quietly, everything seems to be fine, but from episode to episode the signs that something ominous is about to happen increase. E.g. a typical mystery setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4499" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-07-28">
<name>some weird shit goin` on</name>
<description>Scenes of this show point to insanely strange events which seem to be taking place; throughout its episodes, the show may or may not explain what is going on. Either way, many viewers will find that a succinct and accurate way to describe the show is "WTF?", and the show`s explanations (or lack thereof) to the events will often be subject of heated debate.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4522" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>social commentary</name>
<description>Social commentary is the act of rebelling against an individual, or a group of people by rhetorical means. This is most often done with the idea of implementing or promoting change by informing the general populace about a given problem and appealing to people’s sense of justice. (Source: Wikipedia)&#13;
&#13;
Since this is anime, usually, the mores of Japan and the Japanese society are scrutinised, but not restricted to that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4537" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-15">
<name>time skip</name>
<description>The plot features at least one skip or jump in time.
Example: A skip from the present into the past, or time skips in increments, e.g. every hour there is a time skip by a day.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4646" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-31">
<name>hospital</name>
<description>The place or building where sick people receive medical treatment in the hopes of curing their sickness. Also a dandy setting for creepy happenings in anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4663" parentid="2605" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-31">
<name>tone changes</name>
<description>The anime switches quickly, often rather drastically between different moods or tones, sometimes even on the same scene.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6005" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-10-17">
<name>battle of wits</name>
<description>There is some intellectual battle between the characters. They each might attempt to discern what the other knows and/or could be planning. Then, rather than simply relying on the use of raw power, try to deduce an effective strategy to foil their opponent(s). The battle of wits can be in the center of the intrigue or just a side story.
Examples: Death Note, Code Geass</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6018" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-27">
<name>predominantly adult cast</name>
<description>This show features mostly adults. That means children and teenagers are relatively rare and unlikely to hold significance to the plot.
That is a rare trait in anime, as most shows spin around children or teenagers.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6054" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-07-25">
<name>car crash</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6062" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-04-05">
<name>heroic sacrifice</name>
<description>"In order to save the many, the few will need to sacrifice their lives..." or so this character may think. 
In a seemingly hopeless situation, against impossible odds, the character does not choose the path of the coward and run, he or she chooses to bravely face the enemy, fully aware that this will mean death.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6070" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-15">
<name>mystery</name>
<description>The mystery film is a sub-genre of the more general category of crime film. It focuses on the efforts of the detective, private investigator or amateur sleuth to solve the mysterious circumstances of a crime by means of clues, investigation, and clever deduction. (Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6072" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-25">
<name>just as planned</name>
<description>A term usually used to describe a situation, where a seemingly smart and cunning villain sets up a plan that seems grand and impressive, but is actually long winding, ridiculous, and convoluted. And all of that just to trick his opponent(s), like the hero or anybody else, into doing things exactly as he planned. Suffice to say that the villain could have reached his goal by much shorter and easier means, it just wouldn`t seem as awesome anymore.
The phrase is also known as the original Japanese "keikaku doori" where keikaku stands translated for "plan" or "schedule", and doori for "in accordance with ..." or "following ...".
The phrase is a reference to http://anidb.net/ch301 [Yagami Light] from http://anidb.net/a4563 [Death Note], and his love for plans.</description>
<picurl>211219.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6186" parentid="6185" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-29">
<name>spring</name>
<description>During spring, the axis of the Earth is increasing its tilt relative to the Sun, and the length of daylight rapidly increases for the relevant hemisphere. The hemisphere begins to warm significantly causing new plant growth to spring forth, giving the season its name. Snow, if a normal part of winter, begins to melt, and streams swell with runoff. Frosts, if a normal part of winter, become less severe. In climates that have no snow and rare frosts, the air and ground temperatures increase more rapidly. Many flowering plants bloom this time of year, in a long succession sometimes beginning when snow is still on the ground, continuing into early summer. In normally snowless areas spring may begin as early as February (Northern Hemisphere) heralded by the blooming of deciduous magnolias, cherries and quince, or August (Southern Hemisphere) in the same way. Many temperate areas have a dry spring, and wet autumn (fall), which brings about flowering in this season more consistent with the need for water as well as warmth. Subarctic areas may not experience spring at all until May or even June.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>161969.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="106549" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-02-23">
<rating votes="4">8.85</rating>
<name>Nanase Karin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240512.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28602" picture="131381.jpg">Uesaka Sumire</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106550" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-03-31">
<name>Terada Tokunosuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Terada Tokunosuke is a detective who works at the Makurazaka Police Station and is Saki`s superior.</description>
<picture>240513.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="373" picture="191382.jpg">Hamada Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106551" type="main character in" update="2020-04-01">
<rating votes="41">5.41</rating>
<name>Iwanaga Kotoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240508.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="41766" picture="242448.jpg">Kitou Akari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106552" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-28">
<rating votes="22">8.28</rating>
<name>Yumihara Saki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240510.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="304" picture="17139.jpg">Fukuen Misato</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106553" type="main character in" update="2019-10-28">
<rating votes="2">8.16</rating>
<name>Sakuragawa Kurou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240509.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="255" picture="40713.jpg">Miyano Mamoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106554" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-28">
<rating votes="3">9.13</rating>
<name>Koujin Nanase</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240511.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="107938" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-01-11">
<rating votes="3">7.69</rating>
<name>Sakuragawa Rikka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>243178.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1631" picture="243202.jpg">Sako Mayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107939" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Kappa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>243179.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16987" picture="86303.jpg">Shimoyama Yoshimitsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107940" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Ochimusha</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>243180.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16987" picture="86303.jpg">Shimoyama Yoshimitsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107941" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Komainu (Shiro)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>243181.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="57307" picture="229629.jpg">Motoyama Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107942" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Komainu (Kuro)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>243182.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="54643" picture="216300.jpg">Hanawa Manami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107943" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Bakedanuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>243183.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23683" picture="65780.jpg">Gotou Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107944" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Ushi no Ayakashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>243184.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16987" picture="86303.jpg">Shimoyama Yoshimitsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107945" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Nushi no Orochi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>243185.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="689" picture="170354.jpg">Miyata Kouki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107946" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Yosuzume</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>243186.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29667" picture="223460.jpg">Maeda Rena</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107947" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Yama no Ayakashi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>243187.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="57307" picture="229629.jpg">Motoyama Kaori</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="29667" picture="223460.jpg">Maeda Rena</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107948" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Youko</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>243188.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="54643" picture="216300.jpg">Hanawa Manami</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="57307" picture="229629.jpg">Motoyama Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107949" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Gashadokuro</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>243189.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="107950" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Kodama no Gen`ichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>243191.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="190" picture="186145.jpg">Tobita Nobuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107951" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Kudan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>243192.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="107953" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Bakeneko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>243194.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="57030" picture="228211.jpg">Ominami Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107954" type="appears in" update="2020-01-11">
<name>Ittan Momen</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>243199.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="108149" type="appears in" update="2020-02-02">
<name>Tanio Aoi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244039.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="54643" picture="216300.jpg">Hanawa Manami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108243" type="appears in" update="2020-02-02">
<rating votes="1">7.57</rating>
<name>Iwanaga Kotoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244216.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="108438" type="appears in" update="2020-02-23">
<name>Shachou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244594.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43539" picture="214341.jpg">Echigoya Kousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108439" type="appears in" update="2020-02-23">
<name>Manager</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244595.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="56192" picture="223829.jpg">Nakamura Genta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108440" type="appears in" update="2020-02-23">
<name>Yuurei Shougakusei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244596.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="54643" picture="216300.jpg">Hanawa Manami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108441" type="appears in" update="2020-02-23">
<name>Roujin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244597.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23683" picture="65780.jpg">Gotou Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108442" type="appears in" update="2020-04-11">
<name>Karin no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>246013.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="41130" picture="223456.jpg">Torashima Takaaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108443" type="appears in" update="2020-02-23">
<name>Shounen Kurou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244599.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="57307" picture="229629.jpg">Motoyama Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108444" type="appears in" update="2020-04-11">
<name>Shoujo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68798.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="29667" picture="223460.jpg">Maeda Rena</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108445" type="appears in" update="2020-02-23">
<name>Sobo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244601.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="57030" picture="228211.jpg">Ominami Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108446" type="appears in" update="2020-02-23">
<name>Jibakurei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244602.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23683" picture="65780.jpg">Gotou Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109314" type="appears in" update="2020-04-11">
<name>Nanase Hatsumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>246014.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="26751" picture="73236.jpg">Kitahara Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109315" type="appears in" update="2020-04-11">
<name>Shoujo A</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>246015.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38295" picture="222841.jpg">Yamashita Nanami</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="222775" update="2019-10-19">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-06-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">TVアニメ「虚構推理」第1弾PV</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 01 (1:15)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">TV Anime "Kyokou Suiri" Dai 1 Dan PV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="222776" update="2019-10-19">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-10-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">TVアニメ「虚構推理」第2弾PV</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 02 (1:12)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">TV Anime "Kyokou Suiri" Dai 2 Dan PV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225716" update="2020-01-24">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-01-12</airdate>
<rating votes="9">8.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">一眼一足</title>
<title xml:lang="en">One Eye, One Leg</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un œil, une jambe</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">عينٌ وساق</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ichigan Hitoashi</title>
<summary>Iwanaga Kotoko experiences love at first sight with Sakuragawa Kuro, who she happened to randomly bump into at the hospital. Two years later, Kotoko seizes her chance and asks Kuro to date her with marriage in mind. Kuro tells her about when he and his ex, Saki, broke up, but Kotoko seemed to already be aware of the situation. Bake-danuki then appears before Kotoko, telling them that the barrier around the library had been broken, and...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792620</identifier>
<identifier>inspectre</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="225717" update="2020-01-24">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-01-19</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヌシの大蛇は聞いていた</title>
<title xml:lang="en">What the Guardian Serpent Heard</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le seigneur boa a entendu</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">ما سمعه الأفعى الحارس</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nushi no Daija wa Kiite Ita</title>
<summary>Kotoko receives a request for help from a giant snake, who is the guardian spirit of Tsukuna Swamp. It appears that a murderer named Tanio Aoi disposed of a body in the snake’s swamp, but there’s something that’s just not sitting right with the snake. After learning about Kuro’s powers, Kotoko asks Kuro to accompany her on this journey, but Kuro declines for a certain reason...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792621</identifier>
<identifier>inspectre</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="225718" update="2020-02-27">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-01-26</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">鋼人の噂</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Rumors of the Steel Lady</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La rumeur de la fille d’acier</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">إشاعات سيدة الفولاذ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koujin no Uwasa</title>
<summary>Kotoko is asked why a suspect had thrown a dead body into the Guardian’s swamp and she starts constructing a story. This ends up being a rather tragic tale about Tanio Aoi filled with love and regret that the Guardian is also shocked to hear. Two years later, random acts of violence were happening in Makurazaka City. The suspect seems to be the ghost of the former idol, Nanase Karin...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792622</identifier>
<identifier>inspectre</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="225719" update="2020-02-27">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-02-02</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アイドルは鉄骨に死す</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Idol Dies by Steel Beam</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L’idole tombée sous le métal</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">فنانة تموت بدعامة فولاذية</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Idol wa Tekkou ni Shisu</title>
<summary>Kotoko arrived in Makurazaka City to take care of the incidents with Steel Lady Nanase and happens to run into Saki, who had become a police officer. Saki decides to research Nanase Karin a bit more and learns that the former idol had died a mysterious death. In order to defeat Steel Lady Nanase, they would need more details, but...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792623</identifier>
<identifier>inspectre</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="225887" update="2020-01-04">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2020-01-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">TVアニメ「虚構推理」第3弾PV</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 03 (1:18)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">TV Anime "Kyokou Suiri" Dai 3 Dan PV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225975" update="2020-02-10">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-11-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">-ミニアニメ01- ズバッと解決☆琴子ちゃん ~相談者: 鴨川のカッパ~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mini Anime 01: Rapid Problem Solving by Kotoko-chan - Kappa from Kamogawa</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mini Anime 01: Supatto Kaiketsu Kotoko-chan - Soudansha: Kamogawa no Kappa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225976" update="2020-01-11">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2019-11-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">-ミニアニメ02- よく分かる! あやかし解説~カッパ編~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mini Anime 02: Ayakashi Explained - Kappa</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mini Anime 02: Yoku Wakaru! Ayakashi Kaisetsu - Kappa Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225977" update="2020-02-10">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-11-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">-ミニアニメ03- ズバッと解決☆琴子ちゃん ~相談者: 鴨川のカッパ②~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mini Anime 03: Rapid Problem Solving by Kotoko-chan - Kappa from Kamogawa (2)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mini Anime 03: Supatto Kaiketsu Kotoko-chan - Soudansha: Kamokawa no Kappa (2)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225978" update="2020-01-11">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2019-11-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">-ミニアニメ04- よく分かる! あやかし解説~幽霊編~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mini Anime 04 Ayakashi Explained - Ghost</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mini Anime 04: Yoku Wakaru! Ayakashi Kaisetsu - Yuurei Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225979" update="2020-02-10">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-11-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">-ミニアニメ05- ズバッと解決☆琴子ちゃん ~相談者: 落ち武者~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mini Anime 05: Rapid Problem Solving by Kotoko-chan - Ochimusha</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mini Anime 05: Supatto Kaiketsu Kotoko-chan - Soudansha: Ochimusha</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225980" update="2020-02-10">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-12-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">-ミニアニメ06- よく分かる! あやかし解説~化け狸編~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mini Anime 06 Ayakashi Explained - Bakedanuki</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mini Anime 06: Yoku Wakaru! Ayakashi Kaisetsu - Bakedanuki Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225981" update="2020-02-10">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-12-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">-ミニアニメ07- ズバッと解決☆琴子ちゃん ~相談者: 真倉坂市在住Sさん~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mini Anime 07: Rapid Problem Solving by Kotoko-chan - S-san from Makurazaka</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mini Anime 07: Supatto Kaiketsu Kotoko-chan - Soudansha: Makurazaka-shi Zaijuu S-san</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225982" update="2020-02-10">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-12-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">-ミニアニメ08- よく分かる! あやかし解説~がしゃどくろ編~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mini Anime 08: Ayakashi Explained - Gashadokuro</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mini Anime 08: Yoku Wakaru! Ayakashi Kaisetsu -Gashadokuro Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225983" update="2020-02-10">
<epno type="2">S9</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-12-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">-ミニアニメ09- 琴子の乙女道~さしすせそ編~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mini Anime 09: Kotoko`s Maiden Road - SaShiSuSeSo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mini Anime 09: Kotoko no Otomedou - Sashisuseso Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225984" update="2020-01-11">
<epno type="2">S10</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2019-12-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">-ミニアニメ10- よく分かる! あやかし解説~木魂編~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mini Anime 10: Ayakashi Explained - Kodama</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mini Anime 10: Yoku Wakaru! Ayakashi Kaisetsu - Kodama Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225985" update="2020-02-10">
<epno type="2">S11</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-12-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">-ミニアニメ11- ズバッと解決☆琴子ちゃん ~相談者: 木魂の源一郎さん~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mini Anime 11: Rapid Problem Solving by Kotoko-chan - Gen`ichirou the Kodama</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mini Anime 11: Supatto Kaiketsu Kotoko-chan - Soudansha: Kodama no Gen`ichirou-san</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225986" update="2020-01-11">
<epno type="2">S12</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2019-12-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">-ミニアニメ12- 明るい家族計画 四十八手~寄り添い編~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mini Anime 12: Bright Family Plan 48 Moves - Yorisoi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mini Anime 12: Akarui Kazoku Keikaku Shijuuhatte - Yorisoi Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225987" update="2020-01-11">
<epno type="2">S13</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2019-12-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">-ミニアニメ13- 琴子の乙女道~NG行為編~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mini Anime 13: Kotoko`s Maiden Road - NG Acts</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mini Anime 13: Kotoko no Otomedou - NG Koui Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225988" update="2020-02-10">
<epno type="2">S14</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-12-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">-ミニアニメ14- よく分かる! あやかし解説~口裂け女編~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mini Anime 14: Ayakashi Explained - Kuchisake-onna</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mini Anime 14: Yoku Wakaru! Ayakashi Kaisetsu - Kuchisake-onna Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225989" update="2020-01-11">
<epno type="2">S15</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2019-12-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">-ミニアニメ15- ズバッと解決☆琴子ちゃん ~相談者: 真倉坂市在住Tさん~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mini Anime 15: Rapid Problem Solving by Kotoko-chan - T-san from Makurazaka</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mini Anime 15: Supatto Kaiketsu Kotoko-chan - Soudansha: Makurazaka-shi Zaijuu T-san</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225990" update="2020-01-11">
<epno type="2">S16</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2019-12-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">-ミニアニメ16- 明るい家族計画 四十八手~岩清水編~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mini Anime 16: Bright Family Plan 48 Moves - Iwashimizu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mini Anime 16: Akarui Kazoku Keikaku Shijuuhatte - Iwashimizu Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225991" update="2020-01-11">
<epno type="2">S17</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2019-12-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">-ミニアニメ17- 琴子の乙女道~モテファッション編~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mini Anime 17: Kotoko`s Maiden Road - Popular Fashion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mini Anime 17: Kotoko no Otomedou - Mote Fashion Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225992" update="2020-02-10">
<epno type="2">S18</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-12-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">-ミニアニメ18- よく分かる! あやかし解説~くだん編~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mini Anime 18: Ayakashi Explained - Kudan</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mini Anime 18: Yoku Wakaru! Ayakashi Kaisetsu - Kudan Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225993" update="2020-01-11">
<epno type="2">S19</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2019-12-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">-ミニアニメ19- ズバッと解決☆琴子ちゃん ~相談者: 大学生K.Sさん~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mini Anime 19: Rapid Problem Solving by Kotoko-chan - University Student K.S-san</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mini Anime 19: Supatto Kaiketsu Kotoko-chan - Soudansha: Daigakusei K.S-san</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225994" update="2020-01-11">
<epno type="2">S20</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2019-12-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">-ミニアニメ20- 明るい家族計画 四十八手~窓の月編~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mini Anime 20: Bright Family Plan 48 Moves - Mado no Tsuki</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mini Anime 20: Akarui Kazoku Keikaku Shijuuhatte - Mado no Tsuki Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225995" update="2020-02-10">
<epno type="2">S21</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-12-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">-ミニアニメ21- 琴子の乙女道~必須アイテム編~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mini Anime 21: Kotoko`s Maiden Road - Indispensable Items</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mini Anime 21: Kotoko no Otomedou - Hissu Item Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225996" update="2020-02-10">
<epno type="2">S22</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-12-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">-ミニアニメ22- よく分かる! あやかし解説~人魚編~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mini Anime 22: Ayakashi Explained - Mermaid</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mini Anime 22: Yoku Wakaru! Ayakashi Kaisetsu - Ningyo Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225997" update="2020-01-11">
<epno type="2">S23</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2020-01-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">-ミニアニメ23- ズバッと解決☆琴子ちゃん ~相談者: グラビアアイドルNさん~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mini Anime 23: Rapid Problem Solving by Kotoko-chan - Gravure Idol N-san</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mini Anime 23: Supatto Kaiketsu Kotoko-chan - Soudansha: Gravure Idol N-san</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225998" update="2020-01-11">
<epno type="2">S24</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2020-01-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">-ミニアニメ24- 明るい家族計画 四十八手~しがらみ編~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mini Anime 24: Bright Family Plan 48 Moves - Shigarami</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mini Anime 24: Akarui Kazoku Keikaku Shijuuhatte - Shigarami Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225999" update="2020-02-10">
<epno type="2">S25</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2020-01-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">-ミニアニメ25- 琴子の乙女道~モテセリフ編~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mini Anime 25: Kotoko`s Maiden Road - Popular Words</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mini Anime 25: Kotoko no Otomedou - Mote Serifu Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="226000" update="2020-02-10">
<epno type="2">S26</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2020-01-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">-ミニアニメ26 -よく分かる! あやかし解説~狛犬編~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mini Anime 26: Ayakashi Explained - Komainu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mini Anime 26: Yoku Wakaru! Ayakashi Kaisetsu - Komainu Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="226001" update="2020-02-10">
<epno type="2">S27</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2020-01-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">-ミニアニメ27- ズバッと解決☆琴子ちゃん ~相談者: 化け狸さん~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mini Anime 27: Rapid Problem Solving by Kotoko-chan - Bakedanuki-san</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mini Anime 27: Supatto Kaiketsu Kotoko-chan - Soudansha: Bakedanuki-san</title>
</episode>
<episode id="226002" update="2020-01-11">
<epno type="2">S28</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2020-01-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">-ミニアニメ28- 明るい家族計画 四十八手~抱き地蔵編~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mini Anime 28: Bright Family Plan 48 Moves - Dakijizou</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mini Anime 28: Akarui Kazoku Keikaku Shijuuhatte - Daki Jizou Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="226003" update="2020-02-10">
<epno type="2">S29</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2020-01-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">-ミニアニメ29- 琴子の乙女道~ヘアスタイル編~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mini Anime 29: Kotoko`s Maiden Road - Hairstyle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mini Anime 29: Kotoko no Otomedou - Hair Style Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="226004" update="2020-02-10">
<epno type="2">S30</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2020-01-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">-ミニアニメ30- よく分かる! あやかし解説~大蛇編~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mini Anime 30: Ayakashi Explained - Daija</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mini Anime 30: Yoku Wakaru! Ayakashi Kaisetsu - Orochi Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="226370" update="2020-02-10">
<epno type="2">S32</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2020-01-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">虚構占い 1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fabricated Divination 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyokou Uranai 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="226371" update="2020-02-10">
<epno type="2">S33</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2020-01-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">虚構占い 2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fabricated Divination 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyokou Uranai 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="226394" update="2020-03-05">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-02-09</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">想像力の怪物</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Monster of the Imagination</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le monstre de l’imagination</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">وحش من الخيال</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Souzouryoku no Kaibutsu</title>
<summary>Kotoko happens to spot a man fighting with Steel Lady Nanase. She gets closer and realizes that it was actually Kuro that was struggling in this battle. Saki then also joins in and after talking with her, Kotoko remembers the story about Kuro when he was younger that he told her about. Kotoko realizes they will need a special method to defeat Steel Lady Nanase because she is not an ordinary spectre...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792624</identifier>
<identifier>inspectre</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="226395" update="2020-03-05">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-02-16</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">合理的な虚構</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Logical Fiction</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Fiction logique</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">خيال منطقي</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gouriteki na Kyokou</title>
<summary>Kotoko realizes that Steel Lady Nanase is a spectre that was born from her own wiki site. In order to defeat Steel Lady Nanase, who is made up of people’s imaginations, she has to come up with a story that’s more interesting than Steel Lady Nanase’s. Kotoko ends up asking Saki for help to defeat Steel Lady Nanase. She then meets up with a ghost that is at the site where Nanase Karin died, who also happened to see her die...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792625</identifier>
<identifier>inspectre</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="226396" update="2020-03-05">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-02-23</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">鋼人攻略戦準備</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Preparing to Conquer the Steel Lady</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Plan de capture de la fille d’acier</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">الاستعداد لقهر سيدة الفولاذ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koujin Kouryaku Ikusa Junbi</title>
<summary>Detective Terada is killed by Steel Lady Nanase. The Internet goes crazy about the fact that Steel Lady Nanase killing a person. Kotoko and Kuro discuss the matter and figure out the person who is truly behind all of this. So that there are no more victims, Kotoko decides to finish off Steel Lady Nanase that night.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792626</identifier>
<identifier>inspectre</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="226397" update="2020-03-05">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-03-01</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">虚構を紡ぐ者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">She Who Spins Fiction</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Celle qui tisse l’imagination</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">تلك التي تدير الخيال</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyokou o Tsumugu Mono</title>
<summary>Saki remembers the first time she met Kuro’s cousin, Sakuragawa Rikka. Saki had heard that Rikka had passed, and tries to get more information out of Kotoko. Meanwhile, the forums on the wiki site become rather active again, making Steel Lady Nanase’s presence even stronger...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792627</identifier>
<identifier>inspectre</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="226814" update="2020-02-10">
<epno type="2">S34</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2020-01-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">虚構占い 3</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fabricated Divination 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyokou Uranai 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="226815" update="2020-02-10">
<epno type="2">S35</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2020-02-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">虚構占い 4</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fabricated Divination 4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyokou Uranai 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="226816" update="2020-02-10">
<epno type="2">S31</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2020-02-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">-ミニアニメ31- ズバッと解決☆琴子ちゃん ~相談者: 桜川九郎~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mini Anime 31: Rapid Problem Solving by Kotoko-chan - Sakuragawa Kurou</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mini Anime 31: Supatto Kaiketsu Kotoko-chan - Soudansha: Sakuragawa Kurou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="227107" update="2020-03-24">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-03-08</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">鋼人七瀬攻略議会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Committee to Conquer Steel Lady Nanase</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L’assemblée anti-Nanase la fille d’acier</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">لجنة قهر سيدة الفولاذ ناناسي</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koujin Nanase Kouryaku Gikai</title>
<summary>Everything is finally in place, and the committee to conquer Steel Lady Nanase is now in session. Does Steel Lady Nanase actually exist? Perhaps she’s just a made up urban legend. A battle between the truth and lies begins to figure out her existence. Kotoko gets on her PC and starts posting her own deductions...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792628</identifier>
<identifier>inspectre</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="227108" update="2020-03-24">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-03-15</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">虚構争奪</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dueling Fictions</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Duel de fictions</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">مبارزة الخيالات</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyokou Soudatsu</title>
<summary>Just as it looked like the site readers accepted Kotoko’s solution, it ends up getting shot down. However, Kotoko had another solution ready. In order to defeat Steel Lady Nanase, she unleashes a second and third solution, but Sakuragawa Rikka and Steel Lady Nanase continue to get in her way. Will they be able to vanquish the ghost?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792629</identifier>
<identifier>inspectre</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="227109" update="2020-03-24">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-03-22</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">最後の虚構</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Ultimate Fiction</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Fiction ultime</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">الخيال المطلق</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saigo no Kyokou</title>
<summary>Kotoko came up with three solutions, but they all got shot down. Kuro keeps trying to grasp the future where they can defeat Steel Lady Nanase, but Rikka made it disappear once again. But Kotoko wasn’t done yet. Steel Lady Nanase is not a ghost. What is Kotoko’s 4th solution that may finally put an end to Steel Lady Nanase’s existence once and for all?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792630</identifier>
<identifier>inspectre</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="227110" update="2020-04-05">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-03-29</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">秩序を守る者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">She Who Defends Order</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le défenseur de l’ordre</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">تلك التي تحمي النظام</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chitsujo o Mamoru Mono</title>
<summary>Yokai, ayakashi, spectres, demons, mononoke, and ghosts... Everything has order, and you must never go against the order. Kotoko`s fourth solution is accepted by the users on the wiki site and Kuro is able to give the final blow to Steel Lady Nanase. Will that be enough to finish her off?! And what exactly was Rikka`s motive?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792631</identifier>
<identifier>inspectre</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="227121" update="2020-02-23">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2020-01-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="227122" update="2020-02-23">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2020-01-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
