<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="14695" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2019-07-08</startdate>
<enddate>2019-09-23</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Kawaikereba Hentai demo Suki ni Natte Kuremasu ka?</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Would you love a pervert as long as she`s cute?</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="short">変好き</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">hensuki</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">可愛ければ変態でも好きになってくれますか?</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Hensuki: Are You Willing to Fall in Love With a Pervert, As Long As She`s a Cutie?</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">只要长得可爱，即使是变态你也喜欢吗？</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="7622" approval="4" total="5">MM!</anime>
</similaranime>
<url>https://hensuki.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="57479" type="Original Work">Hanama Tomo</name>
<name id="54218" type="Animation Work">Geek Toys</name>
<name id="30803" type="Character Design">Itou Yousuke</name>
<name id="23021" type="Series Composition">Yamashita Ken`ichi</name>
<name id="6529" type="Direction">Imazaki Itsuki</name>
<name id="30803" type="Chief Animation Direction">Itou Yousuke</name>
<name id="9431" type="Music">Sakai Youichi</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a light novel series by http://anidb.net/cr57479 [Hanama Tomo].
Once upon a time, Cinderella left her panties in a boy`s locker...wait, what?! http://anidb.net/ch101593 [Kiryuu Keiki] receives a mysterious love letter, that has no name, but includes a pair of white undies. Curious to find this panty-leaving-Cinderella, his investigation leads him to discover that every candidate is...a total pervert! Surrounded by perversion he still has one important question to answer: who`s the perfect fit?
Source: funimation</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="451">3.73</permanent>
<temporary count="456">5.97</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>233796.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22018</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>39326</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://hensuki.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Hensuki:_Are_you_willing_to_fall_in_love_with_a_pervert,_as_long_as_she’s_a_cutie%3F</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>可愛ければ変態でも好きになってくれますか%3F</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5349</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>367319</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21933</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>hensuki_anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="26">
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=FwWJqhQZEAQ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B07VG2QXZJ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2654" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-13">
<name>medium awareness</name>
<description>Medium awareness is the situational and generally temporary awareness characters in works of fiction have and display of the very fact that they are characters in works of fiction. For example, they may comment about the background music, quip about the script or narration, complain about the roles given to them by the writer or their lack of screen time, see the subtitles that appear on screen, inform the audience about the arrival of the commercial break, and even use medium effects as tools. The most common form of medium awareness is known as breaking the fourth wall, in which characters speak directly to the audience, either to it as a whole or to specific members of it. The "fourth wall" is the imaginary "wall" at the front of the stage of a proscenium theatre through which the audience sees the play; it is a metaphor for the boundary between what happens inside the work, to the characters, and outside it, to the audience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2816" parentid="2856" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>sexual fantasies</name>
<description>One or more characters in this anime let their imaginations run wild thinking about another character.
Yes, they are thinking about sex, and in an ecchi anime these thoughts are often perverted, leading to a nosebleed. But it may also be romanticising simply being husband and wife, and everything that implies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2821" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>sudden naked girl appearance</name>
<description>A character or group of characters are simply minding their own business, when suddenly, a naked girl appears. It does not matter how or why, but a naked someone is there. Sometimes the naked girl is not happy about this. 
Usually this is a fanservice element, but not always.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2822" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-06">
<name>skirt flipping</name>
<description>Naughty characters — usually boys — flip the skirts of female protagonists to ascertain what panties they are wearing (also see Pantsu category).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2845" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-04-30">
<name>blackmail</name>
<description>In general usage, blackmail is a crime involving unjustified threats against a person or organization in order to make a gain or harm or cause material loss to them unless a demand is met. It may be considered similar to or a form of extortion, although some jurisdictions will consider them as separate crimes. Most often, blackmail involves the threat of revealing some secret to a given third party, which may be another person, a rival organization, or a state institution such as the police, or to the general public. In anime and related media, and more specifically in pornographic works, blackmail is also a device used to coerce people, generally female and often schoolgirls, into having sex with another or others; in such cases, it may be considered similar to or a form of rape.</description>
<picurl>136031.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3190" parentid="6083" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-28">
<name>master-slave relation</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3809" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-05-24">
<name>character driven</name>
<description>The main appeal of the show is the way the characters are portrayed and interact, focusing on dialogue, spending time together or getting to know each other. These anime are not "story-less" but story is secondary to character development and the characters themselves and what they experience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4055" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>facial distortion</name>
<description>The characters face are exaggerated into a misshape, deformed, and almost warped. Used as comedy element to express extreme mood swings.
Differing from "http://anidb.net/t2652 [Super Deformed]", here only the face changes to an extreme degree, not the whole body of the protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4228" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-11-09">
<name>subtle OP ED sequence change</name>
<description>A (small) part of the opening or ending sequence changes after a certain episode, usually to reflect a plot milestone.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4761" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-02-11">
<name>love letter</name>
<description>One of the characters in the anime receives a love letter, usually stashed away in their school shoe locker. Or in other cases a girl might directly give the love letter to the boy she loves.
Plot device to further the relationship between characters, may also be used as comedic element creating awkward situations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4860" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false">
<name>lost love</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5518" parentid="7199" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-03">
<name>flat chest jokes</name>
<description>Jokes about the (supposedly or actually) flat chest of a character.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6083" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>master-servant relationship</name>
<description>To some genres, this would suggest a genuine pairing where one person exists to serve another person, such as in some action/dramas where the pair becomes united by destiny as partners — fighting or battles between different pairs/partners will usually be a dominant part of the story.
In other genres, this suggests a relationship where one person may be occupied as or even forcefully treated as a servant or slave to the other who designates themself the master — these services usually apply anywhere from tsundere/romantic-comedies to ecchi or to the more extreme in hentai.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7199" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-12">
<name>sexual humour</name>
<description>Sexual humour is prevalent in this anime. It often involves cheeky or crude sexual language, with innuendos and jokes about the female or male genitalia. Often, such anime also have http://anidb.net/t2856 [ecchi] elements to them.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="101593" type="main character in" update="2019-09-18">
<rating votes="4">3.30</rating>
<name>Kiryuu Keiki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>231661.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="175" picture="167565.jpg">Shimono Hiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101594" type="main character in" update="2019-03-24">
<rating votes="19">7.71</rating>
<name>Tokihara Sayuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>231667.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="590" picture="242467.jpg">Taketatsu Ayana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101595" type="main character in" update="2019-03-24">
<rating votes="8">5.72</rating>
<name>Koga Yuika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>231663.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="430" picture="246278.jpg">Hidaka Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101596" type="main character in" update="2019-09-18">
<rating votes="13">7.22</rating>
<name>Kiryuu Mizuha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>231668.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43552" picture="179144.jpg">Hondo Kaede</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101597" type="main character in" update="2019-03-24">
<rating votes="9">7.73</rating>
<name>Nanjou Mao</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>231662.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5886" picture="30429.jpg">Nomizu Iori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101598" type="main character in" update="2019-03-24">
<rating votes="3">4.56</rating>
<name>Akiyama Shouma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>231664.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23393" picture="158026.jpg">Koumoto Keisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102600" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-06-10">
<rating votes="9">7.32</rating>
<name>Fujimoto Ayano</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>234622.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="46283" picture="235990.jpg">Haruno Anzu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102601" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-06-10">
<rating votes="10">6.53</rating>
<name>Ootori Koharu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>234621.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30554" picture="81681.jpg">Oohashi Ayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104245" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-09-26">
<rating votes="3">3.18</rating>
<name>Okita-sensei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238798.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20025" picture="132938.jpg">Mimori Suzuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105592" type="appears in" update="2019-09-26">
<rating votes="1">5.68</rating>
<name>Hoken no Sensei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238799.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="59131" picture="240746.jpg">Mizuno Eriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105593" type="appears in" update="2019-09-26">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Tenshi Keiki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238802.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40199" picture="156640.jpg">Nitta Hiyori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105594" type="appears in" update="2019-09-26">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Akuma Keiki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238801.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="48852" picture="225071.jpg">Kohara Konomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105595" type="appears in" update="2019-09-26">
<rating votes="1">5.68</rating>
<name>Keiki no Sofu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238803.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17632" picture="170934.jpg">Hirota Minoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105596" type="appears in" update="2019-09-26">
<rating votes="1">7.63</rating>
<name>Youshou no Keiki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238804.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43794" picture="177499.jpg">Kingyo Wakana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105597" type="appears in" update="2019-09-26">
<rating votes="1">7.63</rating>
<name>Mizuha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238805.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43552" picture="179144.jpg">Hondo Kaede</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="217951" update="2019-07-08">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-07-08</airdate>
<rating votes="11">3.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">パンツを落としたシンデレラ!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cinderella Dropped Her Panties?!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Cendrillon a perdu sa culotte ?!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Pantsu o Otoshita Cinderella!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="217952" update="2019-07-08">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-07-15</airdate>
<rating votes="8">4.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">優柔不断な王子様!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Indecisive Prince?!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un prince indécis ?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuujuufudan na Ouji-sama!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="217953" update="2019-07-08">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-07-22</airdate>
<rating votes="8">4.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">恥ずかしがりやのシンデレラ!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cinderella Is Shy?!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une Cendrillon timide ?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hazukashigariya no Cinderella!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="217954" update="2019-07-08">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-07-29</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">素直になれないシンデレラ!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cinderella Can`t Come Out?!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une Cendrillon qui manque de franchise ?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sunao ni Narenai Cinderella!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="218273" update="2019-06-25">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-02-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">『可愛ければ変態でも好きになってくれますか?』TVアニメ化記念PV</title>
<title xml:lang="en">"Kawaikereba Hentai demo Suki ni Natte Kuremasu ka?" TV Animation Commemoration PV</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Kawaikereba Hentai demo Suki ni Natte Kuremasu ka?" TV Animeka Kinen PV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="218578" update="2019-09-24">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-07-08</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="218747" update="2019-09-23">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-07-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="218936" update="2019-07-22">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-08-05</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">『小春ちゃんは一年生だよ☆』大作戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Operation: Koharu Is a First-Year Student</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La tactique d`Ôtori, élève de 2de</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Koharu-chan wa Ichinensei Da yo" Daisakusen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="218937" update="2019-07-22">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-08-12</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">落ちてきたシンデレラ!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cinderella Came Falling Down?!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Cendrillon a fait une chute ?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ochite Kita Cinderella!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="218938" update="2019-07-22">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-08-19</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">『小春ちゃんは一年生だよ☆』大作戦 完結篇</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Operation: Koharu Is a First-Year Student - Conclusion</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L’ultime tactique d’Ôtori, élève de 2de</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Koharu-chan wa Ichinensei Da yo" Daisakusen Kanketsuhen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="218939" update="2019-07-22">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-08-26</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">パンツをなくした王子様!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Prince Lost His Panties?!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le Prince et la culotte perdue</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Pantsu o Nakushita Ouji-sama!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="219529" update="2019-09-22">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-09-02</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">「慧輝くんはご主人様だよ★」大作戦!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Operation: Keiki Is Master Now!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Opération spéciale “Maître Keiki”</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Keiki-kun wa Goshujin-sama Da yo" Daisakusen!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="219530" update="2019-08-19">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-09-09</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">奴隷になった王子様!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Prince Became a Slave?!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le Prince asservi ?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dorei ni Natta Ouji-sama!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="219531" update="2019-08-19">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-09-16</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">水着を脱いだシンデレラ!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cinderella Took Off Her Swimwear?!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Cendrillon a retiré son maillot de bain ?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mizugi o Nuida Cinderella!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="219532" update="2019-08-19">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-09-23</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">可愛ければ××[へんたい]でも○○[すき]になってくれますか?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Are You Willing to Fall in Love With a Pervert, As Long As She`s a Cutie?</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Tomberais-tu amoureux d’une perverse si elle était mignonne ?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kawaikereba Hentai demo Suki ni Natte Kuremasuka?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="221594" update="2019-09-24">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-08-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="221595" update="2019-09-23">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-08-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="221596" update="2019-09-23">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2019-09-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
