<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="14710" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2019-06-30</startdate>
<enddate>2019-09-17</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Sounan Desuka?</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ソウナンですか?</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Are You Lost?</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">你遭难了吗?</title>
</titles>
<url>http://www.sounandesuka.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="56332" type="Chief Animation Direction">Nishio Junnosuke</name>
<name id="54249" type="Animation Work">Ezola</name>
<name id="56332" type="Character Design">Nishio Junnosuke</name>
<name id="677" type="Series Composition">Machida Touko</name>
<name id="783" type="Work">NAS</name>
<name id="25897" type="Direction">Nagayama Nobuyoshi</name>
<name id="38165" type="Music">Tateyama Akiyuki</name>
<name id="57571" type="Original Work">Okamoto Kentarou</name>
</creators>
<description>Because of a plane crash ... starting today, we`re spending the springtime of our lives on a desert island!! There`s nothing here, so we have to make everything!! And eat everything!! (Ugh!) Check out our high-school-girl survival story of courage and knowledge. We`re actually doing pretty well! We learn how to eat cicadas, how to build traps, a simple allergy test, how to eat hermit crabs, etc.
Source: Kodansha Comics
Note: The first episode received an early web screening on June 30, 2019. The regular TV broadcast started on July 2, 2019.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="533">4.85</permanent>
<temporary count="538">6.46</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>234174.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21890</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>39456</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.sounandesuka.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Are_You_Lost%3F</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ソウナンですか%3F</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5356</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>367409</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22093</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>sounan_desuka</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="26">
<externalentity>
<identifier>channel/UCQLY6HeD7kJGcw9I9CbcLLg</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>are-you-lost</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="627" parentid="2856" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-15">
<name>lingerie</name>
<description>Lingerie is a term for fashionable and alluring women`s undergarments.</description>
<picurl>238327.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2631" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-02-11">
<name>island</name>
<description>Part of this anime takes place on an island, a small landmass that is surrounded by the sea. Generally, an island setting involves interaction with "island" elements. Such elements could include (but is not limited towards): riding on a boat, fishing, foraging/hunting, beach scene, "peaceful island life", being "shipwrecked", island fever, lamenting isolation from the mainland, etc.
An island or isle is any piece of sub-continental land that is surrounded by water. Very small islands such as emergent land features on atolls can be called islets, cays or keys. An island in a river or lake may be called an eyot (also ait), or holm. A grouping of geographically or geologically related islands is called an archipelago.
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2875" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>ecology</name>
<description>Nature and ecology are a central theme of this anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3097" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-29">
<name>underwater</name>
<description>Underwater is a term describing the realm below the surface of water where the water exists in a natural feature such as an ocean, sea, lake, pond, or river.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3506" parentid="6397" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-23">
<name>Robinson Crusoe</name>
<description>Literary classic about a man marooned on a distant island.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3625" parentid="2874" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-14">
<name>water scarcity</name>
<description>Water scarcity is the lack of sufficient available water resources to meet water needs within a region.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3953" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-06">
<name>in medias res</name>
<description>In medias res, also medias in res (Latin for "into the midst of affairs (lit. into mid-affairs)"), refers to a literary and artistic technique where the narrative starts in the middle of the story instead of from its beginning. It is generally a plot-driven concept rather than a character-driven one; though characters are commonly used to provide the backstory. The characters, setting, and conflict are often introduced through a series of flashbacks or through characters relating past events to each other.
Probably originating from an oral tradition, the technique is a convention of epic poetry, one of the earliest and most prominent examples in Western literature being Homer`s Odyssey and Iliad. Virgil`s Aeneid began the tradition in literature of imitating Homer, continued in Torquato Tasso`s Jerusalem Delivered, John Milton`s Paradise Lost and "Inferno" from Dante`s Divine Comedy. George Lucas`s Star Wars saga was told using in medias res.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4083" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-04">
<name>drastic change of life</name>
<description>One or more characters in this series go through an event that makes them change their way of life drastically and permanently. This change might be voluntary, or against the character`s will.
Some examples might be an accident, the gaining of superpowers, or simply graduating.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4251" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-20">
<name>ensemble cast</name>
<description>A show with an ensemble cast focuses on a larger group of main characters in a single plot narrative; anime containing several segmented plot narratives (such as episodic or arc-based plots) are excluded. As such, it doesn`t really have a "main" or "lead" character; instead, every member of the central main character group plays an important part in the show`s grander scheme; no single character is more important or prominent than the others (equality of importance). Further, subplots (if any) lead by each character in the ensemble have equal weighting in importance (or lack of weight).

* In a show where no single main character is more important or prominent than the others, 4+ main characters is almost always an ensemble cast.
* A show with 3 main characters of equal importance is likely also an ensemble cast; equality of importance must be considered carefully.
* A show with 2 main characters of equal importance is generally not an ensemble cast situation; however, on an exception basis where neither main character is considered an antagonist, a 2-main-character anime may be considered an ensemble (e.g. http://anidb.net/a11829 [Kimi no Na wa.]).

Pictured: http://anidb.net/a9043 [K (anime)]</description>
<picurl>94914.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4257" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-08-07">
<name>survival</name>
<description>The theme/genre of survival typically depicts the act or process of continuing to live, generally in a hostile, possibly post-apocalyptic environment. Survival-centered media tends to be dark, set most commonly in a contemporary context, and generally leads either to small groups of people forming closely knit and functional units or to individuals turning against their fellows in a return to the survival of the fittest.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4267" parentid="2881" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-07-31">
<name>underwater diving</name>
<description>Underwater diving is the practice of descending below the water`s surface to interact with the environment. It is not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6903 [acrobatic diving]. Please note that this tag is only about underwater diving as a sport; diving for e.g. salvaging shipwreck should be tagged with other, more specific tags.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4344" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-02-26">
<name>motivational anime</name>
<description>The anime motivates doing something which is shown in the show (for example club activity, sports, choosing a job, a hobby etc).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4503" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-23">
<name>castaway</name>
<description>The characters in this title were put in an island isolated from the rest of the world. This probably happened due to their transport vessel failing near said island, most often during a storm. Despite having used products of modern technology before, they are left without such resources, effectively living in some sort of stone age. Being castaway is a hard blow for real and fictional people alike, often shaking the very core of the people involved. As such, it may be the trigger for almost anything in a person, and that fact may be used as a justification for unexpected developments.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4576" parentid="6185" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-03">
<name>summer</name>
<description>At least one of the episodes takes place in summer. Think oppressively warm weather, summer vacation, summer school, summer festival, or a visit to the beach.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4614" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>narration</name>
<description>The most common example is that of a voice, either that of one of the characters or entirely unrelated, that appears at the beginning of an episode to offer a summary or introduction, and at the end of an episode for closure or for a preview to hint upon what to expect next.
Another use of narration comes in the form of a dominant voice belonging to one of the protagonists, intended only for the viewer and revealing the intimate thoughts to whom it belongs. This type of narration occurs frequently throughout the duration of the episode or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4874" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-05-14">
<name>overcoming adversity</name>
<description>Hang in there!
Overcoming problems of different variety.
Sometimes the journey is as important as the goal.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5293" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false">
<name>crash landing</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5769" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-02">
<name>panels that require pausing</name>
<description>Panels that require pausing are image or text panels that interrupt regular animation and flash by so quickly that the viewer cannot recognize the image or read the text fast enough while playing at regular speed; they require pausing the video, or at least viewing it at a lower speed. Given the short screen time these panels are given, they are usually not relevant to the plot.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6075" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-12">
<name>educational</name>
<description>The entire series (at least a major part of it) is centred on a particular subject. Information is fed to the audience in a sublime manner. Most of the time an on-screen written comment by the narrator (or translator) can be seen, e.g. biological specimen, medicine, process, etc. Sometimes at the end of every episode’s closing song, a 20 seconds educational clip is presented.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6397" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-02">
<name>tales</name>
<description>Tales are stories told time and again and passed down from generation to generation, and some of those show up in anime not just once or twice, but several times.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6494" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>half-length episodes</name>
<description>Half-length episodes are regular episodes that are somewhat shorter than the standard length. This includes episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length; shows with episodes up to and including 10 minutes are http://anidb.net/t5852 [short episodes] instead.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="101203" type="main character in" update="2019-03-04">
<rating votes="8">3.73</rating>
<name>Kujou Shion</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230914.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42471" picture="242433.jpg">Waki Azumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101204" type="main character in" update="2019-03-04">
<rating votes="6">6.43</rating>
<name>Amatani Mutsu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230913.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27357" picture="75009.jpg">Yasuno Kiyono</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101205" type="main character in" update="2019-03-04">
<rating votes="6">6.13</rating>
<name>Suzumori Asuka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230912.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="51410" picture="223259.jpg">Kouno Hiyori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101206" type="main character in" update="2019-03-04">
<rating votes="17">8.98</rating>
<name>Onishima Homare</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230911.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36368" picture="224755.jpg">Mao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103147" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-06-02">
<rating votes="4">7.98</rating>
<name>Onishima Jouichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>234179.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="286" picture="17117.jpg">Ootsuka Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="218009" update="2019-08-09">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2019-06-30</airdate>
<rating votes="10">5.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">漂流</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Adrift</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">À la dérive</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hyouryuu</title>
<summary>Four high school girls lie sprawled on a sandy beach. After an accident strikes their class trip, the girls find themselves stranded on a deserted island. While the four introduce themselves, one of them, Onishima Homare, seems unusually calm. Then she says something shocking! "This isn`t the first time I`ve been stranded."
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>786903</identifier>
<identifier>are-you-lost</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="218010" update="2019-07-15">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2019-07-09</airdate>
<rating votes="9">5.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">初めての食事</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Our First Meal</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le repas</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajimete no Shokuji</title>
<summary>In order to procure water, the girls explore the island. Homare and Asuka find a dry stream bed. In order to get water from the dirt they dig up there they`ll have to...!?
Meanwhile, left behind on the beach, Shion and Mutsu, both faint from dehydration, make a certain promise...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>786904</identifier>
<identifier>are-you-lost</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="218011" update="2019-07-22">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2019-07-16</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">島のヌシ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Master of the Island</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le maître de l`île</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shima no Nushi</title>
<summary>Homare and Asuka enter the forest to find food. Asuka is overjoyed to find a plant that looks like taro, but Homare points out it could be dangerous. When Asuka throws a tantrum saying she wants to eat it, Homare gets fed up, suggests they check to see if it`s even edible or not, and suddenly flips Asuka`s skirt up!?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>786905</identifier>
<identifier>are-you-lost</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="218012" update="2019-08-01">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2019-07-23</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">トラップ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Trap</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le piège</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Trap</title>
<summary>One day, Homare and the others find evidence of squirrels and rabbits, and quickly decide to lay traps for them. In order to survive, they use what they can find on the island, and after some hard work, they have a real trap! Lightheartedly, Asuka decides to try the trap out, but...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>786906</identifier>
<identifier>are-you-lost</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="218608" update="2019-09-18">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2019-06-30</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="218609" update="2019-09-18">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2019-06-30</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="218796" update="2019-08-01">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2019-07-30</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">奇妙なサザエ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Strange Turban Shell</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un étrange escargot de mer</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kimyou na Sazae</title>
<summary>Homare and Asuka go diving for food. When underwater, human vision blurs, however using a certain technique creates improvised underwater glasses which they use to look for turban shells and oysters, but...
The severe conditions begin to take their toll on the girls both mentally and physically. Homare remembers something her father taught her - "When things are tough, when you`re sad, have a barbecue."
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>786907</identifier>
<identifier>are-you-lost</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="218797" update="2019-08-06">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2019-08-06</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ウサギ実食</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rabbit Tasting</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le goût du lapin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Usagi Jisshoku</title>
<summary>Asuka and Mutsu go to check the trap they set. Just as they`d hoped, there`s a rabbit caught in the trap, but there`s no time to call in the reliable Homare! If they leave it, it might get away...! What will they choose to do for the sake of survival?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>786908</identifier>
<identifier>are-you-lost</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="218798" update="2019-08-19">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2019-08-13</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">島を探索</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Exploring the Island</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L’exploration de l’île</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shima o Tansaku</title>
<summary>To prepare for the possibility of their cast-away life lasting longer than they thought, Homare and the others decide to explore the island, and they spot, of all things, a house!
With hopes of rescue rising in their hearts, they race forward, but what they discover is the ruins of an abandoned building...
Noting the despair of the other girls, Homare finds an item they`ll need to survive the island!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>786909</identifier>
<identifier>are-you-lost</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="218799" update="2019-09-09">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2019-08-20</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">オアシス発見!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Oasis Found?!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Découverte d’une oasis</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oasis Hakken!?</title>
<summary>While exploring, the four girls spot a column of smoke rising and speed toward the rocks by the beach! Could there be people...? But what they find is...a hot spring?! They soothe bodies and spirits tired from their explorations together!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>786910</identifier>
<identifier>are-you-lost</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="219309" update="2019-09-09">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2019-08-27</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほまれのパパ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Homare`s Papa</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Homare et son papa</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Homare no Papa</title>
<summary>Everyone wants sunblock in order to evade the UV rays of summer. That`s where the squid and seaweed Homare brought back come in... When confronted with all the difficulties of a survival situation, from bug bites to reeking of sweat, Homare remembers what her father taught her.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>786911</identifier>
<identifier>are-you-lost</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="219310" update="2019-09-09">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2019-09-03</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">HONEY BEE</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Honey Bee</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les abeilles</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Honey Bee</title>
<summary>After following the honey bees that have been flying around the camp to their hive, the girls decide to try to get the honey. It isn`t uncommon for people to die from bee stings, so how will they manage to deal with the bees?!
Then, Shion boards a raft to try her hand at fishing and gets caught up in...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>786912</identifier>
<identifier>are-you-lost</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="219311" update="2019-09-15">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2019-09-10</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">絶対助ける</title>
<title xml:lang="en">We Will Rescue Her</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Je la sauverai</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zettai Tasukeru</title>
<summary>Shion has been swept away by a rip current and the others are at a loss. That`s when Homare decides to build a new raft and go after her! She breaks her fathers rule of "you own life comes first," risking her life to go save Shion, but in the vast ocean, Homare can`t find her... Having exhausted every option she can think of, suddenly Homare remembers one of her father`s teachings...!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>786913</identifier>
<identifier>are-you-lost</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="219312" update="2019-09-27">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2019-09-17</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">水の補給方法</title>
<title xml:lang="en">How to Replenish Water</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le problème de l’eau</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mizu no Houkyuu Hohou</title>
<summary>Homare finds the solitary island where Shion washed ashore and the two are reunited. But there`s no time to rejoice. With no food or water, succumbing to dehydration is only a matter of time... All they have is filthy water they find in a cave... In this dire situation, the two of them use a secret technique for rehydration!? Will Homare and Shion make it back to the island?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>786914</identifier>
<identifier>are-you-lost</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="221402" update="2019-09-18">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2019-07-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="221403" update="2019-09-18">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2019-08-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1b</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
