<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="14840" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2019-09-06</startdate>
<enddate>2019-09-06</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Violet Evergarden Gaiden: Eien to Jidou Shuki Ningyou</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Violet Evergarden Side Story: Eternity and the Auto Memory Doll</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Violet Evergarden Side Story: Eternity and the Auto Memories Doll</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ヴァイオレット・エヴァーガーデン 外伝~永遠と自動手記人形~</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Violet Evergarden: Eternity and the Auto Memory Doll</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Violet Evergarden : Eternité et la poupée de souvenirs automatiques</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">바이올렛 에버가든 외전: 영원과 자동수기인형</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="official">فيوليت إيفرغاردن - القصة الجانبية: الأبدية ودمية الذكريات الآلية</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="12138" type="Parent Story">Violet Evergarden</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="3">
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="733904">The animation is top notch. I enjoyed the story, much to my surprise.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="459461">"[b]Violet Evergarden Gaiden[/b] is a landmark work that never wished to be one. First conceived as two extra episodes for the TV series in OVA form, this side story only ended up becoming a feature-length film because the staff heading the work were so invested in its world that they went overboard with it. In contrast to that, its other unintended reality is much more tragic: having been essentially completed the day before the Kyoto Animation arson attack, it’s the final taste of an era of the studio that was brought to a cruel end."
[i]Source: [url=https://blog.sakugabooru.com/2020/04/15/toward-a-new-kyoani-veg-gaiden-haruka-fujita/]kViN via Sakuga Blog[/url][/i]</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.violet-evergarden.jp/sidestory/</url>
<creators>
<name id="736" type="Animation Work">Kyoto Animation</name>
<name id="47074" type="Character Design">Takase Akiko</name>
<name id="45939" type="Original Work">Akatsuki Kana</name>
<name id="47074" type="Chief Animation Direction">Takase Akiko</name>
<name id="39819" type="Music">Evan Call</name>
<name id="1790" type="Series Composition">Yoshida Reiko</name>
<name id="2655" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kadowaki Miku</name>
<name id="32382" type="Direction">Fujita Haruka</name>
</creators>
<description>Note: The movie received early screenings in Mannheim, Germany, on Aug 3 and Aug 4.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="207">8.61</permanent>
<temporary count="212">8.14</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>236689.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22377</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>39741</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.violet-evergarden.jp/sidestory/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>368085</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Violet_Letter</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="26">
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=lWRXk7nOhsE</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2926" parentid="2874" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>post-war</name>
<description>An armed conflict has ended not too long ago, devastation of the world or society is still evident.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3138" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-08">
<name>fictional language</name>
<description>Fictional languages are intended to be the languages of a fictional world and are often designed with the intent of giving more depth and an appearance of plausibility to the fictional worlds with which they are associated, and to have their characters communicate in a fashion which is both alien and dislocated.
Some of these languages, e.g. in worlds of fantasy fiction, alternative universes, Earth`s future, or alternate history, are presented as distorted versions or dialects of modern English or other natural language, while others are independently designed conlangs.
A fictional language often has the least amount of grammar and vocabulary possible, and rarely extends beyond the absolutely necessary. At the same time, some others have developed languages in detail for their own sake, such as J. R. R. Tolkien`s Quenya and Sindarin and Star Trek`s Klingon language which exist as functioning, usable languages. Here "fictional" can be a misnomer.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3170" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-10">
<name>occupation and career</name>
<description>The kind of anime which shows the career of a character, usually from the beginning.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3217" parentid="2864" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-17">
<name>working life</name>
<description>The life of someone actually working on a often less than glamorous job is depicted in this anime. The job is taxing and the pay is low, not really the dream job one would choose to work in.
Examples: Working as salesperson in a department store, or as a waitress in a family restaurant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3809" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-05-24">
<name>character driven</name>
<description>The main appeal of the show is the way the characters are portrayed and interact, focusing on dialogue, spending time together or getting to know each other. These anime are not "story-less" but story is secondary to character development and the characters themselves and what they experience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4083" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-04">
<name>drastic change of life</name>
<description>One or more characters in this series go through an event that makes them change their way of life drastically and permanently. This change might be voluntary, or against the character`s will.
Some examples might be an accident, the gaining of superpowers, or simply graduating.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6018" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-27">
<name>predominantly adult cast</name>
<description>This show features mostly adults. That means children and teenagers are relatively rare and unlikely to hold significance to the plot.
That is a rare trait in anime, as most shows spin around children or teenagers.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="89959" type="main character in" update="2017-08-22">
<rating votes="157">8.53</rating>
<name>Violet Evergarden</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>206544.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="443" picture="145927.jpg">Ishikawa Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90197" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-08-22">
<rating votes="32">6.37</rating>
<name>Cattleya Baudelaire</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>206547.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="424" picture="224027.jpg">Endou Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90199" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-08-22">
<rating votes="16">4.99</rating>
<name>Claudia Hodgins</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>206545.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90200" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-08-22">
<rating votes="12">5.38</rating>
<name>Benedict Blue</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>206548.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2588" picture="153507.jpg">Uchiyama Kouki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92846" type="appears in" update="2017-12-16">
<rating votes="18">3.55</rating>
<name>Iris Cannary</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>210813.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5" picture="233827.jpg">Tomatsu Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92847" type="appears in" update="2018-01-10">
<rating votes="17">3.57</rating>
<name>Erica Brown</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211805.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="245" picture="46862.jpg">Chihara Minori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93416" type="appears in" update="2018-05-02">
<rating votes="2">2.53</rating>
<name>Nerine</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>217119.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38924" picture="188476.jpg">Saitou Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93417" type="appears in" update="2018-04-30">
<rating votes="10">6.25</rating>
<name>Luculia Marlborough</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Luculia Marlborough is a graduate of the Auto Memories Doll Training School and a newbie Auto Memories Doll. She befriended Violet at the training school.
Luculia had a normal, yet very peaceful childhood with her parents and older brother, Spencer. When the war began, Spencer was drafted into the army. However, there wasn`t much fighting on the Western Front where Spencer was located, so Luculia claims that the war didn`t feel real to them. However, one day when her parents went to a town for business, the Western Front was broken through, and her parents were killed in the fighting.
After the war ended, Spencer came back alive, which was more than enough to make Luculia happy despite their parents` deaths. However, Spencer blamed himself for the deaths of their parents, and fell into depression and alcoholism, after which Luculia began taking care of him.
Source: Violet Evergarden Wiki</description>
<picture>217015.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33509" picture="204529.jpg">Tadokoro Azusa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95340" type="appears in" update="2018-05-02">
<rating votes="2">7.78</rating>
<name>Roland</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>217120.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32937" picture="89644.jpg">Kagami Riki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105023" type="main character in" update="2019-09-11">
<rating votes="4">4.93</rating>
<name>Isabella York</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238185.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1798" picture="20493.jpg">Kotobuki Minako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105024" type="main character in" update="2019-09-11">
<rating votes="2">7.78</rating>
<name>Taylor Bartlett</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238184.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1625" picture="226033.jpg">Yuuki Aoi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="215683" update="2019-08-05">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>95</length>
<airdate>2019-09-06</airdate>
<rating votes="3">9.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="219291" update="2019-08-13">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2019-08-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">PV1 (60 sec)</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
