<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="14907" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2020-01-06</startdate>
<enddate>2020-03-23</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Eizouken ni wa Te o Dasuna!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Eizouken</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">映像研には手を出すな!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Keep Your Hands Off Eizouken!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Keep Your Hands Off Eizouken !</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="official">أبعد يديك عن إيزوكين!</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="10779" approval="2" total="4">Shirobako</anime>
<anime id="773" approval="2" total="3">Animation Seisaku Shinkou Kuromi-chan</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="757481">Because in the world of standardized anime clones no one recommends this flight of fantasy.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://eizouken-anime.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="9250" type="Chief Animation Direction">Asano Naoyuki</name>
<name id="47794" type="Music">Oorutaichi</name>
<name id="49" type="Direction">Yuasa Masaaki</name>
<name id="57828" type="Original Work">Oowara Sumito</name>
<name id="9250" type="Character Design">Asano Naoyuki</name>
<name id="48093" type="Animation Work">Science Saru</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on an adventure school life seinen manga by http://anidb.net/cr57828 [Oowara Sumito].
http://anidb.net/ch106476 [Asakusa Midori] wants to create an anime, but she`s too disheartened to make that first step by herself. But by pure chance, she meets http://anidb.net/ch106478 [Mizusaki Tsubame], an up-and-coming socialite secretly dreaming of becoming an animator. Together with Midori`s money-loving best friend http://anidb.net/ch106477 [Kanamori Sayaka], the energetic trio slowly work towards making their "ultimate world" a reality!
Source: M-U</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="381">7.87</permanent>
<temporary count="383">7.56</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>241521.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22561</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>39792</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://eizouken-anime.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Keep_Your_Hands_Off_Eizouken!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>映像研には手を出すな!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5541</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>371423</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>368241</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22432</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Eizouken_anime/status/1217370840049819649</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>Eizouken_anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>Eizouken_anime/status/1214834124868878338</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>keep-your-hands-off-eizouken</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="38">
<externalentity>
<identifier>282433</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1298" parentid="2883" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-02">
<name>drawing</name>
<description>The art or technique of representing an object or outlining a figure, plan, or sketch by means of lines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2867" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>politics</name>
<description>From commies to fat capitalist pigs, all the stuff done by the "guys with the power", mainly evil tactics for gaining more power over the masses.
Watching this title may remind you why CNN is boring.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3170" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-10">
<name>occupation and career</name>
<description>The kind of anime which shows the career of a character, usually from the beginning.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3546" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-01-08">
<name>experimental animation</name>
<description>This anime uses distinct, alternative animation — much unlike other contemporary anime — either throughout or in individual episodes/sequences.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3759" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-11">
<name>teamwork</name>
<description>A cooperative effort by the members of a group or team to achieve a common goal.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3804" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-04-08">
<name>beauty in simplicity</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3946" parentid="2883" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-04-16">
<name>filmmaking</name>
<description>Filmmaking is the process of making a film. This may be tied to studios with very large budgets or to inexpensive independent products alike, and even to amateur films; modern technology allows people to film events of significance in their lives, such as their marriages. Anime in school settings may have a film club, which sometimes produce their own films for e.g. the school culture festival.</description>
<picurl>68842.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3971" parentid="3170" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-07-04">
<name>entertainment industry</name>
<description>The show depicts how the entertainment industry works and how the main protagonists strive to cope with the sudden change to fame. At times this can be a very ugly sight indeed.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3977" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-29">
<name>dialogue driven</name>
<description>A dialogue driven show has its story advanced by dialogue, with action being of much lower priority, and relies heavily on conversations between characters.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3992" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-08-17">
<name>nostalgia</name>
<description>A bitter-sweet longing for things, persons, or situations from the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4030" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-04-13">
<name>mental cinema</name>
<description>The ability to imagine all kinds of things, as if they were real.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4198" parentid="5604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-14">
<name>hard work and guts</name>
<description>One of the character`s motto in the anime. Because there is nothing that cannot be achieved by hard work and guts.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4227" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-03">
<name>detailed landscapes</name>
<description>An amazing view of nature, of artificially sculpted landscapes (i.e. gardens), or of a cityscape.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4251" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-20">
<name>ensemble cast</name>
<description>A show with an ensemble cast focuses on a larger group of main characters in a single plot narrative; anime containing several segmented plot narratives (such as episodic or arc-based plots) are excluded. As such, it doesn`t really have a "main" or "lead" character; instead, every member of the central main character group plays an important part in the show`s grander scheme; no single character is more important or prominent than the others (equality of importance). Further, subplots (if any) lead by each character in the ensemble have equal weighting in importance (or lack of weight).

* In a show where no single main character is more important or prominent than the others, 4+ main characters is almost always an ensemble cast.
* A show with 3 main characters of equal importance is likely also an ensemble cast; equality of importance must be considered carefully.
* A show with 2 main characters of equal importance is generally not an ensemble cast situation; however, on an exception basis where neither main character is considered an antagonist, a 2-main-character anime may be considered an ensemble (e.g. http://anidb.net/a11829 [Kimi no Na wa.]).

Pictured: http://anidb.net/a9043 [K (anime)]</description>
<picurl>94914.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4323" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-04">
<name>spacing out</name>
<description>A comedy element: The character starts to daydream or fantasize about some topic. The typical complete lack of reality makes the spacing out funny. Especially when the protagonist mumbles to himself / herself and friends hear this. Promptly teasing the possibly lovestruck and very embarrassed protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4344" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-02-26">
<name>motivational anime</name>
<description>The anime motivates doing something which is shown in the show (for example club activity, sports, choosing a job, a hobby etc).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4570" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-07">
<name>watercolour style</name>
<description>A watercolour or aquarelle is a painting method in which the paints are made of pigments suspended in a water-based solution. Some anime are created in the style of watercolour paintings, the watercolour style, usually with faded pastels that often give the show a warm and friendly visual presentation. In modern anime, this is generally achieved via computer effects that create an imitation of watercolour, rather than by creating real-life watercolour art. While the watercolour style is more commonly used for backgrounds, it is possible to create the entire anime in such a style.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4576" parentid="6185" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-03">
<name>summer</name>
<description>At least one of the episodes takes place in summer. Think oppressively warm weather, summer vacation, summer school, summer festival, or a visit to the beach.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4642" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-03-08">
<name>economics</name>
<description>Economics is the social science that studies economic activity to gain an understanding of the processes that govern the production, distribution and consumption of goods and services in an economy.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>169811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5227" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-04-26">
<name>alternating animation style</name>
<description>The animation style in this show may change between scenes, usually making the anime experimental in a way. This may be a form of artistic visualisation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5276" parentid="2874" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-25">
<name>typhoon</name>
<description>A typhoon is a mature tropical cyclone that develops in the north-western part of the Pacific Ocean between 180° and 100°E. This region is referred to as the north-west Pacific basin. Identical phenomena in the eastern north Pacific are called hurricanes, with tropical cyclones moving into the western Pacific re-designated as typhoons.
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5515" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>faceless background characters</name>
<description>Unimportant random/extra characters that appear mostly as part of the background are often drawn without much facial details, normally to save money, effort and manpower for more important parts of the show. Sometimes, they have almost or no facial details, meaning their heads only have indications of the presence of parts such as hair or mouth, or not even that. This can go as far as only drawing an abstracted silhouette of the whole body.</description>
<picurl>233515.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5604" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-04">
<name>following one`s dream</name>
<description>No matter what the hardships may be, at least one of the protagonists in this anime is following her/his dream.
Examples: To become a professional athlete, a musician, a painter or the ruler of this world!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5768" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>intact family</name>
<description>The main character`s family is a so-called "nuclear family". Wherein both parents are alive and present in his or her life. This is actually relatively rare for anime, where "parental abandonment" is the norm.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5834" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>show within a show</name>
<description>A fictional TV (or radio, or stage) show that takes place within an actual TV show; or, occasionally, a fictional instalment or incarnation of an actual show. Many comedies have short one-off gags where they parody existing shows.
Example: A large part of Martian Successor Nadesico is centred around the fictional popular anime Gekigangar III, which is being watched by several characters of the Nadesico crew.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5850" parentid="2869" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-13">
<name>absurdly powerful student council</name>
<description>A student council is a student-managed body inside a school which engages in administrative affairs, usually usually working in a partnership with management, staff and parents, for the benefit of the whole school environment. In real life, a student council holds no actual power; however, in many anime/manga, they have an insane amount of power, which usually allows them to overrule nearly everyone else (the school board, the mayor, the prime minster, you name it). In those cases, that device is explored as a major source of slapstick comedy.</description>
<picurl>70561.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5981" parentid="6232" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-10-12">
<name>seeking protagonist</name>
<description>The main character has a main objective that is referenced to through the whole series; he is in search of something, or someone
Should it be treasure, friends, money, power or all of the above nothing will stop our lead character in his quest to find his passion</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6029" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-04-08">
<name>mundane made awesome</name>
<description>Sometimes normal just doesn`t cut it. Eating: you put food in your mouth and chew. Playing sports: you throw a ball around. You need to make it awesome, no matter how mundane it is.
Let`s throw in some gripping orchestral music, lighting changes, different camera angles, something! Don`t write like a man, write like an evil overlord! Exaggerate your expressions and gestures, speak with excessive intonation, and if all else fails, throw in some close-ups, slow motion, and ominous Latin chanting! With practice, even you can turn something like eating chips into an epic battle of light and dark, blinding the viewer with sheer awesomeness.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>149443.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6030" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-22">
<name>otaku culture</name>
<description>Otaku (おたく/オタク) is a Japanese term used to refer to people with obsessive interests, particularly anime, manga, and video games. A female otaku is occasionally referred to as a fujoshi. (Source: Wikipedia)
Here certain aspects of this "fandom" are presented in more detail, e.g. the creation of doujinshi (self-published amateur manga).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6034" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>Engrish</name>
<description>Engrish is actually a mispronunciation of English, as can be the result of someone, who does not have English as their primary language of origin (such as Japanese or Chinese). Occasionally characters in the original Japanese dialogue version of an anime will speak in English... however; this often still requires the assistance of subtitles, for while the words are meant to be said in English, the sentence structure and letter pronunciation may still be strongly related to the person’s primary language.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6075" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-12">
<name>educational</name>
<description>The entire series (at least a major part of it) is centred on a particular subject. Information is fed to the audience in a sublime manner. Most of the time an on-screen written comment by the narrator (or translator) can be seen, e.g. biological specimen, medicine, process, etc. Sometimes at the end of every episode’s closing song, a 20 seconds educational clip is presented.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6232" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-10-21">
<name>character related tags which need deleting or merging</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="106476" type="main character in" update="2019-10-26">
<rating votes="12">8.93</rating>
<name>Asakusa Midori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68028.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="59338" picture="241524.jpg">Itou Sairi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106477" type="main character in" update="2019-10-26">
<rating votes="14">9.31</rating>
<name>Kanamori Sayaka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68029.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="3712" picture="240126.jpg">Tamura Mutsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106478" type="main character in" update="2019-10-26">
<rating votes="11">8.40</rating>
<name>Mizusaki Tsubame</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68030.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="59337" picture="241523.jpg">Matsuoka Misato</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107149" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-11-26">
<name>Sakaki Sowande</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The school council`s secretary. She is better at seeing through the essence of things than the president, and considered as a power broker of the school council. She seems to care about Eizouken which tends to push their ways, but her true intent is unknown.
Source: Official page</description>
<seiyuu id="16085" picture="178446.jpg">Komatsu Mikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107150" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-03-02">
<rating votes="2">5.56</rating>
<name>Doumeki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The only member of Audio Club. She joined the club for the vast numbers of the audio files that are stored in the club, but ended up giving up a part of storage to the student council. Proposed by Eizoken, she accepted to take the role of audio adviser with the condition that she can lodge in their club room.
Source: Official page</description>
<picture>244730.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38634" picture="144425.jpg">Hanamori Yumiri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107151" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-11-26">
<rating votes="1">8.07</rating>
<name>Fujimoto-sensei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Advisor to Eizouken. He is known for the historical-figure-like moustache. He rarely gives direction to Eizouken and leaves the activities up to the members’ independence. He likes to play games in his free time.
Source: Official page</description>
<picture>241522.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="189" picture="203306.jpg">Inoue Kazuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107584" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-12-20">
<name>Roboken Kobayashi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="38670" picture="185856.jpg">Kobayashi Yuusuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107585" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-12-20">
<name>Roboken Ono</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="3155" picture="24137.jpg">Ono Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107586" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-12-20">
<name>Roboken Gotou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="40504" picture="158574.jpg">Watanuki Ryuunosuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107587" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-12-20">
<name>Roboken Seki</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="10410" picture="223211.jpg">Izawa Shiori</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="225481" update="2020-01-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-01-06</airdate>
<rating votes="8">9.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">最強の世界!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Greatest World!</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">العالم الأعظم!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikyou no Sekai!</title>
<summary>Midori ASAKUSA is a first year high school student who dreams of creating her own animation. When she visits a screening event held by Anime Club with fellow student Sayaka KANAMORI, an amateur model Tsubasa MIZUSAKI starts talking to them. As she was being chased by men dressed in all black, ASAKUSA and KANAMORI help her get rid of them. To their surprise, they learn that MIZUSAKI is also aspiring to be an animator. The three of them hit it off to realize their own “Incredible World” together!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792447</identifier>
<identifier>keep-your-hands-off-eizouken</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="225482" update="2020-01-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-01-13</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">映像研, 爆誕す!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Eizouken Takes the Stage!</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">يعتلي الإيزوكين المنصة!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Eizouken, Bakutansu!</title>
<summary>As Mizusaki is banned from joining the anime club by her parents, the only way for the three of them to make anime is to set up a new club. At the staff room, their teacher tells them that they will be granted a certain budget if the objective of their club was to create a live-action movie. Kanamori suggest that they will call their club “Eizou (Film) club” and use its name as a disguise. Thus “ Eizou-ken” came into existence! They head off to a storage space previously used by the anime club and realized all kinds of treasures behind the door!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792448</identifier>
<identifier>keep-your-hands-off-eizouken</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="225483" update="2020-01-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-01-20</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">実績を打ち立てろ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let`s Accomplish Something!</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">لننجز شيئاً!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jisseki o Uchitateru!</title>
<summary>Eizouken’s so-called club room was merely a storage with holes in all sides. Therefore, fixing the room was a priority. Asakusa imagine the process as spaceship fixing training. To promote their club, they decided to create a new anime to show at the “budget decision committee meeting”. Three of them choose a scene from one of Asakusa’s many sketches. Asakusa wants to animate a tank while Mizusaki is persistent about actions. With her producer-like vision, Kanamori eggs on their creative energy.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792449</identifier>
<identifier>keep-your-hands-off-eizouken</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="225484" update="2020-02-27">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-01-27</airdate>
<rating votes="4">9.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">そのマチェットを強く握れ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hold That Machete Tight!</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">أمسكي بذلك الساطور جيّداً</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sono Machete o Tsuyoku Nigire!</title>
<summary>The student council`s budget committee looms on the horizon as the eizouken`s project is still far from finished. As Mizusaki struggles with effects shots, Kanamori reminds her of the grim reality of the approaching deadline. While Asakusa manages to extend their run-time with creative use of existing art, the club is forced to make hard decisions about what parts of their creative vision to sacrifice and which parts to preserve. But even then, will they have something that resembles a complete product in time?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792450</identifier>
<identifier>keep-your-hands-off-eizouken</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="225912" update="2020-01-06">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2020-01-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225913" update="2020-01-06">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2020-01-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="226050" update="2020-01-15">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2020-01-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Mini Anime Episode 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="226051" update="2020-01-15">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2020-01-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Mini Anime Episode 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="226201" update="2020-02-27">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-02-03</airdate>
<rating votes="3">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">鉄巨人あらわる!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">An Iron Giant Appears!</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">ظهور عملاق حديدي</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tetsu Kyojin Arawaru!</title>
<summary>Asakusa discovers a mysterious robot, and before long Mizusaki and Kanamori are implicated in the conspiracy surrounding it. The nature of that insidious plot? The Shibahama High School robot club commissioning an anime short from the eizouken. After exploring the maintenance tunnels beneath the school, the girls have their first production meeting with the robot club, where they run into the complicated contradictions in the visions of their would-be clients.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792451</identifier>
<identifier>keep-your-hands-off-eizouken</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="226202" update="2020-03-04">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-02-10</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">前作より進歩するべし!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let`s Do Better Than Last Time!</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">لنقدّم أداء أفضل من المرّة السابقة!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zensaku yori Shinpo Surubeshi!</title>
<summary>Eizouken 06: Production begins on the Eizouken`s new robot anime, and improving on their last work means expanding the club`s reach. Asakusa struggles to convey her instructions to the art club, who are going to help with the backgrounds this time around, while a run-in with the student council puts a prospective new ally in Kanamori`s sights.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792452</identifier>
<identifier>keep-your-hands-off-eizouken</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="226203" update="2020-03-07">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-02-17</airdate>
<rating votes="4">9.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">私は私を救うんだ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Have to Do It for Myself!</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">عليّ فعلها لأجل نفسي!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Watashi wa Watashi o Sukuunda!</title>
<summary>Doumeki moves into the Eizouken`s clubhouse, securing a sound director for the girls` new robot anime. After a harrowing meeting with the art club, a torrential downpour forces a temporary pause on anime production that results in a afternoon of relaxation and reflection.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792453</identifier>
<identifier>keep-your-hands-off-eizouken</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="226204" update="2020-03-04">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-02-24</airdate>
<rating votes="5">9.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大芝浜祭!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Grand Shibahama Festival!</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">مهرجان شيباهاما العظيم!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ooshibahama Matsuri!</title>
<summary>Eizouken 08: The day of the Shibahama High School culture festival has come, and the eizouken and robot club are teaming up to make their robot anime screening a success! The only problem is that the student council is out for blood after some irregular publicity stunts, and Mizusaki`s parents have shown up, curious about what their daughter is up to...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792454</identifier>
<identifier>keep-your-hands-off-eizouken</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="226947" update="2020-03-04">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-03-02</airdate>
<rating votes="4">9.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">コメットAを目指せ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Aim for Comet A!</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">السّعي وراء كوميت أ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Comet A o Mezase!</title>
<summary>With the robot anime a critical success, if not a financial one, the eizouken sets their sights on their next project. In order to maximize the potential gains for their grueling efforts, the time has come to produce something to sell at a local media convention. The stage is set for an alien invasion at Shibahama`s self-published art expo, Comet A!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792455</identifier>
<identifier>keep-your-hands-off-eizouken</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="226948" update="2020-03-24">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-03-09</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">独自世界の対立!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Against Our Independent World!</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">في وجه عالمنا المستقلّ!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dokuji Sekai no Tairitsu!</title>
<summary>As production starts to spin up for the eizouken`s latest project, Asakusa has trouble nailing down the fine details of the story, which leads to no shortage of anxiety for Kanamori. And if that wasn`t enough, it seems like Shibahama High School`s administration has got major issues with the potential sale of the club`s film at Comet A.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792456</identifier>
<identifier>keep-your-hands-off-eizouken</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="226949" update="2020-03-24">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-03-16</airdate>
<rating votes="3">9.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">それぞれの存在!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Each Other`s Existence!</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">وجود بعضنا الآخر</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sorezore no Sonzai!</title>
<summary>The deadline for Comet A looms large as the Shibahama High School film club gradually feels the squeeze; the school administration pressures other clubs to stop collaborating with the eizouken, Kanamori gets sick, and Asakusa still hasn`t quite figured out the concept for their new film.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792457</identifier>
<identifier>keep-your-hands-off-eizouken</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="226950" update="2020-04-05">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-03-23</airdate>
<rating votes="4">9.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">芝浜UFO大戦!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shibahama UFO Wars!</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">حروب أطباق طائرة في شيباهاما!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shibahama UFO Taisen!</title>
<summary>At the last possible second, the eizouken runs into a snag with their short film for the upcoming Comet A convention. With time running out, can they manage to salvage their new film in time?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792458</identifier>
<identifier>keep-your-hands-off-eizouken</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
