<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="14957" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2020-01-05</startdate>
<enddate>2020-03-22</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Yatogame-chan Kansatsu Nikki Nisatsume</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Yatogame-chan Observation Diary 2</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">八十亀ちゃんかんさつにっき 2さつめ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Yatogame-chan Kansatsu Nikki 2</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="official">ياتوغامي-تشان كانساتسو نيكي المجلد 2</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="14103" type="Prequel">Yatogame-chan Kansatsu Nikki</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>https://yatogame.nagoya/</url>
<creators>
<name id="56367" type="Animation Work">Saetta</name>
<name id="51442" type="Character Design">Hayasaka Satsuki</name>
<name id="51665" type="Series Composition">Words in Stereo</name>
<name id="55239" type="Original Work">Andou Masaki</name>
<name id="44708" type="Chief Direction">Hirasawa Hisayoshi</name>
<name id="44823" type="Music">Abe Ryuudai</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on http://anidb.net/cr55239 [Andou Masaki]`s 4-koma manga.
After growing up in Tokyo, high school student Jin Kaito moves to Nagoya where he meets Yatogame Monaka, a fellow student who puts her Nagoya dialect on full display. With her cat-like appearance and unvarnished Nagoya dialect, Yatogame won`t open up to him at all. This popular local comedy is increasing the status of Nagoya through observation of the adorable Yatogame-chan!
Source: crunchyroll</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="100">3.50</permanent>
<temporary count="100">5.76</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>241236.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22937</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>39960</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://yatogame.nagoya/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Yatogame-chan_Kansatsu_Nikki</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>八十亀ちゃんかんさつにっき</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5528</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>368849</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22491</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>yatogame_chan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>yatogame-chan-kansatsu-nikki</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="28" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-16">
<name>baseball</name>
<description>Baseball is like a complicated version of Rounders. It involves hitting a ball with a stick, then running around several bases placed in the form of a diamond on a field. Big in the US, and also in Japan.</description>
<picurl>29801.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1651" parentid="2883" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>photography</name>
<description>Photography is the art or process of producing images by the action of radiant energy and especially light on a sensitive surface (such as film or an optical sensor).
Source: Merriam-Webster</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2438" parentid="2794" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-16">
<name>idol</name>
<description>In Japanese culture, idols (アイドル) are media personalities in their teens and early twenties who are considered particularly cute and cuddly and who will, for a period ranging from several months to a few years, regularly appear in the mass media, e.g. as singers for J-pop groups, bit-part actors, TV personalities, models in photo spreads published in magazines, advertisements, etc.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>63097.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2805" parentid="2798" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>4-koma manga</name>
<description>Yonkoma manga (4コマ漫画, four cell manga, or 4-koma for short), a comic-strip format, generally consists of gag comic strips within four panels of equal size ordered from top to bottom. (They also sometimes run right-to-left horizontally or use a hybrid 2x2 style, depending on the layout requirements of the publication in which they appear.) Though the word yonkoma comes from the Japanese, the style also exists outside of Japan in other Asian countries as well as in the English-speaking market.</description>
<picurl>70558.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3028" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-17">
<name>real-world location</name>
<description>Places seen in the show exist in reality.
Note: This could be sometime in the future, though names and certain places will still be recognizable.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3185" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-27">
<name>wordplay</name>
<description>The characters play with words. 
E.g. purposely or accidentally use similar-sounding but wrongly applied words in the Japanese original, leading to supposedly funny misunderstandings and confusion.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3305" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-05-14">
<name>light-hearted</name>
<description>Not being burdened by trouble, worry, or care; happy and carefree.
Just a casual and feel-good watch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3977" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-29">
<name>dialogue driven</name>
<description>A dialogue driven show has its story advanced by dialogue, with action being of much lower priority, and relies heavily on conversations between characters.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4131" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-05-11">
<name>cultural references</name>
<description>The plot of this anime shows signs of cultural references, these are often jokes that make reference to a certain custom, habit or history that is specifically attributed to that culture. Knowledge of the culture itself is needed in order to properly understand these jokes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4222" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>walls of text</name>
<description>Walls of text refers to Japanese text that appears in large quantities within the anime itself. This text is most likely vital to the storyline and may come in the form of charts and diagrams or pieces of paper, notes or even thoughts that are only partially or entirely unspoken.
May also be taken as a fair warning to viewers unable to translate Japanese text on their own, suggesting that thorough subtitle support may be required as well as making use of the pause button on their media players so that all text can be read.
Normally, tags don`t refer to physical translations of text, subtitle appearances and karaoke styling added by 3rd parties. But those who seek to describe an anime that is heavy on SPOKEN dialogue (which may tend to create a large quantity of natural subtitling to read for those not fluent in the language being used) could consider this tag but may make clearer reference with the dialogue driven tag.</description>
<picurl>32534.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4223" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>running gag</name>
<description>(Bit) character(s) play out a short skit several times during the course of the anime. The skit may or may not be exactly the same but does tend to have the same theme throughout.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4570" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-07">
<name>watercolour style</name>
<description>A watercolour or aquarelle is a painting method in which the paints are made of pigments suspended in a water-based solution. Some anime are created in the style of watercolour paintings, the watercolour style, usually with faded pastels that often give the show a warm and friendly visual presentation. In modern anime, this is generally achieved via computer effects that create an imitation of watercolour, rather than by creating real-life watercolour art. While the watercolour style is more commonly used for backgrounds, it is possible to create the entire anime in such a style.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4576" parentid="6185" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-03">
<name>summer</name>
<description>At least one of the episodes takes place in summer. Think oppressively warm weather, summer vacation, summer school, summer festival, or a visit to the beach.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4588" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-20">
<name>fast-paced</name>
<description>Hold onto your hats, this anime`s storyline is relentless.
The characters don`t get time to take a breath as events keep both them and the viewer on a roller coaster ride of revelation and excitement!
Hopefully it all makes sense...</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4614" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>narration</name>
<description>The most common example is that of a voice, either that of one of the characters or entirely unrelated, that appears at the beginning of an episode to offer a summary or introduction, and at the end of an episode for closure or for a preview to hint upon what to expect next.
Another use of narration comes in the form of a dominant voice belonging to one of the protagonists, intended only for the viewer and revealing the intimate thoughts to whom it belongs. This type of narration occurs frequently throughout the duration of the episode or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5515" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>faceless background characters</name>
<description>Unimportant random/extra characters that appear mostly as part of the background are often drawn without much facial details, normally to save money, effort and manpower for more important parts of the show. Sometimes, they have almost or no facial details, meaning their heads only have indications of the presence of parts such as hair or mouth, or not even that. This can go as far as only drawing an abstracted silhouette of the whole body.</description>
<picurl>233515.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5697" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-02">
<name>randomness</name>
<description>The anime does not follow a predictable storyline. New, strange, obscure, or otherwise unexpected story elements are introduced at a whim.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5852" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>short episodes</name>
<description>Short episodes are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length. This means up to and including 10 minutes; shows with episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length are http://anidb.net/t6494 [half-length episodes] instead.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6349 [multi-segment episodes], which are regular episodes that are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5862" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-08">
<name>melodrama</name>
<description>A melodrama is a dramatic work that exaggerates plot and characters in order to appeal to the emotions, often with strongly stereotyped characters. Language, behaviour, or events which resemble melodramas are also called melodramatic. In scholarly and historical musical contexts melodramas are dramas of the 18th and 19th centuries in which orchestral music or song was used to accompany the action.
Melodrama is a style of drama that has been applied on the stage, in movies and television, and radio formats, from the 18th century to the present. Because of the long timeframe in which the style has existed, it is difficult to derive a precise definition. The term melodrama is most often used pejoratively, to suggest that the work to which the term is applied lacks sophistication or subtlety.
The term originated from the early 19th-century French word mélodrame, which is derived from Greek melos, music, and French drame, drama (from Late Latin drāma, which in turn derives from Greek drān, to do, perform).
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5916" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-26">
<name>product placement</name>
<description>Otherwise known as a "plug" or "writing commercials right into a show". The practice of prominently displaying or talking about a recognizable product in a program, in exchange for some consideration from the manufacturer, usually monetary. (Source: TV Tropes)
Particularly notorious example, Pizza Hut for the involvement with Code Geass, Darker than Black and other series.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5980" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-24">
<name>live-action imagery</name>
<description>This anime incorporates still images and/or video footage of real-world objects and locations into the animation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6030" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-22">
<name>otaku culture</name>
<description>Otaku (おたく/オタク) is a Japanese term used to refer to people with obsessive interests, particularly anime, manga, and video games. A female otaku is occasionally referred to as a fujoshi. (Source: Wikipedia)
Here certain aspects of this "fandom" are presented in more detail, e.g. the creation of doujinshi (self-published amateur manga).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6034" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>Engrish</name>
<description>Engrish is actually a mispronunciation of English, as can be the result of someone, who does not have English as their primary language of origin (such as Japanese or Chinese). Occasionally characters in the original Japanese dialogue version of an anime will speak in English... however; this often still requires the assistance of subtitles, for while the words are meant to be said in English, the sentence structure and letter pronunciation may still be strongly related to the person’s primary language.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6075" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-12">
<name>educational</name>
<description>The entire series (at least a major part of it) is centred on a particular subject. Information is fed to the audience in a sublime manner. Most of the time an on-screen written comment by the narrator (or translator) can be seen, e.g. biological specimen, medicine, process, etc. Sometimes at the end of every episode’s closing song, a 20 seconds educational clip is presented.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6399" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-25">
<name>episodic</name>
<description>An episodic anime consists of many successive short arcs that are generally 1-2 episodes in length, with strong plot continuity within each arc but generally little continuity from one arc to the next. For long shows (well upwards of 50 episodes), the episode count constraint is less tight; for example, a show with close to 250 episodes would also be considered episodic if it consisted of a majority of arcs of up to 3 or maybe 4 episodes and possibly also very few slightly longer arcs.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="99393" type="main character in" update="2019-12-16">
<rating votes="3">7.02</rating>
<name>Yatogame Monaka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>242174.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5" picture="233827.jpg">Tomatsu Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100468" type="main character in" update="2019-04-05">
<rating votes="1">9.69</rating>
<name>Tadakusa Mai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230980.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34741" picture="222846.jpg">Wakai Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100469" type="main character in" update="2019-04-05">
<rating votes="1">5.77</rating>
<name>Sasatsu Yanna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230981.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16085" picture="178446.jpg">Komatsu Mikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100711" type="main character in" update="2019-04-05">
<name>Jin Kaito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>230979.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="71" picture="171537.jpg">Ichiki Mitsuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100712" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-12-16">
<rating votes="1">2.08</rating>
<name>Jin Toshika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>242176.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32612" picture="223330.jpg">Toujou Hisako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107514" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-12-16">
<rating votes="1">2.08</rating>
<name>Shonai Lala</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>242175.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="617" picture="65451.jpg">Nanjou Yoshino</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107515" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-12-16">
<rating votes="1">2.08</rating>
<name>Jandara Rin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>242177.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34361" picture="127753.jpg">Matsui Eriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107516" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-12-16">
<name>Teppei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>242178.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2487" picture="23183.jpg">Akabane Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="225449" update="2020-01-28">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2020-01-05</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">また会えたでよ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">We Meet Again</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Comme on se retrouve</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">نلتقي مُجدداً</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mata Aeta de yo</title>
<summary>I went through a lot after moving to Nagoya and being forced to join the photography club, but I`ve pretty much settled in by now. My clubmates are Yatogame-chan with the thick Nagoya accent, Tadakusa Mai from Gifu Prefecture, and the club president Sasatsu Yanna, who`s from Mie Prefecture. I`m gonna have them teach me some more of the Nagoya dialect today! I really wish they`d stop saying "chin-chin" over and over, though...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792500</identifier>
<identifier>yatogame-chan-kansatsu-nikki</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="225450" update="2020-01-28">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2020-01-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">怖くにゃあ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Ain`t Scary</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Je nyai pas peur</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">لستُ مخيفة</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kowai Nyaa</title>
<summary>I went through a lot after moving to Nagoya and being forced to join the photography club, but I`ve pretty much settled in by now. My clubmates are Yatogame-chan with the thick Nagoya accent, Tadakusa Mai from Gifu Prefecture, and the club president Sasatsu Yanna, who`s from Mie Prefecture. I`m gonna have them teach me some more of the Nagoya dialect today! I really wish they`d stop saying "chin-chin" over and over, though...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792501</identifier>
<identifier>yatogame-chan-kansatsu-nikki</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="225451" update="2020-01-28">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2020-01-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">しょぼくにゃあ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It Ain`t Dull</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Vraiment décevant</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">ليست مُملة</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shoboku Nyaa</title>
<summary>It`s the day of the ball sports tournament! But just what the heck is this "taspony" sport we`re playing? And why is it that nobody I ask about it knows, either?! It seems like even Toshika wasn`t really able to talk to Yatogame about it... According to Yatogame, taspony is sort of like tennis, except you play it with your bare hands. Just what kind of sport is this, anyway?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792502</identifier>
<identifier>yatogame-chan-kansatsu-nikki</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="225452" update="2020-02-27">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2020-01-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ハブいてにゃあ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Didn`t Leave Nothin` Out</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sentimiaa d’exclusion</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">لم أترك شيئاً</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Habuite Nyaa</title>
<summary>It`s hot... So hot... But I`ve been through this before, haven`t I? But as we were sitting in the club room melting away, someone popped out of a locker. Turns out it wasn`t the product of some curse; it was just the photography club advisor, Rara-sensei. Wait, she was in the locker all that time, in this awful heat? She seems kinda spacey... I`m a little worried about her...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792503</identifier>
<identifier>yatogame-chan-kansatsu-nikki</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="225660" update="2019-12-28">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2019-12-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">直前スペシャル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chokuzen Special</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225661" update="2019-12-28">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2020-01-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">お正月だがね「八十亀ちゃんかんさつにっき 2さつめ」放送直前スペシャル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oshougatsu Daga ne "Yatogame-chan Kansatsu Nikki Nisatsume" Housou Chokuzen Special</title>
</episode>
<episode id="226213" update="2020-02-27">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2020-02-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">主食じゃにゃあ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It Ain`t a Main Dish</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Pas un alimiaa de base !</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">ليس طبقاً رئيسياً</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shushoku ja Nyaa</title>
<summary>Ugh, I caught a cold... I sent my sister out to buy a few things, but when the door to our house opened later, the one who came in was... Yatogame? Why? What`s she doing in my room? And what does "I`m gonna do what I`m gonna do" mean?! As I`m waiting anxiously to find out, Yatogame returns with a pot of miso-stewed udon and... what? Rice? I don`t need rice with udon...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792504</identifier>
<identifier>yatogame-chan-kansatsu-nikki</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="226214" update="2020-03-05">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2020-02-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">譲れにゃあ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Ain`t Backin` Down</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Je lâcherai pas</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">لن أتراجع</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuzurenyaa</title>
<summary>The term "the Nagoya skip" came into use when Nagoya was removed from the Nozomi Shinkansen`s route, and it`s been a real problem for the people of Nagoya. Toshika`s upset because the band she likes isn`t doing a concert here. Even the anime lineup is different here. Fear the Nagoya skip!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792505</identifier>
<identifier>yatogame-chan-kansatsu-nikki</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="226215" update="2020-03-05">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2020-02-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">飛ばさにゃあ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Ain`t Skippin` It</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le trou est comblé</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">لن أتخطاه</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tobasanyaa</title>
<summary>Man, what`s with this "Nagoya skip" anyway? Nothing good has happened since we moved to Nagoya, Tadakusa-san! Local idols? Are any of them hot guys? Wait, no way... oh my God... I have no choice but to support this! Onii-chan, I`m about to watch some music videos, so keep out!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792506</identifier>
<identifier>yatogame-chan-kansatsu-nikki</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="226216" update="2020-03-05">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2020-02-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ビルじゃにゃあ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It Ain`t a Building</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ch’est pas un immeuble</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">ليس بناءً</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Biru ja Nyaa</title>
<summary>I suggested that our club take part in the Nagoya Symbol Photo Contest, but no one seems excited about it! If we`re talking about the symbol of Nagoya, it`s gotta be Nagoya Castle, right?! The golden shachihoko statues are the embodiment of Nagoya! We`ve gotta go take pictures there! Right? You agree, don`t you, Yatogame? ...Yatogame?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792507</identifier>
<identifier>yatogame-chan-kansatsu-nikki</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="226975" update="2020-03-05">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2020-03-01</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">変じゃにゃあ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It Ain`t Weird</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">C’est pas bizarre</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">ليس غريباً</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hen ja Nyaa</title>
<summary>I walked into the club room to find Yatogame bound to a chair... Apparently, Tadakusa-chan doesn`t agree with the saying that Nagoya is one of the three ugliest populations in Japan. What`s going on with Yatogame`s hairstyle, anyway? Sasatsu and Tadakusa-chan are doing all kinds of things to her. And what`s a "Nagoya maki"? Does it involve fried shrimp?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792508</identifier>
<identifier>yatogame-chan-kansatsu-nikki</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="226976" update="2020-03-24">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2020-03-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">うすくにゃあ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It Ain`t Weak</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">C’est pas fade</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">ليست ضعيفة</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Usukunyaa</title>
<summary>Summer in Nagoya is as hot as ever. I really think Tadakusa-chan should switch to her summer uniform now... We all stopped by a convenience store to buy ice pops. What did Yatogame get? A Jun Hit Chocolate Bar? What is that? Is it new? And Sasatsu got... the Azuki Bar that`s famous for being super hard, huh? And what about Tadakusa-chan?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792509</identifier>
<identifier>yatogame-chan-kansatsu-nikki</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="226977" update="2020-03-24">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2020-03-15</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">けらいじゃにゃあ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Ain`t Yer Servant</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Pas ta servante !</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">لستُ خادمتك</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kerai ja Nyaa</title>
<summary>We were out walking around with Yatogame-chan when some grade school kid called out to her. Seems her name is Itemae Shiharu, and she and her friend, Koshiyasu Nanaho, are visiting Nagoya from out of town. Turns out Itemae is Yatogame`s cousin, and she`s... in middle school? Yatogame`s acting really weird, though... And now Sasatsu and Tadakusa-chan are, too?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792510</identifier>
<identifier>yatogame-chan-kansatsu-nikki</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="226978" update="2020-04-05">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2020-03-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">第3じゃにゃあ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It Ain`t Number Three</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ch’est pas la troisième</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">ليست رقم 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dai 3 ja Nyaa</title>
<summary>It looks like Yatogame was really shocked to hear someone say that Nagoya isn`t one of Japan`s three major cities. I mean, there are so many other cities in Japan, like Sapporo, Kyoto, Kobe, Sendai, Hiroshima, Fukuoka... But that aside, Yatogame seems to be having some kind of nightmare...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792511</identifier>
<identifier>yatogame-chan-kansatsu-nikki</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
