<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="14952" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>11</episodecount>
<startdate>2020-01-10</startdate>
<enddate>2020-03-20</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Uchi Tama?! Uchi no Tama Shirimasenka?</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">うちタマ?!~うちのタマ知りませんか?~</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Uchitama?! Have You Seen My Tama?</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="11909" type="Alternative Setting">Tama &amp; Friends: Uchi no Tama Shirimasenka?</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="194184">This was definitely the cutest series of this season!

The character design is adorable and the characters themselves are.. pure, childish, fun-loving or cool.

It`s all about friendship and having fun together.

You can`t get wrong with cat- (and dog-) content such as this and it`s just relaxing to watch this and chuckle here and there.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>https://uchitama.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="57775" type="Chief Animation Direction">Gushiken Mayu</name>
<name id="4255" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ootsuka Mai</name>
<name id="45418" type="Animation Work">Lapintrack</name>
<name id="31375" type="Animation Work">MAPPA</name>
<name id="4255" type="Character Design">Ootsuka Mai</name>
<name id="30884" type="Series Composition">Ueno Kimiko</name>
<name id="57495" type="Original Work">Sony Creative Products</name>
<name id="15969" type="Direction">Matsuda Kiyoshi</name>
<name id="2431" type="Music">Tom-H@ck</name>
</creators>
<description>In a city somewhere in Japan, there`s a flyer often seen on Third Street with a picture of a cat with a kinked tail, bearing the words: "Have you seen Tama?" A young boy gazes at the flyer, but he has fluffy ears on his head...!?
Watch the dogs and cats from Third Street take on a human form and get up to some mischief. Take a peek into the wonderful lives of Tama and his friends.
Source: Official website</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="73">3.47</permanent>
<temporary count="74">5.44</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>238597.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22947</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>39942</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://uchitama.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>https://uchitama-anime.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>うちタマ%3F!_〜うちのタマ知りませんか%3F〜</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5543</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>368742</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22435</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>uchitama_anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>uchitama-have-you-seen-my-tama</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2857" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>anthropomorphism</name>
<description>Anthropomorphism is the attribution of uniquely human characteristics to non-human beings, inanimate objects, or natural or supernatural phenomena. If it`s an animal or an object (AI excluded) and it speaks and/or does other human-like things (dresses up) then we`re dealing with anthropomorphism.
Anthropomorphism leans more on the animal-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t7 [juujin], which leans more on the human-looking side.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3865" parentid="6153" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-08-07">
<name>noitaminA</name>
<description>noitaminA (ノイタミナ) – Animation written backwards – is a Fuji Television programming block, devoted to anime, broadcast each Thursday night from 00:45 to 1:15. It was launched with the intention of expanding the target audience beyond the typical young male demographic.
The timeslot was expanded from half an hour to a full hour in 2010, and now airs Thursday nights from 00:45 to 1:45.
noitaminA aired its first non-anime series in 2010, with the premiere of the live-action adaptation of Moyashimon. On April 15, 2010, Fuji TV and FUNimation announced an agreement that allows FUNimation to simulcast series from the noitaminA block in North America within an hour of their airing in Japan.</description>
<picurl>36897.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3867" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>ED variety</name>
<description>Several ED sequences in this anime have either a different song or different animation, maybe even to the point of having a unique ED for each episode.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3968" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-26">
<name>animal protagonist</name>
<description>The anime revolves around an animal, usually only communicating with typical onomatopoeia. The animal mostly lives in a human family and has adventures on a regular base. This can be the discovery of a new room, or being lost by having taken a wrong turn in the outside world.
Typical example: http://anidb.net/a5801 [Chii`s Sweet Home].
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t4259 [animal world], where the whole world is composed of animals.</description>
<picurl>10255.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4176" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-05-14">
<name>OP and ED sung by characters</name>
<description>OP and/or ED in this anime is sung by the characters and animation shows them singing.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4431" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-04-06">
<name>love at first sight</name>
<description>Plot device: When two characters meet for the first time, at least one party, supposedly, immediately falls in love with the other party, and from then on tries to get to know that party better.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4498" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-20">
<name>heart-warming</name>
<description>The story and its characters give off good vibes — includes elevated feelings of affection such as tenderness, sympathy and love, all in one package.
The kind of anime which leaves you with a warm feeling inside and you can not stop smiling while watching it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6349" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-13">
<name>multi-segment episodes</name>
<description>Multi-segment episodes are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t5852 [short episodes], which are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length (up to and including 10 minutes).
Also not to be confused with an OVA or music video with multiple (otherwise unrelated) full-length http://anidb.net/t7241 [bundled episodes] consolidated into a single episode video track.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="85216" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-12-24">
<name>Okamoto Takeshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>242387.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3830" picture="25450.jpg">Terasaki Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103485" type="main character in" update="2019-06-13">
<name>Nora</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>234761.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1678" picture="68277.jpg">Kaji Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103486" type="main character in" update="2020-01-10">
<name>Mikawa Kuro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>234763.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39792" picture="176251.jpg">Umehara Yuuichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103487" type="main character in" update="2020-01-10">
<name>Kuramochi Bull</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>234767.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="612" picture="79531.jpg">Maeno Tomoaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103488" type="main character in" update="2020-01-10">
<name>Yamada Pochi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>234747.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4755" picture="183070.jpg">Ono Kenshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103489" type="main character in" update="2020-01-10">
<name>Okamoto Tama</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>234745.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36680" picture="153752.jpg">Saitou Souma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103490" type="main character in" update="2020-01-10">
<name>Kiso Tora</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>234751.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30311" picture="223328.jpg">Shirai Yuusuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103491" type="main character in" update="2020-01-10">
<rating votes="2">6.63</rating>
<name>Oketani Koma</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>234757.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16804" picture="224734.jpg">Kurosawa Tomoyo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103492" type="main character in" update="2020-01-10">
<name>Kawara Beh</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>234755.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38579" picture="225249.jpg">Uchida Yuuma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103493" type="main character in" update="2020-01-10">
<rating votes="2">6.63</rating>
<name>Hanasaki Momo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>234753.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="176" picture="192484.jpg">Hanazawa Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103494" type="main character in" update="2020-01-10">
<name>Noda Gon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>234765.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29" picture="202917.jpg">Hatano Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107622" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-12-24">
<name>Kuramochi-kun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>242386.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33633" picture="151771.jpg">Takahashi Minami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107623" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-12-24">
<name>Kiso Tomekichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>242384.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3396" picture="24705.jpg">Takatsuka Masaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107624" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-12-24">
<rating votes="1">2.08</rating>
<name>Hanasaki Emi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>242385.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20762" picture="131325.jpg">Sakura Ayane</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109990" type="appears in" update="2020-05-10">
<name>Sakura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>247234.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="109991" type="appears in" update="2020-05-10">
<name>Waka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>247235.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38431" picture="224824.jpg">Yashiro Taku</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109992" type="appears in" update="2020-05-10">
<name>Choco</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>247236.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42697" picture="223257.jpg">Kinugawa Rika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109993" type="appears in" update="2020-05-10">
<name>Dragon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>247237.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43410" picture="225078.jpg">Horie Shun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109994" type="appears in" update="2020-05-10">
<name>Bermann</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>247238.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33502" picture="246104.jpg">Karino Shou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109995" type="appears in" update="2020-05-10">
<name>Seventh Street Young Kings</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="110121" type="appears in" update="2020-05-16">
<name>Kai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>247489.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38907" picture="243208.jpg">Nanami Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="110122" type="appears in" update="2020-05-16">
<name>Leo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>247491.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="31313" picture="84218.jpg">Hanae Natsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="225627" update="2019-12-27">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-01-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">うちのタマ知りませんか? / 犬会議 / 俺たちのワイハ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Have You Seen My Tama? / Dog Meeting / Our Waiha</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uchi no Tama Shirimasenka? Inu Kaigi / Oretachi no Waiha</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>793635</identifier>
<identifier>uchitama-have-you-seen-my-tama</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="225628" update="2020-02-27">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-01-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">俺さまはブル / 平和 / 海へ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My Name Is Bull / Peace / Going to the Beach</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ore-sama wa Bull / Heiwa / Umi e</title>
<summary>Bull tries his best to be cool, but then he meets Momo. Gon teaches Kuro something interesting about cats and dogs. Tama and Pochi get lost again and end up at the beach.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>793636</identifier>
<identifier>uchitama-have-you-seen-my-tama</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="225629" update="2020-02-27">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-01-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">3丁目最強の男 / 3丁目最弱の男</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Strongest Guy on Third Street / The Weakest Guy on Third Street</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">3-Choume Saikyou no Otoko / 3-Choume Saijaku no Otoko</title>
<summary>Koma and Tora argue about who the strongest person on Third Street is, so they hold a tournament! But because of this tournament, a certain someone feels like he was the weakest guy on Third Street.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>793637</identifier>
<identifier>uchitama-have-you-seen-my-tama</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="225630" update="2020-02-29">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-01-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">タマのお仕事 / 我輩はゴンである / 犬のおまわりさん / 犬のおまわりさん2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tama`s Job / My Name Is Gon / Dog Police / Dog Police 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tama no Oshigoto / Wagahai wa Gon de Aru / Inu no Omawari-san / Inu no Omawari-san 2</title>
<summary>What does Tama do all day while the other cats and dogs are working? Gon has a one One Dog Show where he can never get bored. And Kuro patrols Third Street to protect the peace.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>793638</identifier>
<identifier>uchitama-have-you-seen-my-tama</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="226285" update="2020-03-07">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-02-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">トラの初恋 / お風呂に入ろう / 続・犬のおまわりさん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tora`s First Love / Let`s Take a Bath / Dog Police Continued</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tora no Hatsukoi / Ofuro ni Hairou / Zoku: Inu no Omawari-san</title>
<summary>Tora, Pochi, and Tama venture inside to an abandoned house. It`s Pet Day at Matsu Bath, so all the cats and dogs enjoy a bath together. And Momo has gotten in trouble with the Dog Police.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>793639</identifier>
<identifier>uchitama-have-you-seen-my-tama</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="226286" update="2020-03-14">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-02-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">仁義なき犬猫・前編 / 仁義なき犬猫・後編 / 夜のピクニック</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Battle of Dogs and Cats, Part One / Battle of Dogs and Cats, Part Two / Night Picnic</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jingi Naki Inuneko: Zenpen / Jingi Naki Inuneko: Kouhen / Yoru no Picnic</title>
<summary>The Seventh Street Young Kings have their sights set on taking over Third Street. Can the Third Street Crazy Cats defend their territory? Later on, the Third Street cats and dogs enjoy a night picnic together.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>793640</identifier>
<identifier>uchitama-have-you-seen-my-tama</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="226287" update="2020-03-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-02-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">タマ誘拐される / おったま毛 / 猫カフェ・ヴァイオレット</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tama Gets Kidnapped / Surprise Furball / Cat Cafe Violet</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tama Yuukai Sareru / Ottama Ke / Neko Cafe Violet</title>
<summary>Tama gets kidnapped and the cats and dogs of Third Street are on hot pursuit! Momo`s button flies off as she catches it in the air. What could be causing this? Finally, the cats and dogs of Third Street hear about a new cat café in the next town over.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>793641</identifier>
<identifier>uchitama-have-you-seen-my-tama</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="226288" update="2020-03-28">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-02-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">まつりばやし</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Festival Music</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Matsuri Bayashi</title>
<summary>The Summer Festival is happening on Third Street, but there`s something about the festival music that reminds Nora of his past.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>793642</identifier>
<identifier>uchitama-have-you-seen-my-tama</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="227043" update="2020-04-05">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-03-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">あいつがまちにやってきた / ノラと子猫</title>
<title xml:lang="en">He`s in Town / Nora and the Kitten</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aitsu ga Kichi ni Yatte Kita / Nora to Koneko</title>
<summary>An AIBO has come to Third Street looking for Tama. Nora finds a stray kitten and can`t help but take him under his wing for a little while.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>793643</identifier>
<identifier>uchitama-have-you-seen-my-tama</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="227044" update="2020-04-13">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-03-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">3丁目クイズ / 寝ちゃダメ / ベーとブル~ふたりは仲良し~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Don`t Fall Asleep / Third Street Quiz / Beh and Bull Are BFFs</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">3-Choume Quiz / Necha Dame / Beh to Bull: Futari wa Nakayoshi</title>
<summary>Tama and Tora try not to fall asleep so they can try to get tasty treats. Gon quizzes Tama on how well he knows Third Street. And then, Beh and Bull go on an adventure and they become best friends.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>794834</identifier>
<identifier>uchitama-have-you-seen-my-tama</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="227045" update="2020-04-19">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-03-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">タマの正体 / 猫会議 / ぼくの大切なもの</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tama`s True Identity / Cat Meeting / My Treasure</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tama no Shoutai / Neko Kaigi / Boku no Taisetsu na Mono</title>
<summary>Tama has discovered his true identity! What could it be? The cats gather and have a meeting regarding the strangeness of humans.  Tama and the gang find out what Takeshi`s and Kuramochi`s treasures are.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>794835</identifier>
<identifier>uchitama-have-you-seen-my-tama</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
