<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="14964" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2020-01-15</startdate>
<enddate>2020-04-01</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Isekai Quartet 2</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">異世界かるてっと2</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Isekai Quartet 2</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">이세계 콰르텟 2</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">异世界四重奏 2</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="15481" type="Sequel">Isekai Quartet 3</anime>
<anime id="14435" type="Prequel">Isekai Quartet</anime>
<anime id="11370" type="Other">Re:Zero kara Hajimeru Isekai Seikatsu</anime>
<anime id="11905" type="Other">Youjo Senki</anime>
<anime id="10816" type="Other">Overlord</anime>
<anime id="14477" type="Other">Shinchou Yuusha: Kono Yuusha ga Ore Tsueee Kuse ni Shinchou Sugiru</anime>
<anime id="13246" type="Other">Tate no Yuusha no Nariagari</anime>
<anime id="11261" type="Other">Kono Subarashii Sekai ni Shukufuku o!</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="231802">S1 was a blast, S2 kinda lost its steam in the second half

For the better first half of the season (S2) when the hype from S1 was still fresh, the jokes and character interaction were still top notch as if it seamlessly transitioned over from S1.
However, somehow mid season (probably when shield bro joined the party), things started slowing down and the jokes couldn`t keep up

So yes, they attempted to keep things fresh by adding in more characters from other new popular isekai, however they really are cameos at best (and I think shield bro is just boring and felt out of place in Isekai Quartet). May be it`s the confined scenario within the school that shackles the creativity or that the final battle that`s rather stale and uninteresting or the lack of development.

Watch on if you did S1, the 1st half of S2 is still pretty good, and to be fair the 2nd half does still have spots of really good laugh. For me for now, 5/10</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://isekai-quartet.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="23382" type="Animation Work">Studio Pu Yukai</name>
<name id="21054" type="Character Design">Takehara Minoru</name>
<name id="43256" type="Original Work">Akatsuki Natsume</name>
<name id="42661" type="Original Work">Maruyama Kugane</name>
<name id="44789" type="Original Work">Carlo Zen</name>
<name id="43464" type="Original Work">Nagatsuki Tappei</name>
<name id="21007" type="Direction">Ashina Minoru</name>
<name id="21054" type="Chief Animation Direction">Takehara Minoru</name>
<name id="5818" type="Music">Kawada Ruka</name>
</creators>
<description>* Isekai Quartet is a crossover series featuring characters from popular “isekai” franchises illustrated in cute, superdeformed style.
The button appeared out of nowhere. There weren’t any signs NOT to push it…so the solution is obvious, right? Is it a trap or the start of something new and exciting? The crews of Re:Zero, Overlord, Konosuba, and The Saga of Tanya the Evil will find out when they go from their world to another and get stuck in…class?! See what adorable chaos they’ll get up to in this collection of shorts!
Source: crunchyroll</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="283">5.27</permanent>
<temporary count="284">6.69</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>239201.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22549</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>39988</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://isekai-quartet.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Isekai_Quartet</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>異世界かるてっと</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5537</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>368985</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22459</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>isekai_quartet</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="26">
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=DgAW7Nlcqlw</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=Y3V7h_2qIcQ</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=OFHc0L87Z2g</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>isekai-quartet</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B0849KFLMW</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2773" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-18">
<name>magic circles</name>
<description>A magic circle is circle or sphere of space marked out by practitioners of many branches of ritual magic. It may be marked physically, drawn in salt or chalk, for example, or merely visualised.
Traditionally, circles have been used by ritual magicians to form a protective barrier between themselves and what they summoned. Nowadays, circles often have the more benign function of containing and concentrating the energy raised during a ritual. Circles can also be used as barriers for non-magical work such as meditation.
Generally, as with most magical practices, an incantation is recited stating the purpose and nature of the circle, often repeating an assortment of divine and angelic names.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>32800.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3020" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-08-01">
<name>chibi ED</name>
<description>Some or all of the endings feature chibi versions of the characters.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3202" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-04">
<name>adoring fan club</name>
<description>A character, group or characters, or an organisation is considered so awesome that a adoring fan club is formed to idolise them. Not only do they have notable admirers, but their fans become organised in such a fashion to have a following that could only be guaranteed in real life by precise and long increments of paparazzi-like stalking.
If the character is sufficiently cool, an instant fan club may happen practically overnight (i.e., within a few episodes of them being introduced), although the subject of admiration typically has mixed feelings about the entire affair.</description>
<picurl>48684.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3909" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>talking is a free action</name>
<description>Time in comics is flexible. Each panel shows a single event, which is usually accompanied by a length of dialog, which must take some time to say. This disparity is usually accepted if it isn`t taken to extremes.
But often, characters will exposit when it`s most needed: at the story`s climax, when both the intricacies of the plot and the intensity of action hit their highest.
While the Heroes Outrun the Fireball, Mr. Exposition might explain why the Evil Overlord`s death caused the explosion. The Action Girl can deliver impressive lectures on why the monster`s Achilles` Heel will work, while still engaging in Waif-Fu. The Superhero can quip to his heart`s content and explain his abilities while dueling one insignificant mobster, or deliver a Kirk Summation during the course of a single Finishing Move. Sometimes even apparent mere mortals can give a lecture on what is happening when it would be a much better idea to simply run like hell.
Without stopping to breathe, apparently.
Source: TvTrope</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4474" parentid="2655" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-07-04">
<name>self-parody</name>
<description>The anime is a parody of itself. 
I.e. the authors make fun of the genre they are portraying, and take the actions of their characters and story lightly.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6034" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>Engrish</name>
<description>Engrish is actually a mispronunciation of English, as can be the result of someone, who does not have English as their primary language of origin (such as Japanese or Chinese). Occasionally characters in the original Japanese dialogue version of an anime will speak in English... however; this often still requires the assistance of subtitles, for while the words are meant to be said in English, the sentence structure and letter pronunciation may still be strongly related to the person’s primary language.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6494" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>half-length episodes</name>
<description>Half-length episodes are regular episodes that are somewhat shorter than the standard length. This includes episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length; shows with episodes up to and including 10 minutes are http://anidb.net/t5852 [short episodes] instead.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6744" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-05">
<name>isekai</name>
<description>An isekai story is one in which the lead characters are transferred to and become stuck or trapped in another world, one completely different from the one they lived in up until the transfer. The new world is commonly a http://anidb.net/t2628 [fictional world], such as a http://anidb.net/t2838 [parallel world] or http://anidb.net/t2839 [virtual world] (other fictional world types can also apply). What defines the isekai genre is that the characters are sent to another world, often but not always a parallel one, and they generally cannot come back permanently without meeting a highly specific goal.
In order to adapt to their new environment, they must use the abilities and knowledge brought from their former world as well as any that may have been bestowed upon them by their brave new world. In some cases, they will seek and eventually find a way to return; in others, they will gleefully embrace their new life.
http://anidb.net/a144 [Inuyasha] is an example where isekai applies to a fictional world that is not also a parallel or virtual world. http://anidb.net/ch7246 [Higurashi Kagome] climbs down an ancient well at her grandfather`s shrine and is transported to feudal Japan (time travel). While she eventually gains the physical ability to travel back and forth between her time period and feudal Japan, her bonds and responsibilities to feudal Japan tie her there until they are ultimately resolved.
For clarity, below is an illustrative example where isekai is applied to a non-fictional, non-parallel, non-virtual world.

* The main characters are from Earth. One day, they are abducted by Nazis from Mars (alternate "world") are brought back to their Martian base. The main characters are trapped on Mars. Their only escape is to defeat the Nazis and steal their spaceship to return to Earth (specific goal required to escape); they are left to thier own devices, with no prospect of help from Earth, and no way to contact Earth.
</description>
<picurl>210952.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="101316" type="main character in" update="2019-03-08">
<rating votes="24">7.33</rating>
<name>Ainz</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>231102.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="315" picture="70740.jpg">Hino Satoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101317" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-03-08">
<name>Aura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>231105.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="641" picture="31202.jpg">Katou Emiri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101318" type="main character in" update="2019-03-08">
<name>Albedo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>231103.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23483" picture="85663.jpg">Hara Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101319" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-03-08">
<name>Cocytus</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>231104.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="178" picture="228660.jpg">Miyake Kenta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101320" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-03-08">
<name>Shalltear</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>231099.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28602" picture="131381.jpg">Uesaka Sumire</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101321" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-03-08">
<name>Demiurge</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>231100.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2281" picture="171603.jpg">Katou Masayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101322" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-03-08">
<name>Mare</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>231101.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23686" picture="224554.jpg">Uchiyama Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101323" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-03-08">
<name>Megumin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>231108.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38380" picture="224406.jpg">Takahashi Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101324" type="main character in" update="2019-03-08">
<name>Aqua</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>231107.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34626" picture="144409.jpg">Amamiya Sora</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101325" type="main character in" update="2019-03-08">
<name>Kazuma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>231109.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4821" picture="186259.jpg">Fukushima Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101326" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-03-08">
<name>Darkness</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>231106.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20497" picture="62433.jpg">Kayano Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101327" type="main character in" update="2019-03-08">
<rating votes="5">9.32</rating>
<name>Emilia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>231114.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38380" picture="224406.jpg">Takahashi Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101328" type="main character in" update="2019-03-08">
<name>Subaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>231112.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38670" picture="185856.jpg">Kobayashi Yuusuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101329" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-03-08">
<name>Pack</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>231113.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23686" picture="224554.jpg">Uchiyama Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101330" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-03-08">
<name>Beatrice</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>231116.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="600" picture="148972.jpg">Arai Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101331" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-03-08">
<name>Ram</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>231115.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32020" picture="127735.jpg">Murakawa Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101332" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-03-08">
<rating votes="3">5.12</rating>
<name>Rem</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>231111.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21013" picture="201781.jpg">Minase Inori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101333" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-03-08">
<name>Roswaal</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>231110.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101334" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-03-08">
<name>Glanz</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>231124.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38670" picture="185856.jpg">Kobayashi Yuusuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101335" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-03-08">
<name>Koenig</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>231121.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38674" picture="215795.jpg">Kasama Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101336" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-03-08">
<name>Zettour</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>231127.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="297" picture="233915.jpg">Ootsuka Houchuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101337" type="main character in" update="2019-03-08">
<name>Tanya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>231129.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1625" picture="226033.jpg">Yuuki Aoi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101338" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-03-08">
<name>Neumann</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>231123.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40456" picture="181638.jpg">Hayashi Daichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101339" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-03-08">
<name>Rudersdorf</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>231118.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="343" picture="140430.jpg">Genda Tesshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101340" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-03-08">
<name>Rerugen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>231120.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="233" picture="228661.jpg">Miki Shin`ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101341" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-03-08">
<name>Weiss</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>231125.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39583" picture="186257.jpg">Hamano Daiki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101342" type="main character in" update="2019-03-08">
<name>Visha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>231119.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2296" picture="189623.jpg">Hayami Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108036" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-01-16">
<name>Filo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>243796.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="430" picture="246278.jpg">Hidaka Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108037" type="main character in" update="2020-01-16">
<name>Raphtalia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>243795.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21733" picture="152476.jpg">Seto Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108038" type="main character in" update="2020-01-16">
<rating votes="1">8.17</rating>
<name>Iwatani Naofumi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>243794.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34296" picture="225238.jpg">Ishikawa Kaito</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="222201" update="2019-10-12">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-10-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">『異世界かるてっと 2』 PV</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 01 (1:33)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">`Isekai Quartet 2` PV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225530" update="2019-12-24">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2019-12-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">『異世界かるてっと 2』 PV第2弾</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 02 (0:40)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">`Isekai Quartet 2` PV Dai 2 Dan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225531" update="2019-12-24">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2019-12-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">『異世界かるてっと 2』 番宣CM</title>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 01 (0:15)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">`Isekai Quartet 2` Bansen CM</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225778" update="2020-01-01">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2020-01-15</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">参戦! てんこうせい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Join the Fight! Transfer Student</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sansen! Tenkousei</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792774</identifier>
<identifier>isekai-quartet</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="225779" update="2020-01-22">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2020-01-22</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">潜入! こうちょうしつ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sneak In! The Principal`s Office</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sennyuu! Kouchoushitsu</title>
<summary>Life`s great in this world, except for one thing: there`s no alcohol! When the students sneak into the principal`s office to get their fix from his stash, they run into more than they bargained for.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792775</identifier>
<identifier>isekai-quartet</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="225780" update="2020-01-29">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2020-01-29</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">反省! しどうしつ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Uh-Oh! Detention!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hansei! Shidoushitsu</title>
<summary>This new world is a great place: no fighting, no danger, and the classes are easy. But you REALLY don`t want to get detention!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792776</identifier>
<identifier>isekai-quartet</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="225781" update="2020-02-27">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2020-02-05</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">窮地! がくりょくてすと</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pinch! Test of Learning</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyuuchi! Gakuryoku Test</title>
<summary>It`s time for a test! Everybody expects Ains to score highly, but… he never even passed middle school!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792777</identifier>
<identifier>isekai-quartet</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="226241" update="2020-01-22">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2020-01-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="226242" update="2020-01-22">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2020-01-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="226519" update="2020-02-27">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2020-02-12</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">勤勉! ばれんたいんでー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Work Hard! Valentine`s Day</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kinben! Valentine Day</title>
<summary>It`s Valentine`s Day, which means it`s time to give chocolate to the boy you like! But an unexpected face makes an appearance…
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792778</identifier>
<identifier>isekai-quartet</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="226520" update="2020-02-27">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2020-02-19</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">激突! どっじぼーる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Clash! Dodgeball</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekitotsu! Dodgeball</title>
<summary>It`s time for a battle to settle the most important question of all: what do you put on your chicken wings?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792779</identifier>
<identifier>isekai-quartet</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="226521" update="2020-02-27">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2020-02-26</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">興奮! しんたいそくてい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Excitement! Physicals Day</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koufun! Shintai Sokutai</title>
<summary>It`s time for physicals, and everybody`s ready to get naked and get on the scale! Who will be brave enough to go peek at the opposite sex?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792780</identifier>
<identifier>isekai-quartet</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="226522" update="2020-03-03">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2020-03-04</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">挑戦! あるばいと</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Challenge! Part-Time Job</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chousen! Arbeit</title>
<summary>Visha`s been working overtime lately. But what does she need the money for?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>792781</identifier>
<identifier>isekai-quartet</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="227142" update="2020-03-11">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2020-03-11</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">調査! はじめてのおつかい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Investigate! First Errand</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chousa! Hajimete no Otsukai</title>
<summary>It`s time for a play! But what kind of play should they put on? Filo will find out!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>794274</identifier>
<identifier>isekai-quartet</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="227143" update="2020-03-18">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2020-03-18</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">決起! がくえんさい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rise Up! School Festival</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kekki! Gakuensai</title>
<summary>It`s time for a school festival! But something is lurking outside the school…
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>794275</identifier>
<identifier>isekai-quartet</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="227144" update="2020-03-26">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2020-03-25</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">開幕! がくえんさい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It Begins! School Festival</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaimaku! Gakuensai</title>
<summary>The curtain rises on the school festival! There`s a special guest, too…
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>794276</identifier>
<identifier>isekai-quartet</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="227145" update="2020-02-26">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2020-04-01</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">開演! しょーたいむ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Show Begins! Showtime</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaien! Showtime</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>794277</identifier>
<identifier>isekai-quartet</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
