<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="14965" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2019-10-04</startdate>
<enddate>2019-10-04</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Strike Witches: Gekijouban 501 Butai Hasshin Shimasu!</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ストライクウィッチーズ 劇場版 501部隊発進しますっ!</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="14205" type="Prequel">Strike Witches: 501 Butai Hasshin Shimasu!</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://w-witch.jp/501_takeoff/</url>
<creators>
<name id="55699" type="Animation Work">Giga Production</name>
<name id="22710" type="Animation Work">Acca Effe</name>
<name id="18003" type="Character Design">Ajiki Kei</name>
<name id="10960" type="Original Work">Shimada Fumikane</name>
<name id="35253" type="Direction">Itou Fumio</name>
<name id="1905" type="Music">Nagaoka Seikou</name>
</creators>
<ratings>
<permanent count="5">4.74</permanent>
<temporary count="6">6.50</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>236281.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22342</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>39987</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://w-witch.jp/501_takeoff/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Strike_Witches</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ストライクウィッチーズ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>368963</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22311</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>w_witch_anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<characters>
<character id="98" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-14">
<rating votes="142">7.61</rating>
<name>Francesca Lucchini</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Joining the 501st from the Duchy of Romagna, Francesca is the youngest soldier of the unit at a mere twelve years. Her rank is that of a Warrant officer and her unit affiliation was with Romania`s Regia Aeronautica 4th Air Unit. Francesca is often childish and self-indulgent, shirking training and other duties in order to have fun around the base or nap. However, in battle she displays a true talent and passion for flying. Also displayed as having the ears and tail of a black leopard. Her best friend is Shirley, as the two are often seen together.</description>
<picture>130734.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="305" picture="37148.jpg">Saitou Chiwa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-04-03">
<rating votes="112">8.04</rating>
<name>Charlotte E. Yeager</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A sixteen year old girl hailing from the United States of Liberion with the rank of Flight Lieutenant. Magnanimous in character, tall and buxom in appearance, Charlotte ("Shirley" to her friends) is a thrill-seeker who is fascinated by speed. Like a speedy hare, she gains the ears and tail of a rabbit when equipped with her Striker.</description>
<picture>65913.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="51" picture="39247.jpg">Koshimizu Ami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-04-03">
<rating votes="132">6.09</rating>
<name>Perrine-H. Clostermann</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Perrine is a wealthy and proper fifteen year old Gallian girl who looks down on some of the less-refined habits of her peers. The emotional scars left by the Neuroi`s conquest of her homeland cause her numerous problems. She often refuses to work as part of a team, and develops a dislike for the upstart newcomer Yoshika due to her attachment to Mio, which eventually develops into full-blown jealousy. When wearing her Striker Unit, she gains the dark ears and tail of a Chartreux. Perrine holds the rank of Flying Officer and her original unit was the Armée de l`Air 802nd Flying Corps.</description>
<picture>65912.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="38" picture="171532.jpg">Sawashiro Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-01-13">
<rating votes="101">6.03</rating>
<name>Lynette Bishop</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Fifteen years old, Lynette is the only Witch in the 501st who is native to the Britannia Federation. The middle child of eight siblings, Lynette developed very domestic and practical habits from helping to take care of them. Similarly domestic is the Scottish Fold, from which her Striker-equipped animal features are based. Plagued by occasional clumsiness and sometimes overlooked, she nevertheless strives to do her best. After she meets Yoshika, the two eventually become best friends. Holds the rank of Sergeant and her affiliation is the Royal Air Force 610th Fighter Squadron.</description>
<picture>130692.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="308" picture="44975.jpg">Nazuka Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="110" type="main character in" update="2013-01-14">
<rating votes="106">6.63</rating>
<name>Sakamoto Mio</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The first Strike Witch and sub-commander of the unit, with the commissioned rank of Squadron Leader and official rank of Major. Mio is also the oldest witch at nineteen (later, twenty) years old and, like Yoshika, comes from Fuso. She is seemingly the toughest and most mature of the Witches, being an experienced veteran of the early fighting against the Neuroi. She knew Yoshika`s father while he was first designing the Striker Unit and was the first person to pilot one. Her usual task is to train new recruits, and in this role she becomes a very strict disciplinarian, appropriately gaining the ears and tail of a Doberman when equipped with her Striker. Otherwise she is quite friendly, if a little too forward at times, with a very distinct laugh. Under Mio`s eyepatch is a magic eye that grants her increased visual prowess and the ability to spot Neuroi cores when used.</description>
<picture>130735.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="314" picture="10231.jpeg">Seto Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="114" type="main character in" update="2013-01-13">
<rating votes="146">5.51</rating>
<name>Miyafuji Yoshika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The main character of the series, age fourteen and hailing from the Fuso Empire. A typical young girl who comes from a family of clinicians who use their magic powers to heal people. Yoshika gains the features of a mame-shiba when using said power. Her father designed the Striker Units the Strike Witches use to fight. However, because her father died in the war she is vehemently against fighting when Mio Sakamoto appears to recruit her. Only after entering combat for the first time, helping to defend the Fuso fleet heading to Britannia from a Neuroi attack, does she decide to join the 501st. Now she holds the rank of Sergeant.</description>
<picture>130695.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="304" picture="17139.jpg">Fukuen Misato</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="123" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-14">
<rating votes="116">6.51</rating>
<name>Minna-Dietlinde Wilcke</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The ranking officer of the 501st Joint Fighter Wing at eighteen years old, Minna has a sisterly air that shows her concern for those under her command. Whether in or out of battle, her first priority is the safety of her subordinates. Her more gentle demeanor means that she often acts as the "good cop" to Mio`s "bad cop" when it comes to discipline. She also has a talent for singing, wanting to become a professional before she joined the war effort. However, she gave up that dream when her lover was killed in battle. Because of this, she is afraid of losing anybody else, which leads her to eventually give an order that prohibits the male workers on the base from having unauthorized contact with the witches. Alluding to her namesake, Minna gains wolf features when equipped for combat. She has the power of clairvoyance used to analyze situations such as enemy muster, hidden spies and identify targets.</description>
<picture>130693.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="135" picture="16884.jpg">Tanaka Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="149" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-04-03">
<rating votes="107">7.37</rating>
<name>Gertrud Barkhorn</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Eighteen year old Witch from Karlsland; a Flight Lieutenant formerly of the Luftwaffe JG 52. Quiet, efficient, and private, Gertrud (known as "Trude" to her friends) tends to support her comrades from the shadows. Her naturally calm attitude grants her great battlefield stamina, allowing her to rack up an impressive shot-down tally. A long-time acquaintance of Minna and Erica, she is often seen supporting the former in her leadership tasks and chastising the latter for her sloppiness. She has a younger sister named Chris who was badly injured during the invasion of her country and vaguely resembles Yoshika. Her magical power grants her the most physical strength of all the Witches to the extent where she can lift a steel girder many times her size. In flight she gains the features of a German Wirehaired Pointer.</description>
<picture>65911.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="309" picture="17145.jpg">Sonozaki Mie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="155" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-14">
<rating votes="114">7.62</rating>
<name>Erica Hartmann</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Karlsland`s sixteen year old "ultra ace" of the Luftwaffe JG 52 with more than 200 confirmed victories and the rank of Flying Officer. While extremely efficient and strategic in battle, Erica is surprisingly sloppy with her belongings and often neglects cleaning tasks. The type of person who is only serious when the situation calls for it. Her special technique is an offensive barrel roll named Sturm. With her Striker Unit equipped, Erica gains Dachshund features.</description>
<picture>130732.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="313" picture="158104.jpg">Nogawa Sakura</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="156" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-14">
<rating votes="197">7.91</rating>
<name>Eila Ilmatar Juutilainen</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Eila Ilmatar Juutilainen is the fifteen year old top ace of the Suomus Air Force 24th Unit with the rank of Pilot Officer (although the three roses on her collar would indicate the rank of captain). Eila`s hobby is fortune-telling with tarot cards, although the accuracy of her predictions is questionable at best. In battle however, she literally has the magical power of seeing into the future, allowing her to evade incoming attacks with ease. Somewhat mischievous, like the black fox whose features she gains in flight. She is particularly affectionate towards Sanya and will become cold to anyone who comes too close to her, this usually being Yoshika. In combat her weapons of choice are the MG42 and Suomi M1931 submachine gun. Eila`s Striker Unit is based on the Messerschmitt Bf-109G-2 and she is based on the ace Eino Ilmari Juutilainen.</description>
<picture>193261.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3622" picture="214935.jpg">Oohashi Ayuru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="159" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-13">
<rating votes="227">8.40</rating>
<name>Sanya V. Litvyak</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sanya V. Litvyak is the single Witch out of the Orussia Empire at thirteen years old. Preferring to stay indoors during the day, Sanya has been described as "nocturnal." At times she is literally asleep on her feet, counting on Eila to move her around. Despite this somewhat limiting her contact with the other members of the 501st, her low profile makes her ideal for night missions and sneak attacks. Also helping her in this duty is her magical specialty, the ability to read signals such as radio waves that are invisible to the naked eye, giving her a highly advanced spatial awareness. Gains the ears and tail of a black cat with her Striker Unit equipped. Sanya`s rank is Flying Officer and her original unit affiliation is the Orussia Imperial Army 586th Fighter Regiment. Her Striker Unit design is based on the MiG60 (a fictional warbird combining features of the MiG-1, MiG-3, and Yakovlev Yak-1) and her pilot archetype is http://anidb.net/ch85347 [Lydia Litvyak].</description>
<picture>130691.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="15655" picture="44791.jpg">Kadowaki Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41150" type="main character in" update="2012-11-21">
<rating votes="11">4.60</rating>
<name>Hattori Shizuka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hattori Shizuka is a Witch from Fuso and her archetype is Utou Kazushi. She is a student of the Imperial Fuso Navy Military Academy.</description>
<picture>128411.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1614" picture="148394.jpg">Uchida Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="218275" update="2019-06-25">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2019-10-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
