<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="14977" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>0</episodecount>
<startdate>2020-10</startdate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Shingeki no Kyojin The Final Season</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="synonym">الهجوم على العمالقة: الجزء الاخير</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">進撃の巨人 attack on titan The Final Season</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="14444" type="Prequel">Shingeki no Kyojin Season 3 (2019)</anime>
</relatedanime>
<picture>235592.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22277</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>40028</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Attack_on_Titan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>進撃の巨人_(アニメ)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>368989</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>anime_shingeki</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<characters>
<character id="51114" type="main character in" update="2013-11-17">
<rating votes="179">3.85</rating>
<name>Armin Arlert</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Eren`s best friend, he is physically and emotionally weak. His strategic abilities have saved Eren and Mikasa several times. He himself does not notice the things he does for Eren and Mikasa, and believes himself to be completely incompetent and hates himself for having to rely of Eren and Mikasa.</description>
<picture>134316.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11" picture="32253.jpg">Inoue Marina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51115" type="main character in" update="2013-11-17">
<rating votes="247">3.04</rating>
<name>Eren Yeager</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Eren Yeager is Shingeki`s protagonist. His adoptive sister, Mikasa, notes on numerous occasions that he acts on impulse without thinking things through, and she often pulls/carries/throws him when he starts fighting with others to protect him from himself. Along with Mikasa, he tends to spend his free time with their mutual friend, Armin.
When Eren was a child, he saved Mikasa from being killed when visiting her home with his father. Three men - killers of her parents - were in her house, and he killed two of them--one by slitting his throat and the other by charging at with a quickly assembled spear. Mikasa herself killed the third man when he attempted to strangle Eren. After this, he gave Mikasa his scarf and took her into his family.
Later, when the giants invaded his home, he could only watch on as his mother - trapped under the rubble of their house - was eaten by a giant. This event made him swear that he`d kill every giant and not live a life cowering in fear.
Sometime after this - before the timeskip that jumped a few years ahead, to when he became a soldier - his father injected him with something. It`s unknown what at this time but it turns out, because of the injection, Eren can regenerate lost limbs and transform into a somewhat out of control giant.</description>
<picture>134314.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1678" picture="68277.jpg">Kaji Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51116" type="main character in" update="2020-04-13">
<rating votes="575">7.34</rating>
<name>Mikasa Ackerman</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mikasa Ackerman is the adoptive sister of Eren and mutual childhood friend of Armin, Mikasa hides her emotions but cares deeply for Eren--never hesitating to cry with tears of joy or despair depending on what happens to him. She shares an unbreakable bond with Eren following events in their past, and his mother requesting that she protect him made her even more overly protective of him than she was beforehand.
Subtle (and not-so-subtle) hints throughout the manga suggest she loves Eren as a man, rather than as a brother. However, in the first four volumes he hasn`t shown any such feelings in return; while he does show hints indicating he cares for her, it is still not known if it is as his sister or as a woman.
When Mikasa`s parents were murdered, and she was tied-up on the floor, Eren saved her life - when visiting by chance with his father - by killing two of the three men who killed her parents, in spite of him only being a child at the time. And then, when the third man was strangling a helpless Eren after catching him off-guard, she picked up a knife off the floor and stabbed the man in the back; killing him.
Afterward, Eren gave Mikasa his scarf - which, even many years later, she still wears - and made sure she understood that he, and his parents, were now her family. Because of his heroics and this gesture, she feels her life is Eren`s now, because - in her mind - she already died once.</description>
<picture>246175.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="443" picture="145927.jpg">Ishikawa Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51167" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-03-25">
<rating votes="94">6.14</rating>
<name>Jean Kirstein</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ranked 6th of the trainee class. Extremely pessimistic about the War with the Titans. He ends up leading the people on the supply mission for gas. From the Trost District. He is highly competent at the three dimensional maneuver and highly skilled at efficiently using it. Good at asserting his situation at any given time, but is far too quick to unsheathe his sword. He is also prone to sparking conflict.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>134317.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="181" picture="171560.jpg">Taniyama Kishou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51169" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-03-25">
<rating votes="182">7.13</rating>
<name>Sasha Blouse</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ranked 9th of the trainee class. A thief from the mountain Daupa District, she joined in order to find tasty things to eat. Lightning fast, with an uncanny intuition, but her eccentricity makes her unfit for group operations.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>134321.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="79" picture="228519.jpg">Kobayashi Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51171" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-03-25">
<rating votes="52">2.80</rating>
<name>Connie Springer</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ranked 8th of the trainee class, an upbeat and naive personality. Aims to apply to the scouting legion because he was motivated by Eren. From Ragako District. Good balance especially good at making tight turns but he is slow to the uptake, and his grasp of strategy is often less than perfect.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>134324.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="175" picture="167565.jpg">Shimono Hiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53532" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-03-25">
<rating votes="62">5.17</rating>
<name>Reiner Braun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ranked 2nd of the trainee class, is considered strong-willed with a solid constitution and most adept at gaining the trust of his comrades.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>134326.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3709" picture="84359.jpg">Hosoya Yoshimasa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54440" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-05-26">
<rating votes="380">8.26</rating>
<name>Levi Ackerman</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Known as humanity`s most powerful soldier. He is a clean-freak. While it is said that he is blunt and unapproachable, it is noted that he has a strong respect for structure and discipline. The rumors are that he was originally part of underground crime before he became a soldier.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>140561.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="224" picture="79056.jpg">Kamiya Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54442" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-11-17">
<rating votes="274">7.11</rating>
<name>Hanji Zoe</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A scientist studying the Titans, showing no real fear in them and intense interest in Eren`s new physiology as a Titan. Considered weird by the rest of her comrades, only a few tolerate her obsession with Titans. In the past, she used to have a strong hatred against Titans until the death of her comrade Ilse convinced her to see the Titans in a different light. Hanji is not only responsible for the research the Survey Corps have on the Titans but also the special weapons they use, such as a barrel that fires multiple grappling hooks to capture Titans alive.
Source: Wiki</description>
<picture>140562.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="566" picture="25408.jpg">Paku Romi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54913" type="appears in" update="2013-05-02">
<rating votes="32">8.93</rating>
<name>Chousa Heidan</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>136163.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="54914" type="appears in" update="2014-02-15">
<rating votes="11">8.83</rating>
<name>Chousa Heidan Tokubetsu Sakusen Han</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>150272.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="55904" type="appears in" update="2013-05-19">
<rating votes="24">8.05</rating>
<name>Shingeki no Kyojin</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>136779.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1678" picture="68277.jpg">Kaji Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90141" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-06-26">
<rating votes="6">4.69</rating>
<name>Zeke Yeager</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>204246.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
</anime>
