<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="14978" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2020</startdate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-zht" type="main">Quanzhi Gaoshou 2nd Season</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">The King`s Avatar (2019)</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Full-Time Expert Season 2</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Master of Skills Season 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-zht" type="synonym">Quan Zhi Gao Shou Season 2</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">全职高手 第2季</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="13950" type="Prequel">Quanzhi Gaoshou: Tebie Pian</anime>
</relatedanime>
<picture>235594.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>37932</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="20">
<externalentity>
<identifier>全職高手</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="34">
<externalentity>
<url>https://v.qq.com/detail/3/3r7bnv3gdykfdok.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2674" parentid="2834" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>China</name>
<description>China, officially the People`s Republic of China (PRC), is a unitary sovereign state in East Asia and the world`s most populous country. It is the third- or fourth-largest country by total area, depending on the source consulted. China also has the most neighbor countries in the world. Governed by the Communist Party of China, it exercises jurisdiction over 22 provinces, five autonomous regions, four direct-controlled municipalities (Beijing, Tianjin, Shanghai, and Chongqing), and the special administrative regions of Hong Kong and Macau.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214277.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3323" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-07-03">
<name>computer</name>
<description>A device, usually electronic, that processes data according to a set of instructions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6152" parentid="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>Chinese production</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>origin</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6850" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-03-13">
<name>STAFF MISSING</name>
<description>This anime is missing staff credits. If you can, please assign staff credits to the anime accordingly and then remove the tag.
If the tag is set on an anime level, please assign preferably all credits and then remove it from the anime. If that is not feasible, please assign, at a minimum, credits for all the major/key staff and then transfer it to all relevant episodes (broadly speaking, regular episodes and S-type episodes containing animation). If the tag is already set on an episode level, please assign all credits, including minor staff, to the episode and then remove the tag from it.
Likewise, this tag should either be applied on an anime level, when it is missing key staff (in full or in part), or to all relevant episodes, when key staff is present but at least some episodes don`t have full staff.
For further information on assigning staff credits, please see http://wiki.anidb.net/Content:Staff_Credits [the AniDB Wiki article on them].</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="89102" type="main character in" update="2017-05-19">
<rating votes="13">8.25</rating>
<name>Ye Xiu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ye Xiu is a first-generation and top-tier player. In the past, he led team http://anidb.net/ch89129 [Excellent Era] to three consecutive titles as League Champions and was honored with the title of MVP three times as well. He won the title of Rising Star twice, and One Hit One Kill and King of Dueling once.
The team Excellent Era manager made him leave the club after they found a replacement for Ye Xiu. As a collateral, he was forced to retire from his professional gaming career. Shortly after that, he found a job at Happy Internet Cafe, where he worked as a manager. Possessing over 10 years of experience in Glory, he threw himself into the newly opened 10th server. With his past memories and an incomplete self-made weapon, he once again began his journey back to the top.
Source: Gravity Tales, edited.</description>
<picture>201860.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="89103" type="main character in" update="2017-05-19">
<rating votes="10">4.45</rating>
<name>Jun Mo Xiao</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jun Mo Xiao is http://anidb.net/ch89102 [Ye Xiu]`s 10th server avatar.</description>
<picture>201862.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="89104" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-08-18">
<rating votes="9">6.00</rating>
<name>Chen Guo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chen Guo is the owner of the Happy Internet Cafe as well as the boss of http://anidb.net/ch105096 [Happy]. She is the user of the account Chasing Haze in the Heavenly Domain of Glory. She is also a former member of the in-game guild Excellent Dynasty.</description>
<picture>201863.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="89110" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-05-14">
<rating votes="19">7.76</rating>
<name>Su Mucheng</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>202453.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="89114" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-05-01">
<rating votes="12">7.83</rating>
<name>Tang Rou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>201890.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
</anime>
