<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="14987" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2019-12-15</startdate>
<enddate>2020-03-23</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Id:Invaded</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">イド:インヴェイデッド</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">ID:Вторжение</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ID:INVADED</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Id: Invaded</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="9127" approval="1" total="2">Psycho-Pass</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="5">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="315728">A little pearl in the rough,highly recommended</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="415669">A bit weird at first but it becomes quite good as the stories goes on. Worth watching!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="194184">Another seris I enjoyed. This was rather on the strange side for me and I had to get used to it. Especially to the form of storytelling and the charcter design. The first episode for example just starts strange, really strange.

I haven`t seen many series with detectives and am not to fond of thrillers etc. but I enjoyed watching this show nonetheless.

The main char is great. I especially liked the calm voice of his and his background story. 
The setting and backgrounds were surrealistic and reminded me sometimes of some paintings by Salvador Dalí.

If you like strange stuff you might like it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="794914">This anime, in my opinion, is better watched episodically than binged - so that you can form a few theories in your head before seeing what really happens next. I`d be lying if I said the story is something absolutely new, but it`s still interesting, with some unexpected turns and well-done emotional moments. I`d say this show owes a great deal of its success at creating atmosphere and emotions to its soundtrack, which is just top-notch. Tsuda Kenjirou`s voice-acting is a cherry on top - someone, give this man a Seiyuu oscar or something. There are things one can complain about - being a police drama at its core, it leaves most side characters underdeveloped in favour of the main leads, and the introduction of a certain concept to an otherwise realistic world might put some off - but there`s nothing that ever truly stops it from working. Very atmospheric, very enjoyable, never dumb. Personal AOTS.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>https://id-invaded-anime.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="28638" type="Character Design">Ikariya Atsushi</name>
<name id="5830" type="Direction">Aoki Ei</name>
<name id="39009" type="Animation Work">Naz</name>
<name id="41517" type="Series Composition">Maijou Outarou</name>
<name id="28638" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ikariya Atsushi</name>
<name id="59512" type="Music">U/S</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch107390 [Sakaido] was a famous and very talented detective until the day his daughter was killed, and he committed revenge! Now in jail, he uses his skills to help the police find criminals of cold-blooded crimes through a system that allows him to invade a criminal`s "ID." But he`ll soon find clues that bring back his daughter`s case!
Source: Funimation
Note: The first two episodes were streamed by Funimation on Dec 15 for 24 hours. The regular TV broadcast started on Jan 5, 2020.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="375">6.31</permanent>
<temporary count="380">7.12</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>243721.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22509</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>40046</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://id-invaded-anime.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ID_-_Invaded</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ID：INVADED_イド：インヴェイデッド</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5518</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>369063</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22431</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>idinvadedanim</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="26">
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=IeyJ7MPb7MQ</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=dnVZwj7ZBjs</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=JW_HobftmJs</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=a43DziGyD_8</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B083XR9FH7</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="308" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>detective</name>
<description>A detective is an investigator, generally either a member of a law enforcement agency or as an individual working in the capacity of private investigators, tasked with solving crimes and other mysteries, such as disappearances, by examining and evaluating clues and records in order to solve the mystery; for a crime, this would mean uncovering the criminal`s identity and/or whereabouts. In some police systems, a detective position is achieved by passing a written test after a person completes the requirements for being a police officer; in others, detectives are college graduates who join directly from civilian life without first serving as uniformed officers.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210906.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2555" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-07-14">
<name>amnesia</name>
<description>The character suffers from some kind of amnesia (memory disturbance or loss). This may mean inability to memorize new information, or inability to recollect old memories. Since there are many types of memory, the person may e.g. forget who they are but still retain learned skills.
Amnesia is fairly common in fiction as a plot device. In fact, because it allows for major plot changes while requiring little creativity from the author, it may be subject to heavy overuse.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2839" parentid="2628" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-05">
<name>virtual world</name>
<description>A virtual world is a place where the character interacts with a computer (or some other device)-simulated environment, be it real or imagined. The condition for a virtual reality to exist is the existence of an originating "real" (source/anchor) world for the character. In some cases, a virtual reality where characters can get harmed physically is depicted.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2898" parentid="2885" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>special squads</name>
<description>The Special Squads are called in when the police is completely outclassed, e.g. fighting criminal syndicates. These special forces are trained to combat specific forms of crime, e.g. the anti-cyber-crime division.
There are several such squads: Whereas Section 9 of Ghost in the Shell is an official government organisation, there are also "benevolent" vigilante groups like the Knight Sabers (Bubblegum Crisis).
Criminal syndicates also have their special forces e.g. "death squads".</description>
<picurl>238613.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2979" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-18">
<name>mutilation</name>
<description>Mutilation is an act of physical injury that degrades the appearance or function of any living body. Some ethnic groups practice ritual mutilation, e.g. scarification, burning, flagellation(whipping), tattooing, or wheeling, as part of a rite of passage. In some cases, the term may apply to treatment of dead bodies, such as soldiers mutilated after they have been killed by an enemy. Maiming, or mutilation which involves the loss of, or incapacity to use, a bodily member, is and has been practised by many societies with various cultural and religious significances, and is also a customary form of physical punishment, especially applied on the principle of "an eye for an eye".
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3411" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>fighting</name>
<description>For some reason or other one faction has to take it out on some opponent via fight or battle. Typical examples of this are all the anime with "endless pointless fighting" tag.</description>
<picurl>211266.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3993" parentid="2872" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-28">
<name>kidnapping</name>
<description>In criminal law, kidnapping is the taking away or transportation of a person against that person`s will, usually to hold the person in false imprisonment, a confinement without legal authority. This may be done for ransom or in furtherance of another crime, or in connection with a child custody dispute.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>10583.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4096" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>gore</name>
<description>A Splatter film or Gore film is a sub-genre of horror film that deliberately focuses on graphic portrayals of gore and graphic violence. These films, through the use of special effects and excessive blood and guts, tend to display an overt interest in the vulnerability of the human body and the theatricality of its mutilation. Due to their willingness to portray images society might consider shocking, splatter films share some ideological grounds with the transgressive art movement. The term "splatter cinema" was coined by George A. Romero to describe his film Dawn of the Dead, though Dawn of the Dead is generally considered by critics to have higher aspirations, such as social commentary, than to be simply exploitative for its own sake.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>32491.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4340" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-09-26">
<name>suicide</name>
<description>One or several characters in this anime commit suicide.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4383" parentid="2872" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-23">
<name>hostage situation</name>
<description>One or more characters in this anime are taken hostage, to pressure or blackmail other involved parties.
A person given as a pledge or security for the performance of the conditions of a treaty or stipulations of any kind, on the performance of which the person is to be released.
(Source: Wiktionary)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6062" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-04-05">
<name>heroic sacrifice</name>
<description>"In order to save the many, the few will need to sacrifice their lives..." or so this character may think. 
In a seemingly hopeless situation, against impossible odds, the character does not choose the path of the coward and run, he or she chooses to bravely face the enemy, fully aware that this will mean death.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6070" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-15">
<name>mystery</name>
<description>The mystery film is a sub-genre of the more general category of crime film. It focuses on the efforts of the detective, private investigator or amateur sleuth to solve the mysterious circumstances of a crime by means of clues, investigation, and clever deduction. (Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6254" parentid="2872" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-23">
<name>terrorism</name>
<description>Terrorism is, in the broadest sense, the use of intentionally indiscriminate violence as a means to create terror among masses of people; or fear to achieve a religious or political aim. It is used in this regard primarily to refer to violence during peacetime or in war against non-combatants (mostly civilians and neutral military personnel). Some definitions now include acts of unlawful violence and war.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>10657.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6730" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-11">
<name>torture</name>
<description>Torture involves the deliberate act of inflicting pain, to either fulfill a desire of the torturer, or apply coercion to compel action from the victim. Torture, by definition, is a knowing and intentional act; deeds which unknowingly or negligently inflict pain without a specific intent to do so are not typically considered torture.
This is distinct from http://anidb.net/t2905 [erotic torture], which is generally for the purpose of using (almost) any form of physical or excessive psychological abuse to inflict physical and/or mental pain, with the goal of inducing sexual pleasure.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="107379" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-12-15">
<rating votes="1">3.82</rating>
<name>Kokufu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>242148.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="47913" picture="242796.jpg">Katou Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107380" type="main character in" update="2019-12-15">
<rating votes="2">8.34</rating>
<name>Fukuda Tamotsu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>242141.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10750" picture="186166.jpg">Takeuchi Ryouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107381" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-12-15">
<rating votes="2">1.54</rating>
<name>Hayaseura</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>242144.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="626" picture="170604.jpg">Muraji Manabu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107382" type="main character in" update="2020-01-26">
<rating votes="13">8.48</rating>
<name>Hondoumachi Koharu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>242142.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36368" picture="224755.jpg">Mao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107383" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-12-15">
<rating votes="1">8.27</rating>
<name>Tougou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>242143.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34234" picture="228806.jpg">Bridcutt Sarah Emi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107384" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-12-15">
<rating votes="1">3.82</rating>
<name>Matsuoka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>242150.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="292" picture="68967.jpg">Nishi Rintarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107385" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-12-15">
<rating votes="1">3.82</rating>
<name>Shiratake</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>242145.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="616" picture="18138.jpg">Kondou Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107386" type="main character in" update="2019-12-15">
<rating votes="2">5.14</rating>
<name>Momoki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>242140.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3709" picture="84359.jpg">Hosoya Yoshimasa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107387" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-12-15">
<rating votes="1">3.82</rating>
<name>Habutae</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>242146.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30740" picture="233850.jpg">Iwase Shuuhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107388" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-12-15">
<name>Wakashika</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>242147.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33512" picture="225800.jpg">Enoki Jun`ya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107389" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-12-15">
<rating votes="1">3.82</rating>
<name>Nishimura</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>242149.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="44099" picture="225101.jpg">Ochiai Fukushi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107390" type="main character in" update="2019-12-15">
<rating votes="3">8.51</rating>
<name>Sakaido</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>242138.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="592" picture="170729.jpg">Tsuda Kenjirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107496" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-12-15">
<rating votes="1">6.04</rating>
<name>Narihisago Akihito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>242139.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="592" picture="170729.jpg">Tsuda Kenjirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108706" type="appears in" update="2020-03-16">
<name>Hijiriido Miyo</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>245002.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36368" picture="224755.jpg">Mao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108707" type="appears in" update="2020-03-16">
<name>Anaido</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>245003.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10750" picture="186166.jpg">Takeuchi Ryouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108708" type="appears in" update="2020-05-21">
<name>Kaeru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68658.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="4432" picture="200731.jpg">Miyamoto Yume</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108709" type="appears in" update="2020-03-16">
<rating votes="1">2.58</rating>
<name>Inami Nahoshi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68659.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="20762" picture="131325.jpg">Sakura Ayane</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="110229" type="appears in" update="2020-05-21">
<name>Asukai Kiki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>247649.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4432" picture="200731.jpg">Miyamoto Yume</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="218498" update="2019-07-04">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2019-07-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ID:INVADED イド:インヴェイデッド 予告PV/Official Teaser 第1弾</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 01 (0:38)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">ID:INVADED ID:Invaded Yokoku PV/Official Teaser Dai 1 Dan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="219292" update="2019-08-13">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-08-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ID:INVADED イド:インヴェイデッド Official Trailer 01</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 02 (1:17)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">ID:INVADED ID:Invaded Official Trailer 01</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223710" update="2019-11-01">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-11-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ID:INVADED イド：インヴェイデッド Official Trailer 02</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 03 (1:39)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">ID:INVADED ID:Invaded Official Trailer 02</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225362" update="2019-12-16">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-12-15</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">JIGSAWED</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Jigsawed</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jigsawed</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225363" update="2019-12-16">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-12-15</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">JIGSAWED II</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Jigsawed II</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jigsawed II</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225422" update="2019-12-20">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-12-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ID:INVADED イド：インヴェイデッド Official Trailer 03 / 2020.Jan.5 ON AIR / OP : Sou “ミスターフィクサー MR FIXER”</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 04 (1:49)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">ID:INVADED ID:Invaded Official Trailer 03 / 2020.Jan.5 ON AIR / OP : Sou "MR FIXER MR FIXER"</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225746" update="2019-12-30">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-01-13</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">SNIPED</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sniped</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sniped</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225747" update="2019-12-30">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-01-20</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">EXTENDED</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Extended</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Extended</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225748" update="2020-01-27">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-01-27</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">FALLEN</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fallen</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fallen</title>
<summary>Hondomachi leaves her interaction with missing Perforator victim Haruka Kazuta in a state of confusion. However, Hondomachi`s insight leads to a stunning breakthrough in another open case.
Source: animelab</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="225749" update="2020-02-03">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-02-03</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">CIRCLED</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Circled</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Circled</title>
<summary>Hondomachi plays a major role in the Gravedigger case. After losing so many officers, the Kura and the Wellside search for ways to track down John Walker. Hondomachi`s efforts in the Gravedigger case are rewarded.
Source: animelab</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="225750" update="2019-12-30">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-02-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">THUNDERBOLTED</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Thunderbolted</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Thunderbolted</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225751" update="2019-12-30">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-02-17</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">DESERTIFIED</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Desertified</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Desertified</title>
</episode>
<episode id="226805" update="2020-02-10">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-02-24</airdate>
<rating votes="3">9.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">INSIDE-OUTED</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Inside-outed</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Inside-outed</title>
</episode>
<episode id="226806" update="2020-02-10">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-03-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">INSIDE-OUTED II</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Inside-outed II</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Inside-outed II</title>
</episode>
<episode id="226807" update="2020-02-10">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-03-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">STORMED</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Stormed</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Stormed</title>
</episode>
<episode id="226808" update="2020-02-10">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-03-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">CHANNELED</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Channeled</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Channeled</title>
</episode>
<episode id="226809" update="2020-02-10">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-03-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">CHANNELED II</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Channeled II</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Channeled II</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
