<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="14981" restricted="false">
<type>Web</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2020-03-27</startdate>
<enddate>2020-03-27</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Rebecca</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">レベッカ</title>
</titles>
<url>https://animetamago.jp/title.php?id=2</url>
<creators>
<name id="3653" type="Character Design">Seki Shuuichi</name>
<name id="16297" type="Direction">Teramoto Yukiyo</name>
<name id="773" type="Animation Work">Vega Entertainment</name>
</creators>
<description>Rebecca, a cheerful and energetic 10-year-old girl born as the second of seven siblings, is forced to be left with her two aunts, Miranda and Jane, after her father`s death caused pain and suffering to the family.
Rebecca loves her gentle aunt Jane, but inevitably shrinks in front of Miranda with her strict and nagging behavior. One day, Rebecca was accused by Miranda of wearing a pink dress made by Jane without permission. At that time, she was insulted about his deceased father, making her explode in anger and leaving the house...
Source: AnimeAnime.global</description>
<picture>242464.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>23158</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>40035</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://animetamago.jp/title.php?id=2</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>371192</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="4859" parentid="6153" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-06-09">
<name>Wakate Animator Ikusei Project</name>
<description>The Young Animator Training Project is an annual project launched in 2010 and funded by the Japanese government`s Agency for Cultural Affairs. The project, which culminates in a series of shorts produced by various animation studios each year, means to address the concern that more of the Japanese animation process is being outsourced overseas, thus leading to a decline in opportunities to teach animation techniques within Japan. As such, the animation production for each short is required to be based in Japan, and professionals must impart their know-how to the young animators through on-the-job training.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="227350" update="2020-03-28">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<airdate>2020-03-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
