<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="14984" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2020-08-07</startdate>
<enddate>2020-08-07</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Eiga Doraemon: Nobita no Shin Kyouryuu</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">映画ドラえもん のび太の新恐竜</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="4635" type="Parent Story">Doraemon (2005)</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.doraeiga.com/2020/</url>
<creators>
<name id="11763" type="Character Design">Kojima Takashi</name>
<name id="680" type="Music">Hattori Takayuki</name>
<name id="4732" type="Original Work">Fujiko F. Fujio</name>
<name id="9709" type="Direction">Imai Kazuaki</name>
</creators>
<picture>241345.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>40044</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.doraeiga.com/2020/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>369058</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<characters>
<character id="8456" type="main character in" update="2015-08-14">
<rating votes="868">7.54</rating>
<name>Doraemon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Doraemon is the titular robotic cat sent back in time by Sewashi to aid Nobita. He possesses a fourth-dimensional pocket from which he can acquire various kinds of futuristic tools, gadgets, and playthings from a future department store. Doraemon originally had ears but they were bitten off by a robotic mouse in the 22nd century. As a result, he developed a morbid fear of mice despite being a robotic cat. He also has the tendency to panic during emergencies, characterized by him frantically trying to pull out a very much-needed tool from his pocket, only to produce a huge assortment of unrelated household items.
Doraemon`s physical appearance changed as the manga progressed. At first, he was predominantly blue, with a blue tail, a white stomach, and flesh-coloured hands and feet. He also stooped, and had a body much larger than his head. In later issues, he sported a smaller body, white hands and feet, and a red tail--the appearance most identify him with today.
In "The Doraemons" story arc, it is revealed that Doraemon`s original paint color was yellow. After getting his ears gnawed off by a robot mouse, he slipped into depression on top of a tower, where he drank a potion labeled "sadness". As he wept, the yellow color washed off and his voice changed due to the potion.
Doraemon weighs 129.3 kg (285 lbs) and measures at 129.3 cm (4`3") tall. He is able to run at 129.3 km/h (80.3 mph) when scared and jump 129.3 m (424.2 ft) when threatened. His maximum power is 129.3 bhp. His wrist, head, and chest circumference are all 129.3 cm. His feet is 129.3 mm in diameter. He is manufactured on September 3, 2112 (12/9/3), at the Matsushiba Robot Factory. Doraemon is considered a substandard product because many of his robotic features (ie. radar whiskers and cat-calling bell) malfunctioned after production. One can turn off Doraemon by pulling his balloon tail.
Doraemon`s favourite food is dorayaki, a Japanese treat filled with red bean paste. Speculations led to dorayaki being the origin of his name. However, it was revealed in one of the manga chapters that his name originates from the Japanese word nora neko for "stray cat", and the -emon ending which is part of traditional Japanese names, as seen also in, for example, Ishikawa Goemon.
In the 2007 birthday episode, `MS-903` is used to call Doraemon by the factory owner where Doraemon is produced.
Doraemon usually uses the phrase "nanoda".</description>
<picture>2237.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="2413" picture="22272.jpg">Mizuta Wasabi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8465" type="main character in" update="2010-08-16">
<rating votes="185">2.75</rating>
<name>Nobi Nobita</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nobita is the main character of the series and the center of the story. He is a fourth grader in Tokyo`s Nerima Ward and an only child. He wears glasses, a red or yellow polo shirt with a white collar, and blue shorts. Nobita`s character flaws are endless: he is lazy, uncoordinated, dim-witted, frail, plain-looking, unlucky, and bad at sports. Nobita`s typical day consists of arriving late on classes, scoring zeros in his tests, getting lectured by his teacher, being bullied by his classmates Gian and Suneo, falling into curbside rain gutters, being chased by dogs, and getting scolded by his mom for his sloth and poor academic results.
Despite his flaws, Nobita possesses some unique talents such as his unrivaled marksmanship and ability to weave intricate string figures. Although Nobita is usually portrayed as being cowardly, he has often risked his life to help save others or even entire civilizations (as seen in full-length stories). He has a tendency of acquiring a grade of zero every once out of five tests and has only scored perfect once in his lifetime.</description>
<picture>27735.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12407" picture="170302.jpg">Oohara Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8466" type="main character in" update="2009-06-05">
<rating votes="371">8.33</rating>
<name>Minamoto Shizuka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shizuka, usually called Shizu-chan or Shizuka-chan, is the smart, kind, and pretty neighbourhood girl who is the object of Nobita`s affections. She takes baths several times a day. Nobita often disrupts her in the bath due to some misuse of Doraemon`s gadgets, resulting in Nobita`s head getting dunked. She is also known for taking piano lessons unwillingly, which is sometimes used as an excuse for declining to hang out with Nobita. Her true passions are sweet potatoes, which she`d rather keep to herself out of the knowledge of others, and the violin, in which her playing is as atrocious as Gian`s singing. Due to Doraemon`s intervention, Shizuka will become Nobita`s wife in the future timeline.</description>
<picture>27612.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="223" picture="228520.jpg">Kakazu Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8549" type="main character in" update="2016-08-22">
<rating votes="127">3.47</rating>
<name>Gouda Takeshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gouda Takeshi, usually known by the nickname "Gian" from English word "giant", is the big, strong, and quick-tempered local bully. His nickname may be derived from giant. He is known for his confidence in his terrible singing voice. He regularly subjects the neighborhood children to horrendous singing recitals, which is sometimes combined with his equally bad homemade dinner. He also frequently steals other children`s toys and books under the pretext of "borrowing" them, unless the toy is damaged. This is how most fans considered Gian to be a major antagonist mostly to http://anidb.net/ch8465 [Nobita] and his friends. However, he does not hesitate to help them, including Nobita when they are in real trouble, which often occurs in the movies.
Several of the stories revolve around Nobita and his friends` efforts to avoid Gian`s concerts or in one particular episode or chapter, which summarize his friends avoid visiting Gian`s house on his birthday because of his selfish nature. After reflecting on one event about his birthday, Gian thought of himself why he wasn`t popular among his peers. After getting a lecture from http://anidb.net/ch8456 [Doraemon] to see what an unruly character he is, Gian realize that he should`ve been a better person and he begs Doraemon to give him another chance. However, things didn`t go exactly as planned when his friends at school or at the streets mock him to see how weird Gian was acting and get kicked by http://anidb.net/ch8553 [Suneo] after learning his attempt to become gentle to his peers. This led him to lose control of his temper and start attacking his friends again.
Although he bullies the other children (mostly Nobita), he is terrified of his mother, who runs the local grocery store. He founded his own baseball team named after himself. Although Nobita is often blamed for the losses against the baseball team`s rival, the "Tyranos", Gian and Suneo still force Nobita to play because they do not have enough players.
Gian also has a younger sister named Jaiko, whom he adores.</description>
<picture>27733.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="25023" picture="70106.jpg">Kimura Subaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8553" type="main character in" update="2009-06-05">
<rating votes="223">3.69</rating>
<name>Honekawa Suneo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Suneo is the fox-faced (inherited from his mother) rich kid who loves to flaunt his material wealth before everyone. He is often seen with Gian, serving as Gian`s lackey while they bully Nobita together. Some of the stories start with Suneo showing off some new video game or toy which evokes Nobita`s envy. He has an extensive knowledge of science, and is a talented artist and designer.
In some scenes, Suneo is seen as a narcissist who loves to stare at himself in the mirror while telling himself that he is the most handsome guy in the world. He is still a bed-wetter and needs to wear diapers when he sleeps, despite being in the fourth grade. He considers this humiliating habit his secret weakness. Suneo is also very self-conscious about his height, being the shortest kid in his class.</description>
<picture>27739.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="236" picture="132757.jpg">Seki Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="224448" update="2020-03-19">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<airdate>2020-08-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
