<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="14993" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2020</startdate>
<enddate>2020</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Gekijouban Pocket Monsters: Koko</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Pokemon with You</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Pokemon: Movie 23</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Pocket Monsters: Coco</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">劇場版ポケットモンスター ココ</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="13649" type="Prequel">Gekijouban Pocket Monsters: Minna no Monogatari</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>https://www.pokemon-movie.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="727" type="Animation Work">OLM</name>
<name id="5780" type="Original Plan">Tajiri Satoshi</name>
<name id="31099" type="Direction">Yajima Tetsuo</name>
</creators>
<picture>244672.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>40881</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://www.pokemon-movie.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>370849</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>pokemon_movie</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<characters>
<character id="6693" type="main character in" update="2013-02-13">
<rating votes="911">2.49</rating>
<name>Satoshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Beginning
Ash is the main character of the Pokémon anime. Raised in Pallet Town, he started his journey to become a Pokémon Master at the age of 10. On the day that he started his journey, Ash carelessly woke up late despite being told by his mother, Delia Ketchum to get to bed. He rushed to Professor Samual Oak`s laboratory only to find out that the beginner Pokémon - Bulbasaur, Squirtle, and Charmander - had already been given out to trainers who arrived on time. However, Professor Samual Oak mentioned that there was one more Pokémon available - Pikachu. Despite constantly hitting Ash with Electric-type attacks and refusing to return to its PokéBall, Ash decided to take Pikachu along with him on his journey to become a Pokémon Master. Pikachu is cold towards Ash at first and laughs at his failures; however, when Ash saves Pikachu from a flock of wild Spearow, he begins to warm up to his new trainer and the two finally become friends. After the battle with the flock of Spearow, a Ho-Oh is seen flying towards a rainbow in the sky. The PokéDex reveals that the Ho-Oh is an unidentified Pokémon. Thus, the journey of Ash and Pikachu begins.
Captures in Viridian Forest
While making his way towards Pewter City and his first Kanto League Gym Battle, Ash came upon a wild Caterpie deep within Viridian Forest. Instead of using Pikachu to battle against the wild Pokémon, Ash took his chances and threw a PokéBall without weakining the Caterpie first. Luckily, he was able to catch the Pokémon without any trouble. The capture of Ash`s Caterpie marked Ash`s first capture as a Pokémon Trainer, making Ash`s Caterpie the second Pokémon to join his team.
The next day, while continuing the trek through the Viridian Forest, Ash came up on a wild Pidgeotto. He tried to just throw a PokéBall like he did with Ash`s Caterpie, but Pidgeotto swatted the PokéBall away. Misty informed that he must weaken the Pokémon first before attempting to capture it. He called out Ash`s Caterpie to battle against, but Misty quickly informed him that Bug-type Pokémon are weak against Flying-type Pokémon like Pidgeotto. After Pidgeotto dealt significant damage to Ash`s Caterpie, Ash recalled it and sent out Pikachu. Pikachu was able to use its Thundershock to weaken Pidgeotto and allow Ash to capture it with a PokéBall. Thus, this capture marked Ash`s second capture as a Pokémon Trainer, making Ash`s Pidgeotto the third Pokémon to join his team.
Later on, while still in the Viridian Forest, Ash was approached by Team Rocket, who attempted to steal his Pokémon. After defeating Meowth, James`s Koffing, and Jessie`s Ekans, Ash`s Caterpie evolved into Ash`s Metapod.
Some of Ash`s greatest accomplishments have been at the various Pokémon Leagues. He was the victor at the Orange League and the Battle Frontier. He also competed in the Indigo League and the Johto Silver Conference where he placed admirably in both those competitions as well.
Pokémon World Tournament Junior Cup
Ash participated in the Pokémon World Tournament Junior Cup at the Kagome Town stadium. In the first round he was in the fifth match and faced off against Marris. The match was quickly showcased and Ash won the battle and advanced to the second round while Marris was eliminated from the tournament.
The Isshu League
Ash participated in the Isshu League in the preliminary match where he was matched up against Trip. Trip`s Serperior was sent out to battle Pikachu and Cilan noted that Trip`s Serperior`s speed and its attack power had leveled up quite a bit too since the last time they saw it. The match was pretty one sided for a long time as Pikachu wasn`t able to counter Trip`s Serperior speed and ended up getting wrapped up. After using Iron Tail on the ground to get loose, Pikachu used a combination attack of Iron Tail and Electro Ball to one hit KO Trip`s Serperior. As a result, Trip was eliminated from the Isshu League and Ash advanced to the next round. The two met in the Pokémon Center after the battle, and Trip vowed that the next time they met that he would win. The two shook hands and parted ways.
In the first main round, Ash`s opponent was shown on the match up electronic board but not much else is known about the battle. Ash`s Scraggy participated in the second main round of the Isshu League tournament where it faced off against a Darumakka. It was able to defeat it so that moved on to the next round.
In the third round, Stephan was matched up against Ash. Cilan noted that the two of them have a very direct taste and that it would be a good battle. It was only a 3 on 3 battle but the both of them gave it their all. The first two battles of the third round setup the final match up of Stephan`s Sawk vs Ash`s Krookodile, both of which were very injured from the previous battles. Both of them did their best to muster up their reserve strength but in the end a surprise move of Aerial Ace by Ash`s Krookodile was super effective against Stephan`s Sawk and it knocked it out to give Ash the victory while eliminating Stephan from the tournament. Stephan realized after the battle that the reason that Ash withdrew Waruvial after the first battle was because Ash knew that Stephan would definitely send out Dageki, so he didn`t reveal that it knew Aerial Ace and saved until the end.</description>
<picture>6210.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="1682" picture="41033.jpg">Matsumoto Rika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8091" type="main character in" update="2017-10-30">
<rating votes="989">3.91</rating>
<name>Pikachu (Satoshi)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Beginning
On the morning that Ash was to start his Pokémon journey, he woke up late and by the time he reached Professor Samual Oak`s laboratory, all of the beginner Pokémon were already taken. However, Professor Samual Oak did have one Pokémon left, a wild Pikachu. At first, Pikachu did not like Ash and would refuse to enter his PokéBall. He would often laugh at Ash`s failures and refused to listen to him. However, after Ash proved his loyalty to Pikachu by protecting him from a flock of Spearow, and thus began to earn Pikachu`s trust and respect. The two have since become best friends and Pikachu never leaves Ash`s side.
Since the day Team Rocket first encountered Pikachu, it has been their sole goal to capture it. Day after day, their plan to capture Pikachu has been thwarted mainly due to Pikachu`s amazingly powerful Thunderbolt that keeps on blasting them off.
On numerous occasions, Pikachu has made it evident that he is happy being a Pikachu and has no desire to evolve into a more powerful Raichu. It has proven time and time again that it is a powerful and worthy opponent to any Pokémon that dares to battle it.
Gym Battle against Burgh`s Leavanny
Pikachu was then sent out to battle Burgh`s Leavanny. Burgh`s Leavanny managed to tie up Pikachu with String Shot but unlike Ash`s Swadloon who was able to break free, Pikachu ended up getting hit with a couple of Leaf Storm attacks and a Hyper Beam before it rolled into another of Burgh`s Leavanny`s Leaf Storm attacks to break the string off its body so it could attack. Freed from the String Shot, Burgh`s Leavanny tried to tie it up again but Pikachu managed to avoid it with its speed and then knocked Burgh`s Leavanny out with a combination of Iron Tail and Electro Ball.
Gym Battle against Elesa
Elesa`s Emolga knocked out Ash`s Snivy and was then matched up with Pikachu. Pikachu made quick work of Elesa`s Emolga and knocked it out with one attack, its Iron Tail.
Elesa`s Tynamo was the last Pokémon that she used in her gym battle against Ash. It was matched up against Pikachu who had just defeated her Emonga. Pikachu had a hard time defending against the fast Tackle attack that Elesa`s Tynamo kept hitting it with but Pikachu used its Thunderbolt to create a large dust cloud leaving only a small corridor for Pikachu to focus on it and so Elesa`s Tynamo couldn`t maneuver out of the way. Pikachu one hit K.O`d Elesa`s Tynamo with a Iron Tail. The loss gave Ash the overall victory.
Battle against Alder`s Bouffalant
Ash challenged Alder to a battle and he accepted though he had been walking all night and was actually quite tired. Alder sent out his Buffron to battle Pikachu but just as the battle started, Alder fell asleep standing up and didn`t give any orders to his Buffron. Alder`s Bouffalant stood still as Pikachu began hitting it with attack after attack until it Alder`s Bouffalant finally got mad at Alder and charged at him and set him flying into a tree. After that, Alder`s Bouffalant no longer wished to battle and Alder conceded the battle.
Gym Battle against Skyla
In Skyla air battle simulation, Ash`s Tranquill was matched up against Skyla`s Unfezant and since her Pokémon was the highest evolved form, she determined that her Pokémon would be the winner in that match-up. In the actual gym battle, Ash`s Tranquill was up against Skyla`s Unfezant which was the match-up just after Ash`s Tranquill had defeated Skyla`s Swoobat. Skyla`s Unfezant proved to be stronger and faster than Ash`s Tranquill, so Ash recalled it and set out Pikachu. Pikachu had a definite advantage over Skyla`s Unfezant with its electric attacks and it quickly knocked it out with its Electro Ball attack.
Ash Just after Pikachu ended up knocking out Skyla`s Unfezant, Skyla`s Swanna was sent out to battle against it. Skyla had been watching her grandpa`s battle videos and noticed that he used the move Aqua Ring to defend against Electric attacks. She used that same defense against Pikachu which nullified its Electric attacks. It`s Iron Tail also couldn`t hit it so high in the air. Ash then noticed the rings in the air and Pikachu jumped up on them and managed to hit Skyla`s Swanna but not directly. Pikachu was now up in the air though and Skyla`s Swanna had the advantage there and it quickly knocked Pikachu out with a powerful Brave Bird attack.
Battle Against Trip`s Serperior at the Isshu League
Pikachu participated in the Isshu League in the preliminary match where it is was matched up against Trip`s Serperior. Cilan noted that Trip`s Serperior speed and its attack power had leveled up quite a bit too since the last time they saw it. The match was pretty one sided for a long time as Pikachu wasn`t able to counter its speed and ended up getting wrapped up. After using Iron Tail on the ground to get loose, Pikachu used a combination attack of Iron Tail and Electro Ball to one hit KO Trip`s Serperior. As a result, Trip was eliminated from the Isshu League and Ash advanced to the next round.</description>
<picture>88041.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="7" picture="186500.jpg">Ootani Ikue</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="225224" update="2020-05-13">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
