<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="14997" restricted="false">
<type>Web</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2020-03-21</startdate>
<enddate>2020-05-06</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">BNA</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">BRAND NEW ANIMAL</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">ビー・エヌ・エー</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Совершенно Новый Зверь</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">BNA</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="9875" approval="0" total="2">Kill la Kill</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="211768">I would have given BNA an "8" if the frame rate was higher.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="47809">I do recommend this show for its main characters and story. Has good comedy and wackiness, but still some seriousness in a good combo. The main characters are very likeable and drags you into their quest of saving everyone. Watch it!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>https://bna-anime.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="9904" type="Character Design">Yoshigaki Yuusuke</name>
<name id="51555" type="Chief Animation Direction">Takeda Naoki</name>
<name id="40466" type="Music">Mabanua</name>
<name id="1568" type="Series Composition">Nakashima Kazuki</name>
<name id="29313" type="Original Work">Trigger</name>
<name id="1568" type="Original Work">Nakashima Kazuki</name>
<name id="29313" type="Animation Work">Trigger</name>
<name id="463" type="Direction">Yoshinari You</name>
</creators>
<description>Note: The first 6 episodes received an delivery on Netflix on March 21, the remaining 6 episodes on May 6. A TV broadcast started on April 9, 2020.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="156">7.01</permanent>
<temporary count="158">7.46</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>244892.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22924</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>40060</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://bna-anime.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>BNA:_Brand_New_Animal</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>BNA_ビー・エヌ・エー</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5634</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>369089</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22643</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>bna_anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="7" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>juujin</name>
<description>Kemono, "beast", is a genre of Japanese art and character design that prominently features anthropomorphic animal characters. It is used widely in visual arts, especially drawing and painting, and can be found in many manga, anime, and video game.
Anthropomorphic animal characters in the kemono genre are frequently called juujin, "therianthrope"; the kanji for juujin are also sometimes pronounced kemonobito, "beast-human". While their design differs from artist to artist, they generally employ animal traits considered cute and endearing; most kemono characters retain a fundamentally human personality, however, seldom behaving as the actual animals from which they have been anthropomorphized, and as such they are typically depicted living as humans do.
Juujin leans more on the human-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t2857 [anthropomorphism], which leans more on the animal-looking side.
Source: Manga Wikia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="28" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-16">
<name>baseball</name>
<description>Baseball is like a complicated version of Rounders. It involves hitting a ball with a stick, then running around several bases placed in the form of a diamond on a field. Big in the US, and also in Japan.</description>
<picurl>29801.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1656" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-27">
<name>corrupt</name>
<description>The character is spiritually or morally impure and may accept payment or other benefits for services or material which the recipient is not due, under law.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2636" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>human enhancement</name>
<description>Human enhancement can take various forms: It can be something comparatively non-intrusive as a power-up drug, a form of machine implantation or cyberization (http://anidb.net/a4414 [SAC Solid State Society]), or outright - possibly atrocious - genetic manipulation (http://anidb.net/a361 [Ao no 6 Gou]). Plot-wise enhanced protagonists in anime usually have to pay a price for their enhancements, be it physical or mental.</description>
<picurl>223945.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2760" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>basketball</name>
<description>Basketball is Netball for men, the real game that encourages dribbling and other such uncouth behaviour that was sanitised out of the ladies` version. However, it is itself woozy compared to Ulama, as the losing side are seldom publicly sacrificed.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2840" parentid="2872" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>mafia</name>
<description>A mafia is a type of organized crime syndicate whose primary activities are protection racketeering, the arbitration of disputes between criminals, and the organizing and oversight of illegal agreements and transactions. Secondary activities may be practiced such as gambling, drug trafficking, loan sharking, and fraud. The term was originally applied to the Sicilian mafia, but has since expanded to encompass other organizations of similar methods and purpose, such as in "the Russian mafia" or "the Japanese mafia", and is applied informally by the press and public, but the criminal organizations themselves have their own terms; for example, the original Sicilian and Italian-American mafia call themselves "cosa nostra", while the Japanese mafia calls itself "yakuza".
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>211289.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2907" parentid="2636" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>genetic modification</name>
<description>Story-wise, genetic modification is usually centred on humans, probably the most subtle and creepy way of messing with mankind. Playing with the fear of the unknown, genetically altered humans are technically a new species, that may not only surpass but actually replace unaltered humans. The level of modification will vary from subtle changes in "look" (e.g. super-human beauty), to mental enhancements (PSI powers), to more or less atrocious adaptations to extreme environments (breath under water, radiation resistance). Note that changes in Aliens would be difficult to pinpoint, after all they are alien.</description>
<picurl>223941.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3411" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>fighting</name>
<description>For some reason or other one faction has to take it out on some opponent via fight or battle. Typical examples of this are all the anime with "endless pointless fighting" tag.</description>
<picurl>211266.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4917" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-26">
<name>evil government</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5285" parentid="3411" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>street fighting</name>
<picurl>211275.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5874" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-05-21">
<name>guns are useless</name>
<description>Guns are about as effective as throwing tissue while only manly things like swords, spears, and bare fists are of any use at all.
If the weapon shoots a projectile faster than human eyes can track, it is useless. Most guns only serve as a filler for the protagonist to dodge all their shots so they can kill them with a "real" weapon.
The sniper rifle is an occasional exception to this rule. This is because it can be used to quickly and efficiently reduce the amount of character development the animators have to worry about.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6254" parentid="2872" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-23">
<name>terrorism</name>
<description>Terrorism is, in the broadest sense, the use of intentionally indiscriminate violence as a means to create terror among masses of people; or fear to achieve a religious or political aim. It is used in this regard primarily to refer to violence during peacetime or in war against non-combatants (mostly civilians and neutral military personnel). Some definitions now include acts of unlawful violence and war.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>10657.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7129" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-06-28">
<name>Plus Ultra</name>
<description>+Ultra is an anime programming block established by http://anidb.net/cr741 [Fuji TV] that began in October 2018.</description>
<picurl>66247.png</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="86597" type="cameo appearance in" update="2016-12-05">
<rating votes="2">10.00</rating>
<name>Inferno Cop</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>195631.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="107364" type="main character in" update="2020-05-21">
<rating votes="6">8.33</rating>
<name>Kagemori Michiru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68248.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="9036" picture="215515.jpg">Morohoshi Sumire</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107365" type="main character in" update="2019-12-09">
<name>Oogami Shirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68247.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="3709" picture="84359.jpg">Hosoya Yoshimasa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107366" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-12-09">
<name>Alan Sylvasta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>241896.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34296" picture="225238.jpg">Ishikawa Kaito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107367" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-12-09">
<rating votes="1">1.20</rating>
<name>Hiwatashi Nazuna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>241897.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39889" picture="241534.jpg">Naganawa Maria</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108641" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-13">
<name>Gem Horner</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>246157.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2016" picture="240331.jpg">Yanaka Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108642" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-13">
<name>Juliano Flip</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>246162.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="622" picture="214429.jpg">Tadano Youhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108643" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-13">
<name>Barbara Rose</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>246151.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="404" picture="151682.jpg">Takashima Gara</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108644" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-13">
<rating votes="1">4.75</rating>
<name>Marie Itami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>246153.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36494" picture="171541.jpg">Murase Michiyo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108645" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-13">
<name>Melissa Horner</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>246160.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36" picture="228350.jpg">Saitou Kimiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108646" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-13">
<name>Hakusui-souri</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>246163.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="297" picture="233915.jpg">Ootsuka Houchuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108647" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-13">
<name>Ishizaki Kouichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="611" picture="18094.jpg">Nomura Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108648" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-13">
<name>Tachiki Yuuji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>246155.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2340" picture="151335.jpg">Naka Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109379" type="main character in" update="2020-04-13">
<name>Kagemori Michiru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>246148.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9036" picture="215515.jpg">Morohoshi Sumire</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109380" type="main character in" update="2020-04-13">
<name>Oogami Shirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>246149.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3709" picture="84359.jpg">Hosoya Yoshimasa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109381" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-13">
<rating votes="2">2.19</rating>
<name>Hiwatashi Nazuna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>246150.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39889" picture="241534.jpg">Naganawa Maria</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109382" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-13">
<name>Barbara Rose</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>246152.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="404" picture="151682.jpg">Takashima Gara</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109383" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-13">
<rating votes="1">8.37</rating>
<name>Marie Itami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>246154.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36494" picture="171541.jpg">Murase Michiyo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109384" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-13">
<name>Tachiki Yuuji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>246156.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2340" picture="151335.jpg">Naka Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109385" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-13">
<name>Gem Horner</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>246158.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2016" picture="240331.jpg">Yanaka Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109386" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-13">
<name>Melissa Horner</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>246159.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36" picture="228350.jpg">Saitou Kimiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109387" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-13">
<name>Juliano Flip</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>246161.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="622" picture="214429.jpg">Tadano Youhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109388" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-13">
<name>Kuro</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>246164.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="110310" type="appears in" update="2020-05-25">
<name>Jikkyou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>247762.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3272" picture="172136.jpg">Mizushima Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="227394" update="2020-03-13">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-03-21</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Runaway Raccoon</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Runaway Raccoon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Runaway Raccoon</title>
</episode>
<episode id="227395" update="2020-03-13">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-03-21</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Rabbit Town</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rabbit Town</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rabbit Town</title>
</episode>
<episode id="227396" update="2020-03-13">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-03-21</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Rhino Melancholy</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rhino Melancholy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rhino Melancholy</title>
</episode>
<episode id="227397" update="2020-03-13">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-03-21</airdate>
<rating votes="4">2.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Dolphin Daydream</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dolphin Daydream</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dolphin Daydream</title>
</episode>
<episode id="227398" update="2020-03-13">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-03-21</airdate>
<rating votes="5">8.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Greedy Bears</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Greedy Bears</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Greedy Bears</title>
</episode>
<episode id="227399" update="2020-03-13">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-03-21</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Fox Waltz</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fox Waltz</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fox Waltz</title>
</episode>
<episode id="227502" update="2020-03-22">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2020-03-21</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="227503" update="2020-03-22">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2020-03-21</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="228713" update="2020-05-06">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-05-06</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Easy Albatross</title>
</episode>
<episode id="228714" update="2020-05-06">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-05-06</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">The Mole Rat Speaks</title>
</episode>
<episode id="228943" update="2020-05-05">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-05-06</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Human Scapegoat</title>
</episode>
<episode id="228944" update="2020-05-05">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-05-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Rabid Wolf</title>
</episode>
<episode id="228945" update="2020-05-05">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-05-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">A Beastly Feast</title>
</episode>
<episode id="228946" update="2020-05-05">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-05-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Anima-City</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
