<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="15028" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2021-04-08</startdate>
<enddate>2021-06-24</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Zombie Land Saga Revenge</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Zombie Land Saga 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">zlsr</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ゾンビランドサガ リベンジ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Zombie Land Saga Revenge</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="14198" type="Prequel">Zombie Land Saga</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="235683">Wow this season is...

The performance portions are so improved that it reminded me that this is actually an Idol anime and not just a Saga tourism promo project. Or... I mean, this whole anime is still a Saga tourism promo project but it puts majority of Idol anime to shame. Then again we know this anime and studio is a relatively good budget tier unlike majority of Idol anime so...

The comedy portion feels less tho compared to the first season of more havoc.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>https://zombielandsaga.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="18630" type="Character Design">Fukagawa Kasumi</name>
<name id="40548" type="Series Composition">Murakoshi Shigeru</name>
<name id="31375" type="Work">MAPPA</name>
<name id="11159" type="Direction">Sakai Munehisa</name>
<name id="12248" type="Music">Funta7</name>
<name id="2754" type="Music">Takanashi Yasuharu</name>
<name id="4212" type="Chief Animation Direction">Sai Fumihide</name>
<name id="14200" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kuwahara Mikine</name>
</creators>
<description>One day, http://anidb.net/ch97788 [Minamoto Sakura] lost her life in an unfortunate accident. Then, ten years later... After Sakura wakes up in a strange mansion, mysterious idol producer http://anidb.net/ch97785 [Tatsumi Koutarou] tells her that she will be joining a group of legendary girls to form an idol unit. The seven girls are charged with a quest to save the fading Saga Prefecture and adopt the group name http://anidb.net/ch98875 [Franchouchou]. After overcoming the difficulties stemming from their different ages and different periods of history, their undead zombie bodies allow them to defy expectations of what idols can be. During the final winter of the Heisei era they performed their first featured concert at Karatsu`s Furusato Exhibition Hall, Arpino, taking another step towards becoming a legend. Now, in the modern Reiwa Era... The curtain rises on a new chapter in the story of Franchouchou, as they march towards a bright future full of hope.
Source: crunchyroll</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="194">6.90</permanent>
<temporary count="195">7.19</temporary>
<review count="1">8.00</review>
</ratings>
<picture>255162.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>24019</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>40174</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://zombielandsaga.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Zombie_Land_Saga</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ゾンビランドサガ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5929</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>369269</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>23476</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>zombielandsaga</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="26">
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=Fcgqj08Jwag</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=ZzLZetJVrl4</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>zombie-land-saga</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1152" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-23">
<name>undead</name>
</tag>
<tag id="2257" parentid="1152" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-12">
<name>zombie</name>
<description>A zombie is asserted to be a reanimated corpse, or a human who is being controlled by someone else by use of magic with some media renditions using a pandemic illness to explain their existence.
Stories of zombies originated in the West African spiritual belief system of voodoo, which told of the people being controlled as laborers by a powerful wizard.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2438" parentid="2794" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-12-05">
<name>idol</name>
<description>In Japanese culture, idols (アイドル) are media personalities in their teens and early twenties who are considered particularly cute and cuddly and who will, for a period ranging from several months to a few years, regularly appear in the mass media, e.g. as singers for J-pop groups, bit-part actors, TV personalities, models in photo spreads published in magazines, advertisements, etc.
http://anidb.net/t860 [Virtual idols] are animated characters created as idols. They are often also http://anidb.net/t7774 [vTubers] and/or http://anidb.net/t7250 [vloggers].
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>63097.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4251" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-20">
<name>ensemble cast</name>
<description>A show with an ensemble cast focuses on a larger group of main characters in a single plot narrative; anime containing several segmented plot narratives (such as episodic or arc-based plots) are excluded. As such, it doesn`t really have a "main" or "lead" character; instead, every member of the central main character group plays an important part in the show`s grander scheme; no single character is more important or prominent than the others (equality of importance). Further, subplots (if any) lead by each character in the ensemble have equal weighting in importance (or lack of weight).

* In a show where no single main character is more important or prominent than the others, 4+ main characters is almost always an ensemble cast.
* A show with 3 main characters of equal importance is likely also an ensemble cast; equality of importance must be considered carefully.
* A show with 2 main characters of equal importance is generally not an ensemble cast situation; however, on an exception basis where neither main character is considered an antagonist, a 2-main-character anime may be considered an ensemble (e.g. http://anidb.net/a11829 [Kimi no Na wa.]).

Pictured: http://anidb.net/a9043 [K (anime)]</description>
<picurl>94914.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="97783" type="main character in" update="2018-10-17">
<rating votes="14">6.29</rating>
<name>Yuugiri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>223482.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42697" picture="223257.jpg">Kinugawa Rika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97784" type="main character in" update="2018-10-17">
<rating votes="15">8.14</rating>
<name>Nikaidou Saki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>223479.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="24068" picture="224929.jpg">Tano Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97785" type="main character in" update="2018-09-10">
<rating votes="19">7.98</rating>
<name>Tatsumi Koutarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>223477.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="255" picture="40713.jpg">Miyano Mamoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97786" type="main character in" update="2019-04-02">
<rating votes="11">6.41</rating>
<name>Hoshikawa Lily</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>In episode 8 it was actually revealed that Lily`s dead name was Masao, making her a trans girl.</description>
<picture>223483.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38297" picture="260767.jpg">Tanaka Minami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97787" type="main character in" update="2018-10-17">
<rating votes="25">7.85</rating>
<name>Mizuno Ai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>223480.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32750" picture="227075.jpg">Taneda Risa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97788" type="main character in" update="2018-12-30">
<rating votes="20">7.64</rating>
<name>Minamoto Sakura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>223478.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43552" picture="179144.jpg">Hondo Kaede</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97789" type="main character in" update="2019-01-01">
<rating votes="23">8.03</rating>
<name>Konno Junko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>223481.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43438" picture="186227.jpg">Kawase Maki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97917" type="secondary cast in" update="2021-04-08">
<rating votes="2">1.87</rating>
<name>Romero</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>223486.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1663" picture="23213.jpg">Takato Yasuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97918" type="main character in" update="2018-10-17">
<rating votes="20">8.59</rating>
<name>Yamada Tae</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>223484.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="197" picture="58661.jpg">Mitsuishi Kotono</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97919" type="secondary cast in" update="2021-04-08">
<rating votes="5">4.37</rating>
<name>Keisatsukan A</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>223485.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="65" picture="170428.jpg">Yoshino Hiroyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98702" type="main character in" update="2018-12-30">
<rating votes="15">7.71</rating>
<name>Minamoto Sakura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>225683.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43552" picture="179144.jpg">Hondo Kaede</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98703" type="main character in" update="2018-10-17">
<rating votes="11">8.04</rating>
<name>Nikaidou Saki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>225684.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="24068" picture="224929.jpg">Tano Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98704" type="main character in" update="2018-10-17">
<rating votes="19">7.57</rating>
<name>Mizuno Ai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>225685.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32750" picture="227075.jpg">Taneda Risa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98705" type="main character in" update="2019-01-01">
<rating votes="16">7.91</rating>
<name>Konno Junko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>225686.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43438" picture="186227.jpg">Kawase Maki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98706" type="main character in" update="2018-10-17">
<rating votes="11">5.70</rating>
<name>Yuugiri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>225687.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42697" picture="223257.jpg">Kinugawa Rika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98707" type="main character in" update="2019-04-02">
<rating votes="10">5.59</rating>
<name>Hoshikawa Lily</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>In episode 8 it was actually revealed that Lily`s dead name was Masao, making her a trans girl.</description>
<picture>225688.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38297" picture="260767.jpg">Tanaka Minami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98708" type="main character in" update="2018-10-17">
<rating votes="18">9.01</rating>
<name>Yamada Tae</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>225689.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="197" picture="58661.jpg">Mitsuishi Kotono</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98875" type="appears in" update="2021-04-08">
<rating votes="1">7.62</rating>
<name>Franchouchou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>259685.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="99709" type="appears in" update="2019-01-20">
<rating votes="1">3.78</rating>
<name>Ookoba</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>229388.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2072" picture="223678.jpg">Nara Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99710" type="appears in" update="2019-01-20">
<rating votes="1">3.78</rating>
<name>Inuhashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>229393.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2225" picture="192115.jpg">Kimura Ryouhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99711" type="appears in" update="2018-12-06">
<rating votes="1">3.78</rating>
<name>Shiori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>227484.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21805" picture="169875.jpg">Tokui Sora</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99712" type="appears in" update="2018-12-06">
<rating votes="1">3.78</rating>
<name>Death Oji A</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>227485.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32782" picture="223624.jpg">Kanuka Mitsuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99713" type="appears in" update="2018-12-06">
<rating votes="1">3.78</rating>
<name>Death Oji B</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>227486.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2786" picture="211228.jpg">Satou Setsuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99715" type="appears in" update="2018-12-06">
<rating votes="1">2.37</rating>
<name>Gou Takeo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>227488.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="99717" type="appears in" update="2018-12-16">
<rating votes="2">5.68</rating>
<name>Amabuki Maria</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>227752.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43430" picture="243752.jpg">Koga Aoi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99718" type="appears in" update="2018-12-06">
<rating votes="2">3.12</rating>
<name>Azumatsuru Misa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>227493.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="56869" picture="227746.jpg">Noutomi Momoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99798" type="appears in" update="2018-12-20">
<rating votes="1">3.78</rating>
<name>Master</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>227860.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="297" picture="233915.jpg">Ootsuka Houchuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99815" type="appears in" update="2018-12-16">
<rating votes="1">3.78</rating>
<name>Migigawa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>227754.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38921" picture="147228.jpg">Hon`izumi Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99816" type="appears in" update="2018-12-16">
<rating votes="1">3.78</rating>
<name>Sayama</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>227755.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42471" picture="242433.jpg">Waki Azumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99817" type="appears in" update="2018-12-16">
<rating votes="2">5.82</rating>
<name>Kirishima Reiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>227756.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12409" picture="223671.jpg">Matsushita Komina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102821" type="appears in" update="2019-05-17">
<name>Interviewer</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>233649.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="56862" picture="227739.jpg">Fujino Maria</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102825" type="appears in" update="2019-05-17">
<name>Cock-kun</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>233653.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="56866" picture="227743.jpg">Konno Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="117105" type="appears in" update="2021-04-28">
<name>White Ryuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>260359.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="22004" picture="57080.jpg">Hakuryuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="117170" type="appears in" update="2021-05-06">
<name>Yui</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>260469.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="117178" type="appears in" update="2021-05-07">
<name>Oozora Light</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>260480.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="393" picture="46104.jpg">Takayama Minami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="117179" type="appears in" update="2021-05-07">
<name>Nishimura Manager</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>260481.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2585" picture="248105.jpg">Tsuchida Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="117223" type="appears in" update="2021-05-10">
<name>Iron Frill</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="117402" type="appears in" update="2021-05-21">
<rating votes="4">5.01</rating>
<name>Yuzuriha Maimai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>260869.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="176" picture="192484.jpg">Hanazawa Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="117479" type="appears in" update="2021-05-28">
<name>Itou Seijirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>261019.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2588" picture="153507.jpg">Uchiyama Kouki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="117480" type="appears in" update="2021-05-28">
<name>Momozaki Kiichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>261018.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="255" picture="40713.jpg">Miyano Mamoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="117864" type="appears in" update="2021-06-19">
<name>Machiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>261613.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="53607" picture="212669.jpg">Saitou Kozue</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="236314" update="2021-01-05">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2021-01-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">運命のPV</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fateful PV (2:09)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Unmei no PV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="238654" update="2021-04-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2021-04-08</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">グッドモーニング リターンズ SAGA</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Good Morning Returns Saga</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Good Morning Returns Saga</title>
<summary>A devastating defeat has sent the girls in Franchouchou scrambling for cash to pay off a serious debt, while their producer, Kotaro, falls apart... but all of that will only be prelude as the zombie pop idols prepare for their REVENGE!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>810969</identifier>
<identifier>zombie-land-saga</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="238655" update="2021-04-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2021-04-15</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ぶっ壊れかけのレディオ SAGA</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Saga of an Almost-Broken Radio</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bukkowarekake no Radio Saga</title>
<summary>The REVENGE begins in earnest, as Franchouchou co-hosts a TV segment with the Saga-born superstar, White Ryu.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>810970</identifier>
<identifier>zombie-land-saga</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="238656" update="2021-04-28">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2021-04-22</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛と青春のアコースティック SAGA</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Acoustic Saga of Love and Youth</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ai to Seishun no Acoustic Saga</title>
<summary>Things are escalating rapidly for Franchouchou`s REVENGE when they are booked to perform at the all-new Saga Arena... as the opening act for Iron Frill, the idol group that Ai belonged to when she was alive.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>810971</identifier>
<identifier>zombie-land-saga</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="238657" update="2021-05-05">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2021-04-29</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">純情エレクトリック SAGA</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pure-Hearted Electric Saga</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Junjou Electric Saga</title>
<summary>Iron Frill`s center, Shiori, has approached Ai with the intent of recruiting her. With the group`s REVENGE at stake, will Junko be able to guide Franchouchou towards the kind of performance that will convince her to stay?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>810972</identifier>
<identifier>zombie-land-saga</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="239144" update="2021-04-05">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2021-04-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">運命のPV 第2弾</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fateful PV 2 (1:15)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="239710" update="2021-05-12">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2021-05-06</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">リトルパラッポ SAGA</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Little Bodda Bope Saga</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Little Borappo Saga</title>
<summary>Franchouchou`s notoriety climbs higher and higher, with Lily making an appearance on a nationally-broadcast talent show, shining bright as the group continues their march toward REVENGE.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>810973</identifier>
<identifier>zombie-land-saga</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="239711" update="2021-05-19">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2021-05-13</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ウォーキング・ベット SAGA</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Walking Bet Saga</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Walking Bet Saga</title>
<summary>Franchouchou`s REVENGE is drawing ever closer, but as long as they remain in debt, it`s going to seem out of reach. In the meantime, Tae heads into t own to run some errands in a way that nobody else could!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>810974</identifier>
<identifier>zombie-land-saga</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="239712" update="2021-05-26">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2021-05-20</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">マイマイレボリューション SAGA</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Maimai Revolution Saga</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maimai Revolution Saga</title>
<summary>The REVENGE of Franchouchou takes an unexpected twist when they have to welcome an unexpected new addition to the group!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>810975</identifier>
<identifier>zombie-land-saga</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="239713" update="2021-06-02">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2021-05-27</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">佐賀事変 其ノ壱</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Saga Incident, Part One</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saga Jihen: Sono Ichi</title>
<summary>Long before the REVENGE began, in the year 1882, the legendary courtesan, Yugiri, finds herself in the prefecture formerly known as Saga...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>810976</identifier>
<identifier>zombie-land-saga</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="240400" update="2021-06-09">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2021-06-03</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">佐賀事変 其ノ弐</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Saga Incident, Part Two</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saga Jihen: Sono Ni</title>
<summary>As Yugiri`s journey through the Meiji era continues, Kiichi`s attempts to revive Saga are gaining momentum... but some of his comrades seem to be more focused on REVENGE for the transgressions of the Meiji government, instead of the bright future Kiichi envisions.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>810977</identifier>
<identifier>zombie-land-saga</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="240401" update="2021-06-16">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2021-06-10</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゾンビたちはどう復讐するのか SAGA</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Saga of How These Zombies Will Get Their Revenge</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zombie-tachi wa Dou Fukushuu no ka Saga</title>
<summary>Flash back to the events of early 2019 as Franchouchou undertakes the concert that nearly results in their destruction, and then rejoin them in the early 2020 as they enter the final phase of their REVENGE.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>810978</identifier>
<identifier>zombie-land-saga</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="240402" update="2021-06-23">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2021-06-17</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">たとえば君がいるだけで SAGA</title>
<title xml:lang="en">All It Takes Is for You to Be There Saga</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tatoeba Kimi ga Iru dake de Saga</title>
<summary>Franchouchou`s REVENGE hits a major roadblock as all of Saga is struck by a cataclysmic storm that leaves it`s citizens stranded, without power, and offline. But when the spirits of the living hit their nadir, it may just be the undead who give everyone hope.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>810979</identifier>
<identifier>zombie-land-saga</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="240403" update="2021-06-30">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2021-06-24</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">史上最大の SAGA</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Greatest Saga in History</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shijou Saidai no Saga</title>
<summary>Saga is still recovering from the damage caused by the major storm that devastated the prefecture, but the deadline for Franchouchou`s REVENGE draws near. What started as the group`s attempt to make up for a previous failure has now turned into a saga that may save Saga itself!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>810980</identifier>
<identifier>zombie-land-saga</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="240404" update="2021-05-20">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2021-04-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="240405" update="2021-05-20">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2021-04-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="240773" update="2021-06-04">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>60</length>
<airdate>2021-06-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">~ココ掘れ, ゾンゾン! 10話放送直前スペシャル~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dig Here, Zom Zom! Episode 10 Pre-Broadcast Special</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koko Hore, Zom Zom! 10 Wa Housou Chokuzen Special</title>
</episode>
<episode id="241600" update="2021-06-28">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 2 Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="241601" update="2021-06-28">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 3 Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="241602" update="2021-06-28">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 4 Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="241603" update="2021-06-28">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 5 Preview</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
