<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="15289" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2020-10-03</startdate>
<enddate>2020-12-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Hypnosis Mic: Division Rap Battle - Rhyme Anima</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Гипнотический микрофон: Рэп-баттл дивизионов</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">HypMic</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ヒプノシスマイク -Division Rap Battle- Rhyme Anima</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Hypnosismic: Division Rap Battle - Rhyme Anima</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Гипнотический микрофон: рэп-баттл дивизионов, Райм-Анима</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="official">催眠麥克風</title>
</titles>
<url>https://hypnosismic-anime.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="2459" type="Character Design">Shiba Minako</name>
<name id="4333" type="Series Composition">Yoshida Shin</name>
<name id="42867" type="Original Work">Evil Line Records</name>
<name id="7668" type="Direction">Ono Katsumi</name>
<name id="1303" type="Work">A-1 Pictures</name>
<name id="7062" type="Music">RON</name>
<name id="2459" type="Chief Animation Direction">Shiba Minako</name>
<name id="19127" type="Chief Animation Direction">Takeuchi Yukari</name>
<name id="9383" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ochiai Hitomi</name>
<name id="12915" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kuroiwa Hiromi</name>
</creators>
<description>After war, women have taken over ruling politics in the Chuo ward and have banned and destroyed weapons. This has caused men to fight through rap battles using Hypnosis Mics, which can be used to affect people`s sympathetic nerves and influence their thought process. However, the legendary rap group, The Dirty Dawg, has split up into four groups, each representing a division of Tokyo, Japan and engaging in territorial battles using words and the Hypnosis Mics.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="44">2.95</permanent>
<temporary count="44">4.32</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>245102.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22902</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>40803</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://hypnosismic-anime.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Hypnosis_Mic:_Division_Rap_Battle:_Rhyme_Anima</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ヒプノシスマイク</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5765</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>370753</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>23055</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>hypnosismic_RA</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="34">
<externalentity>
<url>https://www.funimation.com/shows/hypnosismic-division-rap-battle-rhyme-anima/?qid=4d328c07622f810d</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2676" parentid="2672" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo</name>
<description>Tokyo, officially Tokyo Metropolis, is the capital city of Japan and one of its 47 prefectures. The Greater Tokyo Area is the most populous metropolitan area in the world. It is the seat of the Emperor of Japan and the Japanese government. Tokyo is in the Kantou region on the southeastern side of the main island Honshu and includes the Izu Islands and Ogasawara Islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214311.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2926" parentid="2874" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>post-war</name>
<description>An armed conflict has ended not too long ago, devastation of the world or society is still evident.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4170" parentid="5626" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-08-08">
<name>police are useless</name>
<description>The civilian law enforcement representatives do not seem to be of much use, when trying to take on the usually vastly superior foes.
The "helpless" and often clumsy antics of the police can be used as a comedy element.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4176" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-12-05">
<name>OP and ED sung by cast</name>
<description>The OP and/or ED is sung by the anime`s cast.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4251" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-20">
<name>ensemble cast</name>
<description>A show with an ensemble cast focuses on a larger group of main characters in a single plot narrative; anime containing several segmented plot narratives (such as episodic or arc-based plots) are excluded. As such, it doesn`t really have a "main" or "lead" character; instead, every member of the central main character group plays an important part in the show`s grander scheme; no single character is more important or prominent than the others (equality of importance). Further, subplots (if any) lead by each character in the ensemble have equal weighting in importance (or lack of weight).

* In a show where no single main character is more important or prominent than the others, 4+ main characters is almost always an ensemble cast.
* A show with 3 main characters of equal importance is likely also an ensemble cast; equality of importance must be considered carefully.
* A show with 2 main characters of equal importance is generally not an ensemble cast situation; however, on an exception basis where neither main character is considered an antagonist, a 2-main-character anime may be considered an ensemble (e.g. http://anidb.net/a11829 [Kimi no Na wa.]).

Pictured: http://anidb.net/a9043 [K (anime)]</description>
<picurl>94914.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4269" parentid="2794" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>hip-hop</name>
<description>Hip hop music, also called hip-hop, rap music, or hip-hop music, is a music genre consisting of a stylized rhythmic music that commonly accompanies rapping, a rhythmic and rhyming speech that is chanted.
The anime tagged with this shows a strong influence from its culture, or features hip-hop as a theme.</description>
<picurl>169135.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4383" parentid="2872" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-23">
<name>hostage situation</name>
<description>One or more characters in this anime are taken hostage, to pressure or blackmail other involved parties.
A person given as a pledge or security for the performance of the conditions of a treaty or stipulations of any kind, on the performance of which the person is to be released.
(Source: Wiktionary)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4596" parentid="2676" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Shinjuku</name>
<description>Shinjuku is a special ward in Tokyo, Japan. It is a major commercial and administrative centre, housing the Northern half of the busiest railway station in the world (Shinjuku Station) and the Tokyo Metropolitan Government Building, the administration centre for the government of Tokyo.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214322.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5626" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>adults are useless</name>
<description>For when adults can`t do anything right.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5792" parentid="2872" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-08">
<name>gangs</name>
<description>A gang is a group of people, through the organization, formation, and establishment of an assemblage, share a common identity. In current usage it typically denotes a criminal organization or else a criminal affiliation. In early usage, the word gang referred to a group of workmen. In the United Kingdom the word is still often used in this sense, but it later underwent pejoration. The word gang often carries a negative connotation; however, within a gang which defines itself in opposition to mainstream norms, members may adopt the phrase as a statement of identity or defiance.
The word "gang" derives from the past participle of Old English gan "to go". It is cognate with Old Norse gangr, meaning "journey."</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5823" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-09-01">
<name>predominantly male cast</name>
<description>The anime features a mostly male cast, i.e. female characters are rare.
Example: Reverse harem setting with a plethora of bishounen.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6596" parentid="2676" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Ikebukuro</name>
<description>Ikebukuro is a commercial and entertainment district in Toshima, Tokyo, Japan. Toshima ward offices, Ikebukuro station, and several shops, restaurants, and enormous department stores are located within city limits.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214320.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7086" parentid="2846" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>soft science fiction</name>
<description>Soft science fiction is a type of science fiction in which the science presented is scientifically inaccurate or unimportant to the story, in contrast to http://anidb.net/t4667 [hard science fiction]. Its elements generally present themselves via artistic licence.
This is not to be confused with social science fiction, confusingly also called "soft science fiction", which is science fiction concerned with the "soft sciences" (social sciences), as opposed to the "hard sciences" (natural sciences).</description>
<picurl>222752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7693" parentid="2672" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-07-27">
<name>Yamagata</name>
<description>Yamagata is a prefecture of Japan located in the Touhoku region of Honshuu. It borders Akita to the north, Miyagi to the east, Fukushima to the south, and Niigata to the southwest. The capital and largest city is the city of Yamagata, with other major cities including Tsuruoka, Sakata, and Yonezawa. Yamagata Prefecture is located on Japan`s western Sea of Japan coast and its borders with neighboring prefectures are formed by various mountain ranges, with 17% of its total land area being designated as natural parks, and it is home to the Three Mountains of Dewa, which includes the Haguro Five-story Pagoda, a recognised National Treasure of Japan.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="113439" type="main character in" update="2020-10-25">
<name>Izanami Hifumi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>253599.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20273" picture="175422.jpg">Kijima Ryuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="113440" type="main character in" update="2020-10-25">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Iruma Juuto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>253593.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39678" picture="224254.jpg">Komada Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="113441" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-10-25">
<name>Kadenokouji Ichijiku</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>253602.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1665" picture="19756.jpg">Takahashi Chiaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="113442" type="main character in" update="2020-10-25">
<name>Yumeno Gentarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>253596.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36680" picture="153752.jpg">Saitou Souma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="113443" type="main character in" update="2020-10-25">
<name>Yamada Ichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>253573.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="25023" picture="70106.jpg">Kimura Subaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="113444" type="main character in" update="2020-10-25">
<name>Yamada Saburou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>253575.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40642" picture="62085.png">Amasaki Kouhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="113445" type="main character in" update="2020-10-25">
<name>Yamada Jirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>253574.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39260" picture="150015.jpg">Ishiya Haruki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="113446" type="main character in" update="2020-10-25">
<name>Arisugawa Daisu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>253597.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="56160" picture="254954.jpg">Nozuyama Yukihiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="113447" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-10-25">
<name>Touhouten Otome</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>253601.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="79" picture="228519.jpg">Kobayashi Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="113448" type="main character in" update="2020-10-25">
<name>Busujima Mason Riou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>253594.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40355" picture="223014.jpg">Kamio Shin`ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="113449" type="main character in" update="2020-10-25">
<name>Aohitsugi Samatoki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>253592.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="567" picture="80605.jpg">Asanuma Shintarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="113450" type="main character in" update="2020-10-25">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Jinguuji Jakurai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>253598.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27" picture="26123.jpg">Hayami Shou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="113451" type="main character in" update="2020-10-25">
<name>Kannonzaka Doppo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>253600.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39076" picture="181640.jpg">Itou Kento</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="113452" type="main character in" update="2020-10-25">
<name>Amemura Ramuda</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>253595.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30311" picture="223328.jpg">Shirai Yuusuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="113463" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-10-25">
<name>Tom Whisper Weathercock</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>253603.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="44338" picture="223510.jpg">Fukagawa Kazumasa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="113464" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-11-21">
<name>Iris Innocent Traiter</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>253604.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34901" picture="130616.jpg">Lynn</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="113465" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-10-25">
<name>Taroumaru Rex</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>253605.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39583" picture="186257.jpg">Hamano Daiki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="113480" type="appears in" update="2020-10-27">
<name>Leader</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>253642.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="50471" picture="248118.jpg">Shiraishi Kento</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="113482" type="appears in" update="2020-10-27">
<name>Utashiro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>253646.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18755" picture="49459.jpg">Akazawa Ryouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="113483" type="appears in" update="2020-10-27">
<name>Kangoshi A</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>253648.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38905" picture="10121.jpeg">Nanami Karin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="113486" type="appears in" update="2020-10-27">
<name>Sadamezuka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>253657.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="592" picture="170729.jpg">Tsuda Kenjirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="113488" type="appears in" update="2020-10-27">
<name>Keibu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>253658.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43576" picture="223680.jpg">Ishiguro Fumitake</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="113498" type="appears in" update="2020-10-28">
<name>Irihatoma-keiji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>253693.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="46388" picture="200800.jpg">Iwanaka Mutsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="113499" type="appears in" update="2020-10-28">
<name>Degarashi-keibu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>253692.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2067" picture="186243.jpg">Hoshino Mitsuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="113500" type="appears in" update="2020-10-28">
<name>Kachou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>253694.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43576" picture="223680.jpg">Ishiguro Fumitake</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="113501" type="appears in" update="2020-10-28">
<name>Hibakari Mimimi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>253695.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="54091" picture="225341.jpg">Sugiyama Riho</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="113502" type="appears in" update="2020-10-28">
<name>Uwabami</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>253696.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="47919" picture="207907.jpg">Nakamura Shuugo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="113503" type="appears in" update="2020-10-28">
<name>Rentei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>253697.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4270" picture="197671.jpg">Nakagawa Keiichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="113504" type="appears in" update="2020-10-28">
<name>Nouzenkazura Gennou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>253699.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="373" picture="191382.jpg">Hamada Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="113505" type="appears in" update="2020-10-28">
<name>Rentei no Imouto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>253703.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="56989" picture="228076.jpg">Fujii Ayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="113506" type="appears in" update="2020-10-28">
<name>Rou Tenshu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>253704.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43576" picture="223680.jpg">Ishiguro Fumitake</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="113507" type="appears in" update="2020-10-28">
<name>Aohitsugi Nemu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>253705.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="25804" picture="71817.jpg">Yamamoto Nozomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="113845" type="appears in" update="2020-11-17">
<name>Sabasu Kuroya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>254251.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="400" picture="171989.jpg">Majima Junji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="114219" type="appears in" update="2020-12-05">
<name>Buster Bros!!!</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>254745.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="114220" type="appears in" update="2020-12-05">
<name>Mad Trigger Crew</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>254746.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="114221" type="appears in" update="2020-12-05">
<name>Fling Posse</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>254747.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="114222" type="appears in" update="2020-12-05">
<name>Matenrou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>254748.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="114223" type="appears in" update="2020-12-05">
<name>Kotonoha Tou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>254749.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="232511" update="2020-09-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-10-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">As soon as man is born he begins to die.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">As Soon As Man Is Born He Begins to Die.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">As Soon As Man Is Born He Begins to Die.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="232512" update="2020-09-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-10-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">Speak of the devil and he will appear.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Speak of the Devil and He Will Appear.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Speak of the Devil and He Will Appear.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="232513" update="2020-09-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-10-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">Two heads are better than one.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Two Heads Are Better Than One.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Two Heads Are Better Than One.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="232514" update="2020-09-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-10-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">A friend in need is a friend indeed.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Friend in Need Is a Friend Indeed.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">A Friend in Need Is a Friend Indeed.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="233607" update="2020-10-17">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-10-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">Seeing is believing.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Seeing Is Believing.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seeing Is Believing.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="233608" update="2020-10-17">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-11-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">He who laughs last, laughs best.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">He Who Laughs Last, Laughs Best.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">He Who Laughs Last, Laughs Best.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="233609" update="2020-10-17">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-11-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">The darkest hour is just before the dawn.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Darkest Hour Is Just Before the Dawn.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">The Darkest Hour Is Just Before the Dawn.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="233610" update="2020-10-17">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-11-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">Dead men tell no tales.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dead Men Tell No Tales.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dead Men Tell No Tales.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="234410" update="2020-11-15">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-11-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">Life is what you make it.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Life Is What You Make It.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Life Is What You Make It.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="234411" update="2020-11-15">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-12-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">Today is a good day to die.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Today Is a Good Day to Die.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Today Is a Good Day to Die.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="234412" update="2020-11-15">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-12-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">No pain, no gain.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">No Pain, No Gain.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">No Pain, No Gain.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="234413" update="2020-11-15">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-12-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">You can`t make an omelet without breaking eggs.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">You Can`t Make an Omelet Without Breaking Eggs.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">You Can`t Make an Omelet Without Breaking Eggs.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="235500" update="2020-12-12">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-12-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">Tomorrow is another day.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tomorrow Is Another Day.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tomorrow Is Another Day.</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
