<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="15659" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2020-10-14</startdate>
<enddate>2020-12-30</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Dogeza de Tanondemita</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">土下座で頼んでみた</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Dogeza: I Tried Asking While Kowtowing.</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">I Tried Asking While Kowtowing</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="official">土下座跪求給看</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="13698" approval="6" total="7">Iya na Kao Sarenagara Opantsu Misete Moraitai</anime>
</similaranime>
<url>https://dogeza-anime.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="61632" type="Original Work">Funatsu Kazuki</name>
<name id="36326" type="Direction">Nagai Shinpei</name>
<name id="42964" type="Music">Nomy</name>
<name id="62229" type="Animation Work">Adonero</name>
<name id="12112" type="Chief Animation Direction">Miyamoto Takeshi</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on an ecchi comedy manga by http://anidb.net/cr61632 [Funatsu Kazuki].
http://anidb.net/ch112828 [Doge Suwaru] is a man who bows (dogeza) in front of young women and asks them to show him their underwear, bowing deeper and deeper until they listen to his request; the women react to his actions with astonishment, embarrassment, and confusion.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="85">2.06</permanent>
<temporary count="87">4.36</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>252451.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>23542</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>42571</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>42990</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://dogeza-anime.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Dogeza_de_Tanondemita</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>土下座で頼んでみた</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5793</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>373436</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>dgz_anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="26">
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=gVJyfPnUac0</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>dogezai-tried-asking-while-kowtowing</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="7" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-10-04">
<name>juujin</name>
<description>Kemono, "beast", is a genre of Japanese art and character design that prominently features anthropomorphic animal characters. It is used widely in visual arts, especially drawing and painting, and can be found in many manga, anime, and video game.
Anthropomorphic animal characters in the kemono genre are frequently called juujin, "therianthrope"; the kanji for juujin are also sometimes pronounced kemonobito, "beast-human". While their design differs from artist to artist, they generally employ animal traits considered cute and endearing; most kemono characters retain a fundamentally human personality, however, seldom behaving as the actual animals from which they have been anthropomorphized, and as such they are typically depicted living as humans do.
Juujin leans more on the human-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t2857 [anthropomorphism], which leans more on the animal-looking side.
Usage the tag image for reference, when tagging characters:

* This is a juujin.
* This is split between juujin and anthropomorphism, to be decided on a case-by-case basis, but most likely leans on the human-looking juujin side in most cases.
* This is anthropomorphism; tag both anthropomorphism and the respective animal type.
* This is anthropomorphism; tag both anthropomorphism and the respective animal type.
* This is just a regular animal; do not tag juujin or anthropomorphism — only tag the actual animal type.

Source: Manga Wikia (description, not the image)</description>
<picurl>252666.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="780" parentid="2849" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-08-23">
<name>fairy</name>
<description>A fairy is a type of mythical being or legendary creature in European folklore, a form of spirit, often described as metaphysical, supernatural, or preternatural.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>206567.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2008" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-05">
<name>small breasts</name>
<description>This character has a bust size that is considered small. 
The small size is usually a bust that would use a bra which is A or B. In anime, C may rarely enter this category.</description>
<picurl>162720.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3018" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>first person view</name>
<description>The events in this anime are shown from the perspective of one or several characters, as if you watch the scenes through their eyes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5852" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>short episodes</name>
<description>Short episodes are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length. This means up to and including 10 minutes; shows with episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length are http://anidb.net/t6494 [half-length episodes] instead.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6349 [multi-segment episodes], which are regular episodes that are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6744" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-12-05">
<name>isekai</name>
<description>An isekai story is one in which the lead characters are transferred to and become stuck or trapped in another world, one completely different from the world they lived in up until the transfer. The new world is commonly a http://anidb.net/t2628 [fictional world], such as a http://anidb.net/t2838 [parallel world] or http://anidb.net/t2839 [virtual world]; other fictional world types can also apply. Once transferred, they must use the abilities and knowledge brought from their former world as well as any that may have been bestowed upon them by their brave new world. In some cases, they will seek and eventually find a way to return; in others, they will gleefully embrace their new life.
The misnomer "reverse isekai" is sometimes used to describe when characters from another world are sent to Earth, in an inaccurate usage likely born out of a mistaken notion that isekai is designed solely around transfers of earthlings. Rather, isekai is about the transfer itself; the identity of the origin and destination worlds, or the direction in which the transfer occurs, are not relevant. What defines isekai is that the characters are sent to another world, often but not always a parallel one, and that they generally cannot come back permanently without meeting a highly specific goal.
Broadly speaking, the following major characteristics, from most to least important, define the isekai theme:
1. The characters are trapped in a new world that is not the one they lived in up to then. This new world is usually unknown to them, at least in part, but that is not strictly mandatory. Generally speaking, while exceptions may apply, pure time travel does not qualify; there must be a change of location.
2. The trapping is, at least initially, permanent; there must be no quick and easy escape route back to their home world. A known way back may exist from the outset, but it requires effort, such as clearing the 100th floor of a difficult dungeon or defeating the demon lord; alternatively, it may be eventually found or developed.
3. The transfer to the isekai world was not intentional on the part of those being transferred. For example, it may have been orchestrated by a third party (malicious or otherwise), it may have been an accident, and the universe itself could be the actor responsible.</description>
<picurl>210952.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="112828" type="main character in" update="2020-09-24">
<rating votes="1">1.04</rating>
<name>Doge Suwaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="45" picture="44970.jpg">Sugita Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="113182" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-10-15">
<rating votes="1">3.09</rating>
<name>Ninose Sannose</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>253166.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="61276" picture="249844.jpg">Kaida Akane</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="113183" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-12-03">
<rating votes="1">1.22</rating>
<name>Kyan Tama</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>253163.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9510" picture="185781.jpg">Shimizu Ayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="113184" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-10-15">
<rating votes="1">1.80</rating>
<name>Shioya Rei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>253164.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43492" picture="232251.jpg">Tomita Miyu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="113185" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-10-15">
<rating votes="1">1.04</rating>
<name>Oosaka Akari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>253153.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9510" picture="185781.jpg">Shimizu Ayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="113186" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-10-15">
<rating votes="1">5.14</rating>
<name>Aneha Yua</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>253165.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16794" picture="214757.jpg">Ogura Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="113187" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-10-15">
<rating votes="1">1.80</rating>
<name>Gakesaka Minori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>253148.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16794" picture="214757.jpg">Ogura Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="113188" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-10-15">
<rating votes="1">1.80</rating>
<name>Omoi Ayame</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>253168.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16794" picture="214757.jpg">Ogura Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="113189" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-10-15">
<rating votes="1">5.14</rating>
<name>Sukiyabashi Rui</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>253152.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="22625" picture="59506.jpg">Nagatsuma Juri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="113190" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-10-15">
<rating votes="1">1.80</rating>
<name>Murakami Sanami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>253154.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="61240" picture="249744.jpg">Kitamori Saika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="113191" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-10-15">
<rating votes="1">5.14</rating>
<name>Yuuseki Natsumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>253167.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="61240" picture="249744.jpg">Kitamori Saika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="113192" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-10-15">
<rating votes="1">7.47</rating>
<name>Misenai Kanan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>253151.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43492" picture="232251.jpg">Tomita Miyu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="113193" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-10-15">
<rating votes="1">7.47</rating>
<name>Toyofusa Urara</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>253150.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="22625" picture="59506.jpg">Nagatsuma Juri</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="232657" update="2020-09-24">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2020-09-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">PV (1:28)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="232997" update="2020-11-15">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2020-10-14</airdate>
<rating votes="4">2.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">土下座始めました.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Now Groveling</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dogeza Hajimemashita.</title>
<summary>On the school rooftop, Doge Suwaru is desperate to see Gakesaka Minori’s boobs.
Source: Crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>798190</identifier>
<identifier>dogezai-tried-asking-while-kowtowing</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="232998" update="2020-11-15">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2020-10-21</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">不定方程式</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Indeterminate Equation</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Futeihouteishiki</title>
<summary>Doge Suwaru has an urge to see Sukiyabashi Rui-sensei’s boobs during a remedial class.
Source: Crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>798191</identifier>
<identifier>dogezai-tried-asking-while-kowtowing</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="232999" update="2020-11-15">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2020-10-28</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大丈夫! 履いてませんよ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">No Panties? No Problem!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Daijoubu! Haitemasen yo!</title>
<summary>Doge Suwaru is alone with Misenai Kanan in the nurse’s office after school, when he suddenly wants to see her panties.
Source: Crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>798192</identifier>
<identifier>dogezai-tried-asking-while-kowtowing</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="233000" update="2020-11-15">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2020-11-04</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ハードボイルド・ドゲザーランド</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hardboiled Dogezaland</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hard-boiled Dogezaaland</title>
<summary>The sun is sets upon me and Murakami Sanami when, in the orange-lit library room, I become determined to grovel.
Source: Crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>798526</identifier>
<identifier>dogezai-tried-asking-while-kowtowing</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="233064" update="2020-11-27">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<airdate>2021-01-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">異世界転生して土下座始めました</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Isekai Tensei Shite Dogeza Hajimemashita</title>
</episode>
<episode id="233897" update="2020-11-15">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2020-11-11</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">はい, こんにちわー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hey There!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hi, Konnichiwaa</title>
<summary>In the gym, after school, Suwaru is hanging out with his childhood friend, Osaka Akari, who had just transferred from Osaka. This vibe can only mean one thing!
Source: Crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>798527</identifier>
<identifier>dogezai-tried-asking-while-kowtowing</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="233898" update="2020-10-28">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2020-11-18</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">素直になれなくて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Can`t Become More Honest</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sunao ni Narenakute</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>798528</identifier>
<identifier>dogezai-tried-asking-while-kowtowing</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="233899" update="2020-10-28">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2020-11-25</airdate>
<rating votes="3">1.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">見て行って・その・象さん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 7</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mite Itte Sono Zou-san</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>798529</identifier>
<identifier>dogezai-tried-asking-while-kowtowing</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="233900" update="2020-10-28">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2020-12-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">赤ちゃん始めました.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`m a Baby Now</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akachan Hajimemashita.</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>798530</identifier>
<identifier>dogezai-tried-asking-while-kowtowing</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="234882" update="2020-11-27">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2020-12-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヘブン・オア・ヘル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Heaven or Hell</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Heaven or Hell</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>798531</identifier>
<identifier>dogezai-tried-asking-while-kowtowing</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="234883" update="2020-11-27">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2020-12-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">進捗どうですか!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">How`s Work Going?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinchoku Dou Desuka!</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>798532</identifier>
<identifier>dogezai-tried-asking-while-kowtowing</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="234884" update="2020-11-27">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2020-12-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">第4類危険物</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Class 4 Hazardous Materials</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dai 4 Rui Kikenbutsu</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>798533</identifier>
<identifier>dogezai-tried-asking-while-kowtowing</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="234885" update="2020-11-27">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2020-12-30</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">妹始められました</title>
<title xml:lang="en">She Made Herself My Sister</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Imouto Hajimeraremashita</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>798534</identifier>
<identifier>dogezai-tried-asking-while-kowtowing</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="236321" update="2021-01-06">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2020-10-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
