<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="15989" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2021-04-06</startdate>
<enddate>2021-06-29</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Odd Taxi</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">オッドタクシー</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ODD TAXI</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Odd Taxi</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="official">奇巧計程車</title>
</titles>
<url>http://oddtaxi.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="54767" type="Animation Work">P.I.C.S.</name>
<name id="727" type="Animation Work">OLM</name>
<name id="32553" type="Character Design">Nakayama Hiromi</name>
<name id="54767" type="Original Work">P.I.C.S.</name>
<name id="63146" type="Character Design">Kinoshita Baku</name>
<name id="63146" type="Direction">Kinoshita Baku</name>
<name id="63147" type="Music">OMSB</name>
<name id="63148" type="Music">Punpee</name>
<name id="63149" type="Music">Vava</name>
</creators>
<description>This town should look familiar, but suddenly, it`s not. The taxi driver http://anidb.net/ch116212 [Odokawa] lives a very mundane life. He has no family, doesn`t really hang out with others, and he`s an oddball who is narrow-minded and doesn`t talk much. The only people he can call his friends are his doctor, http://anidb.net/ch116210 [Gouriki] and his classmate from high school, http://anidb.net/ch116209 [Kakihana]. All of his patrons seem to be slightly odd themselves. The college student who wants the world to notice him online, http://anidb.net/ch116201 [Kabasawa]. A nurse with secrets named http://anidb.net/ch116211 [Shirakawa]. A comedy duo that just can`t catch a break named the Homosapiens. A local hoodlum named http://anidb.net/ch116199 [Dobu]. An idol group that`s just starting out named Mystery Kiss... All these mundane conversations somehow eventually lead to a girl who`s gone missing.
Source: crunchyroll</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="72">7.91</permanent>
<temporary count="75">7.37</temporary>
<review count="1">6.66</review>
</ratings>
<picture>258280.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>23921</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>46102</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://oddtaxi.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Odd_Taxi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>オッドタクシー</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5949</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>375510</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>23490</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>oddtaxi_</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>oddtaxi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2642" parentid="2624" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-09-28">
<name>alternative present</name>
<description>Anime that fit in the alternative present category usually have technology and society that is very similar to ours, but with differences in both, history and culture, which sometimes are blatantly obvious, but sometimes harder to place; this one can at times be very subjective.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2656" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>satire</name>
<description>In satire, vices, follies, abuses, and shortcomings are held up to ridicule, ideally with the intent of shaming individuals, and society itself, into improvement. Although satire is usually meant to be funny, its greater purpose is often constructive social criticism, using wit as a weapon. (Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2676" parentid="2672" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo</name>
<description>Tokyo, officially Tokyo Metropolis, is the capital city of Japan and one of its 47 prefectures. The Greater Tokyo Area is the most populous metropolitan area in the world. It is the seat of the Emperor of Japan and the Japanese government. Tokyo is in the Kantou region on the southeastern side of the main island Honshu and includes the Izu Islands and Ogasawara Islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214311.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2857" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-10-04">
<name>anthropomorphism</name>
<description>Anthropomorphism is the attribution of uniquely human characteristics to non-human beings, inanimate objects, or natural or supernatural phenomena. If it`s an animal or an object (AI excluded) and it speaks and/or does other human-like things (dresses up) then we`re dealing with anthropomorphism.
Anthropomorphism leans more on the animal-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t7 [juujin], which leans more on the human-looking side.
Usage the tag image for reference, when tagging characters:

* This is a juujin.
* This is split between juujin and anthropomorphism, to be decided on a case-by-case basis, but most likely leans on the human-looking juujin side in most cases.
* This is anthropomorphism; tag both anthropomorphism and the respective animal type.
* This is anthropomorphism; tag both anthropomorphism and the respective animal type.
* This is just a regular animal; do not tag juujin or anthropomorphism — only tag the actual animal type.
</description>
<picurl>252666.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3185" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-27">
<name>wordplay</name>
<description>The characters play with words. 
E.g. purposely or accidentally use similar-sounding but wrongly applied words in the Japanese original, leading to supposedly funny misunderstandings and confusion.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3217" parentid="2864" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-17">
<name>working life</name>
<description>The life of someone actually working on a often less than glamorous job is depicted in this anime. The job is taxing and the pay is low, not really the dream job one would choose to work in.
Examples: Working as salesperson in a department store, or as a waitress in a family restaurant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3968" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-26">
<name>animal protagonist</name>
<description>The anime revolves around an animal, usually only communicating with typical onomatopoeia. The animal mostly lives in a human family and has adventures on a regular base. This can be the discovery of a new room, or being lost by having taken a wrong turn in the outside world.
Typical example: http://anidb.net/a5801 [Chii`s Sweet Home].
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t4259 [animal world], where the whole world is composed of animals.</description>
<picurl>10255.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3977" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-29">
<name>dialogue driven</name>
<description>A dialogue driven show has its story advanced by dialogue, with action being of much lower priority, and relies heavily on conversations between characters.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4259" parentid="2857" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>animal world</name>
<description>All characters of the show are walking-talking animals. Their behaviour and clothing can resemble that of humans. They also may try to mirror human society.
There are no humans present in this world.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t3968 [animal protagonist].</description>
<picurl>10254.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4522" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2021-04-12">
<name>social commentary</name>
<description>Social commentary is the act of using rhetorical means to provide commentary on issues in a society. This is often done with the idea of implementing or promoting change by informing the general populace about a given problem and appealing to people`s sense of justice. Social commentary can be practiced through all forms of communication, from printed form, to conversations to computerized communication.
Since this is anime, usually, the mores of Japan and the Japanese society are scrutinised, but not restricted to that.
This tag should only apply to anime where social commentary is major theme that is explored thoroughly as a main (sub-)plot element. As social commentary, the anime should send a message to the viewers, criticising our society through fiction; merely portraying complex social elements such as racism is not sufficient.
Examples of anime that provide social commentary:
http://anidb.net/a812 [Roujin Z]: criticism of our healthcare system for the elderly and our growing reliance on artificial intelligence in medicine.
http://anidb.net/a191 [GTO (Great Teacher Onizuka)]: many episodes criticise our education system in schools, as well as the ethics and struggles of teaching, showing the negative effects of bullying in schools.
http://anidb.net/a4121 [NHK ni Youkoso!]: criticises the Otaku culture.
Non-examples:
http://anidb.net/a10401 [Tokyo Ghoul]: depicts two different living species hating each other (a common trope in fiction, including anime) as an excuse for action and violence, as well as resolving conflicts between the two species that are irrelevant to our social issues.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6070" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-15">
<name>mystery</name>
<description>The mystery film is a sub-genre of the more general category of crime film. It focuses on the efforts of the detective, private investigator or amateur sleuth to solve the mysterious circumstances of a crime by means of clues, investigation, and clever deduction. (Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6840" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-07">
<name>social media</name>
<description>Social media are computer-mediated technologies that allow the creating and sharing of information, ideas, career interests and other forms of expression via virtual communities and networks.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="116189" type="appears in" update="2021-03-24">
<name>Rena</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>258792.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="63520" picture="259486.jpg">Kagura Chika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="116190" type="appears in" update="2021-03-24">
<name>Kanon</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>258793.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="63519" picture="259488.jpg">Shiomiya Amane</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="116191" type="appears in" update="2021-03-24">
<name>Shoufuutei Donraku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>258794.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="297" picture="233915.jpg">Ootsuka Houchuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="116192" type="appears in" update="2021-03-24">
<name>Kuroda</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>258795.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="371" picture="166173.jpg">Kuroda Takaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="116193" type="appears in" update="2021-03-24">
<name>Sekiguchi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>258796.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="8943" picture="140050.jpg">Horii Chad</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="116194" type="appears in" update="2021-03-24">
<name>Yamamoto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>258797.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34070" picture="130103.jpg">Furukawa Makoto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="116195" type="appears in" update="2021-03-24">
<name>Kondou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>258798.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="63517" picture="10897.jpeg">Phoenix</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="116196" type="appears in" update="2021-03-24">
<name>Fukumoto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>258799.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="63518" picture="259483.jpg">Takai Keisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="116197" type="appears in" update="2021-03-24">
<rating votes="1">7.58</rating>
<name>Tanaka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>258800.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36680" picture="153752.jpg">Saitou Souma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="116198" type="appears in" update="2021-03-24">
<name>Imai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>258801.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36679" picture="223319.jpg">Sakai Koudai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="116199" type="appears in" update="2021-03-24">
<name>Dobu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>258802.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="373" picture="191382.jpg">Hamada Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="116200" type="appears in" update="2021-03-24">
<name>Taeko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>258803.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="63513" picture="259476.jpg">Murakami Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="116201" type="appears in" update="2021-03-24">
<name>Kabasawa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>258804.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="63514" picture="259477.jpg">Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="116202" type="appears in" update="2021-03-24">
<name>Baba</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>258805.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="63515" picture="259480.jpg">Tsuda Atsuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="116203" type="appears in" update="2021-03-24">
<name>Shibagaki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>258806.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="63516" picture="259481.jpg">Yuusuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="116204" type="secondary cast in" update="2021-03-24">
<name>Daimon Otouto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>258807.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="63511" picture="259474.jpg">Asei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="116205" type="secondary cast in" update="2021-03-24">
<rating votes="1">1.23</rating>
<name>Daimon Ani</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>258808.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="63512" picture="259475.jpg">Kousei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="116206" type="secondary cast in" update="2021-03-24">
<name>Mitsuya Yuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>258809.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="61190" picture="249691.jpg">Murakami Manatsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="116207" type="secondary cast in" update="2021-03-24">
<name>Ichimura Shiho</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>258810.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="50014" picture="259512.jpg">Koizumi Moeka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="116208" type="secondary cast in" update="2021-03-24">
<name>Nikaidou Rui</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>258811.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20025" picture="132938.jpg">Mimori Suzuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="116209" type="secondary cast in" update="2021-03-24">
<name>Kakihana</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>258812.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="254" picture="17073.jpg">Yamaguchi Kappei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="116210" type="secondary cast in" update="2021-03-24">
<name>Gouriki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>258813.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2225" picture="192115.jpg">Kimura Ryouhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="116211" type="secondary cast in" update="2021-03-24">
<name>Shirakawa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>258814.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="22171" picture="173757.jpg">Iida Riho</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="116212" type="main character in" update="2021-03-24">
<name>Odokawa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>258815.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="31313" picture="84218.jpg">Hanae Natsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="116661" type="appears in" update="2021-04-05">
<name>Yano</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>259509.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="63524" picture="259511.jpg">Meteor</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="116662" type="appears in" update="2021-04-05">
<name>Nagashima Satoshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>259510.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="238842" update="2021-04-09">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2021-04-06</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">変わり者の運転手</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Eccentric Driver</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der exzentrische Fahrer</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kawarimono no Untenshu</title>
<summary>It`s business as usual for privately-owned taxi driver Odokawa as he drives a variety of passengers around the city. He also pays a visit to his doctor.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>810846</identifier>
<identifier>oddtaxi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="238843" update="2021-04-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2021-04-13</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">長い夜の過ごし方</title>
<title xml:lang="en">How to Spend a Long Night</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Wie man eine lange Nacht verbringt</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nagai Yoru no Sugoshi Kata</title>
<summary>It`s business as usual for privately-owned taxi driver Odokawa as he drives a variety of passengers around the city. He also visits the sauna.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>810847</identifier>
<identifier>oddtaxi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="238844" update="2021-04-28">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2021-04-20</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">付け焼き刃に御用心</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Borrowed Plumes and the Bodyguard</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Geborgte Federn und der Leibwächter</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ukeyakiba ni Goyoushin</title>
<summary>It`s business as usual for privately-owned taxi driver Odokawa as he drives a variety of passengers around the city. He also has a wanted criminal armed with a gun get into his taxi.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>810848</identifier>
<identifier>oddtaxi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="238845" update="2021-05-05">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2021-04-27</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">田中革命</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tanaka`s Revolution</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Tanaka-Revolution</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tanaka Kakumei</title>
<summary>It`s business as usual for privately-owned taxi driver Odokawa as he drives a variety of passengers around the city. Sometimes he drives in a little bit of a hurry.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>810849</identifier>
<identifier>oddtaxi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="239626" update="2021-05-12">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2021-05-04</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アイドルなんて呼ばないで</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Don`t Call Me an Idol</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Nenn mich nicht Idol</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Idol Nante Yobanaide</title>
<summary>It`s business as usual for privately-owned taxi driver Odokawa as he drives a variety of passengers around the city. Sometimes idols ride in his taxi, but don`t worry; he`s as tight-lipped as an authentic bartender.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>810850</identifier>
<identifier>oddtaxi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="239627" update="2021-05-19">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2021-05-11</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">なんでやねんが聞きたいよ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let Me Hear You Say, "What the Hell?"</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Sag mal: „Was zum Teufel“</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nandeyanen ga Kikitai yo</title>
<summary>It`s business as usual for privately-owned taxi driver Odokawa as he drives a variety of passengers around the city. Sometimes he`s taken to a cabaret club in Shinjuku.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>810851</identifier>
<identifier>oddtaxi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="239628" update="2021-05-26">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2021-05-18</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">トリック・オア・トリート</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Trick or Treat</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Süßes oder Saures</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Trick or Treat</title>
<summary>It`s business as usual for privately-owned taxi driver Odokawa as he drives a variety of passengers around the city. Sometimes weirdos pick fights with him in Shibuya on Halloween.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>810852</identifier>
<identifier>oddtaxi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="239629" update="2021-06-02">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2021-05-25</airdate>
<rating votes="6">8.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Bless you</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bless You</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Bless you</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bless You</title>
<summary>It`s business as usual for privately-owned taxi driver Odokawa as he drives a variety of passengers around the city. Come to think of it, he`s driven Goriki before.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>810853</identifier>
<identifier>oddtaxi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="240346" update="2021-06-09">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2021-06-01</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヒーローの憂鬱</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Hero`s Melancholy</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Melancholie eines Helden</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hero no Yuuutsu</title>
<summary>It`s business as usual for privately-owned taxi driver Odokawa as he drives a variety of passengers around the city. However, he`s not very good at car chases.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>810854</identifier>
<identifier>oddtaxi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="240347" update="2021-06-16">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2021-06-08</airdate>
<rating votes="5">8.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">俺たちに明日はない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">We Have No Tomorrow</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Für uns gibt es kein Morgen</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oretachi ni Ashita wa Nai</title>
<summary>It`s business as usual for privately-owned taxi driver Odokawa as he drives a variety of passengers around the city. Sometimes he`s threatened and attacked by passengers.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>810855</identifier>
<identifier>oddtaxi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="240348" update="2021-06-23">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2021-06-15</airdate>
<rating votes="5">9.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あの日に戻れたら</title>
<title xml:lang="en">If We Could Go Back to That Day</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Wenn ich an diesen Tag zurück könnte</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ano Hi ni Modoretara</title>
<summary>It`s business as usual for privately-owned taxi driver Odokawa as he drives a variety of passengers around the city. Due to his profession, he`s familiar with the parking lots around the city.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>810856</identifier>
<identifier>oddtaxi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="240349" update="2021-05-19">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2021-06-22</airdate>
<rating votes="5">9.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">たりないふたり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Not Enough</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tarinai Futari</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>810857</identifier>
<identifier>oddtaxi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="240350" update="2021-05-19">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2021-06-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">どちらまで?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Where To?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dochira made?</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>810858</identifier>
<identifier>oddtaxi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
