<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="1761" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2004-07-08</startdate>
<enddate>2004-09-30</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Galaxy Angel 4th</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">ギャラクシーエンジェルX</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Galaxy Angel s4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Galaxy Angel X</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Galaxy Angel Season 4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">GA4</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ギャラクシーエンジェル4th</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Galaxy Angel X</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="260" type="Prequel">Galaxy Angel 3</anime>
<anime id="4335" type="Character">Galaxy Angel Rune</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.madhouse.co.jp/works/2004-2003/works_tv_galaxyange4.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="731" type="Animation Work">Madhouse</name>
<name id="952" type="Original Work">Broccoli</name>
<name id="3719" type="Series Composition">Inoue Toshiki</name>
<name id="2302" type="Music">Nanase Hikaru</name>
<name id="6028" type="Character Design">Fujita Mariko</name>
<name id="7012" type="Direction">Takayanagi Shigehito</name>
</creators>
<description>Starting out with the new Galaxy Angel, Chitose Karasuma, the Angel Troupe continue their search for The Lost Technology while running into different kinds of mishaps.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="555">6.22</permanent>
<temporary count="564">7.31</temporary>
<review count="4">8.79</review>
</ratings>
<picture>154184.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4163</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>655</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1453</identifier>
<identifier>jvuqga</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.madhouse.co.jp/works/2004-2003/works_tv_galaxyange4.html</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://web.archive.org/web/20040704015047/http://www.tv-osaka.co.jp/galaxyangel_4th/main2.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Galaxy_Angel</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ギャラクシーエンジェル_(アニメ)#.E7.AC.AC4.E6.9C.9F</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>428</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>320852</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6820</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>860</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2660" parentid="2627" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>other planet</name>
<description>The anime will fit this category if some or all of the action takes place on another planet which is supposedly in the same universe as Earth, not a complete fantasy world; usually there has to be some concept of space travel. The Latin name for Earth - Terra, would also pass the condition of being in the same universe as Earth. Basically, even mentioning of Earth existing or having existed would be enough. Although Moon is a moon, it also qualifies as Other Planet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2661" parentid="2627" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>shipboard</name>
<description>Beam me up, Scotty! Space stations (think Death Star) also count. Basically, this category is to tell if the setting takes place onboard a spaceship in space. This category is not applicable if the spaceship lies on a planet and never actually gets into space.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2800" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>game</name>
<description>Based on an interactive (even if minimally so) form of entertainment software, generally available for PCs, consoles or arcade machines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3267" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="true" verified="true" update="2009-05-22">
<name>everybody dies</name>
<description>Not necessarily everyone, but a good portion of the characters kick the bucket.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4521" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-28">
<name>lost technology</name>
<description>Any advanced technology or science-related knowledge that was lost for some reason fits the description. This could be technology from a time before a post-apocalyptic cataclysm, knowledge gained a long time ago but forgotten, or the relics of an old alien civilization only recently discovered.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="3013" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-09">
<rating votes="70">6.81</rating>
<name>Milfeulle Sakuraba</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A seventeen-year-old, selfless pink-haired girl who has an incredible amount of good luck with extremely bad luck periodically to counter it. The bad luck can cause disastrous outcomes like destroying a whole planet or even an entire galaxy. Strangely enough, this could be minimized if Milfeulle is happy at those days. She can be stubborn if she doesn`t get her way, but is usually happy-go-lucky. The newest member of the Angel Troupe at the start of the series. Her hobby is making tea and cooking snacks, particularly cake. The flowers on her head can spin and make her fly or hover in the air. Her first name is derived from the name for the French pastry mille-feuille.</description>
<picture>18666.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="357" picture="32000.jpg">Shintani Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3014" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-09">
<rating votes="52">7.05</rating>
<name>Ranpha Franboise</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A blonde, vain beauty usually featured in a red Chinese dress with remarkable physical strength. Her hobby is fortune-telling, and she`s even successful at times. Her predominant yet ultimately futile obsession is attempting to snag rich (and preferably handsome) men, which rarely appear in the series. Usually when she does meet these men she completely falls apart and makes a total fool of herself. Although apparently pushy she is actually very sensitive, though can come off as domineering. The two metallic things on her head are weapons.</description>
<picture>18668.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="350" picture="20063.jpg">Tamura Yukari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3015" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-09">
<rating votes="77">7.10</rating>
<name>Mint Blancmanche</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An intelligent blue-haired girl who loves to wear full body costumes, but will never, ever be seen by her friends while wearing them (unless it`s work-related). Her family is wealthy and she sometimes comes off snobbish, but she normally has a sincere, distinguished politeness in her voice when in conversations with others. She has a dark side, as she can sometimes be selfish to the point of letting her fellow Angels die rather than be embarrassed, and she likes to play mean pranks on the less-than-bright Ranpha. She also can read minds or emotions in some situations. She has a pair of white rabbit ear-like appendages just above her normal ears that twitch, rise or droop depending on her feelings. The ears also allow her to fly or hover in the air. Her last name is derived from the name for the dessert blancmange.</description>
<picture>18667.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38" picture="171532.jpg">Sawashiro Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3016" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-09">
<rating votes="46">6.73</rating>
<name>Forte Stollen</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A frank, husky-voiced, boyish redhead in a stylised military uniform complete with hat and monocle. Her hobby is collecting guns and other weapons, and is a strong believer in applied force to many situations. She is scared of and allergic to mice.</description>
<picture>18669.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2069" picture="246996.jpg">Yamaguchi Mayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3017" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-09">
<rating votes="77">7.60</rating>
<name>Vanilla H</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A green-haired pale-coloured young girl who rarely speaks, and always in a calm, deadpan voice. Most of the time, when she speaks, she refers to God. She has a strange machine, known as the Nanomachine, in her room and often prays to it. Despite all of this, she is quite caring and always follows orders. She is also apparently the possessor of a hot temper, but keeps it well-hidden. She can heal the injuries of others, the effects made visible by a green glow around her hands, and the red gem at her forehead can sometimes project a powerful beam. She can also speak to various animals like when she talks to monkeys in episode 18. She carries around the stuffed animal in which Normad`s chip has been placed, but she`s not as devoted to Normad as he is to her.</description>
<picture>18670.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="70" picture="171604.jpg">Kanai Mika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21324" type="appears in" update="2013-10-19">
<rating votes="4">8.92</rating>
<name>Angel Tai</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>See also http://anidb.net/cr7010 [Angel Tai (Collaboration)]</description>
<picture>54437.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27564" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-26">
<rating votes="22">7.22</rating>
<name>Normad</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An artificial intelligence, formerly part of an old missile, full of knowledge and experience. It was transferred into a stuffed animal.</description>
<picture>64116.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="70" picture="171604.jpg">Kanai Mika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27565" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-26">
<rating votes="3">7.91</rating>
<name>Volcott O`Huey</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Commander and occasional father figure to the Angel Team. He is close to retiring and has variable patience with the girls.</description>
<picture>64117.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="168" picture="246304.jpg">Fujiwara Keiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27789" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-28">
<name>Major Mary</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The creator of Team Twin Star and the Perot brothers` superior officer.</description>
<picture>64596.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="74" picture="84835.jpg">Oohara Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27790" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-28">
<name>Cocomo Perot</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One half of the Twin Star Team and Malibu`s brother, they work under a female commander, Major Mary. Cocomo is hotheaded, immature and obsesses over parfait.</description>
<picture>64597.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="81" picture="41282.jpg">Sanpei Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27791" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-25">
<name>Malibu Perot</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One Half of the Twin Star Team and Cocomo`s brother, they work under a female commander, Major Mary. Malibu is reserved, thoughtful and enjoys reading.</description>
<picture>64477.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3062" picture="170303.jpg">Saeki Tomo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31068" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-10">
<rating votes="4">5.27</rating>
<name>Karasuma Chitose</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69533.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="355" picture="71573.jpg">Gotou Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="19079" update="2011-04-23">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-07-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">非凡平凡チョコボンボン / 貴女をおもゆ......</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ordinary Extraordinary Chocolates / Steamed, Thinking of You</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hibon Heibon Choko Bonbon / Kijo o Omoyu......</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23410" update="2011-04-23">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-07-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ラッキーモンキー汗かきベソかき穴あきー焼き / 友情の切り身お試し価格</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lucky Monkey~ ... Rice Cracker / Trial Price for a Slice of Friendship</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">lucky Monkey Asekaki Besokaki Anaaki Yaki / Yuujou no Kirimi o Tameshi Kakaku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23799" update="2011-04-23">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-07-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">侵略スパイス中佐三昧 / お見アイス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Commander Flavoured Invasion Spice / Marriage Meeting Ice-cream</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinryaku Spice Chuusa Sanmai / Omi Ice</title>
</episode>
<episode id="23800" update="2011-04-23">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-07-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">わざわざコトコト煮込んだスープ / 哀しみ憎しみ凍み豆腐</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Soup That Has Simmered Extra Long / Sadness and Hatred Tofu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wazawaza Kotokoto Nikon Da Soup / Kanashimi Nikushimi Shimi Toufu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30260" update="2011-04-23">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-08-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">じゃんじゃん炊飯じゃー / ラブ米</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Go Ahead, Rice Cooker / Love Rice</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Janjan Suihan Jaa / Love Kome</title>
</episode>
<episode id="30261" update="2011-04-23">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-08-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">思い出ぎゅうぎゅう鍋 / その時歴史は, プリンセスメロン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Memory-Full, Sukiyaki / History Is a Princess Melon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Omoide Gyuugyuu Nabe / Sono Toki Rekishi wa, Princess Melon</title>
</episode>
<episode id="37903" update="2011-04-23">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-08-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">成りアガリクスダケ / お守りそば</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Upstart Agaricus / Caring Soba</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nari Agarikusudake / Omamori Soba</title>
</episode>
<episode id="42075" update="2011-04-23">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-08-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">トラのうま煮 / 今日風(株)ラ蒸し</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Boiled Tiger of Trauma / Today`s Corporation in Steamed Turnip</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tora no Umani / Kyoufu (Kabu) Ra Mushi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="44483" update="2011-04-23">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-09-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">コ・ロ・ロ・ロシアンティー / アヴェンジャーエール</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hitman`s Russian Tea / Avenger Ale</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kororo Russian Tea / Avenger Ale</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46685" update="2011-04-23">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-09-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">燃焼系傷心揚げ / お笑イグサのコイこく</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Heartbreak-Fried Vegetables for Vegans / Stewed Carp of Comical Rush</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nenshoukei Shoushin Age / Oemi Iguasa no Koi Koku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46698" update="2011-04-23">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-09-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ハーイ! ちりめんじゃっく / レイニーブルー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hi! Crepe Jack / Rainy Blue</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Haai! Chirimen Jack / Rainy Blue</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46699" update="2011-04-23">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-09-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">エンジェルなかまボコ / カレイ煮付けカレー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Angelic Steamed Fish Paste / Boiled Flounder in Curry</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Angel Nakama Boko / Curry Nitsuke Curry</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46875" update="2011-04-23">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2004-09-30</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">のぞみかなえたまごとじ / オールオッケーロケ弁当</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wish Bounded Together with Egg / All Okay Location Lunch Box</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nozomi Kanae Tamago to Ji / All Okay LocaBentou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125488" update="2019-05-23">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2004-07-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125489" update="2019-05-23">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2004-07-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131980" update="2019-05-23">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2004-09-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131981" update="2011-07-18">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Galaxy Angels Eternal Lovers Promo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131982" update="2011-07-18">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131983" update="2011-07-18">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD Commercials</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131984" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>20</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">GATV特別編GAQダブルス②-3</title>
<title xml:lang="en">GAQ Special Edition GATV Double Part 2 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">GATV Tokubetsu Hen GAQ Doubles 2: 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131985" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>15</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">GATV特別編GAQダブルス②-2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">GAQ Special Edition GATV Double Part 2 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">GATV Tokubetsu Hen GAQ Doubles 2: 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131986" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>15</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">GATV特別編GAQダブルス②-1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">GAQ Special Edition GATV Double Part 2 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">GATV Tokubetsu Hen GAQ Doubles 2: 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131987" update="2011-07-18">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>10</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">GATV特別編GAQダブルス3</title>
<title xml:lang="en">GAQ Special Edition GATV Double 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">GATV Tokubetsu Hen GAQ Doubles 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131988" update="2011-07-18">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>8</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">GATV特別編GAQダブルス2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">GAQ Special Edition GATV Double 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">GATV Tokubetsu Hen GAQ Doubles 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131989" update="2011-07-18">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>7</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">GATV特別編GAQダブルス1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">GAQ Special Edition GATV Double 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">GATV Tokubetsu Hen GAQ Doubles 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="217243" update="2019-05-23">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2004-09-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1b</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
