<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="185" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>6</episodecount>
<startdate>1988-10-07</startdate>
<enddate>1989-07-07</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Top o Nerae! Gunbuster</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Aim for the top!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">gunbuster 1</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Дотянись до Неба</title>
<title xml:lang="tr" type="synonym">Zirveyi Hedefle! Avcı Silah</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Top o Nerae</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Top wo Nerae</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Top wo Nerae!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">top1</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">トップをねらえ! GunBuster</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Gunbuster</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Gunbuster</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Gunbuster</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Punta al Top! - Gunbuster</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">กันบัสเตอร์</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="2120" type="Sequel">Top o Nerae 2! Diebuster</anime>
<anime id="4526" type="Summary">Top o Nerae! Gunbuster (2006)</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="4575" approval="56" total="85">Tengen Toppa Gurren Lagann</anime>
<anime id="1072" approval="4" total="8">Ace o Nerae!</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="12">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="181366">Awkward and absurd old-school beginning, but it gets better and better. Also characters are sometimes bit annoying and plain... But I liked (a lot during second half) the plot, universe mechanics and very decent ending.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="292041">An awesome series and in my opinion in the time before Neo Genesis Evangelion. A must see series however the dvd`s are pretty hard to find in most stores and there`s a lot of copies over the internet. The problem with those copies on the internet is that most are fake and aren`t the real thing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When you are watching episode 6 you will be wondering "what the heck" but don`t worry it`s suppose to be like that.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="322302">Good characters (nice girls: some fan-service, but never too much), a story that starts lightly and then turns to a trauma, an 20 years-old animation but still more than just acceptable: I don`t ask for more.
Despite I`m neither a mecha or Evangelion fan, I took a great pleasure watching this anime.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="623957">Never cry so much on a mecha anime since Gurren Lagann... I can`t describe how awesome this anime is. I can`t even believe it was made in 1988.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="479011">the last episode blew my mind and heart; the ark in this story is incredible and so full of powerful stuff ... absolutely essential classic</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="424296">This is a must see for both robot and anime fans. Compared to this, Gurren Lagann means nothing.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.gainax.co.jp/anime/top/</url>
<creators>
<name id="57" type="Direction">Anno Hideaki</name>
<name id="718" type="Work">Gainax</name>
<name id="514" type="Original Work">Okada Toshio</name>
<name id="515" type="Animation Character Design">Kubooka Toshiyuki</name>
<name id="515" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kubooka Toshiyuki</name>
<name id="1393" type="Music">Tanaka Kouhei</name>
<name id="515" type="Character Design">Kubooka Toshiyuki</name>
</creators>
<description>In the very near future, a race of huge, insect like aliens is discovered traveling the galaxy. These aliens seem dedicated to the eradication of the human species as it takes its first steps away from the solar system, and they are getting closer and closer to Earth. Humanity has responded by developing spacegoing battleships and giant fighting robots (original idea there). These robots are piloted by the best and brightest of Earth`s youth, picked from training schools around the world.
The story begins in the year 2023, not long after the first battles with the aliens, and centers on young http://anidb.net/ch1836 [Takaya Noriko]. Although Noriko`s father was a famous Captain in the space fleet who was killed during one of the first battles of the war, her own talents as a pilot are questionable. Nonetheless, she has entered a training school. Through the series Noriko, joined by the beautiful and talented http://anidb.net/ch1837 [Amano Kazumi], will fight to overcome the trauma of war, the doubts of her peers, and her own lack of confidence.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="3310">7.34</permanent>
<temporary count="3334">7.61</temporary>
<review count="5">8.26</review>
</ratings>
<picture>131114.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>466</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7248</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>949</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>5462</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>24123</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>355</identifier>
<identifier>yirmty</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.gainax.co.jp/anime/top/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Gunbuster</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>トップをねらえ!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>760</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>88723</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>922</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/288</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1279" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-18">
<name>all-girls school</name>
<description>This school is only for female students. There may be a few male teachers though.</description>
<picurl>70853.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>36563.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2639" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space travel</name>
<description>Space Travel usually refers going to space or travelling there with or without a spacecraft. There are different forms of space travel like Interplanetary travel, Interstellar travel or Intergalactic travel. Since it isn`t possible to travel faster than light, most anime series involve some sort "sub-space travel mechanism" as a way to travel faster than light.</description>
<picurl>242375.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2644" parentid="2274" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-14">
<name>transforming craft</name>
<description>A transforming craft is an object built by humans or other intelligent lifeforms, usually a robot but sometimes also a vehicle of some sort, that can rearrange its parts in order to switch between a minimum of two forms.</description>
<picurl>224142.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2661" parentid="2627" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>shipboard</name>
<description>Beam me up, Scotty! Space stations (think Death Star) also count. Basically, this category is to tell if the setting takes place onboard a spaceship in space. This category is not applicable if the spaceship lies on a planet and never actually gets into space.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2676" parentid="2672" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo</name>
<description>Tokyo, officially Tokyo Metropolis, is the capital city of Japan and one of its 47 prefectures. The Greater Tokyo Area is the most populous metropolitan area in the world. It is the seat of the Emperor of Japan and the Japanese government. Tokyo is in the Kantou region on the southeastern side of the main island Honshu and includes the Izu Islands and Ogasawara Islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214311.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2681" parentid="2672" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Okinawa</name>
<description>Okinawa Prefecture is the southernmost prefecture of Japan. It encompasses two thirds of the Ryukyu Islands in a chain over 1,000 kilometreslong. The Ryukyu Islands extend southwest from Kyushu (the southwesternmost of Japan`s four main islands) to Taiwan. Naha, Okinawa`s capital, is located in the southern part of Okinawa Island.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214299.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2021-04-12">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators. No frontal (visible genitals) = 1.5 stars or less.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2787" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-08-28">
<name>teacher x student</name>
<description>Suggests a relationship involving a teacher and their student, often times sexual in nature.</description>
<picurl>206646.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3087" parentid="2274" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>super robot</name>
<description>These robots tend to have almost semi-magical attacks, which seem impossible or non-realistic, and/or perform non-realistic transformation sequences where they seem to gain/lose mass and utterly change their form, even if it means making their super-hard armour bend like plastic sheets.</description>
<picurl>222137.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3314" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-10">
<name>fate</name>
<description>Fate — The predestined path of all things. The outcome is inevitable and the consequences predetermined. Whether or not the protagonist ultimately decides to follow this path shall weigh heavily on their soul.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3516" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-28">
<name>insects of doom</name>
<description>Concerns insects, be them biological, magical or robotic in nature, that are either the bane, or a major stepping stone in the way of the main character(s) of the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3606" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-11">
<name>family without father</name>
<description>For some reason the protagonists father is no longer among the living. The much too early death was due to sickness or accident.
This plot device adds a certain degree of tragedy to the anime and usually has repercussions on the rest of the family: Possibly the grieve-stricken mother and children barely function as humans. Or adding emphasis to the overall financial predicament of the family, should the father have been the money earner.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3795" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>remastered version available</name>
<description>This anime has been remastered in a higher quality format than the original release. The remaster may be a simple upscale, or it could be a full enhancement project from the original frames. This is irrespective of whether specific groups have released rips of such formats to the internet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3836" parentid="3314" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-28">
<name>the chosen one!</name>
<description>One of the characters in the anime is the "chosen one", the one to bring about change, the only one to "set things right" in a "good" ending, or bring about complete destruction in a "bad" ending.</description>
<picurl>66957.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3843" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-26">
<name>saving the world</name>
<description>While villains love to take over the world or cause the end of the world as we know it, the heroes are most likely motivated by the polar opposite, saving the world. A fairly simple plot/motivation related to for great justice and what not, this trope is pretty broad and very common for many stories not focused on character interaction only.
Source: TV Trope</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3852" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-09">
<name>Bright slap</name>
<description>"You hit me! Not even my father ever hit me!" 
You are the commander of a spaceship, leader of a faction or a team and your best mecha pilot stops fighting and grows increasingly hysterical and angsty, while the enemy could strike you at any time. What are you going to do? 
You slap or punch him, preferably in the face, and back to his senses while delivering a heroic speech that would turn any wimp into a man of destiny.
Named after Bright Noa of Mobile Suit Gundam, a prominent user of this for-sure method.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4081" parentid="2841" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space battles</name>
<description>There are space battles in this anime. Usually between Earth forces and some alien invader, but ship to ship skirmishes in deep space are just as common.</description>
<picurl>242377.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4128" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-07-29">
<name>zero to hero</name>
<description>With his first appearance, this character is getting his ass kicked by nearly everyone, but as the plot continues, through training (mental or physical) or instant power-up, he changes into a killing/fighting/winning machine.
The best example: Makunouchi Ippo from Hajime no Ippo series.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4193" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-03-23">
<name>improbable physics</name>
<description>The physics in this anime have little to do with real-world physics, and are actually very much exaggerated.
Examples: Cars hitting a tiny obstacle, but then flying through the air for no apparent reason, or flimsy bullets slamming heavy characters clear across the room.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4198" parentid="5604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-14">
<name>hard work and guts</name>
<description>One of the character`s motto in the anime. Because there is nothing that cannot be achieved by hard work and guts.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4215" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-30">
<name>daikaijuu</name>
<description>Literally translating to giant monster, daikaiju is an element found often in Japanese entertainment. Although usually for the science fiction genre it is also often used in horror, fantasy, mecha, and to a lesser extent comedy. Any monster that towers over a house technically qualifies as a daikaiju. Some anime, usually mecha, will go as far as calling their daikaiju with a specific title.</description>
<picurl>60039.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4446" parentid="2639" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-12">
<name>faster-than-light travel</name>
<description>Faster-than-light travel is taken for grated in this anime. This is achieved by travelling via hyperspace, nullspace, or wormholes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4469" parentid="2644" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-29">
<name>gattai</name>
<description>Gattai is when two fighting spirits collide and unite, when a man`s soul is ablaze!
When you are about to get your asses kicked by the big bad evil, it`s time to show your true fighting spirit and gattai, literally combine with your mecha to become at least ten times as powerful and kick the big bad evil`s ass.</description>
<picurl>66429.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4537" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-15">
<name>time skip</name>
<description>The plot features at least one skip or jump in time.
Example: A skip from the present into the past, or time skips in increments, e.g. every hour there is a time skip by a day.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4558" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-12">
<name>long time span</name>
<description>The anime spans a much longer than usual (for that genre) period of time, typically several years (possibly decades or even centuries).
Example: In a school setting this could mean the character development is followed from school through college right into working life and the founding of a family with children.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4588" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-20">
<name>fast-paced</name>
<description>Hold onto your hats, this anime`s storyline is relentless.
The characters don`t get time to take a breath as events keep both them and the viewer on a roller coaster ride of revelation and excitement!
Hopefully it all makes sense...</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5529" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-11-05">
<name>black and white</name>
<description>Some or all of this anime is in black and white, typical of older anime made before ~1960. Some modern anime may intentionally shift to black and white for certain scenes or episodes as an artistic effect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5604" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-04">
<name>following one`s dream</name>
<description>No matter what the hardships may be, at least one of the protagonists in this anime is following her/his dream.
Examples: To become a professional athlete, a musician, a painter or the ruler of this world!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5787" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2016-09-11">
<name>time dilation</name>
<description>Time dilation is a scientific phenomena related to relativity, basically stating that for an observer onboard a spaceship travelling at a certain speed, time passes more slowly than it would for an observer on Earth. 
When near-lightspeed travel becomes involved, the effects become quite drastic: a person might go on a space journey that seems to him to last one year and, on returning, find that 10 years have passed on Earth. This is sometimes extrapolated by sci-fi authors to apply to faster-than-light travel as well, though this would not necessarily be the case. 
Note that this effect occurs at considerably lower velocities as well, as an atomic clock on Earth and one in orbit around Earth will be ever so slightly desynced.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5865" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-22">
<name>manly tears</name>
<description>Somewhere down the line, it became the "norm" that boys don`t cry. The scenario does not matter; shedding tears is the ultimate no-no in terms of what you can and cannot do as a man (at least in the West, anyway). But there comes a time when a man`s emotions do get the better of him, and they pour forth - as prerequisite an impassioned speech may or may not be present - by cascading down his cheeks. These are what we like to call "manly tears". Extremely powerful. Not limited but often used in hot-blooded / super robot shows. Examples include Yuusha Ou GaoGaiGar, Getter Robo and Tengen Toppa Gurren Lagann.
The opposite of manly tears are "girly tears".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5875" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-18">
<name>jealousy</name>
<description>A character is jealous of another character either due to love, or power, or wealth.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5929" parentid="2846" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>space opera</name>
<description>Space opera is a sub-genre of fiction that emphasizes romantic adventures in space. Space opera generally involves large-scale conflicts between opponents with powerful abilities and technology. The genre will often be melodramatic, sometimes playing music that can be nothing short of awesome. Warfare and a battle of wits are usually less emphasized, preferring romance (with exceptions, e.g. Ginga Eiyuu Densetsu). Some space operas tend to be formulaic and sometimes even prosaic, often employing very simple devices and somewhat obvious strategies. An example of this would be the infamous laws of physics in the Macross universe, in which the main male lead will hardly ever get hit in battle.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5952" parentid="2874" weight="200" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-25">
<name>end of the world</name>
<description>The imminent end of the world may range from the total destruction of the planet Earth, to the destruction of Earth`s surface, or to the point where human life on the planet is no longer possible, aka the end of humanity.
In any case it looks grim, and the protagonists battle to preserve what they can.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5980" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-24">
<name>live-action imagery</name>
<description>This anime incorporates still images and/or video footage of real-world objects and locations into the animation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6034" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>Engrish</name>
<description>Engrish is actually a mispronunciation of English, as can be the result of someone, who does not have English as their primary language of origin (such as Japanese or Chinese). Occasionally characters in the original Japanese dialogue version of an anime will speak in English... however; this often still requires the assistance of subtitles, for while the words are meant to be said in English, the sentence structure and letter pronunciation may still be strongly related to the person’s primary language.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6062" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-04-05">
<name>heroic sacrifice</name>
<description>"In order to save the many, the few will need to sacrifice their lives..." or so this character may think. 
In a seemingly hopeless situation, against impossible odds, the character does not choose the path of the coward and run, he or she chooses to bravely face the enemy, fully aware that this will mean death.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7119" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>Super Robot Wars</name>
<description>Super Robot Wars is a series of tactical role-playing video games produced by Banpresto. The main feature of the franchise is having a story that crosses over several popular mecha anime, manga and video games, allowing characters and mecha from different titles to team up or battle one another. Due to the nature of crossover games and licensing involved, only a few games have been released outside Japan, and in English; early English-language games only feature Banpresto`s original characters and mecha, and a flagship installment were to never be released until 2016, with the English release of Super Robot Wars V in Southeast Asian countries. The franchise celebrated its 25th anniversary in 2016.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>221614.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="1836" type="main character in" update="2021-05-03">
<rating votes="78">8.28</rating>
<name>Takaya Noriko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>24548.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="268" picture="17093.jpg">Hidaka Noriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1837" type="main character in" update="2015-06-06">
<rating votes="47">6.14</rating>
<name>Amano Kazumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>24550.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="555" picture="23759.jpg">Sakuma Rei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2481" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-06-18">
<rating votes="53">8.08</rating>
<name>Kusakabe Mei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>29227.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="2482" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-06-18">
<rating votes="182">8.82</rating>
<name>Totoro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>29224.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="2591" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-06-06">
<rating votes="33">6.61</rating>
<name>Oota Kouichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>174382.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2" picture="16471.jpg">Wakamoto Norio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7803" type="cameo appearance in" update="2018-08-13">
<rating votes="155">9.13</rating>
<name>Nausicaa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nausicaa is a charismatic young princess of the peaceful Valley of the Wind. Although a skillful fighter, she is humane and peace-loving. She has an unusual gift for communicating with the giant insects (particularly with the Ohmu who are the most intelligent creatures in the Sea of Decay). She is also noted for her empathy toward animals, humans, and other beings. An intelligent girl, and inspired by the mentor figure http://anidb.net/ch7804 [Yupa], a wandering samurai type possessed of great wisdom, Nausicaa frequently explores the Sea of Decay and conducts scientific experiments in an attempt to define the true nature and origins of the toxic world in which she lives. Her explorations are facilitated by her skill at "windriding"; flying with an advanced jet assisted glider craft called Mahve.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>222292.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="12068" type="cameo appearance in" update="2017-11-12">
<rating votes="57">8.58</rating>
<name>Yamato</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>After the defeat of the Earth`s space fleet by the Gamilas Empire in the year 2199, the inhabitants of Earth secretly convert the ruins of the Japanese battleship Yamato into a massive spaceship, the Space Battleship Yamato. Using blueprints they attain from Queen Starsha of the planet Iscandar, they equip their new ship with a space warp drive, called the "wave motion engine", and a new, incredibly powerful weapon called the "wave motion gun" which fires from the bow.</description>
<picture>36555.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="44258" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-06-06">
<rating votes="21">6.01</rating>
<name>Jung Freud</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>87122.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2193" picture="21749.jpg">Kawamura Maria</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60453" type="appears in" update="2015-06-06">
<rating votes="4">7.75</rating>
<name>Smith Toren</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>174377.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="283" picture="17113.jpg">Yao Kazuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="60454" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-06-06">
<rating votes="5">3.98</rating>
<name>Higuchi Kimiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>174384.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3382" picture="24410.jpg">Fuchizaki Yuriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75745" type="appears in" update="2015-06-05">
<name>Kashihara Reiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>174335.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1813" picture="172159.jpg">Katsuki Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75746" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-06-05">
<rating votes="3">3.57</rating>
<name>Tashiro Tatsumi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>174336.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2366" picture="203225.jpg">Ooki Tamio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75747" type="appears in" update="2015-06-05">
<name>Takaya Yuuzou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Noriko`s father.</description>
<picture>174337.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="418" picture="17270.jpg">Hirose Masashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75768" type="appears in" update="2015-06-06">
<name>Kikuchi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>174379.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5977" picture="30601.jpg">Omoro Masayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75769" type="appears in" update="2015-06-06">
<name>Fukuchou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>174380.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="289" picture="186204.jpg">Nishimura Tomomichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75771" type="appears in" update="2015-06-06">
<name>Akai Kimiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kimiko after 10 years which have passed on the Earth.</description>
<picture>174383.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1813" picture="172159.jpg">Katsuki Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75772" type="appears in" update="2015-06-06">
<name>Akai Takami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kimiko`s daughter.</description>
<picture>174385.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3382" picture="24410.jpg">Fuchizaki Yuriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75773" type="appears in" update="2015-06-08">
<rating votes="4">6.22</rating>
<name>Oota Kazumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>174454.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="555" picture="23759.jpg">Sakuma Rei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75774" type="appears in" update="2015-06-06">
<name>Akai Kimiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>174387.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1813" picture="172159.jpg">Katsuki Masako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75775" type="appears in" update="2015-06-06">
<name>Akai Takami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>174388.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3382" picture="24410.jpg">Fuchizaki Yuriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="75776" type="appears in" update="2015-06-06">
<name>Kashihara Reiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>174389.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="75777" type="appears in" update="2015-06-06">
<name>Linda Yamamoto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>174391.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43297">Shiraishi Ayako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81269" type="appears in" update="2016-03-26">
<name>Gunbuster</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>184582.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="1869" update="2012-06-14">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1988-10-07</airdate>
<rating votes="20">4.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ショック! 私とお姉様がパイロット!?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Unbelievable! Amano and I Are Pilots?!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Incroyable ! Amano et moi sommes pilotes</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ช๊อค! นักบินคือฉันกับคุณพี่งั้นเหรอ!?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shock! Watashi to Onee-sama ga Pilot!?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1870" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1989-07-07</airdate>
<rating votes="17">6.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">お願い!! 愛に時間を!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Please! Save Some Time for Love</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">S`il vous plaît, laissez un peu de temps à l`amour</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ขอร้องละ! ขอเวลาให้ความรักหน่อย</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Onegai!! Ai ni Jikan o!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1871" update="2006-03-15">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1989-01-01</airdate>
<rating votes="15">7.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">発進!! 未完の最終兵器!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Launch! The Uncompleted Final Weapon</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`arme ultime inachevée</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ลุย! อาวุธสุดยอดที่ยังไม่สมบูรณ์</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hasshin!! Mikan no Saishuu Heiki!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1872" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1989-01-01</airdate>
<rating votes="16">6.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">初めてのときめき☆初めての出撃</title>
<title xml:lang="en">First Love, First Sortie</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Premier amour, première sortie</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ใจเต้นครั้งแรก ออกโจมตีครั้งแรก</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajimete no Tokimeki, Hajimete no Shutsugeki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1873" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1988-10-07</airdate>
<rating votes="18">5.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">不敵! 天才少女の挑戦!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Challenge of the Fearless Girl Genius!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le défi d`une fille géniale</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ไร้เทียมทาน! การประลองของสาวน้อยอัจฉริยะ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Futeki! Tensai Shoujo no Chousen!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1874" update="2006-03-29">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>1989-07-07</airdate>
<rating votes="29">9.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">果てし無き, 流れのはてに...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">At the End of the Endless Stream</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Au bout de l`infini...</title>
<title xml:lang="th">ไร้ที่สิ้นสุด, ณ ท้ายที่สุด</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hateshi Naki, Nagare no Hate ni...</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19260" update="2019-05-10">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>1988-10-07</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">トップをねらえ! 科学講座 - 第1回 『エーテル宇宙』</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Science Course - Chapter 1: Ether Space</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Top o Nerae! Kagakukouza - Daiikai "Ether Uchuu"</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19261" update="2014-12-30">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1988-10-07</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">トップをねらえ! 科学講座 - 第2回 『星虹(スターボウ)とウラシマ効果』</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Science Course - Chapter 2: Starbows and the Rip Van Winkle Effect</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Top o Nerae! Kagakukouza - Dainikai "Starbow to Urashima Kouka"</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19262" update="2014-12-30">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1989-01-01</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">トップをねらえ! 科学講座 - 第3回 『超光速航法』</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Science Course - Chapter 3: Faster-than-Light Travel</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Top o Nerae! Kagakukouza - Daisankai "Chou Kousoku Kouhou"</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19263" update="2014-12-30">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1989-01-01</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">トップをねらえ! 科学講座 - 第4回 『凶悪宇宙怪獣の巻』</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Science Course - Chapter 4: The Size of the Fiendish Space Monsters</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Top o Nerae! Kagakukouza - Daiyonkai "Kyouaku Uchuu Kaijuu no Maki"</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19264" update="2015-06-06">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1988-10-07</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19265" update="2015-06-06">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>1988-10-07</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19266" update="2005-08-22">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">7.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Excerpt from Kazumi`s speech before ep3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19267" update="2004-05-14">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Noriko`s preview before ep5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="31814" update="2007-05-25">
<epno type="2">S9</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="2">3.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">はるみ&amp;ゆみこのグッドモーニング沖女!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Harumi &amp; Yumiko`s Good Morning Oki Girls!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Harumi &amp; Yumiko no Good Morning Oki Onna!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="31815" update="2007-05-20">
<epno type="2">S10</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="2">3.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">戦闘宙域</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cosmic Space Battle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sentou Chuuiki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="31816" update="2007-05-20">
<epno type="2">S11</epno>
<length>4</length>
<rating votes="2">4.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">シズラープロジェクト</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sizzler Project</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sizzler Project</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35617" update="2014-12-30">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>1995-09-18</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">新トップをねらえ! 科学講座 - 第4+1回 『宇宙船の歴史』</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Science Course - Chapter 4+1: The History of Spaceships</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shin Top o Nerae! Kagakukouza - Yon plus Daiikai "Uchuusen no Rekishi"</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35618" update="2014-12-30">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>1995-09-18</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">新トップをねらえ! 科学講座 - 最終回 『真・太陽系』</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Science Course - Final Chapter: The True Solar System</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shin Top o Nerae! Kagakukouza - Saishuukai "Shin Taiyoukei"</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125521" update="2010-11-26">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV VHS/LD Vol.3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125522" update="2010-11-26">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV VHS/LD Vol.2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125523" update="2010-11-26">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV VHS/LD Vol.1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="138204" update="2012-08-02">
<epno type="2">S13</epno>
<length>30</length>
<title xml:lang="en">EP5 AR Simple Telecine Prototype</title>
</episode>
<episode id="138205" update="2012-03-27">
<epno type="2">S12</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">EP4 Avant Title No Trimming Version</title>
</episode>
<episode id="138222" update="2012-03-28">
<epno type="2">S15</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">帰ってきた トップをねらえ! 科学講座 新・第2回「銀河中心核とブラックホール」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Science Course Return 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaette Kita Top o Nerae! Kagaku Kouza: Shin Dai 2 Kai "Ginga Chuushinkaku to Black Hole"</title>
</episode>
<episode id="138223" update="2019-05-10">
<epno type="2">S14</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">帰ってきた トップをねらえ! 科学講座 新・第1回「軌道エレベーターと軌道ロープウェイ」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Science Course Return 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaette Kita Top o Nerae! Kagaku Kouza: Shin Dai 1 Kai "Kidou Elevator to Kidou Ropeway"</title>
</episode>
<episode id="138224" update="2012-03-28">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">BD 30sec TV Ad</title>
</episode>
<episode id="138225" update="2012-03-28">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD 15sec TV Ad</title>
<title xml:lang="x-other">Remastered DVD-BOX CM 2004</title>
</episode>
<episode id="138226" update="2012-03-28">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="en">1989 Vol3 VHS/VHD/LD Ad</title>
</episode>
<episode id="143860" update="2015-05-28">
<epno type="2">S16</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Creditless Epilogue</title>
</episode>
<episode id="168658" update="2015-05-25">
<epno type="2">S20</epno>
<length>15</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Gunbuster Perfect Guide Tokuten: Producer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="168659" update="2015-05-25">
<epno type="2">S19</epno>
<length>15</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Gunbuster Perfect Guide Tokuten: Music</title>
</episode>
<episode id="168660" update="2015-05-25">
<epno type="2">S18</epno>
<length>20</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Gunbuster Perfect Guide Tokuten: Director</title>
</episode>
<episode id="168661" update="2015-05-25">
<epno type="2">S17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Gunbuster Perfect Guide Tokuten: Casts Interview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="168662" update="2015-05-25">
<epno type="4">T8</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PS2 Software CM 2004</title>
</episode>
<episode id="168663" update="2015-05-25">
<epno type="4">T7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PS2 Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="168670" update="2015-05-25">
<epno type="4">T10</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Video Magazine</title>
</episode>
<episode id="168671" update="2015-05-25">
<epno type="4">T9</epno>
<length>10</length>
<title xml:lang="en">VHD Magazine</title>
</episode>
<episode id="168672" update="2015-05-25">
<epno type="2">S22</epno>
<length>20</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Sound Reprise Version Interview 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="168673" update="2015-05-25">
<epno type="2">S21</epno>
<length>20</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Sound Reprise Version Interview</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
