<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="259" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>9</episodecount>
<startdate>2002-02-03</startdate>
<enddate>2002-03-31</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Galaxy Angel Z</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Galaxy Angel Z</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Galaxy Angel 2</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">银河天使队2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">GA2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">GA Z</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ギャラクシーエンジェルZ</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="260" type="Sequel">Galaxy Angel 3</anime>
<anime id="108" type="Prequel">Galaxy Angel</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>http://www.madhouse.co.jp/works/2003-2002/works_tv_galaxyange2.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="731" type="Animation Work">Madhouse</name>
<name id="3719" type="Series Composition">Inoue Toshiki</name>
<name id="952" type="Original Work">Broccoli</name>
<name id="1525" type="Direction">Asaka Morio</name>
<name id="1921" type="Direction">Oohashi Yoshimitsu</name>
<name id="6028" type="Character Design">Fujita Mariko</name>
<name id="2302" type="Music">Nanase Hikaru</name>
</creators>
<description>In the far future, the human race advanced to space, and prospered. However, Jikushin ( earthquake of time and space ) which occurred suddenly intercepted all networks, and all the civilizations were reset. However, the human race begins to revive, and enters the prosperity age of The Second by the Transvaal imperial country which rises at the center of the galactic system. The science and technology before the civilization was reset, that is, "Lost Technology" was considered to be god`s task. And, it came to be worshiped by the priest who was called "Tsuki no miko".
On the other hand, a certain guard fleet was stationed in the frontier of the galactic system. Though it was the seemingly perfectly ordinary army, the team composed only of the woman called "Angel Corps" existed in this army. They controlled the spaceship which was called "Angel Frame" which was the relic of Lost Technology. And, they collected the lost technology by using the angel frame, and carried out the duties to manage them.
They were not the elite pilots, but Angel Corps was rather an eccentric person`s group. Arms mania`s Forte, costume player`s Mint, taciturn Vanilla, showy Ranpha and Milfeulle who likes cooking ... Every time, they cause a big trouble in the mission.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="810">6.06</permanent>
<temporary count="817">7.31</temporary>
<review count="2">7.49</review>
</ratings>
<picture>154182.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1346</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2206</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>652</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>793</identifier>
<identifier>mctbji</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.madhouse.co.jp/works/2003-2002/works_tv_galaxyange2.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Galaxy_Angel</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ギャラクシーエンジェルZ#.E7.AC.AC2.E6.9C.9F</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1078</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>236842</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5088</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>860</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="798" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>moe</name>
<description>Moe is a Japanese slang loanword that refers to feelings of strong affection mainly towards characters in anime, manga, and video games. Moe, however, has also gained usage to refer to feelings of affection towards any subject. Moe can be related to lust; however, pure lust without other feelings is considered outside its scope. The word Moe originated in the late 1980s and early 1990s in Japan and is of uncertain origin, although there are several theories on how it came into use.
At the anime level, the http://anidb.net/t7146 [cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] tag may also apply.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2660" parentid="2627" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>other planet</name>
<description>The anime will fit this category if some or all of the action takes place on another planet which is supposedly in the same universe as Earth, not a complete fantasy world; usually there has to be some concept of space travel. The Latin name for Earth - Terra, would also pass the condition of being in the same universe as Earth. Basically, even mentioning of Earth existing or having existed would be enough. Although Moon is a moon, it also qualifies as Other Planet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2661" parentid="2627" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>shipboard</name>
<description>Beam me up, Scotty! Space stations (think Death Star) also count. Basically, this category is to tell if the setting takes place onboard a spaceship in space. This category is not applicable if the spaceship lies on a planet and never actually gets into space.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4521" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-28">
<name>lost technology</name>
<description>Any advanced technology or science-related knowledge that was lost for some reason fits the description. This could be technology from a time before a post-apocalyptic cataclysm, knowledge gained a long time ago but forgotten, or the relics of an old alien civilization only recently discovered.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6349" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-13">
<name>multi-segment episodes</name>
<description>Multi-segment episodes are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t5852 [short episodes], which are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length (up to and including 10 minutes).
Also not to be confused with an OVA or music video with multiple (otherwise unrelated) full-length http://anidb.net/t7241 [bundled episodes] consolidated into a single episode video track.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="3013" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-09">
<rating votes="70">6.81</rating>
<name>Milfeulle Sakuraba</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A seventeen-year-old, selfless pink-haired girl who has an incredible amount of good luck with extremely bad luck periodically to counter it. The bad luck can cause disastrous outcomes like destroying a whole planet or even an entire galaxy. Strangely enough, this could be minimized if Milfeulle is happy at those days. She can be stubborn if she doesn`t get her way, but is usually happy-go-lucky. The newest member of the Angel Troupe at the start of the series. Her hobby is making tea and cooking snacks, particularly cake. The flowers on her head can spin and make her fly or hover in the air. Her first name is derived from the name for the French pastry mille-feuille.</description>
<picture>18666.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="357" picture="32000.jpg">Shintani Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3014" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-09">
<rating votes="52">7.05</rating>
<name>Ranpha Franboise</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A blonde, vain beauty usually featured in a red Chinese dress with remarkable physical strength. Her hobby is fortune-telling, and she`s even successful at times. Her predominant yet ultimately futile obsession is attempting to snag rich (and preferably handsome) men, which rarely appear in the series. Usually when she does meet these men she completely falls apart and makes a total fool of herself. Although apparently pushy she is actually very sensitive, though can come off as domineering. The two metallic things on her head are weapons.</description>
<picture>18668.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="350" picture="20063.jpg">Tamura Yukari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3015" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-09">
<rating votes="77">7.10</rating>
<name>Mint Blancmanche</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An intelligent blue-haired girl who loves to wear full body costumes, but will never, ever be seen by her friends while wearing them (unless it`s work-related). Her family is wealthy and she sometimes comes off snobbish, but she normally has a sincere, distinguished politeness in her voice when in conversations with others. She has a dark side, as she can sometimes be selfish to the point of letting her fellow Angels die rather than be embarrassed, and she likes to play mean pranks on the less-than-bright Ranpha. She also can read minds or emotions in some situations. She has a pair of white rabbit ear-like appendages just above her normal ears that twitch, rise or droop depending on her feelings. The ears also allow her to fly or hover in the air. Her last name is derived from the name for the dessert blancmange.</description>
<picture>18667.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38" picture="171532.jpg">Sawashiro Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3016" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-09">
<rating votes="46">6.73</rating>
<name>Forte Stollen</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A frank, husky-voiced, boyish redhead in a stylised military uniform complete with hat and monocle. Her hobby is collecting guns and other weapons, and is a strong believer in applied force to many situations. She is scared of and allergic to mice.</description>
<picture>18669.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2069" picture="246996.jpg">Yamaguchi Mayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3017" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-09">
<rating votes="77">7.60</rating>
<name>Vanilla H</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A green-haired pale-coloured young girl who rarely speaks, and always in a calm, deadpan voice. Most of the time, when she speaks, she refers to God. She has a strange machine, known as the Nanomachine, in her room and often prays to it. Despite all of this, she is quite caring and always follows orders. She is also apparently the possessor of a hot temper, but keeps it well-hidden. She can heal the injuries of others, the effects made visible by a green glow around her hands, and the red gem at her forehead can sometimes project a powerful beam. She can also speak to various animals like when she talks to monkeys in episode 18. She carries around the stuffed animal in which Normad`s chip has been placed, but she`s not as devoted to Normad as he is to her.</description>
<picture>18670.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="70" picture="171604.jpg">Kanai Mika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21324" type="appears in" update="2013-10-19">
<rating votes="4">8.92</rating>
<name>Angel Tai</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>See also http://anidb.net/cr7010 [Angel Tai (Collaboration)]</description>
<picture>54437.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="27564" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-26">
<rating votes="22">7.22</rating>
<name>Normad</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An artificial intelligence, formerly part of an old missile, full of knowledge and experience. It was transferred into a stuffed animal.</description>
<picture>64116.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="70" picture="171604.jpg">Kanai Mika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="27565" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-26">
<rating votes="3">7.91</rating>
<name>Volcott O`Huey</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Commander and occasional father figure to the Angel Team. He is close to retiring and has variable patience with the girls.</description>
<picture>64117.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="168" picture="246304.jpg">Fujiwara Keiji</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="2928" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-03-03</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">GA解析懐石 / お好み♥復讐ランチ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">(09/10) GA Analytic Tea Ceremony &amp; Served to Taste Revenge Lunch</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">GA Kaiseki Kaiseki / Okonomi Fukushuu Lunch</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA">GA Ceremonia del té analizada / Almuerzo de venganza al gusto</title>
</episode>
<episode id="2929" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-02-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">恋の煮こごり純情包み揚げ / ウェディングケーキ合体スペシャル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">(07/08) Deep Fried Egg Rolls of Love &amp; Wedding Cake Combiner Special</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koi no Nikogori Junjou Tsutsumiage / Wedding Cake Gattai Special</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA">Rollos de inocencia de amor fritos / Fusión especial de pastel de bodas</title>
</episode>
<episode id="2930" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-02-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">思い出激走八宝菜 / 立ちこめる霧のソルベ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">(05/06) Memory Rally Chop Suey &amp; Deep Fog Sorbet</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Omoide Gekisou Happousai / Tachikomeru Kiri no Sorbet</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA">Carrera Chop Suey de memoria / Sorbete de niebla densa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="2931" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-02-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">前略 ため息のバロティーヌ / びっくり点心</title>
<title xml:lang="en">(03/04) Quick Note; Ballottine of Sigh &amp; Surprise Dim Sum</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zenryaku Tameiki no Ballottine / Bikkuri Tenshin</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA">Nota: Ballotine de suspiro / Dulces sorpresas para el té</title>
</episode>
<episode id="2932" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-02-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">天使のチャレンジゼリートライアル / 筋肉隆々担担麺</title>
<title xml:lang="en">(01/02) Angel Challenge Jelly Trial &amp; Muscle Bound Broad Noodles</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tenshi no Challenge Jelly Trial / Kinniku Ryuuryuu Tantanmen</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA">Intento de gelatina de ángel / Fideos de músculos gruesos</title>
</episode>
<episode id="2933" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-03-31</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ツキなし月見そば / 誰も見たことのない謎のカルパッチョ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">(17/18) Moon-View Soba sans Moon &amp; A Never Before Seen Mystery Carpaccio</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsukinashi Tsukimi Soba / Daremo Mita Koto no Nai Nazo no Carpaccio</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA">Fideos de alforfón a la luna sin luna / Misterioso Carpaccio nunca antes visto</title>
</episode>
<episode id="2934" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-03-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">新鮮とれたて驚異の舟盛り / 禁断のムニエル魅惑の山かけ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">(15/16) Fresh Catch; Miraculous Boat-Wrap Sushi &amp; Forbidden Meuniere; Alluring Grated Yam Topping</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinsen Toretate Kyoui no Funamori / Kindan no Meuniere Miwaku no Yamakake</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA">Nueva impresión fresca en maravilla de adorno de barco / Fruta prohibida a la meuniere en encanto a la japonesa</title>
</episode>
<episode id="2935" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-03-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">機内食 (具沢山弁解カレー) / 愛と疑惑のもんじゃ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">(13/14) In-Flight Meal (Excuses Curry Loaded with Ingredients) &amp; Love and Doubt Fried Cabbage Cake</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kinai Shoku (Gudakusan Benkai Curry) / Ai to Giwaku no Monja</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA">Comida al vuelo (Curry con muchos ingredientes) / Tortillas de amor y dudas</title>
</episode>
<episode id="2936" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-03-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">彼岸への回転寿司 / 鋼のジャンバラヤ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">(11/12) Revolving Sushi to the Hereafter &amp; Steel Jambalaya</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Higan e no Kaitenzushi / Hagane no Jambalaya</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA">Sushi girando al otro mundo / Jambalaya de acero</title>
</episode>
<episode id="9800" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2002-04-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">硝煙と紫煙のカスレ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special: Gun Smoke and Tobacco Smoke Cassoulet</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shouen to Shien no Cassoulet</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA">Cassoulet con humo de revólver y humo de cigarrillo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="85832" update="2018-07-04">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2002-02-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="85833" update="2018-07-04">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2002-02-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111961" update="2009-12-11">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">I see 1 to 2 real GA courses</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111962" update="2009-12-11">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="en">I see 3 to 6 real GA courses</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111963" update="2009-12-11">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="en">I see 7 to 10 real GA courses</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111964" update="2009-12-11">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="en">I see 11 to 14 real GA courses</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111965" update="2009-12-11">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="en">I see 15 to 18 real GA courses</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
