<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="28" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1988-07-16</startdate>
<enddate>1988-07-16</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Akira</title>
<title xml:lang="lt" type="synonym">Akira</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Акіра</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">アキラ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Akira</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Akira</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Akira</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Akira</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">Akira</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Акира</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">Akira</title>
<title xml:lang="sv" type="official">Akira</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="official">Akira</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="official">Akira</title>
<title xml:lang="cs" type="official">Akira</title>
<title xml:lang="da" type="official">Akira</title>
<title xml:lang="fi" type="official">Akira</title>
<title xml:lang="el" type="official">Akira</title>
<title xml:lang="he" type="official">אקירה</title>
<title xml:lang="hu" type="official">Akira</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">อากิระ คนไม่ใช่คน</title>
<title xml:lang="tr" type="official">Akira</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="official">Акира</title>
<title xml:lang="sr" type="official">Акира</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA" type="official">Akira</title>
<title xml:lang="fa" type="official">آکیرا</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="14992" type="Alternative Setting">Akira (Shin Anime)</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="4708" approval="53" total="68">Freedom</anime>
<anime id="9002" approval="8" total="29">Shinsekai yori</anime>
<anime id="99" approval="8" total="17">Serial Experiments Lain</anime>
<anime id="1729" approval="5" total="6">Megazone 23</anime>
<anime id="68" approval="4" total="9">Bubblegum Crisis</anime>
<anime id="812" approval="4" total="8">Roujin Z</anime>
<anime id="6529" approval="3" total="13">Redline</anime>
<anime id="13939" approval="2" total="11">Mob Psycho 100 II</anime>
<anime id="6267" approval="1" total="5">Shangri-La</anime>
<anime id="1753" approval="1" total="5">Choujin Locke</anime>
<anime id="604" approval="1" total="5">Palme no Ki</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="40">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="394029">a true legend that everyone MUST SEE !!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="309023">Classic anime.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="364604">Arguably the BEST Anime EVER!&lt;br /&gt;Set the bar for Animes to come.&lt;br /&gt;If you don`t like Akira, you are not going to like Anime.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="210547">Masterpiece from the past , you won`t regret it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="464703">A real classic this movie started a BIG!! anime movement</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="155853">What more can be said for one of the most famous Anime of all time ? Not as good as the manga, but its style and atmosphere are superb. When you seriously start watching Anime, this is one of the two movies you must see. Guess which is the other one.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="638798">Wow. What an incredible ride. You can`t not see this.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="721720">This and Vampire Hunter D were my initiation into anime. It is a true masterpiece, and if you have not seen it, you should. I agree with the other posts in that it is definitely not for younger audiences, but 15 and up shouldn`t have a problem.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="752662">Perfect for anyone who lays claim to being a fan of `80s sci-fi and action.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="219300">If you call you self an otaku (american sense) then you will have seen Akira. It`s that simple.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="842492">This movie is a mastepierce with awesome music and superb animation. A must watch for every anime fan.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="178310">Psycho punk !!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="29472">Classic, if your an anime fan, You have to see it...</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="340646">Classic :D</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="16819">It` s a classic, outstanding masterpiece of japanese animation. It changed the way western people viewed the so-called "japanese cartoons". They finally understood it wasn`t only for children.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="468351">One of my first animes, and i was amazed at the quality of the drawing. i loved that first bike chase scene. i would reccomend the original manga graphic novel for the full story aswell.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="422137">A piece of art.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="317067">If you want to see the absolute pinnacle of animation? Akira is your movie. The best blu-ray purchase possible, I think - aside from being a classic, the movie is possibly the best animated thing I have ever seen. Absolutely jaw-droppingly stunning.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.bandaivisual.co.jp/akira/</url>
<creators>
<name id="3478" type="Animation Work">Tokyo Movie Shinsha</name>
<name id="149" type="Original Work">Ootomo Katsuhiro</name>
<name id="149" type="Direction">Ootomo Katsuhiro</name>
<name id="47256" type="Music">Yamashiro Shouji</name>
</creators>
<description>In the year 2019, thirty-one years after World War III, the authority of Neo-Tokyo is waging a constant battle against Underground rebels. Caught in the middle is a motorcycle gang whose aim is just to make trouble. The gang leader http://anidb.net/ch7558 [Kaneda Shoutarou] gets involved in more ways than one when an experimental psychic child escapes and results in gang member http://anidb.net/ch7560 [Shima Tetsuo]`s capture and subsequent experimentation. Tetsuo the bitter runt of the pack now has the power of http://anidb.net/ch9253 [Akira] and soon escapes when everyone realises that his power can result in the total destruction of Neo-Tokyo.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="10084">6.94</permanent>
<temporary count="10214">7.74</temporary>
<review count="15">7.47</review>
</ratings>
<picture>221551.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>375</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>47</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>33</identifier>
<identifier>xmjics</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.bandaivisual.co.jp/akira/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Akira_(1988_film)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>AKIRA_(漫画)#.E5.8A.87.E5.A0.B4.E3.82.A2.E3.83.8B.E3.83.A1</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>441</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>89993</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2411</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>880</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="19">
<externalentity>
<identifier>아키라_(영화)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="20">
<externalentity>
<identifier>亚基拉_(电影)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2570</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B01MUBSSRA</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="41">
<externalentity>
<identifier>60021103</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1864" parentid="2623" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-14">
<name>extrasensory perception</name>
<description>Extrasensory perception (ESP), involves reception of information not gained through the recognized physical senses but sensed with the mind. The term was coined by Sir Richard Burton, and adopted by Duke University psychologist J. B. Rhine to denote psychic abilities such as telepathy and clairvoyance, and their trans-temporal operation as precognition or retrocognition. ESP is also sometimes casually referred to as a sixth sense, gut instinct or hunch, which are historical English idioms. The term implies acquisition of information by means external to the basic limiting assumptions of science, such as that organisms can only receive information from the past to the present.
In Japanese usage the term is often misappropriated to refer to any supernatural, non-magical, super power. Users of such powers are called `esper` in Japanese. The term `esper` is not normally in use outside of Japan but is slowly being introduced due to its usage in anime and manga.
In anime/manga the following powers, among others, are described as ESP:
- telepathy
- precognition
- clairvoyance
- retrocognition
- remote viewing
- aura reading
- out-of-body experiences (OBE)
- psychokinesis</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2636" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>human enhancement</name>
<description>Human enhancement can take various forms: It can be something comparatively non-intrusive as a power-up drug, a form of machine implantation or cyberization (http://anidb.net/a4414 [SAC Solid State Society]), or outright - possibly atrocious - genetic manipulation (http://anidb.net/a361 [Ao no 6 Gou]). Plot-wise enhanced protagonists in anime usually have to pay a price for their enhancements, be it physical or mental.</description>
<picurl>223945.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2021-04-12">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators. No frontal (visible genitals) = 1.5 stars or less.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2759" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>motorsport</name>
<description>Driving involves driving in a competitive manner. Note that just driving to get groceries does not suffice, unless one does it like Takumi Fujiwara in Initial D.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2766" parentid="2759" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>street racing</name>
<description>Seen The Fast and The Furious or played Need for Speed Underground series? This is it: people racing in illegal races on the streets with their own modified cars and maybe seeing the police chasing them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2851" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>horror</name>
<description>The horror cinematic genre is characterized by the attempt to make the viewer experience dread, fear, terror, or horror. Often their plots involve the intrusion of an evil force, event or personage, sometimes of supernatural origin, on the mundane world and the consequences thereof.</description>
<picurl>214682.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2861" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>cyberpunk</name>
<description>Cyberpunk focuses on computers or information technology, usually coupled with some degree of breakdown in social order. The plot often centres on a conflict among hackers, artificial intelligences, and mega corporations, tending to be set within a near-future dystopian Earth.</description>
<picurl>211264.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2907" parentid="2636" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>genetic modification</name>
<description>Story-wise, genetic modification is usually centred on humans, probably the most subtle and creepy way of messing with mankind. Playing with the fear of the unknown, genetically altered humans are technically a new species, that may not only surpass but actually replace unaltered humans. The level of modification will vary from subtle changes in "look" (e.g. super-human beauty), to mental enhancements (PSI powers), to more or less atrocious adaptations to extreme environments (breath under water, radiation resistance). Note that changes in Aliens would be difficult to pinpoint, after all they are alien.</description>
<picurl>223941.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2923" parentid="2874" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-06-25">
<name>post-apocalyptic</name>
<description>An anime that takes place on future Earth (or it could be an alternative universe) after a major cataclysm has occurred. World War III, an alien invasion, plague, global warming or some other general disaster are common themes to build a post-apocalyptic world upon, where the effects were severe enough that mankind barely survived.
The time frame may be immediately after the catastrophe, focusing on the travails or psychology of survivors, or considerably later, often including the theme that the existence of pre-catastrophe civilization has been forgotten (or mythologised). Post-apocalyptic stories often take place in an agrarian, non-technological future world, or a world where only scattered elements of technology remain. There is a considerable degree of blurring between post-apocalyptic fiction and that which deals with false utopias or dystopian societies.</description>
<picurl>42081.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3167" parentid="2874" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-16">
<name>Tokyo destroyed</name>
<description>Tokyo is depicted as being or having been destroyed, either partially or completely, by some sort of disaster, such as a nuclear blast, a very large-scale fire, or rising sea levels. Should the situation be dire enough, Tokyo may be destroyed again after a recovery, or a new Tokyo may be built and subsequently destroyed, by a new disaster.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3374" parentid="2925" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-25">
<name>civil war</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3433" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false">
<name>power corrupts</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3664" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-24">
<name>futuristic motorcycle</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3795" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>remastered version available</name>
<description>This anime has been remastered in a higher quality format than the original release. The remaster may be a simple upscale, or it could be a full enhancement project from the original frames. This is irrespective of whether specific groups have released rips of such formats to the internet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3822" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-15">
<name>strong male lead</name>
<description>The lead male protagonist in this anime shows backbone, is competent, and does not shy away from seemingly insurmountable objectives.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4096" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>gore</name>
<description>A Splatter film or Gore film is a sub-genre of horror film that deliberately focuses on graphic portrayals of gore and graphic violence. These films, through the use of special effects and excessive blood and guts, tend to display an overt interest in the vulnerability of the human body and the theatricality of its mutilation. Due to their willingness to portray images society might consider shocking, splatter films share some ideological grounds with the transgressive art movement. The term "splatter cinema" was coined by George A. Romero to describe his film Dawn of the Dead, though Dawn of the Dead is generally considered by critics to have higher aspirations, such as social commentary, than to be simply exploitative for its own sake.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>32491.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4227" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-03">
<name>detailed landscapes</name>
<description>An amazing view of nature, of artificially sculpted landscapes (i.e. gardens), or of a cityscape.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4278" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-15">
<name>stand-alone movie</name>
<description>You can watch this movie without having to watch something else first. This tag should not used for sequels, side stories, or summary movies, but may be used if the movie is either the first anime in a franchise or a remake.
The movie must be feature-length. For shorts, use the `short movie` tag. In general, a "show-in-show" would not qualify as standalone. For example, an anime has a cartoon show within it. If the show within was released as an OVA or movie, it would not be considered standalone.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4522" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2021-04-12">
<name>social commentary</name>
<description>Social commentary is the act of using rhetorical means to provide commentary on issues in a society. This is often done with the idea of implementing or promoting change by informing the general populace about a given problem and appealing to people`s sense of justice. Social commentary can be practiced through all forms of communication, from printed form, to conversations to computerized communication.
Since this is anime, usually, the mores of Japan and the Japanese society are scrutinised, but not restricted to that.
This tag should only apply to anime where social commentary is major theme that is explored thoroughly as a main (sub-)plot element. As social commentary, the anime should send a message to the viewers, criticising our society through fiction; merely portraying complex social elements such as racism is not sufficient.
Examples of anime that provide social commentary:
http://anidb.net/a812 [Roujin Z]: criticism of our healthcare system for the elderly and our growing reliance on artificial intelligence in medicine.
http://anidb.net/a191 [GTO (Great Teacher Onizuka)]: many episodes criticise our education system in schools, as well as the ethics and struggles of teaching, showing the negative effects of bullying in schools.
http://anidb.net/a4121 [NHK ni Youkoso!]: criticises the Otaku culture.
Non-examples:
http://anidb.net/a10401 [Tokyo Ghoul]: depicts two different living species hating each other (a common trope in fiction, including anime) as an excuse for action and violence, as well as resolving conflicts between the two species that are irrelevant to our social issues.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5826" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-12">
<name>rivalry</name>
<description>Quite broadly used term describing a conflict, contest, struggle, or opposition of some sort.
Typical examples: The mostly comedic rivalry for the love of a protagonist in a harem anime (love polygon), the more "mindless" battles between wannabe delinquents in a school fighting anime, or the struggle between good &amp; evil in an epic conflict for world domination.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5954" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-17">
<name>call my name</name>
<description>"TETSUOOOOOO!!" "KANEDAAAAAA!!"
"TAMAHOMEEEE!!" "MIAKAAAA!!"
Feelings of any kind towards other characters are best shown by calling each other`s name, loud, REALLY LOUD. For better effect at least twice or thrice. For lover`s couples and mortal enemies it is a requirement to run towards each other while calling each other`s name, unaware of the surroundings.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7220" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-29">
<name>sexual abuse</name>
<description>Sexual abuse is the act of one person forcing sexual activities upon another. Sexual abuse includes not only physical coercion and sexual assault, especially rape, but also psychological abuse, such as verbal sexual behaviour or stalking, including emotional manipulation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7238" parentid="7220" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-11">
<name>attempted rape</name>
<description>Attempted rape is an unsuccessful attempt at http://anidb.net/t2715 [rape]. For AniDB purposes, generally an "unsuccessful" attempt is where both fellatio and penetration did not occur. Discretion should be applied on a case-by-case basis.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="7558" type="main character in" update="2018-04-26">
<rating votes="35">8.49</rating>
<name>Kaneda Shoutarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kaneda is a carefree gang-leader who boasts a custom-modified motorcycle. He and http://anidb.net/ch7560 [Tetsuo] have been best friends since early childhood. He is brash and not above teasing Tetsuo despite feeling affection for him as a younger brother. Upon rescuing http://anidb.net/ch9255 [Kei], Kaneda becomes involved in the activities of her group of anti-government guerrillas in hopes of locating Tetsuo.
Source: wikipedia.org</description>
<picture>26314.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="554" picture="244340.jpg">Iwata Mitsuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7560" type="main character in" update="2018-04-26">
<rating votes="27">7.59</rating>
<name>Shima Tetsuo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shima Tetsuo is http://anidb.net/ch7558 [Kaneda]`s best friend since preschool and the second principal subject of the story`s theme. Tetsuo is shown as a black sheep in the gang he and Kaneda are part of, and quietly suffers from a deeply rooted inferiority complex. He admires his friend yet at the same time strongly resents his own reliance upon him. After his psychokinetic abilities manifest, Tetsuo quickly becomes Kaneda`s nemesis; he desires Kaneda`s motorcycle (a symbol of status and power), and seeks to prove himself supremely powerful, without need of protection. Eventually, his power overwhelms him and the Espers are forced to awaken http://anidb.net/ch9253 [Akira] to stop him.
Source: wikipedia.org</description>
<picture>26317.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="270" picture="25681.jpg">Sasaki Nozomu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9253" type="appears in" update="2010-05-19">
<rating votes="12">7.43</rating>
<name>Akira</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Akira is the eponymous, principal subject of the story. Akira was a young boy who developed transcendent psionic, nearly god-like abilities when serving as a test subject for secret government ESP experiments in the 1980s. He subsequently lost control of this power and annihilated Tokyo in 1988. After the cataclysmic event, Akira`s dead body was recovered and subjected to every test known to modern science, which proved unable to solve the mystery. His remains were placed within a cryogenic chamber underneath the Neo-Tokyo Olympic Stadium, to be entrusted to the study of future generations.
Source: en.wikipedia.org</description>
<picture>28771.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="9255" type="main character in" update="2019-11-20">
<rating votes="15">5.67</rating>
<name>Kei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kei is a young female revolutionary whom http://anidb.net/ch7558 [Kaneda] meets and becomes enamoured with on his quest to find http://anidb.net/ch7560 [Tetsuo]. She is a member of an anti-government faction that Ryu and Nezu are also involved in. Although she does not possess preternatural abilities, Kei is employed by the espers as a type of medium on several occasions.
Source: wikipedia.org</description>
<picture>241355.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="407" picture="17254.jpg">Koyama Mami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9256" type="main character in" update="2014-05-10">
<rating votes="15">6.11</rating>
<name>Shikishima-taisa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Colonel Shikishima (敷島大佐), also known as simply The Colonel - The head of the ongoing government project which was responsible for inadvertently unleashing Akira`s power thirty years earlier. Appearing tough and ruthless, he is nevertheless pragmatic enough to recognize the danger Tetsuo`s fledging powers pose and cares for the three Epsers under his supervision.
(taken from en.wikipedia.org)</description>
<picture>28777.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3280" picture="24278.jpg">Ishida Tarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9450" type="main character in" update="2014-05-10">
<rating votes="10">4.65</rating>
<name>Kiyoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kiyoko - designated "Number 25", Kiyoko is an Esper who is physically so weak she is confined to a bed. She has the ability to use teleportation and precognition.
(taken from en.wikipedia.org)</description>
<picture>2295.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="5103">Itou Fukue</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9454" type="main character in" update="2014-05-10">
<rating votes="11">3.64</rating>
<name>Takashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Takashi - designated "Number 26", Takashi is the first Esper to be introduced when he causes Tetsuo`s accident in self-defense. He has the power to use psychokinesis.
(taken from en.wikipedia.org)</description>
<picture>2296.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="5101">Nakamura Tatsuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9458" type="main character in" update="2014-05-10">
<rating votes="11">5.20</rating>
<name>Masaru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Masaru - designated "Number 27", Masaru is physically confined either to a wheelchair or a special floating chair. He has the power to use psychokinesis.
Source: wiki</description>
<picture>2297.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="5102">Shintou Kazuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12042" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-09-29">
<rating votes="11">3.64</rating>
<name>Kaori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kaori is a caring young girl who`s part of the gang`s following and a girlfriend to Tetsuo. She`s weak, like Tetsuo, but doesn`t have the same energy or motivation. Very much a lonely person.</description>
<picture>36427.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3382" picture="24410.jpg">Fuchizaki Yuriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83435" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-05-17">
<rating votes="1">4.10</rating>
<name>Kai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189439.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="198" picture="202893.jpg">Kusao Takeshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83436" type="appears in" update="2016-09-19">
<rating votes="1">4.10</rating>
<name>Tenchou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Harukiya barkeeper.</description>
<picture>189440.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="420" picture="186676.jpg">Akimoto Yousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83437" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-05-17">
<rating votes="1">4.10</rating>
<name>Doctor</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189441.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10993" picture="39475.jpg">Suzuki Mizuho</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="83438" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-05-17">
<rating votes="3">3.73</rating>
<name>Yamagata</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>189442.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2041" picture="215974.jpg">Ookura Masaaki</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="5083" update="2005-11-05">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>65</length>
<airdate>1988-07-16</airdate>
<rating votes="2">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 1 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="5084" update="2011-01-15">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>60</length>
<airdate>1988-07-16</airdate>
<rating votes="2">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 2 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="10063" update="2018-03-24">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>125</length>
<airdate>1988-07-16</airdate>
<rating votes="37">7.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
<summary>Clandestine army activities threaten the war torn city of Neo-Tokyo when a mysterious child with powerful psychic abilities escapes his prison and inadvertently draws a violent motorcycle gang into a heinous web of experimentation. As a result, a biker with a twisted mind embarks on a path of war, seeking revenge against a society what once called him weak.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="11439" update="2005-09-05">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>40</length>
<airdate>1988-07-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 1 of 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="11440" update="2005-09-05">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>45</length>
<airdate>1988-07-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 2 of 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="11531" update="2011-01-15">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>40</length>
<airdate>1988-07-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 3 of 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="95657" update="2010-04-07">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>50</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Akira Making</title>
</episode>
<episode id="126972" update="2011-01-15">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Special Announcement B</title>
</episode>
<episode id="126973" update="2011-01-15">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Special Announcement A</title>
</episode>
<episode id="126974" update="2011-01-15">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Japanese Trailer B</title>
</episode>
<episode id="126975" update="2011-01-15">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Japanese Trailer A</title>
</episode>
<episode id="126976" update="2011-01-15">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">English Trailer</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
