<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="379" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>1984-02-11</startdate>
<enddate>1984-02-11</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Urusei Yatsura 2: Beautiful Dreamer</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="synonym">Lamu - Un rêve sans fin</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="synonym">Lamu - Film 2</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Несносные пришельцы: Прекрасная мечтательница (фильм #2)</title>
<title xml:lang="sv" type="synonym">Beautiful Dreamer</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">urusei yatsura movie 2</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">うる星やつら2 ビューティフル・ドリーマー</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Lamu - Beautiful Dreamer</title>
<title xml:lang="sv" type="official">Urusei Yatsura</title>
<title xml:lang="fi" type="official">Beautiful Dreamer</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">福星小子：绮丽梦中人</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="377" type="Parent Story">Urusei Yatsura</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="3">
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="587448">A mindfuck masterpiece</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://pierrot.jp/archives/mov_list_20th/mov_002.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="1640" type="Character Design">Yamazaki Kazuo</name>
<name id="818" type="Original Work">Takahashi Rumiko</name>
<name id="131" type="Direction">Oshii Mamoru</name>
<name id="7094" type="Music">Hoshi Katsu</name>
</creators>
<description>Life is but a dream. Or is it? How do you know if you are awake, or just dreaming that you are awake? This may sound like a silly question — unless you are a student at Tomobiki High School.
Something strange, stranger than usual, is happening at Tomobiki High School, but with wacky classmates like http://anidb.net/ch9099 [Lum] (a beautiful alien princess with a "shocking" personality), http://anidb.net/ch9101 [Ataru] (the lecherous loser she loves), and http://anidb.net/ch9104 [Mendou] (the suave scion of the wealthiest family on Earth), anything can happen! When Ataru, Lum, Mendou, and the rest of the gang discover that they have been reliving the day before the School Festival over and over again, they may be confused, but they are not suprised! But things are getting worse, and if they do not find a way to break the chain, they will be trapped in a time loop forever.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="610">7.64</permanent>
<temporary count="617">7.54</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>12776.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>647</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1921</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>348</identifier>
<identifier>lkdzyy</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://pierrot.jp/archives/mov_list_20th/mov_002.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Urusei_Yatsura_(film_series)#Beautiful_Dreamer</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>うる星やつら2_ビューティフル・ドリーマー</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4078</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>148866</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>143</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>urusei-yatsura-movies</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1660</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B07DQ7X3DS</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2775" parentid="2202" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>humanoid alien</name>
<description>Humanoids are aliens, intelligent beings who do not originate from Earth, but have a striking similarity to humans or at least show the basic body layout, i.e. two arms and legs, head with two eyes and ears, one nose and mouth. Though the latter - head-related features - may vary. As "DearS" shows some aliens actually exhibit super-human beauty, or as in the case of "Onegai Teacher" they are genetically compatible to humans for some strange reason.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2837" parentid="2628" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2021-02-01">
<name>floating island</name>
<description>A floating island is an island either floating in the sky, or actually floating in the ocean (mobile). The island`s flotation can be powered either by magic or science.</description>
<picurl>256529.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2996" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2021-06-01">
<name>journey to the center of the mind</name>
<description>A journey to the center of the mind or dreamworld trip is a "visit" that involves involves characters entering and visiting another character`s mind, the "dreamworld", a place that only exists in the mind of an asleep and dreaming person, or, more generally, any place in someone`s mind or other world that is not part of reality; in anime, this means the characters` reality, not our own.
The trip can be benign, accidental, or malicious. For example, a villain may entrap a character in a dream world and erase the trapped person`s memories.
Not to be confused with dream sequence, where a sleeping character has a dream, and the episode`s plot includes playing through that dream.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4062" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-10-14">
<name>deja vu</name>
</tag>
<tag id="4280" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-06-02">
<name>surreal</name>
<description>Refers to things or occurrences that are generally bizarre or dreamlike, with the relentless capability of replacing reality through the eyes of the beholder. Surrealism is boundless, limited only by thought itself.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4927" parentid="2837" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-18">
<name>aspidochelone</name>
<description>According to the tradition of the Physiologus and medieval bestiaries, the aspidochelone is a fabled sea creature, variously described as a large whale or vast sea turtle, and a giant sea monster with huge spines on the ridge of its back. No matter what form it is, it is always described as being huge, often it is mistaken for an island and appears to be rocky, with crevices and valleys with trees and greenery and having sand dunes all over it.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5970" parentid="6397" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-17">
<name>Urashima Tarou</name>
<description>A Japanese legend about a fisherman, Urashima Tarou, who rescues a turtle, the daughter of the emperor of the sea, Ryuujin, from being bullied by children. Upon this, the princess Otohime - previously the turtle - rewards him with a visit to the Dragon God`s palace. He stays there for three days but, upon his return to his village, he finds himself in a strange world that is actually 300 years in the future, as time passed differently in the palace.
The anime or episode is either completely devoted to depicting the tale of Urashima Tarou or contains important references to this tale.</description>
<picurl>169472.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6055" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-15">
<name>time loop</name>
<description>A time loop is a common plot device in science fiction (especially in universes where time travel is commonplace). Events in the story repeat themselves a number of times with or without some variation with each pass. Most characters either do not realise this is occurring or are attempting to break the cycle in some way. 
One well-known example of this is in the 1993 film Groundhog Day, in which the main character is the only one aware of the time loop, although time loops had appeared in many fictional works prior to that. Stories with time loops commonly center on correcting past mistakes or on getting a character to recognise some key truth; escape from the loop may then follow.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6397" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-02">
<name>tales</name>
<description>Tales are stories told time and again and passed down from generation to generation, and some of those show up in anime not just once or twice, but several times.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="9099" type="main character in" update="2019-01-14">
<rating votes="569">8.31</rating>
<name>Lum</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lum (also referred to in some Western versions as Lamu - since her name in Japanese is technically pronounced "Ramu") is the second main protagonist of the series. She is a beautiful Oni alien who is capable of flying and generating electrical shocks and even lightning. She is extremely popular and is famous for ending her sentences with ~daccha (loosely translated as "yes?" or "you know?"). Except when in her school girl`s uniform, she usually wears a sexy outfit consisting of a tiger-striped bikini and knee-high go-go boots. While generally good-natured, sweet, faithful, and innocent, Lum also has a very hot temper and she is extremely jealous. Her dream in life is to live in a "Sweet Home with Darling" in which she keeps house and raises babies while Ataru, her "Darling," works a job. Unfortunately, Lum`s idea of "cooking" is to take very spicy ingredients like jalapenos, cayenne peppers and Tabasco sauce and irradiate them with an alien energy bazooka until they carbonize into inedible, crystallized nuggets. As an alien she has access to many bizarre gadgets whose use she really doesn`t understand all that well, leading to comic results. Differences between human and "Invader" physiology also drive many stories, like the time Lum`s horns begin to grow larger after she is bitten by a cow, or the time she becomes drunk by eating pickled plums.
(Source: Wikipedia.com)</description>
<picture>28639.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3304" picture="186561.jpg">Hirano Fumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9101" type="main character in" update="2019-01-14">
<rating votes="209">8.40</rating>
<name>Moroboshi Ataru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A student at Tomobiki High School, Class 2-4, Ataru suffers from an incredible amount of bad luck, having been born on the unluckiest day of the Bhuddist calendar. He is very lecherous, stupid, and lazy. Though he often tries to escape from Lum and flirts with other women, he really does have feelings for her. Ataru`s main goal in life is to live in the center of a harem composed of exotic and beautiful women (including Lum and most of her alien friends). His pick-up techniques would creep out most stalkers. Usually, he just walks up to a woman he`s never met before and asks for her name, phone number, and address. Once he decides to go after a particular female, virtually no force on Earth (or from outer space) can stop him. He refused to admit it but, deep down, he proved in the later episodes that it was Lum that he truly loved.
(source:Wikipedia)</description>
<picture>28589.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2583" picture="23188.jpg">Furukawa Toshio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9104" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-12">
<rating votes="63">7.40</rating>
<name>Mendou Shuutarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shuutaro Mendo is heir to the Mendou Zaibatsu with staggering wealth and its own private army. He commutes to school in a gigantic helicopter that is more like a flying mansion. Shuutaro carries a samurai sword which he often tries to use on Ataru (who has become expert at blocking it with his bare hands). Although very handsome he is just as stupid and lecherous as Ataru (just much more sophisticated in his approach). He takes his role as heir to the vast Mendou fortune extremely seriously. Mendou is vain, narcissistic, charming, overly dramatic, claustrophobic and afraid of the dark. He loves Lum, tolerating the presence of Ataru in order to be close to her. Shinobu is the closest thing he has to a girlfriend.
(source:Wikipedia)</description>
<picture>28592.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="406" picture="186436.jpg">Kamiya Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9108" type="appears in" update="2021-01-21">
<rating votes="53">6.09</rating>
<name>Miyake Shinobu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ataru`s childhood friend and classmate. Until Lum showed up she was also Ataru`s girlfriend. She is a neat, clean, sweet, and petite young lady who can be viewed as the archetypically perfect Japanese female. Not long after Lum showed up Shinobu began to develop super-human strength. She like all female members of her class has a huge crush on Mendou. She is often part of a "foursome" consisting of Ataru, Lum, Shuutaro, and herself. By the end of the series, she`d given up on Shuutaro, thinking herself a likely "old maid", until she met a young boy named Inaba who sweeps her off her feet (eventually).
(source:Wikipedia)</description>
<picture>255971.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2055" picture="21393.jpg">Shimazu Saeko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9115" type="appears in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="71">3.69</rating>
<name>Ten</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lum`s infant cousin. He is often called "Ten-chan" by Lum and many of the other main female characters, the male characters often call him by his full-name "Jariten" ("Jari" means something like "brat" in Japanese). He comes to earth after flying in a spaceship inside a peach (a reference to the Japanese folktale of Momotaro) to live with Lum in the Moroboshi household when his Oni powers first manifest. He appeared much earlier in the anime (making his debut in Episode Two) than in the Manga. Ten has a single horn on his head, can breathe fire, flies very slowly, and wears tiger striped diaper. He and Ataru utterly loathe each other and often fight. Ten`s character design and relationship to the series` male lead is somewhat similar to that of Shippo from Inuyasha (though there is much more acrimony between Ten and Ataru than between Shippo and Inuyasha).
(Source: Wikipedia.com)</description>
<picture>28603.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2890" picture="23182.jpg">Sugiyama Kazuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9117" type="appears in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="76">8.80</rating>
<name>Cherry</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sakura`s wandering monk uncle. Cherry`s real name is Sakuranbou, which literally means "cherry" in Japanese. But because the word`s kanji can be read to mean "deranged monk", a phrase that is quite accurate in describing him, he prefers to be called by the English word. Cherry has amazing spiritual powers (or so he claims) and he often predicts doom for Ataru (no great feat). He has a habit of popping up out of nowhere, often from very strange places. His ugly face and very short stature are frequently used for comedic effect. Cherry has made a vow of asceticism, living in a tent in an empty lot not far from Ataru`s house. However, this vow apparently doesn`t apply to food, as he is an enormous mooch. Rei Hino of Sailor Moon`s Grandpa looks a lot like Cherry.
(Source: Wikipedia.com)</description>
<picture>28605.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="201" picture="17016.jpg">Nagai Ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9134" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="51">7.89</rating>
<name>Sakura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>In Japanese "Sakura" means "cherry blossom". She was once a very sickly girl who suffered from a variety of ailments. Many of them were the result of spirits that infested her body. On the advice of her uncle Cherry, she tried to exorcise Ataru, during which process, the demons who inhabited her transferred themselves to the unlucky young man. The second time she attempts to exorcise him, one of the demons possessing Ataru causes him to pounce onto her and suck her breast. Now in perfect health, Sakura is the Tomobiki High school nurse and a Shinto priestess or miko. Unlike her mother (who looks exactly like Cherry), Sakura is tall, slender and physically attractive, which makes her a common target of the lecherous boys of the school and even Mr. Onsen-Mark. The boys have been known to purposely injure themselves in order to see her. Like her uncle, she possesses an enormous appetite and has been known, despite never seeming to gain an ounce, to out-eat him. Sakura is extremely powerful and can summon foul and baleful creatures from Japanese folklore, by virtue of her mystical training.
(Source: Wikipedia.com)</description>
<picture>28622.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5061" picture="28866.jpg">Washio Machiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9138" type="appears in" update="2009-06-12">
<rating votes="33">7.37</rating>
<name>Megane</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The leader of the Stormtroopers, whose nickname means "eyeglasses", he has a strong personality and generally directs the schemes of the Stormtroopers to gain Lum`s attention (though mostly for himself). Though usually antagonistic towards Ataru, he often hangs out with him in his spare time. He is often given to rambling philosophical musings and outbursts, and seems to have an affinity for fascism and communism.
(Source: Wikipedia.com)</description>
<picture>28627.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="541" picture="26117.jpg">Chiba Shigeru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9144" type="appears in" update="2021-01-21">
<rating votes="16">5.08</rating>
<name>Akira</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>His nickname is derived from his height ("chibi" means "small" or "short"), he is a timid crybaby, speaks with a cracked voice, and is often beaten up by the rest of the Gang of Four. He is often together with Kakugari. He also has buck teeth like that of a beaver`s (though his nameless Manga counterpart did not have this). His real name is Akira.
(Source: Wikipedia.com)</description>
<picture>256048.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="281" picture="151723.jpg">Futamata Issei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9145" type="appears in" update="2021-04-18">
<rating votes="16">3.04</rating>
<name>Hiroyuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>His nickname is derived from his hairstyle ("kakugari" means "crew cut"), he has a large build. He is the least used of the stormtroopers and he often seen with Chibi. He is also the one who beats up Chibi the most. His real name is Hiroyuki.
(Source: Wikipedia.com)</description>
<picture>260099.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5069" picture="32189.jpg">Nomura Shinji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9146" type="appears in" update="2011-04-07">
<rating votes="41">7.87</rating>
<name>Fujinami Ryuunosuke</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ryuunosuke is a classmate of Ataru. She is a girl, but her eccentric father has raised her as a boy, going so far as to demand that she wrap her breasts in tight cloth strips to hide them. Even her name sounds masculine, roughly equivalent to "Duke" or "Butch" in English. Ryuunosuke is a kind person at heart, but her father is always antagonizing her and pulling her into very destructive knock-down, drag-out fights, one of the reasons for their extreme poverty. She and her father run the school store, and live on-campus in the back. Her greatest desire is to wear girl`s clothing and behave appropriately for her gender, but she has had no female role models in her life. Any attempt to obtain feminine clothing is thwarted by her father.
(Source: Wikipedia.com)</description>
<picture>28635.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="322" picture="17159.jpg">Tanaka Mayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9148" type="appears in" update="2021-04-18">
<rating votes="24">6.62</rating>
<name>Shirai Kousuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>His nickname is derived from his hairstyle ("permanent"), he is tall and skinny (though his nameless Manga counterpart had quite a fatter form). Perm often displays the most character development, including being the only one of the Stormtroopers to have a visible girlfriend. His real name is Kosuke, likely after Kosuke Shirai, who most of his lines are given to in the anime.
(Source: Wikipedia.com)</description>
<picture>260100.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3296" picture="151729.jpg">Murayama Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="41939" type="appears in" update="2012-03-02">
<rating votes="6">8.34</rating>
<name>Kouchou-sensei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The principal of Tomobiki High School. A soft-spoken, balding, nearsighted middle-aged man, he treats all of the weird goings-on at the school as harmless student shenanigans. He occasionally instigates the weirdness, however, like the time the entire student body was called on to compete in teams to create the largest bust of himself possible using only rice paste. He is often seen sitting at the kotatsu in his office, sharing tea and taiyaki with his friend Kotatsu Neko. Not unlike Onsen-Mark, he has shown mild attraction to his female students (though no more than any other male, and never acting on it; it is more of an admiration than an attraction. He does admire any beauty when he sees it.). He first appeared in the second season.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>82699.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="289" picture="186204.jpg">Nishimura Tomomichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="44419" type="appears in" update="2012-05-07">
<rating votes="17">8.36</rating>
<name>Onsen-Mark</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>One of Ataru`s teachers.
A sad, middle-aged man, whose only interest is to teach at Tomobiki High, but fails due to the constant interruptions during class, when the classroom itself is not destroyed by Lum, Ten or Shinobu.
His name means "Mark of the Hot Springs", and he usually wears a shirt with hot springs on it.</description>
<picture>87382.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3312" picture="24691.jpg">Ikemizu Michihiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66449" type="appears in" update="2014-04-09">
<rating votes="10">6.13</rating>
<name>Ataru no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He is Ataru`s father and married with Ataru`s mother.</description>
<picture>153338.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="604" picture="154161.jpg">Ogata Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68011" type="appears in" update="2014-06-17">
<rating votes="13">8.73</rating>
<name>Ataru no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ataru no Haha is a typical housewife, and mother of http://anidb.net/ch9101 [Moroboshi Ataru]. She is married tohttp://anidb.net/ch66449 [ Ataru no Chichi].
Source: Urusei Yatsura wikia</description>
<picture>156833.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29995" picture="170254.jpg">Sakuma Natsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68069" type="appears in" update="2014-06-22">
<rating votes="7">8.16</rating>
<name>Ryuunosuke no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>156986.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1821" picture="258578.jpg">Anzai Masahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84849" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-17">
<name>Mujaki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>10390.jpeg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33699" picture="92476.jpg">Fujioka Takuya</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="13236" update="2021-03-11">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>100</length>
<airdate>1984-02-11</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
<summary>Tomobiki High is in a frenzy to get ready for the school festival. Props need to be made, costumes designed, and maybe somewhere sleep to be had! Ataru, Lum, Shutaro, Shinobu, and the rest of Class 2-4 are determined to not be outdone this year, and they`re rushing to make the final preparations for tomorrow`s grand opening. Once they wake up the next morning, they continue their mad rush to get ready for tomorrow`s grand opening. And then the next day... hey, isn`t something strange going on? Silence lingers over the city, the buildings filled with nothing but dust and mold. Is this a dream? Or have the kids (and a few related adults) of Class 2-4 finally woken up? If they can spend each day having fun with each other, does it matter?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>808455</identifier>
<identifier>urusei-yatsura-movies</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="17346" update="2014-11-11">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>50</length>
<airdate>1984-02-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 1 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="17347" update="2005-09-06">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>50</length>
<airdate>1984-02-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Part 2 of 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="228161" update="2020-04-10">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer (2:02)</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
