<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="40" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>39</episodecount>
<startdate>1990-04-13</startdate>
<enddate>1991-04-12</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Fushigi no Umi no Nadia</title>
<title xml:lang="zh" type="synonym">冒險少女娜汀亞</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Nadia of the Mysterious Seas</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">The Secret of Blue Water</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Nadia: Secret of Blue Water</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="synonym">Il mistero della pietra azzurra</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="synonym">Nadia: el Secreto del Agua Azul</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Надя c загадочного моря</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">신비한 바다의 나디아</title>
<title xml:lang="ca" type="synonym">Nadia: el Secret de l`Aigua Blau</title>
<title xml:lang="cs" type="synonym">Nadja z tajemných moří</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">不可思议之海的娜迪娅</title>
<title xml:lang="tl" type="synonym">Ang Mahiwagang Kwintas</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Nadia</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">nadia tv</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ふしぎの海のナディア</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Nadia: The Secret of Blue Water</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Die Macht des Zaubersteins</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Nadia, le secret de l`eau bleue</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Nadia - Il mistero della pietra azzurra</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="official">الماسة الزرقاء</title>
<title xml:lang="cs" type="official">Nadia: Tajemství Modré vody</title>
<title xml:lang="fi" type="official">Matka maapallon ympäri</title>
<title xml:lang="tr" type="official">Nadia: Mavi Suyun Esrarı</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="603" type="Sequel">Fushigi no Umi no Nadia Gekijou you Original Han</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="7873" approval="56" total="70">Fractale</anime>
<anime id="331" approval="36" total="41">Tenkuu no Shiro Laputa</anime>
<anime id="330" approval="25" total="33">Mirai Shounen Conan</anime>
<anime id="477" approval="14" total="15">Patapata Hikousen no Bouken</anime>
<anime id="5569" approval="6" total="12">Allison to Lillia</anime>
<anime id="3340" approval="5" total="9">Tide-Line Blue</anime>
<anime id="520" approval="2" total="6">Ashita no Nadja</anime>
<anime id="1122" approval="2" total="5">Mujin Wakusei Survive</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="11">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="307364">Wonderful show that weaves the light-heartedness and serious overtones together to form an anime that viewers can revisit for years.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="376567">Remember to skip the infamous island episodes. They`re horrible. Highly recommended if you wish to know what Hideaki Anno did before Neon Genesis Evangelion.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="3976">anime with a great story lines</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="330175">This is highly recommended if you look for some old school anime , the story is great and the characters are awesome , sometimes you will love them and sometimes you will hate them . The romance is kinda slow , boring and not progressing but rather looping around to the beginning for most of the anime . The strong part of this anime is the action , it does not happen all the time but when it starts sparks fly left and right . Recommended for old shcool anime needs .</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="313716">This is a timeless classic that brings you a unique adventure, great characters and a well constructed story. If you`re a fan of Jules Verne, you`ll enjoy it even more, since the anime borrows premises from a couple of his novels, and you can feel the influence. Though there are a few fillers, it`s nothing too boring, and the progress of the story and development of characters more than make up for it. I highly recommend it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="167">it`s one of these classics that should be watched. in fact why haven`t you done so already?!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.gainax.co.jp/anime/nadia/index.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="57" type="Chief Direction">Anno Hideaki</name>
<name id="1389" type="Character Design">Sadamoto Yoshiyuki</name>
<name id="4875" type="Work">Kubota Hiroshi</name>
<name id="511" type="Direction">Higuchi Shinji</name>
<name id="22619" type="Work">Yoshida Keiichirou</name>
<name id="1955" type="Music">Sagisu Shirou</name>
<name id="5973" type="Original Plan">Jules Verne</name>
<name id="5973" type="Original Work">Jules Verne</name>
</creators>
<description>The Industrial Revolution has taken over and the world is being consumed by new technology and machines. A young scientist, http://anidb.net/ch15976 [Jean], sees a beautiful young girl with dark skin while in France. He follows her to only find trouble; a woman and two thugs are after an amulet in the girl`s possession called Blue Water. Jean helps the girl escape and learns that her name is http://anidb.net/ch7216 [Nadia]. From then on, the two join forces to evade the minions of a man named Gargoyle, who wants Nadia`s Blue Water to bring forth an armageddon.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1594">7.18</permanent>
<temporary count="1613">7.59</temporary>
<review count="5">7.69</review>
</ratings>
<picture>221740.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>48</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1251</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>3381</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>281</identifier>
<identifier>zxubqv</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www3.nhk.or.jp/anime/nadia/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.gainax.co.jp/anime/nadia/index.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Nadia:_The_Secret_of_Blue_Water</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ふしぎの海のナディア</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>372</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>89135</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1162</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4553</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3223</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="635" parentid="36" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-30">
<name>navy</name>
</tag>
<tag id="898" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-04-17">
<name>submarine</name>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2640" parentid="2625" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-06-02">
<name>alternative past</name>
<description>An anime that takes place in an alternative past is an anime that clearly does not belong to the future or the present, and isn`t tied particularly closely to our history, or has ties to our history but only as a premise: there are too many things that don`t make sense for the time-period. In some cases there is futuristic technology present, but the overall setting still feels that of the past. However the setting must still take place on Earth, since we can not know if the history of a fantasy world is an alternate one or not.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2763" parentid="2807" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Paris</name>
<description>Paris is the capital and most populous city in France. The city is a commune and department, and the heart of the Île-de-France region (colloquially known as the `Paris Region`). Since the 17th century, Paris has been one of Europe`s major centres of finance, commerce, fashion, science, and the arts.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214344.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2807" parentid="2831" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>France</name>
<description>France, officially the French Republic, is a country whose territory consists of metropolitan France in western Europe, as well as several overseas regions and territories. The metropolitan area of France extends from the Mediterranean Sea to the English Channel and the North Sea, and from the Rhine to the Atlantic Ocean. The overseas territories include French Guiana in South America and several islands in the Atlantic, Pacific and Indian oceans.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214343.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2831" parentid="2630" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Europe</name>
<description>Europe is a continent located entirely in the Northern Hemisphere and mostly in the Eastern Hemisphere. It is bordered by the Arctic Ocean to the north, the Atlantic Ocean to the west, and the Mediterranean Sea to the south. It comprises the westernmost part of Eurasia.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192044.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2835" parentid="2630" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>Africa</name>
<description>The world`s second-largest continent and the birthplace of the human species, Africa is a place of a huge diversity, with deserts and savannas, with famine and precious stones, with cultural and economical riches of all kinds. Throughout history, Africa has been the cradle of empires and has been ruled by foreign powers, and as of the early 21st century sees swift changes and economic boom going side by side with inhuman levels of poverty.</description>
<picurl>126530.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2870" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-17">
<name>steampunk</name>
<description>Steampunk is a sub-genre of science fiction that typically features steam-powered machinery, especially in a setting inspired by industrialized Western civilization during the 19th century. Steampunk works are often set in an alternative history of the 19th century`s British Victorian era or American "Wild West", in a post-apocalyptic future during which steam power has regained mainstream use, or in a fantasy world that similarly employs steam power.
Noteworthy attributes of the theme include large amounts smoke pollution from wood or coal burning, the affinity to metal constructs like cogs and metal tubing, and the mechanization of everyday objects.
Steampunk perhaps most recognisably features anachronistic technologies or retro-futuristic inventions as people in the 19th century might have envisioned them, and is likewise rooted in the era`s perspective on fashion, culture, architectural style, and art.
Such technology may include fictional machines like those found in the works of H. G. Wells and Jules Verne, or the modern authors Philip Pullman, Scott Westerfeld, Stephen Hunt and China Miéville. Other examples of steampunk contain alternative history-style presentations of such technology as lighter-than-air airships, analog computers, or such digital mechanical computers as Charles Babbage`s Analytical Engine.
Steampunk can also exemplify everything that is bad about unrestrained technological progress (dead matter), when compared to life and nature. The anime usually makes a point to propound the latter.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162830.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2878" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>conspiracy</name>
<description>The conspiracy thriller (or paranoid thriller) is a sub-genre of the thriller which flourished in the 1970s in the US (and was echoed in other parts of the world) in the wake of a number of high-profile scandals and controversies (most notably Vietnam, the assassination of President Kennedy, Chappaquiddick and Watergate), and which exposed what many people regarded as the clandestine machinations and conspiracies beneath the orderly fabric of political life.
The protagonists of conspiracy thrillers are often journalists or amateur investigators who find themselves (often inadvertently) pulling on a small thread which unravels a vast conspiracy that ultimately goes "all the way to the top".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2895" parentid="2608" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>dark-skinned girl</name>
<description>The anime features a girl with dark skin. A fetish of sorts, since the other protagonists are usually as white-skinned as porcelain dolls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3575" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-13">
<name>damsel in distress</name>
<description>The damsel in distress is usually a young, nubile woman placed in a dire predicament by a villain or a monster and requires a hero to dash to her rescue. Often used to unite the cast of a show for this one goal, to make them put differences aside and become a band of nakama. 
Examples: Sakoshita Yanagi from Rekka no Honoo, Yuuki Miaka from Fushigi Yuugi or Higurashi Kagome from Inuyasha.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4440" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>boy meets girl</name>
<description>A classical type of plot in story writing, where the story begins with a boy meeting a girl leading to romantic development between the two. More often than not the boy loses the girl later on and has to find her again.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4480" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>happy ending</name>
<description>And they lived "happily ever after"... *sniff*.
All issues in the anime have been resolved, the love polygons sorted out, the conflicts resolved, the guy gets the girl (or the other way around), and everyone else lives on blissfully.
(Not very realistic, but then again this is anime.)</description>
<picurl>222185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4521" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-28">
<name>lost technology</name>
<description>Any advanced technology or science-related knowledge that was lost for some reason fits the description. This could be technology from a time before a post-apocalyptic cataclysm, knowledge gained a long time ago but forgotten, or the relics of an old alien civilization only recently discovered.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7005" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-17">
<name>ancient aliens</name>
<description>Ancient aliens, hundreds, thousands, or millions of years in the past; aliens from another world or dimension played a significant role in human history.
Pictured: http://anidb.net/a40 [Nadia: The Secret of The Blue Water / Fushigi no Umi no Nadia]</description>
<picurl>222751.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7119" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>Super Robot Wars</name>
<description>Super Robot Wars is a series of tactical role-playing video games produced by Banpresto. The main feature of the franchise is having a story that crosses over several popular mecha anime, manga and video games, allowing characters and mecha from different titles to team up or battle one another. Due to the nature of crossover games and licensing involved, only a few games have been released outside Japan, and in English; early English-language games only feature Banpresto`s original characters and mecha, and a flagship installment were to never be released until 2016, with the English release of Super Robot Wars V in Southeast Asian countries. The franchise celebrated its 25th anniversary in 2016.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>221614.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="7216" type="main character in" update="2013-02-08">
<rating votes="57">5.72</rating>
<name>Nadia La Arwall</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nadia is a 14 year old (15 toward the end of the series) who works in a circus as an acrobat in order to survive, since she is an orphan and of unknown origins. She is chased by Grandis and her associates Sanson and Hanson, who are looking for the jewel that Nadia possesses, the Blue Water. While escaping from them, she meets Jean, and from that moment the two of them will be together in the series, where she tries to discover her origins and find out the truth about her past and the Blue Water, the jewel that seems to have an enormous intrinsic power.
Nadia is quite stubborn, easily irritable, socially inept, and has the ability to talk with animals. For example, she is able to communicate easily with her little lion, King. Nadia is also known among those who have knowledge of the blue water for being its possessor. She even happens to be a strict vegetarian and believes that there is no excuse for eating meat or killing (although her friends attempt to justify their reasons for doing so). Because of her unhappy past, Nadia is even extremely suspicious of all grown-ups--particularly Nemo. As a result of her growing love for Jean however, she comes to learn valuable lessons about friendship, respect, and trust for those around her.</description>
<picture>25590.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3890" picture="186170.jpg">Takamori Yoshino</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15976" type="main character in" update="2010-03-20">
<rating votes="14">6.69</rating>
<name>Jean Rocque Raltique</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The second main protagonist of the series. Jean is a young 14 year old orphan who fell in love with Nadia ever since he first laid eyes on her; unlike her, however, Jean has a completely different personality and interests. He is very generous, patient, friendly, and devoted to the things he loves, which are his friends and the love for science. He is also a genius inventor, in fact he is capable of creating complex machines at a very young age. Jean`s father is a wealthy trader and ship`s captain, but was recently lost at sea and is presumed dead. (We later find out that there has been a rash of mysterious disappearances of ships lately and the rumors are that a sea monster has been attacking them) Jean, however, chooses to deny them and is determined to finally find his father along with his big adventure with Nadia to find about the Blue Water. Despite being somewhat awkward when it comes to social graces around the opposite sex (such as giving compliments or lack of awareness in some cases where he`s inventing and/or reading when Nadia wants his attention), Jean is genuinely well-behaved and is nice to everyone—even Gargoyle finds something to admire about his courage and cleverness.
His relationship with Nadia is one of the more central aspects of the show. When they first meet on the Eiffel Tower, Nadia refuses his overtures, but when Jean rescues her, he earns her trust. A close friendship forges between the two of them—Jean is consistently loyal to her and vows to take her to Africa someday; later their relationship begins to turn romantic, but Nadia does not know how to express her feelings to him. This leads to outbursts of anger often misdirected at Jean, yet he continually forgives her. When she is not brooding over their relationship, Nadia often goes out of her way to do something nice for him, such as cooking, encouraging him to build a gyrocopter, or comforting him when he grieves about his father (in Episode 16). Likewise, each time Nadia gets into trouble, Jean continually rescues her. Occasionally a disagreement will occur between them about certain issues (notably eating meat or the use of technology vs. nature), but they do not last long. As a result of Jean`s love, Nadia is gradually transformed as a person; his optimism overcomes her pessimism, and she becomes more trusting, respectful, and caring of others.</description>
<picture>44940.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="268" picture="17093.jpg">Hidaka Noriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15977" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-04-19">
<rating votes="8">7.30</rating>
<name>Eleusis La Arwall</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nemo is the captain of the submarine called Nautilus, whose purpose is to destroy the Neo-Atlanteans at all costs. He is a mysterious man with a dark past; in fact only step by step we discover that he is Nadia`s father and the real Emperor of Atlantis. Though he could have all mankind under his command, he chooses to live peacefully along with them on Earth, as he believes in humans and in their ability to love. While he acts cold and aloof when he first meets Jean, he nonetheless warms up to his outgoing cheerfulness and enthusiasm. Nadia, meanwhile, is very distrustful of him and is quick to accuse him of murder when he shoots a Neo-Atlantean to save her from death. However, she eventually learns to respect Nemo, and, at the end, at last acknowledges him as her father. Nemo then dies after overloading the Neo Nautilis`s reactors to blow a passage out of Red Noah, permitting the rest of the cast to return to Earth.</description>
<picture>44941.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="286" picture="17117.jpg">Ootsuka Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15978" type="main character in" update="2012-06-09">
<rating votes="6">4.59</rating>
<name>Marie en Carlsberg</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Marie is a 4 year child orphaned by the hands of Gargoyle and the Neo-Atlantean troops, who killed her parents. She is soon found by Nadia and Jean, who decide to keep her and to take good care of her. Although she is a kid, Marie is a very strong character, who is at the same time a child but also acts like an adult in difficult situations. She has a good relationship with King, her playmate. In fact, she later comes to see him as husband and wife and Nadia and Jean as her new parents. Later on, however, she will develop an interest in Sanson; in fact, in the epilogue, when a grown-up Marie tells what has happened to all the characters, she finishes her story by telling that she has married him, and is expecting their first child.
Source: Wikipedia
Note 1: The spelling of her name is uncertain. In the episode guide she appears as "Marie", in the Japanese series books she is "Mary", Streamline Pictures calls her "Mari", and in episode 24 she signs one of her drawings as "Marry" (though this could simply be that as a four-year-old she doesn`t know how to spell her name). Even so, Marie is probably the most accurate spelling, as it is the French one.
Note 2: In the CD audio dramas, her full name was revealed to be "Marie en Carlsberg" (マリー・エン・カールスバーグ), whereas in the anime`s epilogue, it is "Marie en Löwenbräu" (マリー・エン・レーヴェンブロイ).</description>
<picture>44942.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1870" picture="186893.jpg">Mizutani Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="15979" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-20">
<rating votes="18">5.75</rating>
<name>Grandis Granva</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Grandis is a 28 year old who grew up in a royal Italian family. At first she was rather rich, spoiled and powerful young woman, but later when she was tricked by her first husband, who married her just for her money until he leaves her broke and alone. After her frail mistake she is exiled by her relatives and the only people who remained faithful and loyal to her were Hanson and Sanson, with whom she then formed the Grandis Gang, a group of jewel thieves. Her life and behavior change dramatically when she meets Nadia and the others; having to first steal the Blue Water, then wanting to protect them after finding out she has soft spot for them when learning about their troubles with Gargoyle. Once aboard the Nautilus she falls hopelessly in love with Captain Nemo competing and having a strict rivalry with Electra. She tries to seduce him with any power she has until the very end, but her love for him is never returned.
In the epilogue, a grown-up Marie tells us that she is alive and well, but still looking for a serious and stable love. She`s quite popular though with men and is seen at the end in a golf court surrounded by them. Every man there offers her to use their club and according to Marie, "Grandis is always gallivanting around."</description>
<picture>44943.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4718" picture="27537.jpg">Takizawa Kumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16002" type="main character in" update="2010-03-22">
<rating votes="5">6.95</rating>
<name>King</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>King is a small lion, and he is Nadia`s best friend before she meets Jean and the others. He will become eventually Marie`s playmate during the episodes, playing with her all day. He is a very jealous animal, especially when Nadia and Jean become more intimate.
In the epilogue, King is still living with a now married Nadia and Jean, and has several cubs of his own.</description>
<picture>45002.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2603" picture="22591.jpg">Sakurai Toshiharu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="16003" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-03-22">
<rating votes="7">7.65</rating>
<name>Sanson</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sanson is the brawn side of the team and serves as the Gratan`s navigation pilot. Depite his slight yet muscular build, his strength overcomes even the most powerful of mecha. When he was younger he was slimmer and girls made fun of him; as he trained day by day he became stronger but incredibly vain. Sanson also is an outstanding marksman. He was the chauffeur to Granva`s family before they lost their fortune, and he remains faithful to her until the end of the series. In the epilogue, he has married a grown-up Marie and they are expecting their first child.</description>
<picture>45003.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2037" picture="244859.jpg">Horiuchi Ken`yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54791" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-04-19">
<rating votes="5">6.43</rating>
<name>Hanson</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hanson is the mechanic of the Grandis Gang. He has exceptional skills; he built the Gratan and lots of other devices. He is in love with Electra, but alas, his love is not returned. Jean and Hanson become close friends thanks to their mutual fascination with technology, they spend a lot of time together discussing technical details and ideas about mecha.
In the epilogue, Hanson has become an industrial giant, rich and respected-he lives in fictional world`s equivalent of the Chrysler building. Having made his fortune as a manufacturer of automobiles, he still claims that he will find a girlfriend someday.</description>
<picture>153064.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2603" picture="22591.jpg">Sakurai Toshiharu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54792" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-04-19">
<rating votes="7">7.49</rating>
<name>Medina La Lugensius Electra</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Full Name: Medina La Lugensius Electra
Electra is an orphan since the destruction of her hometown, after which she is saved by captain Nemo and she is the First Officer of the `Nautilus`, fighting Gargoyle and the Neo-Atlanteans. Electra is deeply in love with Nemo, although she also burgeons a deep grudge toward him for the deaths of her family. Even so, she becomes extremely envious of Grandis` mad infatuation for the Captain, igniting a heated rivalry for his love. She grows fond of Jean and his determination to learn about technology, seeing him as the equivalent of her long lost brother. Nadia, on the other hand, detests Electra and becomes increasingly (and irrationally) jealous of Jean`s friendship with the First Officer (her inability to express her concern to Jean nearly ruins their own relationship); likewise, Electra fears that Nadia will somehow steal Nemo`s heart away from her. Eventually, however, both open up to each other.
In the end of the series, Electra is revealed to be pregnant with Nemo`s child, and Marie tells in the epilogue that she gave birth to him and raised him with love, like Nemo asked her.</description>
<picture>153063.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="240" picture="17059.jpg">Inoue Kikuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54793" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-04-07">
<rating votes="5">7.60</rating>
<name>Nemesis La Algol</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Full Name: Nemesis La Algol
Gargoyle is the main antagonist. He is head of the Neo-Atlantean forces. He was the prime minister of Tartessos, and his main objectives are:
Destroy Nemo and the Nautilus,
Take possession of the Blue Waters
Dominate over the entire world and humans, whom he considers inferior.
He is a cunning yet brutal villain who speaks in a soft voice and taps into other people`s weaknesses to make them comply with his wishes. We never see the face behind the mask until the final episode (and even then, his face is only briefly shown before he dies).
His name is also a mix of Latin and Greek mythology, as for Nemo and Electra.
He considers himself an Atlantean, but he is not aware of the fact that he is one of the humans that he despises, as the mere creation of the Atlantean technology.</description>
<picture>153065.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="564" picture="146195.jpg">Kiyokawa Motomu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54794" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-04-06">
<rating votes="2">9.35</rating>
<name>Gratan</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>Designed and built from scratch by skilled mechanic Hanson, Gratan is a small multi-purpose vehicle: it has wheels for ground movement, but may also fly using a hot-air balloon and propellers, and even travel underwater. Configuration can be switched by the pilot using a piano keyboard in the cockpit. Gratan, whose original meaning is "Grandis` tank", is the common name for the vehicle, while Grandis prefers to call it "Catherine." After being damaged and repaired countless times during the series, Gratan is eventually crushed by the igniter of Red Noah`s Light of Babel, a sacrifice needed to avoid destruction of a defenseless Excelion.</description>
</character>
<character id="54795" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-04-06">
<rating votes="2">9.35</rating>
<name>Nautilus</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>An Atlantean space-ship converted to submarine, Nautilus` is Nemo`s main weapon against Gargoyle and his minions. Notable features of this ship are: ability to withstand high pressures and depths, exceptionally resistant Space Titanium armoured hull (the clear ports are made from Tektite), and water-jet magnetic propulsion.
The name of the original spaceship was Eritrium, as is discovered by Jean and Nadia in episode 15, while the origin of the Nautilus is explained at the end of the series. Eritrium (sometimes spelled Elitrium or Eltrium) is also the name of a space ship in Gunbuster, and the robot-ship that blast off at the end of Otaku No Video.</description>
</character>
<character id="66303" type="appears in" update="2014-04-07">
<name>Neo-koutei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Emperor Neo is apparently the leader of the Neo-Alanteans. Later in the story we discover that he is Nemo`s son and Nadia`s brother, but his body was destroyed in the collapse of Tartessos, and was mechanically recreated by Gargoyle. He is then controlled like a puppet by him; he tries to take over the world using his psychic powers and technology, and also shoots his own father against his will.
In the end he will eventually liberate his free will and love for his family, sacrificing himself to save Nadia.</description>
<picture>153066.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1819" picture="20694.jpg">Shiozawa Kaneto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66304" type="appears in" update="2014-04-07">
<name>Ayerton Grenavan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ayerton is first seen in the series as a scientific officer aboard US warship Abraham; he states he`s been sent on a secret mission to investigate the sea monsters phenomena. Later in the series, Jean and Nadia meet him again partially buried on a mysterious moving island, completely drunk and telling stories about a strange witch who inhabits the island (who naturally turns out to be Grandis). While on the island, Ayerton falls in love with Grandis, and to strike her, he pretends to be an English nobleman who`s going to inherit a large wealth from his family.
Ayerton is quite a weird, loudmouthed character, who is never really able to completely grasp the reality around him, and to tell good from evil. In the epilogue, Marie says that Ayerton was really a noble and wealthy man, and eventually he returned to his homeland.</description>
<picture>153067.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="342" picture="17179.jpg">Tsujitani Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68411" type="appears in" update="2014-07-04">
<rating votes="1">3.76</rating>
<name>Jean no Ojisan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>157577.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3228" picture="151725.jpg">Masuoka Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68412" type="appears in" update="2014-07-04">
<name>Circus no Danchou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>157580.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="8057">Sasaoka Shigezou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69736" type="appears in" update="2014-08-31">
<rating votes="1">2.32</rating>
<name>Jean no Obasan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>160274.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38362" picture="141492.jpg">Fuji Natsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="69737" type="appears in" update="2014-08-31">
<rating votes="1">3.76</rating>
<name>Meville-kanchou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>160275.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3283" picture="24293.jpg">Oomiya Teiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70418" type="appears in" update="2014-10-01">
<name>Fait</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>162138.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="384" picture="17230.jpg">Seki Toshihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70442" type="appears in" update="2014-10-02">
<name>Eiko Ville</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>162190.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="455" picture="17356.jpg">Matsumoto Yasunori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70443" type="appears in" update="2014-10-02">
<name>Ikolina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>162191.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1870" picture="186893.jpg">Mizutani Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70451" type="appears in" update="2014-10-03">
<rating votes="1">5.71</rating>
<name>Irion</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>162225.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="547" picture="17780.jpg">Takagi Hitoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70492" type="appears in" update="2014-10-05">
<name>Hama-Hama</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>162322.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="254" picture="17073.jpg">Yamaguchi Kappei</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="1989" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">33</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-02-15</airdate>
<rating votes="7">1.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">キング救助作戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">King`s Rescue</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Großangriff</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Au secours d`Attila</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">King Kyuujo Sakusen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1990" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-09-14</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ネモの親友</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nemo`s Best Friend</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Wal</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`amie du capitaine</title>
<title xml:lang="it">L`amico di Nemo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nemo no Shin`yuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1991" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">32</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-02-08</airdate>
<rating votes="6">1.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ナディアの初恋</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nadia`s Love</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Schatz</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le coup de foudre de Nadia</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il primo amore di Nadia?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nadia no Hatsukoi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1992" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-09-07</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ノーチラス対ノーチラス号</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nautilus vs Nautilus</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Kurs auf den Südpol</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Cap au sud</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Nautilus contro Nautilus</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nautilus Tai Nautilus Gou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1993" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">31</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-02-01</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さらば, レッドノア</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Farewell, Red Noah</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die unbekannte Stimme</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La Noah pourpre</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Addio, Red Noah</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saraba, Red Noah</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1994" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-08-31</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ジャンの新発明</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Jean`s New Invention</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Liebesgefühle</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La dernière invention de Jean</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La nuova invenzione di Jean</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jean no Shin Hatsumei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1995" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">30</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-01-25</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">地底の迷路</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Labyrinth in the Earth</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Im Innern der Insel</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le passage souterrain</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il labirinto sotterraneo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chitei no Meiro</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1996" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-08-24</airdate>
<rating votes="5">8.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">消えた大陸の秘密</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Mystery of the Lost Continent</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Atlantis</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le mystère du continent perdu</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il segreto del continente scomparso</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kieta Tairiku no Himitsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1997" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-07-27</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ノーチラス最大の危機</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Nautilus Faces Its Biggest Crisis</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Kampfunfähig</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Vont-ils couler le Nautilus</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La più grande crisi del Nautilus</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nautilus Saidai no Kiki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1998" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-07-20</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ディニクチスの谷</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Valley of Dinicthys</title>
<title xml:lang="de">In der Tiefe</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La grande faille</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La valle del Dinichthys</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dinichthys no Tani</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1999" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-06-08</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ネモの秘密</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nemo`s Secret</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Kapitän Nemos Geheimnis</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le secret du capitaine Némo</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il segreto di Nemo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nemo no Himitsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="2000" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-07-13</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">走れ! マリー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Run Marie Run!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Wo ist Mari?</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sauve toi, Marie</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Corri, Marie!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hashire! Marie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="2001" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">29</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-01-11</airdate>
<rating votes="4">2.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">キング対キング</title>
<title xml:lang="en">King vs King</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Rennen der Roboter</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Attila contre Attila</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">King Tai King</title>
</episode>
<episode id="2002" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-06-01</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ナディア救出作戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mission to Rescue Nadia</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Ende von Atlantis</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Il faut délivrer Nadia</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il salvataggio di Nadia</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nadia Kyuushutsu Sakusen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="2003" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-07-06</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">グランディスの初恋</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Grandis and Her First Love</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Landgang</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Première escale</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il primo amore di Grandis</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Grandis no Hatsukoi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="2004" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-12-21</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">流され島</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Floating Island</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Liebesbeweise</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Retrouvailles</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nagasarejima</title>
</episode>
<episode id="2005" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-05-25</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">バベルの塔</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Tower of Babel</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Turm zu Babel</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La tour de Babel</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La torre di babele</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Babel no Tou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="2006" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-06-22</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ノーチラス号の新入生</title>
<title xml:lang="en">New Recruits for the Nautilus</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Neuen Rekruten</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le secret du Nautilus</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nautilus Gou no Shinnyuusei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="2007" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-12-14</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔女のいる島</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Island of the Witch</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Könige des Schreckens</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`île de la sorcière</title>
<title xml:lang="it">L`isola della strega</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Majo no Iru Shima</title>
</episode>
<episode id="2008" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-05-18</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">孤島の要塞</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Infiltration of the Secret Base</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Bergwerk</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La nouvelle Atlantide</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kotou no Yousai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="2009" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-06-15</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">グラタンの活躍</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Crowning Performance by the Gratan</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Minenfelder</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le passage</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Gratan in azione</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gratan no Katsuyaku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="2010" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-12-07</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ひとりぼっちのキング</title>
<title xml:lang="en">King, the Lonely Lion</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Wo ist King?</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le chagrin d`Attila</title>
<title xml:lang="it">King tutto solo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hitoribocchi no King</title>
</episode>
<episode id="2011" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-05-11</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">マリーの島</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Marie`s Island</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die mysteriöse Insel</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`île mystérieuse</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Marie no Shima</title>
</episode>
<episode id="2012" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-11-30</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">はじめてのキス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The First kiss</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Im Rausch</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Premier aveu</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il primo bacio</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajimete no Kiss</title>
</episode>
<episode id="2013" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-05-04</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">万能潜水艦ノーチラス号</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nautilus, the Fantastic Submarine</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Kapitän Nemo</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le Nautilus</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bannou Sensuikan Nautilus Gou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="2014" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-11-16</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">リンカーン島</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lincoln Island</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Auf sich gestellt</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Retour à la nature</title>
<title xml:lang="it">L`isola di Lincoln</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Lincoln-tou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="2015" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-04-27</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">謎の大海獣</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Riddle of the Giant Sea Monsters</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Schiffbrüchig</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le monstre des mers</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il mostro marino</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nazo no Daikaijuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="2016" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-11-09</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">小さな漂流者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Young Drifters</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die einsame Insel</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`île déserte</title>
<title xml:lang="it">I piccoli naufraghi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chiisana Hyouryuusha</title>
</episode>
<episode id="2017" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-04-20</airdate>
<rating votes="9">7.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">小さな逃亡者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Little Fugitive</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Notlandung</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les fugitifs</title>
<title xml:lang="it">I piccoli fuggiaschi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chiisana Toubousha</title>
</episode>
<episode id="2018" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">39</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-04-12</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">星を継ぐ者...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Successor of the Stars</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Entscheidung</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Héritiers d`une planète</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hoshi o Tsugu Mono...</title>
</episode>
<episode id="2019" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-11-02</airdate>
<rating votes="6">8.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">裏切りのエレクトラ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Electra the Traitor</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Nadjas Vater</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La déception d`Electra</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il tradimento di Electra</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uragiri no Electra</title>
</episode>
<episode id="2020" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-04-13</airdate>
<rating votes="8">8.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">エッフェル塔の少女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Girl at the Eiffel Tower</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Geheimnisvolle Nadja</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La petite fille du cirque</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La ragazza sulla Torre Eiffel</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Eiffel Tou no Shoujo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="2021" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">38</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-04-05</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">宇宙へ...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To the Sky</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der letzte Kampf</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le jugement du capitaine Némo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uchuu e...</title>
</episode>
<episode id="2022" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-10-26</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さよなら...ノーチラス号</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Farewell Nautilus</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Supermagnet</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le Nautilus pris au piège</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Addio, Nautilus</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sayonara... Nautilus Gou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="2023" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">37</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-03-29</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ネオ皇帝</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Emperor Neo</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Größenwahn</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`empereur Neo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Neo Koutei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="2024" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1990-09-21</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ジャンの失敗</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Jean Makes a Mistake</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Jeans Fehler</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La bêtise de Jean</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il fallimento di Jean</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jean no Shippai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="2025" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">36</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-03-08</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">万能戦艦N-ノーチラス号</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The New Nautilus</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die neue Nautilus</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le nouveau Nautilus</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bannou Senkan N-Nautilus Gou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="2026" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">35</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-03-01</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ブルーウォーターの秘密</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Secret of Blue Water</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Zukunftsängste</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Gravé dans la pierre</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il segreto della pietra azzurra</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Blue Water no Himitsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="2027" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">34</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1991-02-22</airdate>
<rating votes="5">1.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">いとしのナディア</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My Darling Nadia</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ein Liebeslied und seine Folgen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ma chère Nadia</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La mia adorata Nadia</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Itoshi no Nadia</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8066" update="2011-12-28">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>1990-04-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8067" update="2011-12-28">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>1990-04-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8068" update="2005-08-23">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Prologue</title>
</episode>
<episode id="21771" update="2007-09-18">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2003-02-18</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Omake Part 1 - 1889: Nadia`s World</title>
</episode>
<episode id="21772" update="2007-10-23">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2003-02-18</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Omake Part 2 - This is Neo Atlantis!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="21773" update="2005-08-23">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2003-02-18</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Omake Part 3 - 26 Secrets of the Invincible Submarine Nautilus</title>
</episode>
<episode id="21774" update="2005-08-23">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2003-02-18</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Omake Part 4 - The Big Secret of Blue Water</title>
</episode>
<episode id="21775" update="2005-08-23">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2003-02-18</airdate>
<rating votes="2">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Omake Part 5 - Nadia Enters a Pageant</title>
</episode>
<episode id="21776" update="2005-08-23">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2003-02-18</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Omake Part 6 - Welcome to Neo Atlantis!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="21777" update="2005-08-23">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2003-02-18</airdate>
<rating votes="2">7.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Omake Part 7 - Nadia Super Encyclopedia</title>
</episode>
<episode id="21778" update="2005-08-23">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2003-02-18</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Omake Part 8 - Sunset JanJan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="21779" update="2005-08-23">
<epno type="2">S9</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2003-02-18</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Omake Part 9 - In Search of that Lost Time...</title>
</episode>
<episode id="21780" update="2005-08-23">
<epno type="2">S10</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2003-02-18</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Omake Part 10 - Comparison!! New Nautilus vs. Red Noah</title>
</episode>
<episode id="85767" update="2007-12-12">
<epno type="2">S11</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Music Video - Clip 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="85768" update="2007-12-12">
<epno type="2">S12</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Music Video - Clip 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="85769" update="2007-12-12">
<epno type="2">S13</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Music Video - Clip 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="85770" update="2007-12-12">
<epno type="2">S14</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Music Video - Clip 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="85771" update="2007-12-12">
<epno type="2">S15</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Music Video - Clip 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="85772" update="2007-12-12">
<epno type="2">S16</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Music Video - Clip 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="85773" update="2007-12-12">
<epno type="2">S17</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Music Video - Clip 7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="85774" update="2007-12-12">
<epno type="2">S18</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Music Video - Clip 8</title>
</episode>
<episode id="85775" update="2007-12-12">
<epno type="2">S19</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Music Video - Clip 9</title>
</episode>
<episode id="85776" update="2007-12-12">
<epno type="2">S20</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Music Video - Clip 10</title>
</episode>
<episode id="85777" update="2007-12-12">
<epno type="2">S21</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Music Video - Clip 11</title>
</episode>
<episode id="85778" update="2007-12-12">
<epno type="2">S22</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Music Video - Clip 12</title>
</episode>
<episode id="85779" update="2007-12-12">
<epno type="2">S23</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Music Video - Clip 13</title>
</episode>
<episode id="93357" update="2014-06-05">
<epno type="2">S24</epno>
<length>50</length>
<rating votes="2">6.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Nadia Omake complete volume</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120262" update="2011-12-28">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Italian Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120263" update="2011-12-28">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Italian Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120264" update="2011-12-28">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">French Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120265" update="2011-12-28">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">French Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="135852" update="2011-12-28">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>1991-03-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="156390" update="2013-11-26">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">LD-BOXプロモーション映像</title>
<title xml:lang="en">LD-BOX Promotional Video</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">LD-BOX Promotion Eizou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="156391" update="2014-06-05">
<epno type="2">S25</epno>
<length>30</length>
<rating votes="1">7.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">メカニックアンソロジー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mechanic Anthology</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mechanic Anthology</title>
</episode>
<episode id="156392" update="2013-11-26">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="156393" update="2013-11-26">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CMs</title>
</episode>
<episode id="156394" update="2014-06-05">
<epno type="2">S26</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">番組PR用映像</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PR program for video</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bangumi PR-you Eizou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="163604" update="2014-10-19">
<epno type="3">C8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">German Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198576" update="2018-04-27">
<epno type="2">S27</epno>
<length>45</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Variety Video</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198577" update="2018-04-27">
<epno type="2">S30</epno>
<length>120</length>
<title xml:lang="en">The Nautilus Story 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198578" update="2018-04-27">
<epno type="2">S29</epno>
<length>115</length>
<title xml:lang="en">The Nautilus Story 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198579" update="2018-04-27">
<epno type="2">S28</epno>
<length>115</length>
<title xml:lang="en">The Nautilus Story 1</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
