<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="4777" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>24</episodecount>
<startdate>2007-04-08</startdate>
<enddate>2007-09-17</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Lucky Star</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">Lucky☆Star</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Счастливая Звезда</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="synonym">Szczęśliwa gwiazda</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="synonym">نجم محظوظ</title>
<title xml:lang="pt" type="synonym">Estrela da Sorte</title>
<title xml:lang="tr" type="synonym">Şanslı Yıldız</title>
<title xml:lang="vi" type="synonym">Ngôi sao may mắn</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Късметлийска звезда</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Lucky Star TV</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Зірка☆Щастя</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Лакі☆Стар</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">幸运星</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="short">L☆S</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">ls</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">LSTV</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">らき☆すた</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Lucky Star</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">러키☆스타</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="official">幸運☆星</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">幸运☆星</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="5932" type="Sequel">Lucky Star OVA: JK</anime>
<anime id="9622" type="Same Setting">Miyakawa-ke no Kuufuku</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="106" approval="188" total="227">Azumanga Daiou The Animation (2002)</anime>
<anime id="6257" approval="52" total="106">K-On!</anime>
<anime id="8107" approval="51" total="65">A Channel: The Animation</anime>
<anime id="8168" approval="42" total="71">Nichijou</anime>
<anime id="8890" approval="26" total="53">Acchi Kocchi</anime>
<anime id="3298" approval="23" total="30">PaniPoni Dash!</anime>
<anime id="8729" approval="14" total="29">Danshi Koukousei no Nichijou</anime>
<anime id="2787" approval="13" total="26">Ichigo Marshmallow</anime>
<anime id="4125" approval="11" total="21">Gakuen Utopia Manabi Straight!</anime>
<anime id="8899" approval="11" total="16">Joshiraku</anime>
<anime id="9418" approval="10" total="15">Aiura</anime>
<anime id="6556" approval="8" total="19">Seitokai no Ichizon</anime>
<anime id="9722" approval="6" total="21">Non Non Biyori</anime>
<anime id="8552" approval="6" total="15">Kill Me Baby</anime>
<anime id="7525" approval="5" total="33">Ore no Imouto ga Konna ni Kawaii Wake ga Nai</anime>
<anime id="6780" approval="5" total="19">Working!!</anime>
<anime id="9311" approval="4" total="11">GJ-bu</anime>
<anime id="8661" approval="2" total="10">Gudaguda Fairies</anime>
<anime id="5083" approval="1" total="21">Sayonara Zetsubou-sensei</anime>
<anime id="8888" approval="1" total="8">Binbougami ga!</anime>
<anime id="6531" approval="1" total="7">Kanamemo</anime>
<anime id="1697" approval="1" total="4">Sensei no Ojikan: Doki Doki School Hours</anime>
<anime id="12290" approval="0" total="5">Gabriel Dropout</anime>
<anime id="14156" approval="0" total="5">Watashi ni Tenshi ga Maiorita!</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="43">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="215397">A Funny anime with numerous references to other anime and mangas. A good anime to test your knowledge on other animes!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="508247">This is a MUST see but for fans , if you want : slice of school life + otaku culture + hilarious comedy , then dont waste your time here and start watching it</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="527728">A charming cast of wacky characters, funny episodes and plenty of parodies and references you may or may not get make this a must see for fans.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="293766">Lucky star is a jam-packed thrill! Very amusing and entertaining to watch. Loads of comedy and parodies! If you`re into Japanese culture and a fan of "The surreal life" (not the show ofc), then this one I recommend to you =).</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="834921">A fascinating time capsule of the anime industry and community between 2005-2009.
If you didn`t live through this period (or at least haven`t seen most of the major anime out at the time),
then your experience will differ greatly from most of the fanbase`s.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="538887">Well i don`t think that revansghost is right. I saw only one anime prior to this. Tough i know what i.e. 4chan and WoW etc. Obvious WTF is the age of girls and how they look, but it is anime. Maybe i did not get all the jokes but i still enjoyed it as it was slow pace piece from life :)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="284501">excellent humor</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="221060">ZOMG. I can actually relate to what they were saying. =D Fun, fun series it is.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="100535">great otaku/gamer slice-of-life comedy full of references</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="125248">One of the funniest anime ever.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="274396">Funny as hell, i loved it!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="255852">Slice of life, highly enjoyable&lt;br /&gt;see: Azumanga Daioh</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="393493">Lucky Shit isnt funny, it is only boring, dumb and lame as hell.

Overrated crap!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="354280">A delightfully nonsensical parade of otaku jokes and general silliness.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="317829">Great slice of life and comedy. Easy to rewatch and not in the slightest, a waste of time.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="417398">There is a reason why this anime is so famous, it is hilarious; especially if you can get the references the anime makes. It is very relaxing and very enjoyable with frequent laughs.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="430888">after 10 eps it starts to get really annoying, after 5 more it starts to suck and in the end... well never watched last 3 episodes.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="298777">You can`t be an otaku without enjoying this.  My wife kept saying, "what`s so funny?"</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="525522">Like everyone else has said: You`ve got to have a lot of anime under your belt to get most of the jokes in this anime. That being said, I can`t even begin to count all of the satires in this show, and that`s the best part. My favorite part has to be the "show" at the end tho. This is a really well thought out show, especially considering how entertaining it is for there being no real over-arching plot between episodes. Its a slice-of-life show that`s all about the satire, and it accomplishes this goal perfectly. Just make sure you`ve seen a good bit of anime or a lot will be lost on you.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="267233">All I can say is that it is funny, slightly random, and is very kawaii!  (for those that know me, the good kawaii).  Watch the first three episodes and you`ll know if you will love it or not</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="63783">KAWAIIII, theres so much nostalgia in this series. A MUST for every real Anime and manga fan. I enjoyed the most the karaoke sessions at the end of every episode, and of course Lucky Channel! Ah and a recommendation for all lolicon-lovers on this planet, LOL.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="135820">must see for any anime lover out there. this is perfect moe</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="117495">Best otaku anime ever, its hilarious!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="430063">How much your otaku level is ?
If you understand most of the plots and conversations in this series, then your otaku level is high.

You will enjoy this series after you watch a lot of anime / manga which aired until 2007 and Japanese culture stuffs.

This is NOT recommended for someone who just recently watched anime / read manga.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="4119">Hilarious comedy.... great for watching, specially for geeks/otakus</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="18027">Hilarious!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="181980">Kagami-sama &amp;lt;3</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="242116">Actually one of the best comedy animes I`ve seen.&lt;br /&gt;+ for sarcasm&lt;br /&gt;+ for slice of life&lt;br /&gt;++ for the ending songs&lt;br /&gt;+ for crazyness</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.lucky-ch.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="736" type="Animation Work">Kyoto Animation</name>
<name id="121" type="Direction">Yamamoto Yutaka</name>
<name id="528" type="Character Design">Horiguchi Yukiko</name>
<name id="677" type="Series Composition">Machida Touko</name>
<name id="528" type="Chief Animation Direction">Horiguchi Yukiko</name>
<name id="530" type="Music">Kousaki Satoru</name>
<name id="533" type="Direction">Takemoto Yasuhiro</name>
<name id="6366" type="Original Work">Yoshimizu Kagami</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the 4-koma manga by http://anidb.net/cr6366 [Yoshimizu Kagami], serialised in http://anidb.net/cr30434 [Comptiq].
Having fun at school is all about doing homework together, cooking and eating, playing video games, and watching anime. All those little things make up the daily life of the anime- and chocolate-loving http://anidb.net/ch2999 [Izumi Konata] and her friends...</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="7990">7.61</permanent>
<temporary count="8140">8.05</temporary>
<review count="12">7.01</review>
</ratings>
<picture>231732.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7222</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1887</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3875</identifier>
<identifier>xrijyy</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.lucky-ch.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Lucky_Star_(manga)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>らき☆すた_(アニメ)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1102</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>326766</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8918</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/1670</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>387</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2007/lukisuta</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10006</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="362" parentid="2793" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-09-24">
<name>dancing</name>
<description>Dance is when people move their body to music. There are many kinds of dance, like ballet or waltz. Dancing can be done for fun but can be also an art.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1152" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-23">
<name>undead</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1783" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>immature</name>
<description>Marked by or indicating a lack of maturity</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2396" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-08">
<name>swimsuit</name>
<description>A swimsuit is one of several kinds of garments designed to be worn by people engaging in water-based activities or sports or during certain activities under sunlight. Most kinds of swimsuit reveal a large portion of the body surface area, but exceptions exist. The more revealing kinds may also be worn as undergarment in sports that require wetsuits, or when there is a need to display the body, as in the case of beauty pageants or bodybuilding contests.
There is a very wide range of styles of modern swimsuits, which vary in relation to body coverage and materials. The choice of style of swimsuit is dependent on current fashions, community standards of modesty, and plain personal preference. Swimsuits for men usually expose the chest, while those for women do not usually do so; however, many women prefer to engage in water or sun activities with their torso uncovered, in a practice commonly described as toplessness or topfreedom. Since the early twentieth century a naturist movement has developed in western countries that seeks a return to non-sexual nakedness when swimming and during other appropriate activities; in some places around the world, nude beaches have been set aside for people who choose to engage in normal beach activities in the nude, and such beaches may or may not enforce nudity onto their goers.
In anime, it is common for at least one episode to feature the characters in swimsuits, usually as an excuse for gratuitous fanservice; when that happens, the episode is usually labeled a pool or beach episode, after the place the characters went to. Swimsuits, and in particular one-piece swimsuits, are a very common fetish in Japan; while the reason for that is uncertain, a common folk explanation is the fact that boys throughout their entire adolescence are commonly exposed to their female classmates wearing them, in what might be called an experiment in sexual discovery waiting to happen.</description>
<picurl>149786.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2535" parentid="1152" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-18">
<name>ghost</name>
<description>In traditional belief, a ghost is the soul or spirit of a deceased person or animal that can appear, in visible form or other manifestation, to the living. Descriptions of the apparition of ghosts vary widely: The mode of manifestation can range from an invisible presence to translucent or wispy shapes, to realistic, life-like visions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2566" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-31">
<name>loli</name>
<description>Lolita (often also just abbreviated to loli) refers originally to a novel by Vladimir Nabokov. The book is internationally famous for its controversial subject: the narrator and protagonist, middle aged Humbert Humbert, becomes obsessed and sexually involved with a 12-year-old girl named Dolores Haze.
Nowadays the name "Lolita" describes a sexually precocious young girl.
Related to this is http://anidb.net/t2415 [lolicon], the Japanese abbreviation of the English phrase "Lolita Complex". Sometimes written as "roricon" or "rorikon" due to the inexact mapping between Japanese and English phonemes. This is the term used to describe the fetish/fascination some mature people have for underage girls. There is an entire industry in Japan devoted to providing legal but schoolgirl-themed pornography, taking advantage of the cute childlike appearance some Japanese women maintain well into their twenties.
Because the characters in anime are often young by convention, many fans think that a character can only be Lolicon if she is twelve or younger. Exceptions are granted if the other character in the relationship is a lot older.
One particular device used to skirt the boundaries of taste and legality is the exotic being (alien, creature of magic, robot or the like) which takes the form of an underage human girl, but is in fact for all other practical purposes an adult.
Another reason why lolicon is fetishized by people may be because some of them just view it as a substitute for their fetish for flat-chested, but otherwise well-developed, women.
Source: Wikipedia / TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32760.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2654" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-13">
<name>medium awareness</name>
<description>Medium awareness is the situational and generally temporary awareness characters in works of fiction have and display of the very fact that they are characters in works of fiction. For example, they may comment about the background music, quip about the script or narration, complain about the roles given to them by the writer or their lack of screen time, see the subtitles that appear on screen, inform the audience about the arrival of the commercial break, and even use medium effects as tools. The most common form of medium awareness is known as breaking the fourth wall, in which characters speak directly to the audience, either to it as a whole or to specific members of it. The "fourth wall" is the imaginary "wall" at the front of the stage of a proscenium theatre through which the audience sees the play; it is a metaphor for the boundary between what happens inside the work, to the characters, and outside it, to the audience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2662" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>school excursion</name>
<description>True for almost all anime with school setting, there will be a school excursion or field trip. Tokyo and Kyoto seem to be particularly popular as sightseeing destinations. So are hiking excursions into the local mountains. This also is a good excuse to present the prefecture`s / city`s food specialities.
Potential for ecchi moments: Obviously the "boys" will get all sorts of ideas with the "girls" sleeping so close by.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2665" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-16">
<name>school sports festival</name>
<description>To show off the students in sports clothing — in ecchi anime the female students in particular — a sports festival (or athletic meet) is quite popular in your typical anime with school setting. Here the protagonists can show their skills in diverse athletic competitions.
Note: This festival may also, though very rarely, take place at a kindergarten or preschool.</description>
<picurl>161025.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2679" parentid="2672" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Kyoto</name>
<description>Kyoto Prefecture is a prefecture of Japan in the Kansai region of the island of Honshu. The capital is the city of Kyoto.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214383.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2793" parentid="2883" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>performance</name>
<description>The song performance on stage or acting in a theatre is a central part of the character`s life in this anime type.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2805" parentid="2798" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>4-koma manga</name>
<description>Yonkoma manga (4コマ漫画, four cell manga, or 4-koma for short), a comic-strip format, generally consists of gag comic strips within four panels of equal size ordered from top to bottom. (They also sometimes run right-to-left horizontally or use a hybrid 2x2 style, depending on the layout requirements of the publication in which they appear.) Though the word yonkoma comes from the Japanese, the style also exists outside of Japan in other Asian countries as well as in the English-speaking market.</description>
<picurl>70558.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2830" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>furo scene</name>
<description>Furo (polite: Ofuro) is Japanese for bath, specifically a type of bath which originated as a short, steep-sided wooden bathtub. Baths of this type are found all over Japan in houses, apartments and traditional Japanese inns (Ryokans).
Furo are part of the Japanese ritual of bathing, not used for washing but for relaxing and warming oneself. Washing is carried out separately outside the furo, and only when completely clean does the bather enter the water. Generally Japanese bathrooms are small, so the bathroom is set up much like a walk-in shower area but containing the ofuro.
The cheapest and shortest way to show naked skin on TV, at least as much as allowed. It usually only takes up few minutes at most and as such it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in the nude and raise the DVD sales while still maintaining a "non-filler" episode.
Compare to the big brothers http://anidb.net/t4290 [sentou episode] and http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode].
See also http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode], and http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].</description>
<picurl>160785.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2865" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-16">
<name>summer festival</name>
<description>The summer festival is used to show off the female protagonists in traditional Japanese clothing — the yukata — a casual form of kimono.
The festivities include food stalls (cotton candy, candy apples, choco bananas, taiyaki), various games (scoop goldfishes), and a fireworks display.</description>
<picurl>161023.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2873" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-03">
<name>Valentine`s Day</name>
<description>Valentine`s Day is a festive day celebrated every February 14.
In Japan, South Korea, Taiwan, and China, Valentine`s Day is one month before http://anidb.net/t3147 [White Day], a celebration unique to those countries.
In the rest of the world:
On Valentine`s Day, both males and females will express their feelings of affection towards their loved ones, by exchanging gifts (such as cards, candies, and chocolates), going on dates, and other signs and actions of affection. Some people also take the opportunity to confess and propose for marriage. In Western countries, it is generally expected of the male to offer gifts to the significant other.
In many countries, friends and co-workers also exchange small gifts to show their friendship towards each other.
In Japan, South Korea, Taiwan, and China:
On Valentine`s Day, many women feel obliged to give chocolates to all male co-workers, except when the day falls on a Sunday, a holiday. This is known as giri choco (義理チョコ, "obligation chocolate"), with unpopular co-workers receiving only chougiri choco (超義理チョコ, "ultra-obligatory chocolate") cheap chocolate.
This contrasts with honmei choco (本命チョコ, "love chocolate"), chocolate given to a loved one.
Friends, especially girls, may exchange chocolate referred to as tomo choco (友チョコ, "friend chocolate").
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>160891.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2886" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-16">
<name>New Year`s Day</name>
<description>It is tradition in Japan to celebrate the new year at a Shinto shrine (hatsumode). The protagonists will offer some money, ring a bell at the end of a thick rope, and then pray for good fortune.
This usually goes along with gorging yourself at the many temporary food stalls, playing various games, and drawing a fortune.
The female characters in the anime will usually dress up in a kimono, to show off their traditional Japanese clothing, while watching the fireworks.</description>
<picurl>161028.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3028" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-17">
<name>real-world location</name>
<description>Places seen in the show exist in reality.
Note: This could be sometime in the future, though names and certain places will still be recognizable.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3610" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-12-19">
<name>game references</name>
<description>Be it the sound of a 1-up being grabbed, three golden triangles appearing on someones shirt or a blatant parody portraying a monkey throwing barrels down a poorly constructed facility, this anime contains characteristics dedicated to the remembrance/worship of an actual video game.</description>
<picurl>166123.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3809" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-05-24">
<name>character driven</name>
<description>The main appeal of the show is the way the characters are portrayed and interact, focusing on dialogue, spending time together or getting to know each other. These anime are not "story-less" but story is secondary to character development and the characters themselves and what they experience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3867" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>ED variety</name>
<description>Several ED sequences in this anime have either a different song or different animation, maybe even to the point of having a unique ED for each episode.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3977" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-29">
<name>dialogue driven</name>
<description>A dialogue driven show has its story advanced by dialogue, with action being of much lower priority, and relies heavily on conversations between characters.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4131" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-05-11">
<name>cultural references</name>
<description>The plot of this anime shows signs of cultural references, these are often jokes that make reference to a certain custom, habit or history that is specifically attributed to that culture. Knowledge of the culture itself is needed in order to properly understand these jokes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4290" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>bath house visit</name>
<description>A sentou is a type of Japanese communal bath house where customers pay for entrance. Some Japanese find social importance in going to public baths, out of the theory that physical intimacy brings emotional intimacy, which is termed skinship in Japanese. Traditionally it is gender-segregated — men usually bathe only with men, and women with women. 
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in the nude and raise the DVD sales.
See also http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode], http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode], and http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].</description>
<picurl>160783.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4386" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-19">
<name>eating Pocky</name>
<description>Pocky (ポッキー) is a Japanese snack food produced by the Ezaki Glico Company of Japan. Pocky was first sold in 1966, and consists of a biscuit stick coated with chocolate. It was named after the Japanese onomatopoetic word for the sound Pocky makes when bitten, pokkin (ポッキン). The original was followed by "Almond Pocky" in 1971, with an almond coating, and "Strawberry Pocky" in 1977. Today, the product line includes such variations as milk, mousse, green tea, honey, banana and coconut flavored coatings, and themed products such as "Decorer Pocky," with colourful decorative stripes in the coating, and "Men`s Pocky," a dark (bittersweet) chocolate and "mature" version.
Source: Wikipedia
It`s marketed in Germany under the name Mikado (Note: NOT the game, the snack).</description>
<picurl>73630.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4498" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-20">
<name>heart-warming</name>
<description>The story and its characters give off good vibes — includes elevated feelings of affection such as tenderness, sympathy and love, all in one package.
The kind of anime which leaves you with a warm feeling inside and you can not stop smiling while watching it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4570" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-07">
<name>watercolour style</name>
<description>A watercolour or aquarelle is a painting method in which the paints are made of pigments suspended in a water-based solution. Some anime are created in the style of watercolour paintings, the watercolour style, usually with faded pastels that often give the show a warm and friendly visual presentation. In modern anime, this is generally achieved via computer effects that create an imitation of watercolour, rather than by creating real-life watercolour art. While the watercolour style is more commonly used for backgrounds, it is possible to create the entire anime in such a style.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4573" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-02">
<name>Comiket</name>
<description>Comiket, also known as the Comic Market, is the world`s largest self-published http://anidb.net/t6989 [comic book fair], held twice a year in Tokyo, Japan.</description>
<picurl>167005.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5515" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>faceless background characters</name>
<description>Unimportant random/extra characters that appear mostly as part of the background are often drawn without much facial details, normally to save money, effort and manpower for more important parts of the show. Sometimes, they have almost or no facial details, meaning their heads only have indications of the presence of parts such as hair or mouth, or not even that. This can go as far as only drawing an abstracted silhouette of the whole body.</description>
<picurl>233515.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5697" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-02">
<name>randomness</name>
<description>The anime does not follow a predictable storyline. New, strange, obscure, or otherwise unexpected story elements are introduced at a whim.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5725" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-15">
<name>purikura</name>
<description>A standard on a date in a school setting, to remember the moment with the "loved one".
In Japan, purikura (プリクラ) refers to a photo sticker booth or the product of such a photo booth. The name is a shortened form of the registered trademark Purinto Kurabu (プリント倶楽部). The term derives from the English print club.
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5843" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>sibling yin yang</name>
<description>In real life, siblings hardly ever act the same. Fiction sometimes takes this to an extreme.
Enter Sibling Yin Yang, the occurrence of siblings that are nearly polar opposites. If he`s cool and reckless, she`s responsible and thoughtful. If she`s a spiky-haired hooligan, he`s the nerdy wimpy one. If he`s an immature brat, she`s... well, you get the picture.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5846" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-26">
<name>beach visit</name>
<description>Every anime has to have them, episodes in which the characters for whatever reason end up going to the sea, ocean, random island or the local pond.
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in swimsuits and raise the DVD sales.
The cheap version is the http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].
Other marginally less used variants of this are the http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode] and the http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], used when it is too cold for a beach/pool episode.
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene].</description>
<picurl>160805.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6023" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-06-01">
<name>cosplay restaurant</name>
<description>Cosplay restaurants are theme restaurants and pubs that originated in Akihabara, Tokyo, Japan around the year 1999. They include maid cafés and butler cafés, where the service staff dress as elegant maids, or as butlers. Such restaurants and cafés have quickly become a staple of Japanese otaku culture. Compared with service at normal cafés, the service at cosplay cafés involves the creation of a rather different atmosphere. The staff treat the customers as masters and mistresses in a private home rather than merely as café customers.
The popularity of the cosplay restaurants and maid cafés has spread to other regions in Japan, such as Osaka`s Den Den Town as well as other countries, such as Hong Kong, Taiwan, Singapore, Mexico, and Canada.
Often such cafés or a more simple kissaten, small Japanese-style coffee shops, are part of school festivals where the protagonists` class runs one.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6029" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-04-08">
<name>mundane made awesome</name>
<description>Sometimes normal just doesn`t cut it. Eating: you put food in your mouth and chew. Playing sports: you throw a ball around. You need to make it awesome, no matter how mundane it is.
Let`s throw in some gripping orchestral music, lighting changes, different camera angles, something! Don`t write like a man, write like an evil overlord! Exaggerate your expressions and gestures, speak with excessive intonation, and if all else fails, throw in some close-ups, slow motion, and ominous Latin chanting! With practice, even you can turn something like eating chips into an epic battle of light and dark, blinding the viewer with sheer awesomeness.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>149443.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6030" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-22">
<name>otaku culture</name>
<description>Otaku (おたく/オタク) is a Japanese term used to refer to people with obsessive interests, particularly anime, manga, and video games. A female otaku is occasionally referred to as a fujoshi. (Source: Wikipedia)
Here certain aspects of this "fandom" are presented in more detail, e.g. the creation of doujinshi (self-published amateur manga).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="32" type="main character in" update="2019-12-28">
<rating votes="653">8.97</rating>
<name>Hiiragi Kagami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tsukasa`s elder twin sister. Konata`s close friend. Her thought process is normal, so she often pokes fun at Konata. She may be the most right-minded character. An aloof-chummy type, who is warm-hearted only when she has gotten to know you.</description>
<picture>18662.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="641" picture="31202.jpg">Katou Emiri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38" type="cameo appearance in" update="2017-11-12">
<rating votes="2581">8.44</rating>
<name>Saber</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Saber, an agile and powerful warrior. Known as the King of Knights, she maintains a high code of honour. Saber is loyal, independent, and reserved; she appears cold, but is actually suppressing her emotions to focus on her goals. Her class is considered the "Most Outstanding", with excellent ratings in all categories.
In Fate/Zero, though she and Emiya Kiritsugu are Servant and Master seeking the same ultimate goal of peace, their differing ideological perspectives result in a strained relationship where Kiritsugu does not directly acknowledge Saber. After Kiritsugu summoned Saber, he made Irisviel hide Avalon - which had served as a catalyst to the summoning - inside her body so to serve as insurance while she performed her act of fake Master. Irisviel`s and Saber`s role at the time was to openly take action and serve as a decoy in order to lure out enemies, while Kiritsugu worked in the shadows with his assistant, Hisau Maiya. Because Saber could not dematerialise her spiritual body, she disguised herself as a man while staying at Irisviel`s side.
In the Fate route, because her master Emiya Shirou cannot effectively provide her with Mana, she minimises her activity to preserve what she has. Saber is bewildered by Shirou`s "protective" tendencies, and believes his erratic and reckless behaviour jeopardise her chances of winning the Holy Grail War.</description>
<picture>209482.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="271" type="cameo appearance in" update="2015-03-25">
<rating votes="1798">7.02</rating>
<name>Suzumiya Haruhi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>In the beginning of the story, she is initially shown as anti-social and displayed various personality quirks, but as the series progressed, she became more open with her emotions, whilst still remaining highly active. She became the founder of, and recruiter for, the SOS Brigade, forcibly enlisting Kyon, Yuki Nagato (the only member of the Literature Club), Mikuru Asahina, and Itsuki Koizumi. She is responsible for organizing most of their activities as a group.
Unknown to her, she has the power to change, destroy, or create a new reality based on her inner desires and feelings. She is described in various ways; Yuki states that she has `the potential for auto-evolution`, Mikuru believes that she is the originator of a large time-quake and finally Itsuki declares her to be `God`. Due to this, she is the main focus of the Integrated Data Entity, the Organization, and an organization of future humans.</description>
<picture>10490.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="4" picture="177060.jpg">Hirano Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="272" type="cameo appearance in" update="2015-03-25">
<rating votes="1318">8.81</rating>
<name>Kyon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kyon is one of Haruhi`s companions, and the second founding member of the SOS Brigade. Upon his entry into high school, he resigns himself to a lifestyle where his adolescent fantasies such as aliens, time travelers, and espers have no place. After one small conversation with him, Haruhi unexpectedly opened up to him and dragged him into her new club. His reputation and fate have since become entangled with Haruhi`s.</description>
<picture>60733.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="45" picture="44970.jpg">Sugita Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="274" type="cameo appearance in" update="2015-03-25">
<rating votes="1367">8.80</rating>
<name>Nagato Yuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yuki is initially portrayed as an introverted, taciturn bibliophile. She is actually an artificial human created by the Integrated Data Entity, and possesses supernatural powers as a result. She joins Haruhi Suzumiya`s SOS Brigade in order to observe her on the behalf of the Integrated Data Entity. In addition, she is present to ensure that Haruhi does not use her godlike powers, and aids the other Brigade members in stopping forces that wish her to do so.</description>
<picture>31404.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="245" picture="46862.jpg">Chihara Minori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1906" type="cameo appearance in" update="2015-04-20">
<rating votes="656">7.92</rating>
<name>Archer</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He is the Servant of one of the series` main heroines, Toosaka Rin. Archer is sarcastic and cynical - but under his hardened exterior lies a complex and dark personality that unfolds throughout the story. Though skilled with ranged weapons, he can hold his own in melee combat. Archer considers Shirou Emiya`s idealism to be weak and delusional, recognising Shirou`s mentality of "wanting to save everyone" as naïve and impossible.
Archer is actually an older version of Emiya Shirou, who actually became a heroic spirit in his own right in the future. Embittered and betrayed by his ideals, he participates in the Holy Grail War in an opportunity to kill his past self and in the ensuing paradox free himself from the path which led to his betrayal.</description>
<picture>172323.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="2999" type="main character in" update="2013-10-22">
<rating votes="974">9.11</rating>
<name>Izumi Konata</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A girl who loves manga, anime, and video games. Because of this, her thought process is largely influenced by her favourite works... She has great athletic ability, but is an indoor person who rarely utilises this talent.</description>
<picture>18649.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4" picture="177060.jpg">Hirano Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3000" type="main character in" update="2019-12-28">
<rating votes="230">7.15</rating>
<name>Hiiragi Tsukasa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kagami`s younger twin sister and close friend of Konata`s. She has a tolerant attitude and shrugs aside Konata`s silliness. Perhaps she just simply goes with the flow. A typical friendly, soothing character. Is actually a mayonnaise fiend?</description>
<picture>18650.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="425" picture="17296.jpg">Fukuhara Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3001" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-09">
<rating votes="27">3.62</rating>
<name>Minegishi Ayano</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A reserved, ladylike girl. Kagami`s classmate and rather like a devoted wife to Misao. She is always with Misao and the others, so there did not seem to be any boy in her life... but that is apparently not necessarily the case.</description>
<picture>18652.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="539" picture="228668.jpg">Aizawa Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3002" type="main character in" update="2009-02-09">
<rating votes="172">5.13</rating>
<name>Takara Miyuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Classmate to Konata and the others. She is a model student with beauty, excellent grades, and exemplary conduct, but is a space cadet. She becomes acquainted with Kagami through her connection as class president and becomes friends with her. She is utterly superhuman and is a walking mass of fan-favoured characteristics.</description>
<picture>18651.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="424" picture="224027.jpg">Endou Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3003" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-08-25">
<rating votes="92">7.90</rating>
<name>Kuroi Nanako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Homeroom teacher to Konata and the others. A friendly teacher, the likes of which you find at every school. Happy-go-lucky and rather irresponsible. She often trades games with Konata. Teaches world history. She feels a one-sided closeness towards Yui Narumi.</description>
<picture>18653.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1430" picture="18688.jpg">Maeda Konomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3004" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-09">
<rating votes="85">6.25</rating>
<name>Kobayakawa Yutaka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Konata`s cousin. She has been sickly since she was little. Having enrolled at Ryoo, she currently lives with Konata. She is adored by everyone for her honest nature and expressiveness. A bit absent-minded.</description>
<picture>18654.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2031" picture="21359.jpg">Hasegawa Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3005" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-09">
<rating votes="117">7.33</rating>
<name>Iwasaki Minami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Quiet and caring model student. Because she is taciturn, she is sometimes mistaken as being scary. She excels both academically and athletically, but she has a complex about having no chest.</description>
<picture>18655.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="245" picture="46862.jpg">Chihara Minori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3006" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-09">
<rating votes="72">7.84</rating>
<name>Kusakabe Misao</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A simple and pure, energetic girl. Kagami`s classmate and Ayano`s childhood friend. It is her nature to enjoy everything and she has a positive, calm attitude, but academics is not her forte.</description>
<picture>18656.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1609" picture="19579.jpg">Mizuhara Kaoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3007" type="appears in" update="2009-02-09">
<name>Sakuraba Hikaru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hikaru Sakuraba is the biology teacher at Ryuou High School, and is the homeroom teacher of Kagami`s class 3-C. She is also the captain of the Lucky Star informational ad section, which was renamed "Lucky Paradise". She is feared by Akira, but Akira later calls Hikaru a betrayer. She likes CalorieMate and sleeping, dislikes vegetables, and people who quickly misunderstand things. She is Fuyuki`s good friend, who works as a school nurse. She appears briefly in episode twenty-four of the anime, making sure that Akira and Minoru will do things right, who are in bad terms after the event of episode twenty-one of "Lucky Channel".</description>
<picture>18657.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="458" picture="171388.jpg">Inoue Miki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3008" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-09">
<rating votes="44">4.63</rating>
<name>Patricia Martin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A geeky exchange student from America. Nickname: Patty. Classmate to Yutaka and Minami, her Japanese is very fluent. Her knowledge of geek vocabulary is particularly extensive. She works part-time at the cosplay café with Konata and they have also put out a CD together.</description>
<picture>18658.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1992" picture="151673.jpg">Sasaki Nozomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3009" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-09">
<rating votes="48">6.94</rating>
<name>Tamura Hiyori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Classmate to Yutaka and Minami, and a geek like Konata. Her hobby is to draw doujinshi (self-published manga) and she sometimes draws art using Yutaka and Minami as models</description>
<picture>18659.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="56" picture="16651.jpg">Shimizu Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3010" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-07-22">
<rating votes="70">6.67</rating>
<name>Kogami Akira</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Host of radio show "Lucky Channel". An idol currently appearing on TV and radio! At first sight, she looks like the cute type of character, but at 14 years old, she has 11 years of experience in the entertainment business, so she is also a veteran entertainer, who is strict about etiquette! She seems greatly displeased with Minoru Shiraishi, a newcomer recently experiencing a wave of success.</description>
<picture>18660.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1429" picture="18686.jpg">Konno Hiromi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3011" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-07-02">
<rating votes="36">5.01</rating>
<name>Takara Yukari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Takara Yukari is Takara Miyuki`s mother, who tends to be very well-mannered, but can be a bit of a klutz. She is warm and friendly, once talking with a telemarketer for over an hour, and has a mischievous sense of humour. Yukari`s hair is short and unlike her daughter, she does not wear eyeglasses. She doesn`t like to do household chores, which explains why she isn`t very skilled with household items. On one occasion, she thought that a coloured candle was a popsicle. Yukari is often mistaken for Miyuki`s "big sister", rather than mother proper, due to her youthfully cuddly appearance, which combined with her adorably cheerful personality and endearing clumsiness, has resulted in her being regarded as moe, a trait not common for women in anime in their thirties.</description>
<picture>18661.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1431" picture="25110.jpg">Kosuge Mami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3719" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-05-30">
<rating votes="15">2.15</rating>
<name>Ono Ichiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yumemi`s classmate and childhood friend. Ichiko is a very positive and energetic person. She always encourages Yumemi whenever she feels gloomy and is very protective of her. However, she also seems to have co-dependent tendencies and can be overly controlling due to her own insecurities. She had always wanted to see the islands in the sky Yumemi spoke of, and quietly wished for the day that she would see them.</description>
<picture>26490.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="56" picture="16651.jpg">Shimizu Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="3764" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-05-30">
<rating votes="15">7.05</rating>
<name>Imamura Suzume</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yumemi`s classmate and childhood friend. She is a very optimistic and cheerful girl who lives at her own pace. She has a rather immature and childish personality, but is always smiling. Though she is a girl with a very soft-spoken nature and childish at that, she often surprises others by her wise words and "outsider-looking-in" view.</description>
<picture>26491.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6635" type="appears in" update="2009-06-18">
<name>Cherry</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Iwasaki Minami`s dog</description>
<picture>29225.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3368" picture="132584.jpg">Kujira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6636" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-24">
<rating votes="81">8.18</rating>
<name>Shiraishi Minoru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shiraishi Minoru appears in the "Lucky Channel" segment at the end of each Lucky Star episode, but is also a minor recurring character, as a member of Konata Izumi`s class. He is the animated version of his voice actor, Minoru Shiraishi, although it is likely that the animated version is only around eighteen years old, due to his being in class 3-B. In one of the early karaoke ending theme sequences, it was revealed that Minoru has a part-time position, working at the karaoke bar Konata and her friends sing at. In the "Lucky Channel" segment, Minoru is Akira Kogami`s assistant, who repeatedly gets yelled at (and physically abused) by Akira, if he does or says something not to her liking. Minoru was nicknamed "Sebastian" by Konata one day, because of his likeness to a butler. After a trip to the forests around Mt. Fuji to get spring water for Akira, Minoru comes back a dirty and torn-up mess, and was more than likely mauled by a bear during his quest judging from the claw-marks on his back. Akira dubbed the water as too warm, spat it on the camera lens and then threw the rest in his face. This, after her cocktail of constant physical and mental abuse (not to mention being mauled by a bear for nothing), was the straw that broke the camel`s back, causing Minoru to go berserk and destroy the set for "Lucky Channel". During their confrontation in episode twenty-one of the anime, it seems that he has lost his fear of Akira, yelling right back at her and thwarting her desire to perform. In the final episode, with the stage wrecked, they do their last show, only to have yet another argument—she starts singing her song, but he, claiming this is merely a microphone check, cuts her off after only a few seconds. He appears briefly in Lucky Star: Ryouou Gakuen Outousai, the PlayStation 2 game of Lucky Star in a secret scene, where he is shown to trying to find the spring water in Mt. Fuji before being mauled.</description>
<picture>28324.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="434" picture="41082.jpg">Shiraishi Minoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6637" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-18">
<rating votes="9">1.77</rating>
<name>Hiiragi Tadao</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hiiragi Tadao is the father of the Hiiragi family and has short black hair. He works as the priest of the Takanomiya Shrine (Washinomiya Shrine). As a parent, he often makes sure that his daughters are doing their school work, and checks on their progress. He is the only one in the Hiiragi family who is right-handed.</description>
<picture>29234.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3124" picture="24096.jpg">Furusawa Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6638" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-18">
<rating votes="30">4.09</rating>
<name>Hiiragi Miki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hiiragi Miki has long blue-gray hair and is the mother of the Hiiragi family. She is able to maintain a trim, young-and-beautiful appearance, despite having given birth to four daughters.</description>
<picture>29233.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="240" picture="17059.jpg">Inoue Kikuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6639" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-08-02">
<rating votes="73">7.52</rating>
<name>Anizawa Meito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Anizawa Meito, also known as Anime Tenchou, is the manager of the Animate Ikebukuro shop (However, he appeared in the (old) Oomiya shop and the comic market booth in the Anime and appeared in the Akihabara shop in the PS2 Video Game), he was originally the mascot of Animate and Hero of Anime Tenchou.
He and his staff consider Konata their most valued customer, known as "Legendary Girl A" (伝説の少女A ,Densetsu no Shoujo A), and go to great lengths to sell their merchandise to her, often to the point of using espionage and military-style strategies, and at one point, Meito himself uses "Geass" on Konata to persuade her to buy a DVD from him; however when she tries to pay it, she fell short only three yen. Their attempts usually fail miserably. His appearance is heavily stylized, compared to the other characters, and he is known for his passionate yelling and highly energetic movements and poses. He appeared as a special guest during the Lucky Channel segment in episode seventeen, during which he and Minoru parody Mobile Fighter G Gundam`s Domon Kasshu, referencing the fact that Meito`s voice actor also played the character. He also appeared in episode twelve, fighting against another sales manager (about how valuable "so-called leftovers" can be after they ran out of rare and limited edition "thingies") in a dramatic way. Meito`s colleagues at Animate are all similarly enthusiastic about selling their merchandise. In 2002, Gainax produced a single original video animation, where Meito Anisawa and his fellow employees are the focus.</description>
<picture>29604.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="236" picture="132757.jpg">Seki Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6640" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-08-04">
<name>Hoshii Lamica</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hoshii Lamica is the clerk (Laminate card and Boys Love commodity charge) of the Animate Ikebukuro shop (However, she appeared in the (old) Omiya shop in the anime). She is the heroine of Anime Tenchou.</description>
<picture>32523.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="290" picture="24139.jpg">Nagasawa Miki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6641" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-08-22">
<rating votes="27">5.18</rating>
<name>Hiiragi Inori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hiiragi Inori has short dark-purple hair and is the eldest sister of the Hiiragi sisters. She is a miko at the Takanomiya Shrine.</description>
<picture>29230.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1444" picture="172066.jpg">Masu Nozomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6642" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-18">
<rating votes="28">3.52</rating>
<name>Hiiragi Matsuri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hiiragi Matsuri has short light brown hair and is the second eldest sister of the Hiiragi sisters, after Inori Hiiragi. She is a college student and a miko at the Takanomiya Shrine. She tends to be less dependable than Inori when helping their younger twin sisters with school work.</description>
<picture>29232.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1511" picture="173601.jpg">Akesaka Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6643" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-01-24">
<rating votes="42">8.40</rating>
<name>Izumi Soujirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Izumi Soujirou is Konata Izumi`s father, an author who works at home. He always wears loose, traditional Japanese clothing as his work clothes. He loves watching anime and playing video games, which influenced his daughter`s interests. Soujirou is "also a lolicon". This appreciation for neoteny may be one factor that caused him to fall in love with Kanata, whom he eventually married. He describes that he likes girls as some men do, but that he also appreciates younger ones. This means that this attraction is equal or possibly secondary, meaning he does not have a preference for them, so despite being a lolicon (person with a lolita complex) he would not be a pedophile. Throughout the show news reports and conversations indicate that young girls in the area are being approached by a strange man, and a running joke in the show involves hints that Soujirou is in fact the one doing it. The best example of this is the opening, part of which involves Soujirou spying on two schoolgirls from behind a lamppost.
Soujirou is very thin, and has unshaven facial hair, he has a mole under his left eye which his daughter inherited and has thick eyebrows. Additionally, he is allergic to pollen and when he decided to wear goggles and masks as protection from it, Konata sighed that, "Now you look weirder as well". She also frequently reminds him, "Please don`t do anything as to be taken away by the cops". Also, he often forgets to lock the door when he is using the toilet, which has left Yutaka with a tremendous shock.
Soujirou holds a deep love for his wife, Kanata Izumi, who passed away many years before. When Konata asks why Kanata chose to be with Soujirou (largely as a joke at his erotic personality`s expense), Soujirou points out that he and his wife simply looked past outwards appearances: Kanata loved Soujirou despite his otaku tendencies, and Soujirou obviously did not mind that Kanata had an unusual physique and did not share his hobbies.</description>
<picture>26901.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1613" picture="158486.jpg">Hiramatsu Hirokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6644" type="appears in" update="2010-08-22">
<rating votes="14">8.96</rating>
<name>Izumi Kanata</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Izumi Kanata was Konata Izumi`s mother, who was also very short and bore a striking resemblance to Konata (minus Konata`s ahoge, the catlike smile and the beauty mark under her left eye). She is described by Konata and Soujirou Izumi as having a personality straight out of a bishoujo game. She died when Konata was an infant of unspecified causes and her only appearances in the manga are through a single photograph and through Soujirou`s memory. Since she was Soujirou`s childhood friend, Konata has wondered if that was one of the main reasons why her mother married Soujirou. In the animated version, Kanata returns to the Izumi residence as a spirit, and walks in on a conversation both Konata and Soujirou were having about her. She is touched by Soujirou`s kind words that he was the only one who truly loved her as much as he did (she later realized that she too, loved him deeply), and even took a picture with him and Konata together. However, when Soujirou and Konata look at the photo image in the camera, they are spooked at what appears to be a shadow standing behind them. Konata wants to delete the image, while Soujirou wants to burn it, thinking that the family will end up cursed if they let it be, but Kanata pleads with them not to delete the picture to no avail, as no one can see or hear her.
Kanata`s spirit seems pleased with how Konata was raised, despite being a bit unsure of Soujirou exposing their daughter to erotic games, claiming that it could damage her "moral growth." However, she easily recognizes that Konata takes after her father, in both the good and bad ways, which leaves Kanata with a deep sense of relief. Soujirou also states that Kanata died a peaceful death without any regrets, and that she left them both with a smile.</description>
<picture>26900.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="508" picture="140061.jpg">Shimamoto Sumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6645" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-06-01">
<rating votes="31">6.22</rating>
<name>Narumi Yui</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>26903.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23480" picture="64123.jpg">Nishihara Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6646" type="appears in" update="2009-05-03">
<name>Narumi Kiyotaka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Narumi Kiyotaka is Yui Narumi`s husband and Konata Izumi`s cousin, by family. He is currently away and his only appearances throughout the series was through a phone conversation with his wife.</description>
<seiyuu id="42817" picture="90853.jpg">Kobushi Nobuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6647" type="appears in" update="2009-06-19">
<rating votes="5">8.73</rating>
<name>Nyamoo</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nyamoo is a mysterious creature that looks like a cat head with a tail. He is handled as a self-portrait of the creator, Kagami Yoshimizu.</description>
<picture>3053.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="10905" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-08-03">
<name>Takahashi-shachou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Animated version of http://anidb.net/cr4352 [Takahashi Yutaka].</description>
<picture>32481.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="220" picture="17038.jpg">Kosugi Juurouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10906" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-08-03">
<rating votes="2">3.53</rating>
<name>Sugita Ten`in</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Animated version of seiyuu, http://anidb.net/cr45 [Sugita Tomokazu].</description>
<picture>32483.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45" picture="44970.jpg">Sugita Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10908" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-08-04">
<rating votes="2">6.54</rating>
<name>Chihara Minori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Animated version of seiyuu, http://anidb.net/cr245 [Chihara Minori].</description>
<picture>32524.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="245" picture="46862.jpg">Chihara Minori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10910" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-08-04">
<rating votes="8">8.93</rating>
<name>Hirano Aya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Animated version of seiyuu, http://anidb.net/cr4 [Hirano Aya].</description>
<picture>32530.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4" picture="177060.jpg">Hirano Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10921" type="appears in" update="2009-08-06">
<rating votes="2">6.08</rating>
<name>Iwasaki Minami no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch3005 [Iwasaki Minami]`s mother.</description>
<picture>32595.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2068" picture="28743.jpg">Iwao Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10922" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-08-05">
<rating votes="3">7.30</rating>
<name>Ono Daisuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Animated version of seiyuu, http://anidb.net/cr250 [Ono Daisuke].</description>
<picture>32580.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="250" picture="157976.jpg">Ono Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10923" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-08-05">
<rating votes="1">2.05</rating>
<name>Hachiya Seiichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Animated version of animation producer, http://anidb.net/cr7590 [Hachiya Seiichi].</description>
<picture>32588.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32" picture="16618.jpg">Tachiki Fumihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10924" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-08-06">
<rating votes="4">7.54</rating>
<name>Gottouuza-sama</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Animated version of seiyuu, http://anidb.net/cr248 [Gotou Yuuko].</description>
<picture>32596.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="248" picture="45126.jpg">Gotou Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10925" type="appears in" update="2014-04-16">
<rating votes="12">3.88</rating>
<name>Miyakawa Hinata</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Miyakawa Hinata is a young girl with long salmon pink hair, which she ties just a bit to the left of her forehead with a rabbit clip; she has pink droopy eyes and is a meganekko. She makes a living through a job at a local doujin shop. However, she remains poor, as all her money is spent on manga and doujinshi.</description>
<picture>60546.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="6305" picture="223494.jpg">Takaguchi Yukiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10926" type="appears in" update="2014-04-16">
<rating votes="17">7.11</rating>
<name>Miyakawa Hikage</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Miyakawa Hikage is the younger sister of http://anidb.net/ch10925 [Miyakawa Hinata] and is in the fourth grade; she is the youngest character in Lucky Star. She attends the Sakura-en Public Elementary School, and is in class 4-1. She is not an otaku like her older sister, and as such carries the typical tsundere personality. Hikage lives in poverty because of her older sister and wants to grow up so she can get a job on her own; ironically, though, her dream is to eat meat. It is also because of her poverty caused by her sister that she starts to have distaste over otaku. Hikage likes to play gachapon, shopping, and travelling. Hikage`s appearance in the game has her with long light-purple hair; her hairstyle is distinctive, as she thinly braids her hair to the right, and uses that as a ribbon to tie her remaining hair. Her eyes are light blue and are slanted upward. Her appearance is a little different in the anime and manga, as she has short, blue hair instead of long, purple hair.</description>
<picture>60545.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="2291" picture="23193.jpg">Kano Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66374" type="appears in" update="2014-04-08">
<name>Gamers Ten`in</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>153165.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32" picture="16618.jpg">Tachiki Fumihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="71650" update="2011-06-19">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2007-04-05</airdate>
<rating votes="7">3.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Commercial</title>
</episode>
<episode id="71699" update="2017-10-27">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-08</airdate>
<rating votes="53">3.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">つっぱしる女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Girl Who Dashes Off</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">A garota da corrida</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsuppashiru Onna</title>
<summary>Anime super fan Konata and her friends debate the proper way to eat desserts and learn the difference between the flu and the common cold before paying a visit to a sick classmate.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="71829" update="2017-10-27">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-16</airdate>
<rating votes="29">5.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">努力と結果</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Efforts and Results</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Esforço e resultados</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Doryoku to Kekka</title>
<summary>Kagami and Tsukasa spend Golden Week together, but while Kagami’s been making time to work on her homework, Tsukasa hasn’t even started!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="71830" update="2017-10-27">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-23</airdate>
<rating votes="27">5.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">いろいろな人たち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Various People</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Diferentes tipos de pessoa</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Iroiro na Hito-tachi</title>
<summary>Konata schools the girls on how to win mail-in contests. Then, they discuss myths surrounding twins, the pros and cons of rainy days, and switching up hair styles.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="71831" update="2017-10-27">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-04-30</airdate>
<rating votes="28">5.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">やる気の問題</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Question of Motivation</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Problemas de motivação</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yaruki no Mondai</title>
<summary>Konata always has a creative excuse for her habitual tardiness, but karma comes back to bite her when she actually gets sick and isn’t given permission to miss class.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="71832" update="2017-10-27">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-07</airdate>
<rating votes="27">6.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">名射手</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Famous Shooter</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Bom atirador</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Meishashu</title>
<summary>The girls put on their yukata and head to a summer festival where they meet Konata’s cousin Yui.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="73052" update="2017-10-27">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-14</airdate>
<rating votes="28">6.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夏の定番</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fixtures of Summer</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Eventos de verão</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Natsu no Teiban</title>
<summary>The girls head to the beach for some much-needed summer fun!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="73055" update="2010-06-03">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2007-04-08</airdate>
<rating votes="6">8.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73383" update="2017-10-27">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-21</airdate>
<rating votes="26">5.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">イメージ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Image</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Imagem</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Image</title>
<summary>School is back in session, but Konata isn’t acting like herself, and Miyuki has to make it through the day without her glasses.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="73384" update="2017-10-27">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-28</airdate>
<rating votes="24">5.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">私じゃなくても旺盛</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Energetic Despite Not Being Myself</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Não precisa de mim para uma explosão</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Watashi Janakute mo Ousei</title>
<summary>The athletic festival kicks off, and the girl’s pick their events before dishing about whatever’s on their minds.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="73385" update="2017-10-27">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-04</airdate>
<rating votes="23">4.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">そんな感覚</title>
<title xml:lang="en">That Feeling</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Só um sentimento</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sonna Kankaku</title>
<summary>With exams around the corner, the girls discuss good study habits.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="74225" update="2017-10-27">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-11</airdate>
<rating votes="24">6.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">願望</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Desires</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Aspiração</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ganbou</title>
<summary>Tsukasa gets a new phone, the twins meet Konata’s dad, and the girls visit an anime shop where they attract the attention of the unique staff.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="74226" update="2017-10-27">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-18</airdate>
<rating votes="23">4.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">いろんな聖夜の過ごし方</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Various Ways to Spend Christmas Eve</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">As diversas maneiras de se passar a véspera do Natal</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ironna Seiya no Sugoshikata</title>
<summary>The approaching holidays spark conversations about Santa Claus, Christmas cake, and final exams.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="75084" update="2017-10-27">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-26</airdate>
<rating votes="25">7.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">お祭りへいこう</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let`s Go to the Festival</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Vamos ao festival</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Omatsuri e Ikou</title>
<summary>The girls head to a dōjinshi convention before attending a New Year’s festival.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="75085" update="2017-10-27">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-02</airdate>
<rating votes="28">6.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">おいしい日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Delicious Day</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Dia delicioso</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oishii Hi</title>
<summary>With the New Year on their minds, the girls talk about diets and various food traditions.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="75086" update="2017-10-27">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-09</airdate>
<rating votes="22">6.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ひとつ屋根の下</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Under One Roof</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Sob o mesmo teto</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hitotsu Yane no Shita</title>
<summary>Konata’s younger cousin comes to stay with her after she’s accepted to the same high school as the other girls.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="79924" update="2017-10-27">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-16</airdate>
<rating votes="23">6.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">いきなりは変われない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Can`t Suddenly Change</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Não posso mudar</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ikinari wa Kawarenai</title>
<summary>The girls go to a live concert event, and April Fools gives Konata the perfect chance to prank Kagami.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="80243" update="2017-10-27">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-23</airdate>
<rating votes="27">8.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">リング</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ring</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Toque</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ring</title>
<summary>Kagami, Tsukasa, and Miyuki visit the cosplay café where Konata works.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="80499" update="2017-10-27">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-30</airdate>
<rating votes="23">7.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">お天道様のもと</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Base of the Sun</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Debaixo do sol</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Otentou-sama no Moto</title>
<summary>It’s Konata’s birthday, but her surprise party doesn’t go exactly as planned!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="80989" update="2017-10-27">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-06</airdate>
<rating votes="21">5.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">十人十色</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To Each Her Own</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Pessoas diferentes, mentes diferentes</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Juunintoiro</title>
<summary>The girls discuss what kinds of animals they’re most like, Konata asks Miyuki about her vision, and Yutaka spends the day with her new friends.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="81082" update="2007-08-07">
<epno type="5">P1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<rating votes="1">3.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Omake 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="81083" update="2007-08-07">
<epno type="5">P2</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Omake 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="81084" update="2007-08-07">
<epno type="5">P3</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">OP + Omake 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="81164" update="2017-10-27">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-13</airdate>
<rating votes="19">6.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">二次に本質あり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">There`s Substance in 2-D</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">2-D tem substância</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Niji ni Honshitsu Ari</title>
<summary>Konata and her father discuss the Gundam franchise, Nanako gets a little jealous of Miyuki, and Yutaka asks Hiyori about her dōjinshi.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="81247" update="2017-10-27">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-20</airdate>
<rating votes="19">5.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夏の過ごし方</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ways to Spend Summer</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Como passar o verão</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Natsu no Sugoshi Kata</title>
<summary>A study session turns into a trip to a fireworks festival where Konata and her friends run into Yutaka’s group.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="81248" update="2017-10-27">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-27</airdate>
<rating votes="19">7.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">パンドラの箱</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pandora`s Box</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">A caixa de Pandora</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Pandora no Hako</title>
<summary>The third-year girls take a trip to Kyoto to visit Kyoto Animation. Tsukasa spends some time with the local wildlife, and Kagami receives a letter from a boy!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="81249" update="2017-10-27">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-03</airdate>
<rating votes="23">8.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ここにある彼方</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Yonder Here</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Então por aqui</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koko ni Aru Kanata</title>
<summary>The spirit of Konata’s mother appears to check in on her and reminisce about the times she spent with Konata’s father.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="81250" update="2017-10-27">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-10</airdate>
<rating votes="19">7.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">微妙なライン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Delicate Line</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Um linha segura</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bimyou na Line</title>
<summary>Konata and Yutaka are both under the weather—giving Konata the perfect excuse to stay home and play video games!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="82802" update="2017-10-27">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-17</airdate>
<rating votes="21">9.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">未定</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To Be Decided</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR">Pendente</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mitei</title>
<summary>The school’s cultural festival brings all the girls together to work on a group cheer routine!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="91532" update="2014-03-20">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-06-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">名場面カット集 #01</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Scenes Cut Collection 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Meibamen Cut Shuu #01</title>
</episode>
<episode id="157983" update="2014-03-20">
<epno type="2">S12</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-05-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">名場面カット集 #12</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Scenes Cut Collection 12</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Meibamen Cut Shuu #12</title>
</episode>
<episode id="157984" update="2014-03-20">
<epno type="2">S11</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-04-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">名場面カット集 #11</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Scenes Cut Collection 11</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Meibamen Cut Shuu #11</title>
</episode>
<episode id="157985" update="2014-03-20">
<epno type="2">S10</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-03-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">名場面カット集 #10</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Scenes Cut Collection 10</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Meibamen Cut Shuu #10</title>
</episode>
<episode id="157986" update="2014-03-20">
<epno type="2">S9</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-02-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">名場面カット集 #09</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Scenes Cut Collection 9</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Meibamen Cut Shuu #09</title>
</episode>
<episode id="157987" update="2014-03-20">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-01-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">名場面カット集 #08</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Scenes Cut Collection 8</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Meibamen Cut Shuu #08</title>
</episode>
<episode id="157988" update="2014-03-20">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-12-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">名場面カット集 #07</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Scenes Cut Collection 7</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Meibamen Cut Shuu #07</title>
</episode>
<episode id="157989" update="2014-03-20">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-11-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">名場面カット集 #06</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Scenes Cut Collection 6</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Meibamen Cut Shuu #06</title>
</episode>
<episode id="157990" update="2014-03-20">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-10-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">名場面カット集 #05</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Scenes Cut Collection 5</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Meibamen Cut Shuu #05</title>
</episode>
<episode id="157991" update="2014-03-20">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-09-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">名場面カット集 #04</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Scenes Cut Collection 4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Meibamen Cut Shuu #04</title>
</episode>
<episode id="157992" update="2014-03-20">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-04-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">名場面カット集 #03</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Scenes Cut Collection 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Meibamen Cut Shuu #03</title>
</episode>
<episode id="157993" update="2014-03-20">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-07-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">名場面カット集 #02</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Scenes Cut Collection 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Meibamen Cut Shuu #02</title>
</episode>
<episode id="179339" update="2016-08-02">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">US BD Trailer</title>
<summary>FUNimation trailer for BluRay release</summary>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
