<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="5" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>10</episodecount>
<startdate>2001-07-11</startdate>
<enddate>2001-09-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Seikai no Senki II</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Banner of the Stars 2</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Battle Flag of the Stars 2</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">성계의 전기 II</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Seikai no Senki 2</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">星界的战旗2</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">BFotS2</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">BotS2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">SnS2</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">星界の戦旗II</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Banner of the Stars II</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="2673" type="Sequel">Seikai no Senki III</anime>
<anime id="4" type="Prequel">Seikai no Senki</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="5">
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="125868">You must see Seikai no Monshou and Seikai no Senki I before seeing this.  Within the series, this season has the best character development, an excellent plot, and was very moving.  This is my favorite anime.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="691547">a great continuation to a great story 
and Lafiel rocks like always :)</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.sunrise-inc.co.jp/seikai/</url>
<creators>
<name id="4891" type="Series Composition">Takeda Yuuichirou</name>
<name id="4303" type="Music">Hattori Katsuhisa</name>
<name id="4495" type="Original Work">Morioka Hiroyuki</name>
<name id="4234" type="Direction">Nagaoka Yasuchika</name>
<name id="4516" type="Character Design">Watabe Keisuke</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the Seikai no Senki sci-fi novel series by http://anidb.net/cr4495 [Morioka Hiroyuki].
The Abh star force won a decisive battle at Aptic Gate, completely breaking the counter offensive of the United Mankind fleet. Now a new operation has begun: Operation Hunter — seek and completely annihilate all of the remaining scattered fleet.
Basroil, part of 4th fleet, was sent to the Lobnas system on an escort mission. http://anidb.net/ch28 [Lafiel] and http://anidb.net/ch4081 [Jinto] were assigned to become acting governor/vice governor of the system and negotiate with the planet-side government to establish empire rule. But little did they know that that the Lobnas system is a prison planet of United Mankind and millions of prisoners are just about to start a rebellion to overwhelm the security forces detached there.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="3457">8.27</permanent>
<temporary count="3469">8.24</temporary>
<review count="4">8.99</review>
</ratings>
<picture>221217.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>448</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>39333</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>397</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>369</identifier>
<identifier>vkudpu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.sunrise-inc.co.jp/seikai/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Banner_of_the_Stars</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>星界の戦旗</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1452</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>234608</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4768</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7566</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1438" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-18">
<name>ruthless</name>
<description>This character will stop at nothing to achieve their goals and will be unbound by any constraints</description>
<picurl>214979.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1996" parentid="36" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-05-19">
<name>air force</name>
<description>An air force, also known in some countries as an air army or air corps, is in the broadest sense, the national military organization that primarily conducts aerial warfare. More specifically, it is the branch of a nation`s armed services that is responsible for aerial warfare as distinct from an army, navy or other branch. Typically, air forces are responsible for gaining control of the air, carrying out strategic-bombing missions and providing support to surface forces.
The term "air force" may also refer to a tactical air force or numbered air force, which is an operational formation within a national air force. Air forces typically consist of a combination of fighters, bombers, helicopters, transport planes and other aircraft.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2633" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>prison</name>
<description>A building used to house convicted criminals and accused persons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2636" parentid="2846" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>human enhancement</name>
<description>Human enhancement can take various forms: It can be something comparatively non-intrusive as a power-up drug, a form of machine implantation or cyberization (http://anidb.net/a4414 [SAC Solid State Society]), or outright - possibly atrocious - genetic manipulation (http://anidb.net/a361 [Ao no 6 Gou]). Plot-wise enhanced protagonists in anime usually have to pay a price for their enhancements, be it physical or mental.</description>
<picurl>223945.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2639" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space travel</name>
<description>Space Travel usually refers going to space or travelling there with or without a spacecraft. There are different forms of space travel like Interplanetary travel, Interstellar travel or Intergalactic travel. Since it isn`t possible to travel faster than light, most anime series involve some sort "sub-space travel mechanism" as a way to travel faster than light.</description>
<picurl>242375.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2660" parentid="2627" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>other planet</name>
<description>The anime will fit this category if some or all of the action takes place on another planet which is supposedly in the same universe as Earth, not a complete fantasy world; usually there has to be some concept of space travel. The Latin name for Earth - Terra, would also pass the condition of being in the same universe as Earth. Basically, even mentioning of Earth existing or having existed would be enough. Although Moon is a moon, it also qualifies as Other Planet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2661" parentid="2627" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>shipboard</name>
<description>Beam me up, Scotty! Space stations (think Death Star) also count. Basically, this category is to tell if the setting takes place onboard a spaceship in space. This category is not applicable if the spaceship lies on a planet and never actually gets into space.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2907" parentid="2636" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>genetic modification</name>
<description>Story-wise, genetic modification is usually centred on humans, probably the most subtle and creepy way of messing with mankind. Playing with the fear of the unknown, genetically altered humans are technically a new species, that may not only surpass but actually replace unaltered humans. The level of modification will vary from subtle changes in "look" (e.g. super-human beauty), to mental enhancements (PSI powers), to more or less atrocious adaptations to extreme environments (breath under water, radiation resistance). Note that changes in Aliens would be difficult to pinpoint, after all they are alien.</description>
<picurl>223941.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3138" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-08">
<name>fictional language</name>
<description>Fictional languages are intended to be the languages of a fictional world and are often designed with the intent of giving more depth and an appearance of plausibility to the fictional worlds with which they are associated, and to have their characters communicate in a fashion which is both alien and dislocated.
Some of these languages, e.g. in worlds of fantasy fiction, alternative universes, Earth`s future, or alternate history, are presented as distorted versions or dialects of modern English or other natural language, while others are independently designed conlangs.
A fictional language often has the least amount of grammar and vocabulary possible, and rarely extends beyond the absolutely necessary. At the same time, some others have developed languages in detail for their own sake, such as J. R. R. Tolkien`s Quenya and Sindarin and Star Trek`s Klingon language which exist as functioning, usable languages. Here "fictional" can be a misnomer.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3929" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-09">
<name>sociocultural evolution</name>
<description>Describes how cultures and societies develop over time, based on both cultural evolution and social evolution.
A post-apocalyptic or a Utopian setting would show very interesting changes in human behaviour, mental state, or simply daily life.</description>
<picurl>191062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3977" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-29">
<name>dialogue driven</name>
<description>A dialogue driven show has its story advanced by dialogue, with action being of much lower priority, and relies heavily on conversations between characters.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4081" parentid="2841" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space battles</name>
<description>There are space battles in this anime. Usually between Earth forces and some alien invader, but ship to ship skirmishes in deep space are just as common.</description>
<picurl>242377.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4299" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-29">
<name>flashback</name>
<description>A flashback is a moment in which someone remembers events from their past. In fiction, flashbacks are used primarily to give insight into a character`s mind or to reveal information which had been previously kept from the audience. They normally consist essentially of new content; in some cases, they may also consist of short snippets of already displayed content, as in http://anidb.net/ch23266 [Okabe Rintarou]`s flashbacks in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate], but even in these cases the flashbacks are used to look into what the character is thinking. As such, they are different from and should not be confused with recaps, which are old content being shown again for no particular purpose other than padding or reminding the audience of the events up to that point. As a rule of thumb, to qualify as a flashback, the scene must advance the show`s content in some way or form; anything else is just a recap.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4446" parentid="2639" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-12">
<name>faster-than-light travel</name>
<description>Faster-than-light travel is taken for grated in this anime. This is achieved by travelling via hyperspace, nullspace, or wormholes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4943" parentid="2633" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-10-21">
<name>prison planet</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5929" parentid="2846" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>space opera</name>
<description>Space opera is a sub-genre of fiction that emphasizes romantic adventures in space. Space opera generally involves large-scale conflicts between opponents with powerful abilities and technology. The genre will often be melodramatic, sometimes playing music that can be nothing short of awesome. Warfare and a battle of wits are usually less emphasized, preferring romance (with exceptions, e.g. Ginga Eiyuu Densetsu). Some space operas tend to be formulaic and sometimes even prosaic, often employing very simple devices and somewhat obvious strategies. An example of this would be the infamous laws of physics in the Macross universe, in which the main male lead will hardly ever get hit in battle.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="28" type="main character in" update="2012-07-25">
<rating votes="1318">9.14</rating>
<name>Abriel Nei Debrusc Borl Paryun Lafiel</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ablïarsec néïc Dubreuscr Bœrh Parhynr Lamhirh (a.k.a., Viscountess Paryunu Abriel Nei Dobrusk Lafiel) is the main female protagonist in the anime Crest of the Stars, Banner of the Stars, and Banner of the Stars II, as well as all the novels written by Morioka Hiroyuki on which the shows were based. She is a strong-willed Abh princess (granddaughter of the Abh empress) who has a steely exterior, but ends up befriending Ghintec Linn (Jinto Lynn in the Martinh tongue). Like all Abh, she has bluish hued hair, and has a natural lifespan of over 200 years. Lamhirh also has lapis lazuli colored eyes. As an Ablïarsec, she has pointed ears, yet hers are markedly less so than other Ablïarsec. This is because half her genes (those not from her father) are from someone outside the Abriel clan and her father chose not to make any unnecessary alterations in her genes. She is deemed "child of love" (an Abh child with the genes of the parent, and the one the parent loves). Her full name can be roughly translated to Lamhirh (néïc Dubleuscr) Ablïarsec, Viscountess of Parhyn.
Despite being a princess, she rarely acts like one and hates being treated as one. One of the reasons she took a liking towards Ghintec is because when they first met, he neither recognized her as a princess nor treated her as one. Their relationship is so close that she freely allows him to use her real name of Lamhirh when addressing her, something that is very uncommon when addressing those of nobility or royalty.
She acts remarkably older than her age (at her introduction in Crest of the Stars, she is 16 years old) and can, in most cases, logically think her way out of most situations. However, her headstrong nature sometimes clouds her judgement and can lead her to become impulsive. An example of this is when she is reprimanded by Laicch for wishing to stay behind on the Gothlauth instead of continuing her mission of escorting Ghintec to the capital. She believes that she would have been of more use fighting with the crew rather than abandoning them. She is quickly shown how wrong her line of reasoning is and how much more disgraceful it would have been to abandon Ghintec and her mission. She is a remarkably good shot and although she sometimes doubts herself, she proves to be a worthy ship captain (deca-commander) in Banner of the Stars. She shows little emotion throughout Crest of the Stars, but as time goes by became very close friend with Ghintec through Banner of the Stars. This is especially true in later installments, where she more frequently questions how their friendship will last due to the doubt of Ghintec`s lifespan.
She is one of the candidates for the Abh Imperial Throne and, as indicated by her full name, she is the Viscountess of Parhynh, the so-called "Country, or Nation, of Roses."</description>
<picture>14304.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12" picture="184301.jpg">Kawasumi Ayako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4079" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-28">
<rating votes="19">6.18</rating>
<name>Abriel Nei Debrusc Larth Kryb Debeus</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lafiel`s father, the King of Kryv and a son of the current reigning empress.</description>
<picture>20037.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3136" picture="24121.jpg">Suzuoki Hirotaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4081" type="main character in" update="2012-07-25">
<rating votes="217">7.63</rating>
<name>Linn Syun-Rock Dreu Haider Jinto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Born Jinto Lynn on planet Martine (spelt as Martinh in Baronh) of the Hyde star system (Haïdec in Baronh), he was the son of Rock Lynn, a politician who eventually became president of the Hyde star system. It was during his administration that the Abh empire was able to annex the Hyde stellar system into its territory through an invasion. Making his own ideas more valuable than the rights of the people of Martine, Rock Lin made a deal with the leaders of the invading forces that the territorial lord of Hyde shall be chosen amongst the people of Martine. The leader of the invading forces agreed to this however this meant that an election cannot be held making Rock, as the current leader of Martine, the natural choice to become its territorial lord. Because of this, Rock Lynn, and with him, Jinto, rose to the ranks of Abh nobility as Count of Haïdec.</description>
<picture>20036.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="362" picture="74735.jpg">Imai Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4082" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-28">
<rating votes="63">8.71</rating>
<name>Abriel Nei Lamsar Larth Balkei Dusanyu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The current Dusanyu, or Crown Prince, of the Abh Empire of Mankind, the Baronh name of which is Frybar Gloer Gor Bari (Frybarec Gloer Gor Bari), Also the Commander-in-Chief of the Abh Armed Forces, who personally led the invasion of the Hyde star system.</description>
<picture>20035.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1819" picture="20694.jpg">Shiozawa Kaneto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4083" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-28">
<rating votes="19">6.72</rating>
<name>Trife Boli Yuvdale Remsale</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Despite verging on excessive caution, he is nonetheless one of the most able tacticians in the Labule. He puts every aspect and factor under consideration, frequently asking his subordinates` opinions and assessments before starting an operation. He is also one of the least loved officers.</description>
<picture>20034.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="220" picture="17038.jpg">Kosugi Juurouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4084" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-28">
<rating votes="253">8.98</rating>
<name>Spoor Aron Sekpadao Letopanyu Peneju</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>This red-eyed Grand Duchess is one of the most eccentric officers in the Labule, which does not change the fact that she is one of its most able admirals. Though complaining of boredom most of the time, she suddenly springs into action when needed. One of her favourite pastimes is mercilessly teasing Kaselia, her chief of staff.</description>
<picture>20033.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1509" picture="19311.jpg">Fukami Rika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4089" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-28">
<rating votes="52">7.13</rating>
<name>Ekuryua Wef Tryuz Noel</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>20049.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="56" picture="16651.jpg">Shimizu Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4090" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-28">
<rating votes="7">5.46</rating>
<name>Sobaash Weh Dowl Yuse</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>20050.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="180" picture="171567.jpg">Saiga Mitsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4091" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-28">
<rating votes="18">6.34</rating>
<name>Samson Bolge Tilsal Tiluse</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>20051.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="286" picture="17117.jpg">Ootsuka Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4093" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-28">
<rating votes="7">7.11</rating>
<name>Kufadis Wef Espiel Sespy</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>20053.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="375" picture="17221.jpg">Chiba Susumu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4094" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-28">
<rating votes="12">5.95</rating>
<name>Keneeshu Wef Stumal Kipeil</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>20054.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4770" picture="76766.jpg">Suzuka Chiharu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4095" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-28">
<rating votes="13">3.80</rating>
<name>Bebaus Alon Nerem Nereis</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>20055.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="189" picture="203306.jpg">Inoue Kazuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4096" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-28">
<rating votes="13">4.00</rating>
<name>Bebaus Alon Nerem Nefee</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>20056.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="189" picture="203306.jpg">Inoue Kazuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7514" type="appears in" update="2009-05-27">
<rating votes="12">8.23</rating>
<name>Abh Teikoku</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>26171.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="40209" type="appears in" update="2012-01-04">
<rating votes="15">5.38</rating>
<name>Diaho</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jinto`s cat.

Lafiel gave him to Jinto at the end of http://anidb.net/a1 [Seikai no Monshou].
He is the son of Zanelia who is the daughter of Holia.
</description>
<picture>79471.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="46949" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-07-18">
<rating votes="3">7.06</rating>
<name>Geol Meideen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91095.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="409" picture="24867.jpg">Arimoto Kinryuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="66420" type="appears in" update="2014-04-09">
<rating votes="1">5.68</rating>
<name>Basroil</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>153272.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="45" update="2005-12-30">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-07-11</airdate>
<rating votes="13">5.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">狩人作戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Operation Hunter</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Karyuudo Sakusen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="46" update="2005-12-30">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-07-18</airdate>
<rating votes="12">6.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">流刑の星</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Planet of Exile</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ryuukei no Hoshi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="47" update="2005-12-30">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-07-25</airdate>
<rating votes="10">7.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">移民計画</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Emigration Plan</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Imin Keikaku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48" update="2005-12-30">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-08-01</airdate>
<rating votes="11">5.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">狩人たち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Hunters</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Karyuudo-tachi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="49" update="2005-05-19">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-08-08</airdate>
<rating votes="10">7.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">叛乱</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rebellion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hanran</title>
</episode>
<episode id="50" update="2005-05-19">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-08-15</airdate>
<rating votes="13">8.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アーヴの地獄</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Abh Hell</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Abh no Jigoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="51" update="2005-05-19">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-08-29</airdate>
<rating votes="12">7.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">金色鳥(ガサルス)の旗</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Flag of Gasarus</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gatharsr no Hata</title>
</episode>
<episode id="52" update="2005-05-19">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-09-12</airdate>
<rating votes="10">8.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">守るべきもの</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Things to Protect</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mamoru Beki Mono</title>
</episode>
<episode id="53" update="2005-05-19">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-09-21</airdate>
<rating votes="10">7.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">弓を置くとき</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To Lay Down the Bow</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yumi o Oku Toki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="54" update="2005-05-19">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2001-09-26</airdate>
<rating votes="16">9.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アブリアルの涙</title>
<title xml:lang="en">An Abriel`s Tears</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Abriel no Namida</title>
</episode>
<episode id="48664" update="2010-09-11">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2001-07-11</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120770" update="2010-09-11">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2001-07-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="163129" update="2014-10-06">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>135</length>
<airdate>2005-07-22</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">星界の戦旗II 特別篇</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Banner of the Stars II Movie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seikai no Senki II Tokubetsu Hen</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
