<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="575" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2003-04-08</startdate>
<enddate>2003-07-08</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Kino no Tabi: The Beautiful World</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Kinos Journey</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Kino`s Travels: The Beautiful World</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="synonym">Viaje de Kino: El Maravilloso Mundo</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Странствия Кино</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Путешествие Кино - прекрасный мир</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Прекрасный мир кинопутешествия</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="synonym">Podróż Kino</title>
<title xml:lang="sv" type="synonym">Kino no tabi</title>
<title xml:lang="tr" type="synonym">Kino`nun Seyahati: Güzel Dünya</title>
<title xml:lang="ro" type="synonym">Călătoria lui Kino: Lumea frumoasă</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Пътуването на Кино - Прекрасният Свят</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Подорож Кіно ~Прекрасний світ~</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">Kino`s Journey</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">kino</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Kino no tabi</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">キノの旅 -the Beautiful World-</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Kino`s Journey: The Beautiful World</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Kino`s Journey</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">L`Odyssée de Kino</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">키노의 여행: The Beautiful Woirld</title>
<title xml:lang="sv" type="official">Kinos resa</title>
<title xml:lang="fi" type="official">Kino`s Journey</title>
<title xml:lang="he" type="official">המסע של קינו</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">奇诺之旅</title>
<title xml:lang="fa" type="official">سفرهای کینو: دنیای زیبا</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="12959" type="Alternative Setting">Kino no Tabi: The Beautiful World - The Animated Series</anime>
<anime id="2651" type="Side Story">Kino no Tabi: Nanika o Suru Tame ni - Life Goes On.</anime>
<anime id="4939" type="Side Story">Kino no Tabi: The Beautiful World - Byouki no Kuni - For You</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="3433" approval="178" total="206">Mushishi</anime>
<anime id="271" approval="85" total="124">Haibane Renmei</anime>
<anime id="13256" approval="39" total="47">Shoujo Shuumatsu Ryokou</anime>
<anime id="3464" approval="26" total="31">Aru Tabibito no Nikki</anime>
<anime id="9482" approval="25" total="34">Kamisama no Inai Nichiyoubi</anime>
<anime id="15202" approval="16" total="22">Majo no Tabitabi</anime>
<anime id="5406" approval="8" total="17">Ookami to Koushinryou</anime>
<anime id="6032" approval="8" total="14">Casshern Sins</anime>
<anime id="99" approval="6" total="19">Serial Experiments Lain</anime>
<anime id="5549" approval="6" total="13">Shigofumi</anime>
<anime id="12136" approval="5" total="15">ACCA 13-ku Kansatsu-ka</anime>
<anime id="5569" approval="4" total="12">Allison to Lillia</anime>
<anime id="555" approval="4" total="9">Ou Dorobou Jing</anime>
<anime id="12138" approval="2" total="9">Violet Evergarden</anime>
<anime id="1553" approval="2" total="7">Hi no Tori</anime>
<anime id="5588" approval="2" total="3">A Piece of Phantasmagoria</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="24">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="311540">An absolute gem of a series...  If you`re after something with travel, personal development, action, beauty, sociology, psychology, comedy and trust - yes, all these things - then join Kino on her travels for a wholly wonderful experience.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="290127">Nifty stories</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="503983">If you are a fan of world-building, you must watch this anime. They introduce different countries and exaggerate a certain aspect/problem which occur in real countries nowadays. This provokes the main characters` thoughts, which leads to interesting conversations.

If you`re not a fan, this probably won`t appeal to you as much as it did to me. It has no over-arching story. There is almost no character development. The visuals are bad for today`s standard (good for 2003 probably).</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="183228">Entrancing</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="553695">Really good anime about an introvert child who travels to different countries and learns about their history. Let`s not forget Kino`s talking bike, Hermes.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="396387">I`m not skilled in writing review or similar things, even just a comment.
Fortunately this anime does not require any writing skill to pass concepts, suggestions and so on. 
It is my opinion that there is not one single person in this world who will not apreciate this.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="255852">Fantastic series</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="180200">Great series of little stories about a boy and his bike Hermes traveling together around a worls made of diferent countries with diferent cultures and traditions and how people relate to one another based on their background. Must watch!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="475674">i watched about more than 60 animes... but this one ,is completely different it has a very deep view of humanity and various issues of people`s psychology i have no comment to describe the MAGNIFICENCE this anime has ...it worths every second of ur time...its my num1 anime so far... :)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="526839">Screw ecchi and all that pointless action crap. This anime is a MUST SEE becaue it has soo much depth and thought in it. Really makes you reflect on life and society as you travel with kino on this exciting adventure. Just watch one or two a day, it`s all you need. Don`t expect some defined plot with an obvious goal, get ready for some serious and moving stuff</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="420391">One of my favorites.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="507844">I thought I figured out everything about humanity. Well... I was wrong.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="460147">Best philosophy anime out there, so deep you can`t resist. If animes were meals, I`d consider Kino no Tabi as the perfect breakfast. I would recommend this to people that have prejudice over anime and their minds would certainly being blown away.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="410747">Series are interesting, unusual and character is among my favourite anime characters.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.kinonotabi.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="4184" type="Direction">Nakamura Ryuutarou</name>
<name id="6575" type="Character Design">Suga Shigeyuki</name>
<name id="769" type="Animation Work">ACGT</name>
<name id="5617" type="Original Work">Shigusawa Keiichi</name>
<name id="5132" type="Music">Sakai Ryou</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a light novel series by http://anidb.net/cr5617 [Shigusawa Keiichi].
Composed in the form of a series of short stories, this is the story of the travels and observations of the human Kino and the talking motorbike Hermes. http://anidb.net/ch7856 [Kino] and http://anidb.net/ch7857 [Hermes] visit various fantastic countries - a country that can`t coexist with others due to the development of telepathy (thus, a country that understands people`s pain); a country striving to make everything equal, whose residents are extremely united (i.e., ruled by majority); and so on.
Small ripples are formed in the everyday lives of the people living in the various countries by the appearances of the unusual Kino. These ripples gradually become a major influence, rattling the foundations of their normal lives.
What will Kino and Hermes see in their travels? And what will be left in the hearts and minds of the people they encounter?
Source: AnimeNfo, edited by 5plada0</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="4827">8.58</permanent>
<temporary count="4860">8.32</temporary>
<review count="9">7.72</review>
</ratings>
<picture>238807.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1965</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>486</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1152</identifier>
<identifier>xgqirs</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.kinonotabi.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Kino's_Journey</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>キノの旅</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>434</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>240374</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5981</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5710</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="34">
<externalentity>
<url>https://www.hidive.com/tv/kinos-journey</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1637" parentid="2565" weight="200" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-09">
<name>reverse trap</name>
<description>A reverse trap is a plot device where a female character is mistaken for a male, with the intention of sexually deceiving other characters and/or the viewer. This behavior does not need to be intentional by the female (it is often not intentional) or continually maintained by the female, but the occurrence is common enough to deserve this fetish-specific tag.
This is often achieved by portraying the female character as a male; primarily via their clothing and physical appearance, but also through her behaviour, and/or language. A female character misinterpreted by others as male, without action from the female (explicitly masculine dress or behaviour), is generally not considered a reverse trap; instead they are likely just http://anidb.net/t2561 [androgynous].
The reverse case is known as a http://anidb.net/t618 [trap].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2090" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-17">
<name>trauma</name>
<description>Character with emotional or psychological injury, caused by single or multiple events/experiences in the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2565" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-14">
<name>cross-dressing</name>
<description>This character sometimes wears clothes traditionally worn by and associated with the opposite sex.
Cross-dressers often hide their cross-dressing identity for a long period of time and thus tend to become adept in accurately portraying the opposite sex in terms of voice, movement, behaviour, temperament, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2641" parentid="2625" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>historical</name>
<description>Historical anime have clear ties to our history and usually occur in a particular epoch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2656" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>satire</name>
<description>In satire, vices, follies, abuses, and shortcomings are held up to ridicule, ideally with the intent of shaming individuals, and society itself, into improvement. Although satire is usually meant to be funny, its greater purpose is often constructive social criticism, using wit as a weapon. (Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2689" parentid="2641" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-02">
<name>1920s</name>
<description>During the 1920s, we had gangsters, Mafia, alcohol, and gambling prohibition.
The Corleones ruled that time.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2851" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>horror</name>
<description>The horror cinematic genre is characterized by the attempt to make the viewer experience dread, fear, terror, or horror. Often their plots involve the intrusion of an evil force, event or personage, sometimes of supernatural origin, on the mundane world and the consequences thereof.</description>
<picurl>214682.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2857" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-10-04">
<name>anthropomorphism</name>
<description>Anthropomorphism is the attribution of uniquely human characteristics to non-human beings, inanimate objects, or natural or supernatural phenomena. If it`s an animal or an object (AI excluded) and it speaks and/or does other human-like things (dresses up) then we`re dealing with anthropomorphism.
Anthropomorphism leans more on the animal-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t7 [juujin], which leans more on the human-looking side.
Usage the tag image for reference, when tagging characters:

* This is a juujin.
* This is split between juujin and anthropomorphism, to be decided on a case-by-case basis, but most likely leans on the human-looking juujin side in most cases.
* This is anthropomorphism; tag both anthropomorphism and the respective animal type.
* This is anthropomorphism; tag both anthropomorphism and the respective animal type.
* This is just a regular animal; do not tag juujin or anthropomorphism — only tag the actual animal type.
</description>
<picurl>252666.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2866" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>slavery</name>
<description>Someone is owned by somebody else. In anime this usually affects body (slaves in a fantasy setting) or mind (the evil villain brainwashes a sidekick, creates an obedient minion or places a spell on some poor bloke). Slavery is also a common element of hentai.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2867" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>politics</name>
<description>From commies to fat capitalist pigs, all the stuff done by the "guys with the power", mainly evil tactics for gaining more power over the masses.
Watching this title may remind you why CNN is boring.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2870" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-17">
<name>steampunk</name>
<description>Steampunk is a sub-genre of science fiction that typically features steam-powered machinery, especially in a setting inspired by industrialized Western civilization during the 19th century. Steampunk works are often set in an alternative history of the 19th century`s British Victorian era or American "Wild West", in a post-apocalyptic future during which steam power has regained mainstream use, or in a fantasy world that similarly employs steam power.
Noteworthy attributes of the theme include large amounts smoke pollution from wood or coal burning, the affinity to metal constructs like cogs and metal tubing, and the mechanization of everyday objects.
Steampunk perhaps most recognisably features anachronistic technologies or retro-futuristic inventions as people in the 19th century might have envisioned them, and is likewise rooted in the era`s perspective on fashion, culture, architectural style, and art.
Such technology may include fictional machines like those found in the works of H. G. Wells and Jules Verne, or the modern authors Philip Pullman, Scott Westerfeld, Stephen Hunt and China Miéville. Other examples of steampunk contain alternative history-style presentations of such technology as lighter-than-air airships, analog computers, or such digital mechanical computers as Charles Babbage`s Analytical Engine.
Steampunk can also exemplify everything that is bad about unrestrained technological progress (dead matter), when compared to life and nature. The anime usually makes a point to propound the latter.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162830.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2876" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>religion</name>
<description>Religion is a collection of belief systems, cultural systems, and worldviews that relate humanity to spirituality and, sometimes, to moral values. Many religions have narratives, symbols, traditions and sacred histories that are intended to give meaning to life or to explain the origin of life or the universe. They tend to derive morality, ethics, religious laws or a preferred lifestyle from their ideas about the cosmos and human nature.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2882" parentid="2952" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-17">
<name>dystopia</name>
<description>A dystopia (from Ancient Greek: δυσ-, "bad, ill", and Ancient Greek: τόπος, "place, landscape"; alternatively cacotopia, or anti-utopia) is, in literature, an often futuristic society that has degraded into a repressive and controlled state, often under the guise of being utopian. Dystopian literature has underlying cautionary tones, warning society that if we continue to live how we do, this will be the consequence. A dystopia, thus, is regarded as a sort of negative utopia and is often characterized by an authoritarian or totalitarian form of government. Dystopias usually feature different kinds of repressive social control systems, a lack or total absence of individual freedoms and expressions and constant states of warfare or violence. Dystopias often explore the concept of humans abusing technology and how humans individually and collectively cope with technology that has evolved too quickly such as the car, the flamethrower or the microwave. A dystopian society is also often characterized by widespread poverty and brutal political controls such as a large military-like police.</description>
<picurl>69879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2952" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-06">
<name>rotten world</name>
<description>A rotten world is a setting or situation where the jaded notion that "anything that can go wrong will go horribly wrong" almost always applies. Oppression, perpetual warfare, lawlessness, despair or other forms of mental instability, and other highly undesirable factors tend to be rampant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3285" parentid="2850" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true">
<name>journey</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3369" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-06-23">
<name>human psyche</name>
<description>How that grey mass inside the skulls of us earthlings works.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3815" parentid="2851" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-10-04">
<name>human cannibalism</name>
<description>Cannibalism is the practice of an individual of a species eating parts or the whole of another individual of the same species; as such, human cannibalism is when a human eats the flesh, organs, or other parts of another human being. Human cannibalism is not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t3435 [eating of humans]; the former is about humans eating fellow humans, while the latter is about other species eating people.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3929" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-09">
<name>sociocultural evolution</name>
<description>Describes how cultures and societies develop over time, based on both cultural evolution and social evolution.
A post-apocalyptic or a Utopian setting would show very interesting changes in human behaviour, mental state, or simply daily life.</description>
<picurl>191062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3992" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-08-17">
<name>nostalgia</name>
<description>A bitter-sweet longing for things, persons, or situations from the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4021" parentid="36" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-08">
<name>evil military</name>
<description>The military is depicted as being of a nefarious nature in this anime. Be it through the heartlessness that their soldiers convey, or the ruthless killing of innocents, the military in this anime is not to be messed with.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4203" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>rebellion</name>
<description>Rebellion, uprising, or insurrection is a refusal of obedience or order. It may, therefore, be seen as encompassing a range of behaviors aimed at destroying or taking over the position of an established authority such as a government, governor, president, political leader, financial institution, or person in charge. On the one hand the forms of behaviour can include non-violent methods such as the (overlapping but not quite identical) phenomena of civil disobedience, civil resistance and nonviolent resistance. On the other hand it may encompass violent campaigns. Those who participate in rebellions, especially if they are armed rebellions, are known as "rebels".&#13;
&#13;
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>163803.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4257" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-08-07">
<name>survival</name>
<description>The theme/genre of survival typically depicts the act or process of continuing to live, generally in a hostile, possibly post-apocalyptic environment. Survival-centered media tends to be dark, set most commonly in a contemporary context, and generally leads either to small groups of people forming closely knit and functional units or to individuals turning against their fellows in a return to the survival of the fittest.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4314" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-04-11">
<name>psychological</name>
<description>Directed toward dealing with or affecting the mind, especially as a function of awareness, feeling, or motivation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4340" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-09-26">
<name>suicide</name>
<description>One or several characters in this anime commit suicide.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4520" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>betrayal</name>
<description>Friends become enemies.
Strong bonds of trust receive violations of confidence while friendships are faithlessly given up or revealed to have been false from the start.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4522" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>social commentary</name>
<description>Social commentary is the act of rebelling against an individual, or a group of people by rhetorical means. This is most often done with the idea of implementing or promoting change by informing the general populace about a given problem and appealing to people’s sense of justice. (Source: Wikipedia)&#13;
&#13;
Since this is anime, usually, the mores of Japan and the Japanese society are scrutinised, but not restricted to that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4614" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>narration</name>
<description>The most common example is that of a voice, either that of one of the characters or entirely unrelated, that appears at the beginning of an episode to offer a summary or introduction, and at the end of an episode for closure or for a preview to hint upon what to expect next.
Another use of narration comes in the form of a dominant voice belonging to one of the protagonists, intended only for the viewer and revealing the intimate thoughts to whom it belongs. This type of narration occurs frequently throughout the duration of the episode or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5104" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-11-22">
<name>vignetted picture</name>
<description>In photography and optics, vignetting is a reduction of an image brightness or saturation at the periphery compared to the image center, usually caused by faulty optics.
Although vignetting is normally unintended and undesired, it is sometimes purposely introduced for example in comics, animation or video games as a creative, false camera effect, such as to draw attention to the center of the screen.</description>
<picurl>43292.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6399" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-25">
<name>episodic</name>
<description>An episodic anime consists of many successive short arcs that are generally 1-2 episodes in length, with strong plot continuity within each arc but generally little continuity from one arc to the next. For long shows (well upwards of 50 episodes), the episode count constraint is less tight; for example, a show with close to 250 episodes would also be considered episodic if it consisted of a majority of arcs of up to 3 or maybe 4 episodes and possibly also very few slightly longer arcs.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6972" parentid="2874" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-11-07">
<name>volcanic eruption</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="7856" type="main character in" update="2017-10-07">
<rating votes="256">8.97</rating>
<name>Kino</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kino is sort of a valiant stoic cipher almost like a seinen hero. Kino comes off as androgynous and is considered male as often as female by the people she meets. Kino never talks much and never unnecessarily. She will lend a hand to someone in need and even risk her life for another but she does not purposely get involved in the affairs of others. Kino is often cynical and skeptical but you get the feeling deep down she still believes in people and the world. If Kino has one strong driving force and personality trait it seems to be curiosity. She will always investigate something if it seems intriguing and is sometimes the only reason she will interact with anyone.
Source: Reverse Thieves</description>
<picture>187645.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1661" picture="19751.jpg">Maeda Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7857" type="main character in" update="2017-10-07">
<rating votes="53">6.57</rating>
<name>Hermes</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>Hermes is a talking Brough Superior motorcycle and is Kino`s loyal companion; although it can be reluctant sometimes, it faithfully accompanies Kino through all their travels. The relationship between Kino and Hermes is presented as symbiotic — as explained in the Land of Adults where Hermes provides speed, and Kino provides balance. In the first couple of episodes of the anime and almost all of the chapter in the novels, it has a tendency to mispronounce words and phrases. Its name is a reference to the Greek god Hermes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>187646.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4589" picture="36949.jpg">Aigase Ryuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="52973" type="appears in" update="2017-11-04">
<rating votes="5">6.98</rating>
<name>Riku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Riku is a talking dog who travels with http://anidb.net/ch82564 [Shizu]. He is large, white, and his face seems to be always smiling.</description>
<picture>209248.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="297" picture="233915.jpg">Ootsuka Houchuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82564" type="appears in" update="2017-11-26">
<rating votes="1">5.66</rating>
<name>Shizu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shizu is a young man with a great talent for swordsmanship. He travels in a dune buggy with http://anidb.net/ch52973 [Riku], his talking dog companion.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>187662.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17479" picture="47647.jpg">Irie Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82565" type="appears in" update="2016-06-15">
<rating votes="1">7.62</rating>
<name>Sakura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sakura is a girl from the country Kino visited in the last episode of the anime series. She shares many similarities to Kino, such as her parents also owning an inn.
[Taken from Wikipedia.]</description>
<picture>187666.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42112" picture="80617.jpg">Yabusaki Aoi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82567" type="appears in" update="2016-06-15">
<rating votes="3">9.24</rating>
<name>Kino</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Young man with glasses and a calm demeanor who traveled by the same three-day rule that the main character Kino does. He arrived to the Land of Adults and was most likely the reason why the main character goes on her journey after he dies protecting her from the customs of her country.
[Edited from Wikipedia.]</description>
<picture>187667.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="189" picture="203306.jpg">Inoue Kazuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="7588" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-04-08</airdate>
<rating votes="31">5.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">人の痛みがわかる国</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Land of Visible Pain</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Land des sichtbaren Schmerzes</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le pays où l`on comprend la douleur des autres</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">남의 아픔을 아는 나라</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hito no Itami ga Wakaru Kuni</title>
</episode>
<episode id="7610" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-04-15</airdate>
<rating votes="29">9.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">人を喰った話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Tale of Feeding Off Others</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Vom Fressen und Gefressen werden</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une histoire culinaire</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">인간을 먹은 이야기</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hito o Kutta Hanashi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="8122" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-04-22</airdate>
<rating votes="30">7.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">予言の国</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Land of Prophecies</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Land der Prophezeiungen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le pays de la prophétie</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">예언의 나라</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yogen no Kuni</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13103" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-05-06</airdate>
<rating votes="32">9.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大人の国</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Land of Adults</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Land der Erwachsenen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le pays des adultes</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">어른의 나라</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Otona no Kuni</title>
</episode>
<episode id="13478" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-05-13</airdate>
<rating votes="30">8.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">レールの上の三人の男</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Three Men Along the Rails</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Auf den Schienen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le pays où l`on n`a pas à travailler</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">레일 위의 세 남자</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rail no Ue no Sannin no Otoko</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14486" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-05-20</airdate>
<rating votes="24">7.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">コロシアム (前編)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Coliseum Part 1</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Kollosseum (Teil 1)</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Colisée - Premier volet</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">콜로세움(전편)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Colosseum (Zenpen)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="14551" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-05-27</airdate>
<rating votes="24">7.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">コロシアム (後編)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Coliseum Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Kollosseum (Teil 2)</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Colisée - Second volet</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">콜로세움(후편)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Colosseum (Kouhen)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="15621" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-06-03</airdate>
<rating votes="22">7.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">魔法使いの国</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Land of Wizards</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Land der Magier</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le pays des magiciens</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">마법사의 나라</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mahoutsukai no Kuni</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18090" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-06-10</airdate>
<rating votes="22">7.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">本の国</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Land of Books</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Land der Bücher</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le pays des livres</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">책의 나라</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hon no Kuni</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18148" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-06-17</airdate>
<rating votes="21">8.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">機械人形の話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Tale of Mechanical Dolls</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Puppenhaus</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`histoire des poupées mécaniques</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">기계인형 이야기</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kikai Ningyou no Hanashi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19894" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-07-01</airdate>
<rating votes="22">7.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">平和な国</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Peaceful Land</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ein friedliebendes Land</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un pays en paix</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">평화로운 나라</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Heiwa na Kuni</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19895" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-06-24</airdate>
<rating votes="20">7.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">彼女の旅</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Her Journey</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ihre Reise</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Son odyssée</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">그녀의 여행</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanojo no Tabi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="19896" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2003-07-08</airdate>
<rating votes="24">9.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">優しい国</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Kind Land</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ein gastfreundliches Land</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un pays accueillant</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">친절한 나라</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yasashii Kuni</title>
</episode>
<episode id="21328" update="2012-03-29">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD 1 Production Sketches</title>
</episode>
<episode id="21329" update="2012-03-29">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD 2 Production Sketches</title>
</episode>
<episode id="21330" update="2012-03-29">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD 3 Production Sketches</title>
</episode>
<episode id="21331" update="2012-03-29">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD 4 Production Sketches</title>
</episode>
<episode id="67458" update="2007-02-15">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Prologue</title>
</episode>
<episode id="167869" update="2015-04-12">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="167870" update="2015-04-12">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
