<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="5909" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>25</episodecount>
<startdate>2008-10-02</startdate>
<enddate>2009-03-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Toradora!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Tiger x Dragon</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">ТораДора!</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Тигр против Дракона!</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Тигър срещу Дракон!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">toradora</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">龙虎斗</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">龙与虎</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">虎X龙</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">TxD</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">とらドラ!</title>
<title xml:lang="zh" type="official">TIGER x DRAGON!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Toradora!</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Toradora!</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">토라도라!</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">โทระโดระ: ยัยเสือใสกับนายหน้าโหด!</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="official">TIGER×DRAGON！</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA" type="official">Toradora</title>
<title xml:lang="fa" type="official">ببر و اژدها</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="5053" approval="160" total="225">Lovely Complex</anime>
<anime id="4146" approval="156" total="279">Zero no Tsukaima</anime>
<anime id="9153" approval="82" total="133">Sakura-sou no Pet na Kanojo</anime>
<anime id="2165" approval="41" total="91">School Rumble</anime>
<anime id="6466" approval="29" total="104">Kimi ni Todoke</anime>
<anime id="9771" approval="24" total="45">Golden Time</anime>
<anime id="3408" approval="22" total="55">Shakugan no Shana</anime>
<anime id="7008" approval="15" total="35">Kaichou wa Maid-sama!</anime>
<anime id="8620" approval="15" total="35">Ano Natsu de Matteru</anime>
<anime id="6323" approval="11" total="25">Hatsukoi Limited</anime>
<anime id="6025" approval="10" total="30">Akane-iro ni Somaru Saka</anime>
<anime id="6780" approval="9" total="29">Working!!</anime>
<anime id="9235" approval="9" total="18">Tonari no Kaibutsu-kun</anime>
<anime id="6327" approval="7" total="70">Bakemonogatari</anime>
<anime id="6424" approval="5" total="34">Cross Game</anime>
<anime id="6757" approval="5" total="22">Shakugan no Shana S</anime>
<anime id="7381" approval="5" total="16">Ookami-san to Shichinin no Nakama-tachi</anime>
<anime id="11998" approval="3" total="26">Kuzu no Honkai</anime>
<anime id="4309" approval="3" total="21">Minami-ke</anime>
<anime id="8883" approval="3" total="18">Chuunibyou demo Koi ga Shitai!</anime>
<anime id="10110" approval="3" total="13">Mikakunin de Shinkoukei</anime>
<anime id="8742" approval="2" total="18">Kokoro Connect</anime>
<anime id="6398" approval="2" total="11">Sora no Manimani</anime>
<anime id="14512" approval="1" total="9">Araburu Kisetsu no Otome-domo yo.</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="114">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="583710">This is one of the best romance-comedies I`ve ever watched. I completely love this anime.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="81741">Pretty cool and entertaining show with fun characters. Definitely recommended :)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="353622">Everithing is well balanced during the first half (comedy, drama and brave moment). The second half is somewhat more serious with some gags. Anyways, it`s a great one here.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="329665">school, romance... everything as usual, but i like it...</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="331409">its abselutly saiko</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="298716">One of the best romantic comedies I`ve EVER seen.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I loved it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="226266">For those who crave for drama with unique comedy~ ToraDora is a must!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="179020">this is one to watch</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="38868">A must watch for anyone fans of romatic comedy anime, it has just about the right amount of everything you want in an anime.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="334337">I really enjoyed the whole series. The characters, the humor, the drama - it`s all spot on.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="208937">one of best anime nice start and end !! no open ending :-)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="100670">Maybe the best school love story evar.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="178631">I longed for some good comedy-romance like this one for quite a time. Watch it</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="269123">Relly nice and good anime!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="198490">an nice comedy, school life, romance anime!!!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="293766">Toradora is a prime example of the whole "The Life and Times of" with a romantic twist. It has a very modern high school setting.  Good character descriptions, great character development. Loads of drama and comedy. Everything you could ever ask for in a romantic series. Very beautiful story. I highly recommend it  if you`re a romanticist like myself =)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="313575">Great romance comedy series. Lots of fun moments. Very interesting development.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="488989">Best school romance anime yet(IMO) animation and sound are also very good, not to mention the characters are extremely cute.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="508260">While I initially overlooked this show based on the frequent image of Taiga looking rather generic and Tsundere, and even the first few episodes gave me that impression, I soon found that the show was deeper than it appeared.  What was slow to develop turned out to be one of the stronger and more emotional love stories I`ve seen in the Anime medium.  My advice is, watch up to episode 5 before you make a judgement, because the show becomes quite powerful after that.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="473284">An exciting love polygon drama, that`s pretty humorous. To be honest, the plot didn`t seem that great, but the characters are well developed, and their are some points where the plot spectacularly makes up for its short comings during other parts. In short, if you like love polygons and drama, a good show for you.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="527292">Its great simply great heartwarming and all, story still gets me and the characters are so unique this is a different style of romance comedy then normal. So if your a big fan of the genre then you should be watching it soon... very soon</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="536061">Chances are, if you`ve watched enough romantic comedies or even enough anime, you`ve heard of this one. I am getting kind of sick to death of the tsundere trope, but this was the anime that got the archetype very very right. If other series used the archetype so well, I might not mind it`s ubiquity so much.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="366429">If you like tsunderes, character development and romance look no further - this is the anime for you!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="332605">A serious romance with a light and bright spirit.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="373896">I liked this series a lot. I have nothing to complain about EXCEPT the ending. It`s just my personal preference and maybe it`s because I`ve read too many shoujo mangas and seen too many romance anime. But I`m getting kinda sick of these endings. I don`t wannna spoil anything though.
But seriously, other than that, it was very good. I liked how they showed different sides of the characters. And how it all developed.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="532954">One of the best romance stories out there!! with enough funny moments to please you</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="512828">Now this is pure hilariousism. To me at least, Taiga is basically tsundere goddess or should i say Kugimiya Rie is... Nonetheless, this show is heart warming in each episode. Gives a twist and voila things changed from "wanting to be..." to "what had happen was....". 

I really enjoyed this show and you might too.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="442226">It is a nice show, I liked it even though I`m not exactly into romance and stuff. But it was good. There were some parts where I just wanted to get in the screen and slap the characters, but in the end it was worth the watch I believe.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="740286">Must see for anyone who watches anime. Funny, fluent, engaging, likable real characters, good story, real emotions, good comedy.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="298465">Good romance.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="211121">Funny, enjoyable, decent story for this type of anime.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="303583">love this xD</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="31560">Great drama.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="355563">Absolutely my favorite anime yet! Must see, will bring tears to your eyes in the final episodes.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="354864">A masterpiece that everyone watching anime should see. An emotional roller coaster with love friendship and comedy. Great voice actors that fits the characters perfectly.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="285600">I was pleasantly surprised with this series. I took a chance on it and wound up watching it all in a three day span.  It is a nice mix of romantic comedy with drama and a bit of slapstick thrown in for good measure. The character development was wonderful and even though I don`t like many high school themed shows, I found myself wishing this one wouldn`t end. :)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="272780">Magnificent, last couple of episodes will give you a thrill.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="188990">One of the best of the genre, it has good flow of the story, it`s not unnecessary annoying, the finish is very cute.
If you`re fan of highschool romance it`s must see. And even if you aren`t then it`s highly recommended.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="364344">Simply put, if you like anime that is more than violence/flashy lights, watch this.

If you have any sense of romance and deep character development, watch this.

If not, watch this anyway.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="453465">This is the best anime I have ever watched. Seriously, get your hands on it as soon as possible without hesitation. The series will leave you wanting more of which, unfortunately, there is none. This anime is in desperate need of a 2nd season but it looks like that will never come.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="178645">Go Go  tiger. Masterpiece.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="450633">It`s been over 5 years since I`ve seen this but... I just can`t get it out of my head. This is easily in my top 3 anime of all time, and #1 in the romance category.
If you (like me) like real character development, and a relationship that blossoms in unexpected ways, and a plot that doesn`t veer off randomly or resort to cheap tricks, AND a show where the main characters are both actually likeable, AND well-placed comedy...
Let`s put it this way: as a man, I thought romance was for sappy people and exclusively for girls, but since watching this, I have spent the last 5 years desperately searching for a show of its equal, in vain.
Watch it. Now.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="456383">One of the best romantic stories ever. Awesome characters and twists in the story. Taiga is one of the best tsundere characters too and Ami its extremely interesting. It`s a must watch for every anime fan specially if you like romantic stories. I recommend that you free your schedule before playing episode 1 because you wont be able to stop watching until you finish it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="455302">this is a must watch! this is one of the best high school drama with gr8 love story, romance and sweet cute friends sacrificing for each other`s sake. really good ending too. A very sweet anime ! loved it! watch it, and u`ll never forget!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="525522">This is one of those shows that almost everyone knows about and talks about. I was kind of slow to get to the party, but better late than never. I got hooked with the first episode. This is anime is definitely going down on my favorite list. Its hilarious and ridiculous throughout, but it has those "feels." I sat thru most of the series tonight(pulled an all-nighter). I`m glad I did. Some of what happened in the show was expected plot wise, but Taiga and Ryuuji`s interactions were great. I don`t often seriously laugh while watching anime, but this one got me going on more than one occasion. I know some people don`t like the ending, and I thought it could have been better. But, I`m glad it ended the way it did. If you want a romance series that stands out from all the others, then check this one out.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="738331">Too good to ignore!
Fun and very satisfying.
Great ending that makes you wonder why there wasn`t a second season.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="770700">If you want a RomCom with loveable characters,  good plot and several scenes that can only be described as precious then this is for you!
Toradora is an anime classic and perfect for people just starting to get into RomComs. 
Lots of moments that are super emotional when it comes down to it. 
Something you should definitely watch.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="270436">One of the best, most unique school setting love stories that I`ve ever seen.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="657678">This is a unique story about love and friendship, how those too can conflict with one another and the results of valuing one over the other. It`s also about self discovery and acceptance of oneself, it will make you laugh and cry.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="116224">it`s a romance, if you like those then this is for you&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;even if you don`t you might wanna try it out</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="81496">The series is great and full of laughs</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="422749">Simply the best.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="366427">Great story, absolutely outstanding character design and character and story development.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="134325">It has renewed my faith in the high school drama genre.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="344241">Toradora is like Karate Kid. Don`t expect to much of it, don`t get hyped by comments or higher ratings. Just watch with a smile on your face and you`ll love it!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="302924">One of the best</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="347444">Most amazing drama/romance series I`ve ever seen, and one of my all-time favorites. Brilliant.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="192240">marvelous</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="125787">Ok, just to make clear, I`m a sucker for romance. 
Having said that, this one is an anime beyond any expectations i could possibly have, as it has a great story, strong romantic relationships, hilarious humor, IMperfect characters (not like the "I am just to good to be true" chars in other anime) but very likable to the very last and to the very end, and trust me on that, after finishing it you will thanking me sooooooo much !

I`m on episode 16 on my 6th or 7th run right now.. ;)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="331330">I totally love this anime, deeply in my heart i like the strange relationship Ryuuji and Taiga build up and this anime makes be cry ;_;&lt;br /&gt;but still only anime can make cry don`t know why :3</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="589491">They are all alive. It`s very close to reality, however, don`t think you want to have Taiga in friends IRL. Only one disappointment is Ryuuji`s appearance is useful. What`s in it, if even he was a handsome, what`s the difference? a couple of humorous events disappears?</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="373701">One of the best in the genre romantic-comedy, all the characters have a specific personnality and charm. I thought at the beginning that anime will be an average anime but it has became an anime really funny and "mature" at the same time. Really a good surprise, to watch !</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="309738">if you like the high school animes this is a must see ^^</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="377192">Just must see!!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.starchild.co.jp/special/toradora/</url>
<creators>
<name id="720" type="Animation Work">J.C.Staff</name>
<name id="2210" type="Character Design">Tanaka Masayoshi</name>
<name id="122" type="Series Composition">Okada Mari</name>
<name id="2188" type="Direction">Nagai Tatsuyuki</name>
<name id="3073" type="Music">Hashimoto Yukari</name>
<name id="2210" type="Chief Animation Direction">Tanaka Masayoshi</name>
<name id="2932" type="Chief Animation Direction">Shitaya Tomoyuki</name>
<name id="2175" type="Chief Animation Direction">Iwakura Kazunori</name>
<name id="8626" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kawada Tsuyoshi</name>
<name id="9383" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ochiai Hitomi</name>
<name id="4255" type="Character Design">Ootsuka Mai</name>
<name id="8966" type="Original Work">Takemiya Yuyuko</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a light novel series by http://anidb.net/cr8966 [Takemiya Yuyuko], illustrated by http://anidb.net/cr8965 [Yasu].
http://anidb.net/ch1010 [Takasu Ryuuji] is frustrated with the way he looks as he enters his second year of high school, for despite his gentle personality, he actually looks like an intimidating delinquent. Thus he does not see his chances of getting a girlfriend improving any time soon, and does not have many close friends either. After being greeted by his hungover http://anidb.net/ch6937 [mother] in the morning, Ryuuji goes to school and finds out that he is in the same class as his best friend http://anidb.net/ch1013 [Kitamura Yuusaku]. But what makes him extremely happy is that he gets to be in the same class as his crush http://anidb.net/ch1011 [Kushieda Minori]. However, it is then that he unexpectedly bumps into http://anidb.net/ch1009 [Aisaka Taiga] — the creature ranked most dangerous in the school — who goes by the nickname Palmtop Tiger and also just happens to be in his class.
Taiga has a negative attitude towards others and will not hesitate to snap at people. After a series of misunderstandings between Ryuuji and Taiga, Ryuuji is taken in by Taiga as her personal servant. Taiga had moved out to live on her own due to family issues and is inept at doing household chores. After discovering the state of her apartment Ryuuji, who has a real talent for domestic chores, decides to do all of her house work. Taiga spends a lot of her time over at his house, so much so that she could almost be considered a member of his family. And since Ryuuji spends a lot of time with Taiga, he opens up to her world and to a side of her that most people do not see. The two also attempt to help each other in order to improve their relationship with their respective crushes — Taiga has a crush on Ryuuji`s best friend, Yuusaku, and Ryuuji has a crush on Taiga`s best friend, Minori. However, fellow students start to become curious about their strange relationship together and rumours begin to spread about them...</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="10171">8.05</permanent>
<temporary count="10337">8.24</temporary>
<review count="8">7.22</review>
</ratings>
<picture>13913.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10050</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4224</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>23701</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>6127</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>11553</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4336</identifier>
<identifier>nxrjev</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.starchild.co.jp/special/toradora/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>http://nisamerica.com/index.php?nav=ap&amp;aid=toradora</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://starchild.fm/special/en/toradora/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Toradora!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>とらドラ!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1471</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>331739</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10428</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>toradora</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B07L7BFBKJ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="28" parentid="2881" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-16">
<name>baseball</name>
<description>Baseball is like a complicated version of Rounders. It involves hitting a ball with a stick, then running around several bases placed in the form of a diamond on a field. Big in the US, and also in Japan.</description>
<picurl>29801.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="204" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-06-19">
<name>violent</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1157" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>horny nosebleed</name>
<description>In Japanese media, healthy young men who have no other sexual outlet will often suffer nosebleeds upon seeing the naked female body, or even just a pair of well-filled panties.
The nosebleed is, of course, a visual shorthand/euphemism for sexual arousal. It is commonly interpreted that way for males and females, with little trickles of blood indicating mild arousal, and gushing fountains of blood indicating erection/extreme arousal in both sexes. It can also be interpreted as shorthand strictly for erections in males. In that case, when blood shoots from the nose explosively, and in ridiculous quantity, the implication would be an ejaculation.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>233513.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1241" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-18">
<name>swimming</name>
<description>Swimming is an individual or team sport that involves using arms and legs to move the body through water. Typically, the sport takes place in pools or in open water. Competitive swimming is one of the most popular Olympic sports, with events in butterfly, backstroke, breaststroke, freestyle, and individual medley. In addition to these individual events, swimmers take part in relays.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>208479.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1446" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-15">
<name>energetic</name>
<description>An energetic character, often also called a genki character, shows great, often excessive levels of activity or vitality, and seems to always be doing everything extra fast. Genki characters are often slightly, or sometimes very, eccentric, and are filled with confidence and determination, regardless of whether they are competent or not; in fact, they often have little to no actual competence at whatever they generally do. Although genki characters are usually played exclusively for comedy effect, sometimes they may slow down for a serious or introspective moment. The most common genki character archetype is the genki schoolgirl, who will often be late to school and run with a toast in her mouth.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2069" parentid="2869" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-15">
<name>delinquent</name>
<description>Delinquents - Every school has them, but not all anime with school setting make delinquents a central topic. There are several versions of these delinquents, though some are grounded on a misunderstanding:
* The student with a really bad image and attitude, based on his real criminal actions outside of the school and is even feared by teachers.
* The primitive "class bully" that pushes around ("clobbers") his classmates for no apparent reason, possibly extorting lunch money.
* The student with an sinister complexion or "evil eye", but is actually a "good" student (unfoundedly feared character).
* The rebellious student, who does not care for studying, but is otherwise docile. Called a "delinquent" as a joke.</description>
<picurl>243713.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2396" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-08">
<name>swimsuit</name>
<description>A swimsuit is one of several kinds of garments designed to be worn by people engaging in water-based activities or sports or during certain activities under sunlight. Most kinds of swimsuit reveal a large portion of the body surface area, but exceptions exist. The more revealing kinds may also be worn as undergarment in sports that require wetsuits, or when there is a need to display the body, as in the case of beauty pageants or bodybuilding contests.
There is a very wide range of styles of modern swimsuits, which vary in relation to body coverage and materials. The choice of style of swimsuit is dependent on current fashions, community standards of modesty, and plain personal preference. Swimsuits for men usually expose the chest, while those for women do not usually do so; however, many women prefer to engage in water or sun activities with their torso uncovered, in a practice commonly described as toplessness or topfreedom. Since the early twentieth century a naturist movement has developed in western countries that seeks a return to non-sexual nakedness when swimming and during other appropriate activities; in some places around the world, nude beaches have been set aside for people who choose to engage in normal beach activities in the nude, and such beaches may or may not enforce nudity onto their goers.
In anime, it is common for at least one episode to feature the characters in swimsuits, usually as an excuse for gratuitous fanservice; when that happens, the episode is usually labeled a pool or beach episode, after the place the characters went to. Swimsuits, and in particular one-piece swimsuits, are a very common fetish in Japan; while the reason for that is uncertain, a common folk explanation is the fact that boys throughout their entire adolescence are commonly exposed to their female classmates wearing them, in what might be called an experiment in sexual discovery waiting to happen.</description>
<picurl>149786.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2662" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>school excursion</name>
<description>True for almost all anime with school setting, there will be a school excursion or field trip. Tokyo and Kyoto seem to be particularly popular as sightseeing destinations. So are hiking excursions into the local mountains. This also is a good excuse to present the prefecture`s / city`s food specialities.
Potential for ecchi moments: Obviously the "boys" will get all sorts of ideas with the "girls" sleeping so close by.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2670" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>school festival - TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>THIS TAG NEEDS TO BE SPLIT:
into http://anidb.net/perl-bin/animedb.pl?show=tag&amp;tagid=6119&amp;reltb=eptb [school culture festival]
and http://anidb.net/perl-bin/animedb.pl?show=tag&amp;tagid=2665&amp;reltb=eptb [school sports festival]
The obligatory school festival (or cultural fair) with cosplay cafe, haunted house, theatre performance, and food booths cannot be missing in any school setting.
For good measure there may also be an athletics or sports festival in this anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2760" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>basketball</name>
<description>Basketball is Netball for men, the real game that encourages dribbling and other such uncouth behaviour that was sanitised out of the ladies` version. However, it is itself woozy compared to Ulama, as the losing side are seldom publicly sacrificed.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2770" parentid="2653" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>violent retribution for accidental infringement</name>
<description>A comedy / slapstick element often found in Ecchi anime: The hilarity derives from spontaneous embarrassment, overreaction of the "victim" (girl), immediate retribution for a seemingly inappropriate act, and a sense of pity with the supposed "aggressor" (boy).
Typically a boy will - through no fault of his own - stumble into a girl, thus invading her personal space. In the process the boy may e.g. pull down her skirt, grab the girl`s breasts, or accidentally kiss her. Any level-headed girl would see the accident just for what it is. Not so the girl with an overly developed sense of modesty, and a thing for violence. She - often a tsundere - will clobber the boy with excessive brutality.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2780" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-06">
<name>indirect kiss</name>
<description>Comedy element: Especially in a school setting the character who has fallen for a fellow student, but has not yet confessed his/her love, will be desperate for any sign of "closeness".
The indirect kiss: Anything the adored person touches with his/her lips — e.g. a used glass of lemonade, some half-eaten food, a half-emptied can of soda — the love struck will want to touch with her/his own lips.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2788" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-21">
<name>confession</name>
<description>Someone confesses his/her love to someone else.</description>
<picurl>160903.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2873" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-03">
<name>Valentine`s Day</name>
<description>Valentine`s Day is a festive day celebrated every February 14.
In Japan, South Korea, Taiwan, and China, Valentine`s Day is one month before http://anidb.net/t3147 [White Day], a celebration unique to those countries.
In the rest of the world:
On Valentine`s Day, both males and females will express their feelings of affection towards their loved ones, by exchanging gifts (such as cards, candies, and chocolates), going on dates, and other signs and actions of affection. Some people also take the opportunity to confess and propose for marriage. In Western countries, it is generally expected of the male to offer gifts to the significant other.
In many countries, friends and co-workers also exchange small gifts to show their friendship towards each other.
In Japan, South Korea, Taiwan, and China:
On Valentine`s Day, many women feel obliged to give chocolates to all male co-workers, except when the day falls on a Sunday, a holiday. This is known as giri choco (義理チョコ, "obligation chocolate"), with unpopular co-workers receiving only chougiri choco (超義理チョコ, "ultra-obligatory chocolate") cheap chocolate.
This contrasts with honmei choco (本命チョコ, "love chocolate"), chocolate given to a loved one.
Friends, especially girls, may exchange chocolate referred to as tomo choco (友チョコ, "friend chocolate").
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>160891.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2886" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-16">
<name>New Year`s Day</name>
<description>It is tradition in Japan to celebrate the new year at a Shinto shrine (hatsumode). The protagonists will offer some money, ring a bell at the end of a thick rope, and then pray for good fortune.
This usually goes along with gorging yourself at the many temporary food stalls, playing various games, and drawing a fortune.
The female characters in the anime will usually dress up in a kimono, to show off their traditional Japanese clothing, while watching the fireworks.</description>
<picurl>161028.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3107" parentid="6232" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-10-12">
<name>unfoundedly feared character</name>
<description>Due to some strange misunderstanding, or some other unfounded reason the character in the anime is feared by his contemporaries.
Example: A male student with an "evil eye" is mistaken for a delinquent, and thus feared by the students in his class.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3408" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>skiing</name>
<description>Skiing is a recreational activity and competitive sport in which the participant uses skis to glide on snow.
Popular school excursion destination in winter is a ski resort, a town or village in the mountains where students do skiing, snowboarding and other winter sports.</description>
<picurl>161690.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3758" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-28">
<name>concert</name>
<description>The main characters play one or more live music performances during the show. This mostly happens for anime with the main focus on music.</description>
<picurl>169133.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4480" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>happy ending</name>
<description>And they lived "happily ever after"... *sniff*.
All issues in the anime have been resolved, the love polygons sorted out, the conflicts resolved, the guy gets the girl (or the other way around), and everyone else lives on blissfully.
(Not very realistic, but then again this is anime.)</description>
<picurl>222185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5846" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-26">
<name>beach visit</name>
<description>Every anime has to have them, episodes in which the characters for whatever reason end up going to the sea, ocean, random island or the local pond.
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in swimsuits and raise the DVD sales.
The cheap version is the http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].
Other marginally less used variants of this are the http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode] and the http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], used when it is too cold for a beach/pool episode.
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene].</description>
<picurl>160805.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5943" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-06-14">
<name>misunderstanding</name>
<description>Suggests that a large portion of storyline revolves around a rather large misunderstanding between two or more characters, usually forming long lasting situations of separation or hostility between all those involved.
A large portion of the story may be dedicated to gradually working all parties into a mutual understanding to true intentions or changes of heart.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6046" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>pool episode</name>
<description>An episode playing at the pool, mostly in school, sometimes outside of it when the cast does not have a chance for a beach episode.
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in swimsuits and raise the DVD sales.
The cheap version of the http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode].
Other variants are the http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode] and the http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], used when it is too cold for a beach/pool episode.
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene].</description>
<picurl>160904.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6083" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>master-servant relationship</name>
<description>To some genres, this would suggest a genuine pairing where one person exists to serve another person, such as in some action/dramas where the pair becomes united by destiny as partners — fighting or battles between different pairs/partners will usually be a dominant part of the story.
In other genres, this suggests a relationship where one person may be occupied as or even forcefully treated as a servant or slave to the other who designates themself the master — these services usually apply anywhere from tsundere/romantic-comedies to ecchi or to the more extreme in hentai.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6232" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-10-21">
<name>character related tags which need deleting or merging</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="1009" type="main character in" update="2011-08-22">
<rating votes="737">7.54</rating>
<name>Aisaka Taiga</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A girl in Ryuuji`s class. She has a well-regulated and beautiful appearance though is unable to stomach company from others. Due to her often snapping at others in brutal ways and her short stature at 143.6 cm, she is given the nickname "Palmtop Tiger". Her under-developed body and the added nickname has given her a complex which in turn serves to give her a negative attitude and facial expression. Essentially, Taiga gets upset easily and is considerably clumsy. Due to her cute looks (described as a doll by Ryuuji), she often gets confessions by boys her age, but she turns down every one of them. She comes from a rich family but due to bad family relations, she has taken to living on her own. However, since she came from a privileged household, she does not know how to do any domestic chores. When she meets Ryuuji and learns of his domestic talents, she ends up relying on Ryuuji to clean up after her. Aside from sleeping in her own house, and going to school, she spends most of her time at Ryuuji`s house; so much so that she is almost considered a member of his family. At the beginning of the story, she is infatuated with his best friend Kitamura Yuusaku to the point that she drools at her picture collection of him and gets nervous every time he appears. Due to this, Taiga and Ryuuji team up to help each other get into a relationship with each other`s best friend. However, as the story goes on, she too develops feelings for Ryuuji, commenting once how even though they are in a big room, they still sit so close together like at his cramped apartment.</description>
<picture>25133.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3" picture="44969.jpg">Kugimiya Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1010" type="main character in" update="2010-07-20">
<rating votes="143">7.50</rating>
<name>Takasu Ryuuji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ryuuji is a sixteen-year-old high school student in his second year, class C. Due to biological inheritance, his eyes make him look like an intimidating delinquent and causes many misunderstandings in his life. He lives in a fatherless family with just his mother, and due to this, Ryuuji has learned to be self-sufficient. He is good at cooking and keeping everything in his house clean (nearly to the point of obsession), and also excels at sewing. He holds a crush on Kushieda Minori, a girl his age in his class as he appears to have a weakness for the airhead type. He has a pet parakeet named "Inko-chan" (inko literally means parakeet in Japanese). Ryuuji often helps Taiga with domestic chores which she is otherwise unable to perform. At school, he is known as "the only person able to stop the palmtop tiger", referring to Taiga`s nickname. Ryuuji and Taiga become rumoured as a couple since they spend so much time together, though this rumour stopped when Taiga viciously destroyed her classroom trying to make everyone see that it was a misunderstanding. As the story continues, he starts to develop feelings for Taiga.</description>
<picture>25132.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="400" picture="171989.jpg">Majima Junji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1011" type="main character in" update="2009-05-19">
<rating votes="308">6.62</rating>
<name>Kushieda Minori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A girl in Ryuuji`s class, and is a close friend to Taiga. She is also known by the pet name "Minorin". In contrast to the negative Taiga, Minori is always smiling and cheerful, but is also a natural airhead. She is very athletic and is the captain of the girl`s softball club at school, though at the same time she holds many part time jobs. She is a glutton when it comes to food, but is also constantly combating with dieting, calling herself a Diet Warrior. She has a habit of singing cheerfully off key and tends to walk with more energy than needed (such as kicking up her legs with each step). She seems to get a thrill out of being scared: she pretends to be terrified of supernatural things in hopes that others will take advantage of this statement and try to frighten her. Despite her air-headed tendencies, she is very perceptive to other people`s characters, and is one of the few people to see Ryuuji for the gentle person he is, and is also not fooled by Ami`s act of innocence.</description>
<picture>25126.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="61" picture="58663.jpg">Horie Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1012" type="main character in" update="2009-05-19">
<rating votes="324">7.50</rating>
<name>Kawashima Ami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yuusaku`s childhood friend who transfers into his class midway through their second year of high school. She is very beautiful and even works as a model, though after she transfers school, she temporarily stops modelling. However, she still continues to go to the gym readily and maintains a slim figure. She is always kind and generous towards others, though this is merely a deception. In truth, she is arrogant and will not hesitate to use abusive language towards others. During her first meeting with Taiga, Ami shows her true colours, but the tables are turned when Taiga throws a counterattack back at her. Since then, Ami and Taiga have been enemies, though Ami still sometimes envies Taiga since she can always be honest. Ami has a love interest in Ryuuji, asking him if he would love her real self, going as far as to bet Taiga to a swim race for the chance of having Ryuuji all to herself at her villa. She has recently shown a deeper affection for Ryuuji when she states that Minori will not be good for him, comparing the two to her being the sun and him the moon, and if he is with her he would burn out. Then states that a person more suited for him, would be her.</description>
<picture>25128.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="401" picture="223216.jpg">Kitamura Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1013" type="main character in" update="2009-05-19">
<rating votes="72">3.99</rating>
<name>Kitamura Yuusaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yuusaku is a male student in Ryuuji`s class, and is his best friend. He is the vice-president of the student council, the class representative, and captain of the boy`s softball club at school. Yuusaku wears glasses, and has a diligent personality. He thinks he is poor at talking to girls, though Ryuuji observes otherwise; Yuusaku likes the student council president Kanou Sumire. Despite being on the student council, he is in violation of riding a motorcycle to school. A running gag is that he will appear out of nowhere behind Taiga and Ryuuji when they are discussing a "plan of attack" to get their crushes.</description>
<picture>25129.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="214" picture="238138.jpg">Nojima Hirofumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2967" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-19">
<rating votes="52">5.53</rating>
<name>Inko-chan</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>25130.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="355" picture="71573.jpg">Gotou Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6934" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-19">
<rating votes="16">4.81</rating>
<name>Noto Hisamitsu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A male student in Ryuuji`s class who wears glasses. He was also in Ryuuji`s class the previous year and is on good terms with him. Noto begins to develop feelings for Kihara Maya following an argument they had during the class winter ski trip.</description>
<picture>25118.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1692" picture="224934.jpg">Okitsu Kazuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6935" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-19">
<rating votes="23">5.73</rating>
<name>Haruta Kouji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A male student in Ryuuji`s class who has long hair and is on good terms with him. He is regarded as a class `idiot` and that opinion is deepened by his poor school marks and overly energetic behaviour. His childish pranks often target Taiga and he has been the victim of her violent outbursts.</description>
<picture>25119.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="65" picture="170428.jpg">Yoshino Hiroyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6936" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-19">
<rating votes="40">5.36</rating>
<name>Kanou Sumire</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The student council president and always manages to get the top grades in school; she is in fact a scholarship student and has horrible eyesight. She has a strong-minded personality which she depends on to be a figure those will follow. Her younger sister is Sakura and her parents own a supermarket. Sumire likes Yuusaku and as a result is the object of a one-sided hostility from Taiga.
She later studies abroad in America as she wants to become an astronaut, and because of this, she rejects Yuusaku`s confession of his feelings.</description>
<picture>25120.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="160" picture="30490.jpg">Kaida Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6937" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-19">
<rating votes="52">7.77</rating>
<name>Takasu Yasuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ryuuji`s thirty-three-year-old mother, though she refers to herself as eternally twenty-three; she has large, F-cup-sized breasts. She works at a hostess bar named Bishamontengoku where she goes by the name "Mirano", and single-handedly supports her two-member family financially. However, she has a childish personality and since she works, she entrusts the household chores to Ryuuji. She instantly takes a liking to Taiga and already regards her as a member of her family, getting depressed when Taiga will not appear for dinner. However, she does get angry when woken up early. Despite the childish behaviour, Yasuko proves to have a rather good insight of other people.
Though she tells Ryuuji his father died before he was born, the truth is they were never married; he left her before Ryuuji was born, and she raised her son by herself.</description>
<picture>25124.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="74" picture="84835.jpg">Oohara Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6938" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-19">
<rating votes="21">6.50</rating>
<name>Koigakubo Yuri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The twenty-nine-year-old homeroom teacher of Ryuuji`s class. She likes to do things at her own pace and is timid towards Taiga`s way of speaking out. Since her twenties are almost over, Yuri is in a hurry to get married soon and she even tries to dress well so as to be able to get into a relationship quicker. After she becomes thirty without getting married, she develops a twisted and depressed personality, which does not help that when Taiga talks about her, she emphases her single status. She has an interest in real estate.</description>
<picture>25125.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="135" picture="16884.jpg">Tanaka Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6973" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-19">
<rating votes="24">5.67</rating>
<name>Kihara Maya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A female student in Ryuuji`s class who often hangs out with Nanako. She is a kogal. She has a crush on Yuusaku, and she circuitously opposes the idea of Taiga and Yuusaku being a couple, although she wants Taiga and Ryuuji to be together.</description>
<picture>25197.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="347" picture="41555.jpg">Nonaka Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6974" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-19">
<rating votes="19">5.04</rating>
<name>Kashii Nanako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A female student in Ryuuji`s class who often hangs out with Maya and Ami.</description>
<picture>25199.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3769" picture="25256.jpg">Ishikawa Momoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11115" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-26">
<rating votes="13">5.76</rating>
<name>Kanou Sakura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sakura is Sumire`s younger sister who attends the same high school as Sumire though her grades are horrible.
She can unconsciously flirt with people, and like her sister, she hates snakes.</description>
<picture>41961.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="479" picture="222800.jpg">Asumi Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14349" type="appears in" update="2014-02-05">
<rating votes="3">2.61</rating>
<name>Takasu Seiji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>149669.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6411" picture="44853.jpg">Aoki Tsuyoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14350" type="appears in" update="2014-02-05">
<rating votes="3">2.61</rating>
<name>Takasu Sonoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>149670.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12433" picture="235104.jpg">Kobayashi Mina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14351" type="appears in" update="2010-01-25">
<rating votes="3">1.60</rating>
<name>Kuroma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gym teacher at Takasu`s school.</description>
<picture>41918.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1683" picture="223030.jpg">Kanemitsu Nobuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14352" type="appears in" update="2010-09-29">
<rating votes="2">1.89</rating>
<name>Inage</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Owner of the liquor store where Yasuko works at. Divorced his wife.</description>
<picture>5106.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="6411" picture="44853.jpg">Aoki Tsuyoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14353" type="appears in" update="2010-01-25">
<rating votes="3">1.16</rating>
<name>Stalker Otoko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A fan of Kawashima Ami who goes as far as to stalk her and is mainly the reason she transferred to Takasu and Taiga`s school.</description>
<picture>41917.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1680" picture="132752.jpg">Tachibana Shinnosuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14354" type="appears in" update="2010-01-25">
<rating votes="2">1.89</rating>
<name>Suugaku Kyoushi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>41924.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6411" picture="44853.jpg">Aoki Tsuyoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14355" type="appears in" update="2014-01-30">
<rating votes="1">5.25</rating>
<name>2 Nen C Gumi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>149298.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="14359" type="appears in" update="2010-04-03">
<rating votes="7">1.06</rating>
<name>Aisaka Rikurou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Taiga`s father.</description>
<picture>45664.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3124" picture="24096.jpg">Furusawa Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14378" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-01-26">
<rating votes="6">3.90</rating>
<name>Tomiie Kouta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kouta is a first-year student who is the main character to Toradora Spin-off!. He is generally unhappy about his life. He works on the student council in general affairs, and gets good grades.</description>
<picture>41960.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="390" picture="33609.jpg">Okamoto Nobuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14380" type="appears in" update="2010-01-26">
<rating votes="3">4.33</rating>
<name>Mitsui Yuriko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A first year from class A. Despite her timid nature she took part in the beauty contest dressed as a maid.</description>
<picture>41962.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4780" picture="28006.jpg">Fujita Mami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14388" type="appears in" update="2010-01-26">
<rating votes="1">3.43</rating>
<name>Murase</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A student council member from 2-A. It is him who tells Takasu of the reason behind Takamura`s weird behaviour in episode 16.</description>
<seiyuu id="2708" picture="37823.jpg">Oohara Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14400" type="appears in" update="2010-01-26">
<rating votes="2">1.89</rating>
<name>Ramen Tenchou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>41986.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1683" picture="223030.jpg">Kanemitsu Nobuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14404" type="appears in" update="2014-02-04">
<rating votes="2">1.89</rating>
<name>Cake Tenshu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>149583.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6411" picture="44853.jpg">Aoki Tsuyoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14405" type="appears in" update="2014-02-04">
<rating votes="2">1.89</rating>
<name>Gakunen Shunin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>149584.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1683" picture="223030.jpg">Kanemitsu Nobuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14406" type="appears in" update="2010-01-26">
<rating votes="2">2.81</rating>
<name>Hamada Sena</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A 3rd Grade junior in an art university. Lives alone in an apartment. Meets with Haruta right after breaking up with her boyfriend, Ryousuke. Without knowing anything about Ryousuke, she plans of reuniting with the help of Haruta.
First appears briefly in novel vol.9 along with Haruta when Takasu and Taiga are selling chocolates. (and in anime EP23 relatively) Her main story is told in novel Spin-off vol.2 "Let`s go to Gunma when it`s spring! (春になったら群馬に行こう!)" chapter.</description>
<picture>41989.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="355" picture="71573.jpg">Gotou Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="14407" type="appears in" update="2010-03-24">
<rating votes="3">1.09</rating>
<name>Taiga Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Taiga`s mother. Her name is not mentioned. She married another man and is pregnant with his baby, which was the reason for Taiga to leave their new family.</description>
<picture>45098.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="142" picture="68482.jpg">Ooura Fuyuka</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="93151" update="2008-12-04">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="2">7.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="93223" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-10-02</airdate>
<rating votes="46">6.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">虎と竜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tiger and Dragon</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La tigre e il drago</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Tygrys i Smok</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tora to Ryuu</title>
<summary>The dragon and tiger have a shocking encounter!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>656743</identifier>
<identifier>toradora</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="93275" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-10-09</airdate>
<rating votes="35">7.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">竜児と大河</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ryuuji and Taiga</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Ryuji e Taiga</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Ryuuji i Taiga</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ryuuji to Taiga</title>
<summary>What will Taiga and Ryuji decide?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>656745</identifier>
<identifier>toradora</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="93280" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-10-16</airdate>
<rating votes="29">6.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">君の歌</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Your Song</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La tua canzone</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Twoja Piosenka</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kimi no Uta</title>
<summary>Full throttle at both school and work!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>656747</identifier>
<identifier>toradora</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="93510" update="2017-03-03">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-10-30</airdate>
<rating votes="26">7.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">かわしまあみ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kawashima Ami</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Kawashima Ami</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kawashima Ami</title>
<summary>Angel or Demon? Ami Kawashima appears!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>656751</identifier>
<identifier>toradora</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="93511" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-10-23</airdate>
<rating votes="27">6.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あのときの顔</title>
<title xml:lang="en">That Moment`s Face</title>
<title xml:lang="it">L`espressione di quel momento</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Stawić czoło chwili</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ano Toki no Kao</title>
<summary>Love began with rejection!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>656749</identifier>
<identifier>toradora</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="93792" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-11-06</airdate>
<rating votes="29">7.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほんとの自分</title>
<title xml:lang="en">True Colors</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La vera me stessa</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Moje prawdziwe ja</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Honto no Jibun</title>
<summary>The true self is neither angel nor demon.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>656753</identifier>
<identifier>toradora</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="93878" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-11-13</airdate>
<rating votes="27">7.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">プールびらき</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pool Opening</title>
<title xml:lang="it">L`apertura della piscina</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Otwarcie basenu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Pool-biraki</title>
<summary>Pool! Swimsuit! Summer is coming!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>656755</identifier>
<identifier>toradora</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="93911" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-11-20</airdate>
<rating votes="26">7.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">だれのため</title>
<title xml:lang="en">For Whose Sake?</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Per il bene di chi?</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Z czyjego powodu?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dare no Tame</title>
<summary>Taiga`s true feelings finally take form?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>656757</identifier>
<identifier>toradora</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="94829" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-11-27</airdate>
<rating votes="30">7.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">海にいこうと君は</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let`s Go to the Ocean, You Say</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Quando si parla di andare al mare, tu...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Umi ni Ikou to Kimi wa</title>
<summary>A horror surprise scheme!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>656759</identifier>
<identifier>toradora</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="94830" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-12-04</airdate>
<rating votes="22">6.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">花火</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fireworks</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Fuochi d`artificio</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hanabi</title>
<summary>A summer to be remembered.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>656761</identifier>
<identifier>toradora</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="95159" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-12-11</airdate>
<rating votes="23">7.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大橋高校文化祭[前編]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Oohashi High School Festival - First Part</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il festival culturale della scuola superiore Ohashi [prima parte]</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oohashikoukou Bunkasai [Zenpen]</title>
<summary>Being with family is the best?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>656763</identifier>
<identifier>toradora</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="95160" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-12-18</airdate>
<rating votes="24">7.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大橋高校文化祭[中編]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Oohashi High School Festival - Second Part</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il festival culturale della scuola superiore Ohashi [seconda parte]</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oohashikoukou Bunkasai [Chuuhen]</title>
<summary>The Ohashi High School Culture Festival Finally Begins!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>656765</identifier>
<identifier>toradora</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="95241" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-12-25</airdate>
<rating votes="25">8.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大橋高校文化祭[後編]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Oohashi High School Festival - Final Part</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il festival culturale della scuola superiore Ohashi [terza parte]</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oohashikoukou Bunkasai [Kouhen]</title>
<summary>To Taiga, before everyone else!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>656767</identifier>
<identifier>toradora</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="95645" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-01-08</airdate>
<rating votes="28">7.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">しあわせの手乗りタイガー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Palmtop Tiger of Bliss</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La tigre palmare della felicità</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shiawase no Tenori Tiger</title>
<summary>Where is Taiga`s happiness?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>656769</identifier>
<identifier>toradora</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="96217" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-01-15</airdate>
<rating votes="25">6.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">星は, 遠く</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Stars Are Far Away</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Le stelle, come sono lontane</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hoshi wa, Tooku</title>
<summary>Student Council Vice President goes insane.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>656771</identifier>
<identifier>toradora</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="96352" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-01-22</airdate>
<rating votes="39">8.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">踏みだす一歩</title>
<title xml:lang="en">One Step Forward</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Un passo avanti</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Krok naprzód</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fumidasu Ippo</title>
<summary>Emotions run high and clash!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>656773</identifier>
<identifier>toradora</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="96353" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-01-29</airdate>
<rating votes="26">6.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">クリスマスに水星は逆行する</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mercury Retrogrades at Christmas</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Mercurio retrogado a natale</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">W święta Merkury porusza się wstecz</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Christmas ni Suisei wa Gyakkou Suru</title>
<summary>Angel Taiga appears at Christmas!?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>656775</identifier>
<identifier>toradora</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="96354" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-02-05</airdate>
<rating votes="23">7.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">もみの木の下で</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Under the Fir Tree</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Sotto l`abete</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Pod jodłą</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Momi no Ki no Shita de</title>
<summary>Will important things fix themselves?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>656777</identifier>
<identifier>toradora</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="96571" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-02-12</airdate>
<rating votes="36">9.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">聖夜祭</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Holy Night Party</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Festa nella Notte Santa</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Wigilijne przyjęcie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seiyasai</title>
<summary>His thoughts and emotions failed to reach
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>656779</identifier>
<identifier>toradora</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="96572" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-02-19</airdate>
<rating votes="24">7.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ずっと, このまま</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Always, Like This</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Così, per sempre</title>
<title xml:lang="pl">Już tak na zawsze</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zutto, Kono Mama</title>
<summary>They both must like each other.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>656781</identifier>
<identifier>toradora</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="96926" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-02-26</airdate>
<rating votes="41">9.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">どうしたって</title>
<title xml:lang="en">No Matter What</title>
<title xml:lang="it">A qualunque costo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Doushitatte</title>
<summary>Can`t help these feelings!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>656783</identifier>
<identifier>toradora</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="96927" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-03-05</airdate>
<rating votes="28">6.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">君のいる景色</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Scene With You</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Un panorama dove sei anche tu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kimi no Iru Keshiki</title>
<summary>What path will Ryuji take!?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>656785</identifier>
<identifier>toradora</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="97029" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-03-12</airdate>
<rating votes="28">8.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">進むべき道</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Road That We Must Advance on</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La strada da percorrere</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Susumubeki Michi</title>
<summary>Judgment Day is coming!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>656787</identifier>
<identifier>toradora</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="97112" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-03-19</airdate>
<rating votes="33">7.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">告白</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Confession</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La dichiarazione</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kokuhaku</title>
<summary>Will their getaway succeed!?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>656789</identifier>
<identifier>toradora</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="97113" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-03-26</airdate>
<rating votes="33">8.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">とらドラ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Toradora!</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Toradora!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toradora!</title>
<summary>Two finally become one.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>656791</identifier>
<identifier>toradora</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="97258" update="2013-11-04">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>5</length>
<rating votes="13">1.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">とらドラSOS! 食いしん坊万々歳 小さな命をたっぷり食らう つぶつぶうまいぜビバたらこスパ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Toradora SOS</title>
</episode>
<episode id="97497" update="2010-05-21">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-10-09</airdate>
<rating votes="4">8.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="99269" update="2010-05-21">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-10-02</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="102064" recap="true" update="2014-09-09">
<epno type="2">S10</epno>
<length>30</length>
<rating votes="1">3.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">PSP Bonus DVD</title>
</episode>
<episode id="106053" update="2011-12-25">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>5</length>
<rating votes="7">1.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">とらドラSOS! 食いしん坊万々歳 子供スウィーツその名はプリン プリン体 多いの? 少ないの?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Toradora SOS! 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="106054" update="2011-12-25">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>6</length>
<rating votes="7">1.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">とらドラSOS! 食いしん坊万々歳 インドではカレーは右手で トイレは左手 だらだら続くよ カレー道!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Toradora SOS! 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="108076" update="2010-05-21">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-01-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="108077" update="2010-05-21">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-01-29</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="108528" update="2009-09-13">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>5</length>
<rating votes="7">2.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">とらドラSOS! 食いしん坊万々歳 食わず嫌いはよくないよ! 愛してやまない, いとおしいピンクの霜降りコンビーフ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Toradora SOS! 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="113257" update="2010-05-21">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-03-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="113258" update="2010-05-21">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-02-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128855" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="2">S9</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2009-08-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Cast Video 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128856" update="2012-01-03">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>20</length>
<airdate>2009-07-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Cast Video 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128857" update="2012-01-03">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2009-05-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Cast Video 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128858" update="2011-03-16">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>9</length>
<airdate>2009-03-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Cast Video 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130878" update="2011-06-13">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PSP Game CM</title>
</episode>
<episode id="130879" update="2011-06-13">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>7</length>
<title xml:lang="en">TV CM Collection</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134566" update="2013-11-04">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-12-21</airdate>
<rating votes="13">7.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">弁当の極意</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The True Meaning of Bentou</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bentou no Gokui</title>
<summary>Kitamura brings a gigantic bentou to school: His parents are on a business trip, so his grandma is taking care of him for the time being. While everyone else is happy to be allowed to eat from this bentou, Takasu considers it a challenge to his own housewife skills; during the following days he tries to make creative special bentous in order to "beat" his mysterious opponent... before he learns what making bentou is ultimately about.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="135462" update="2011-12-22">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Special Episode PV</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
