<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="6113" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2008-10-06</startdate>
<enddate>2008-12-22</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Ga-Rei: Zero</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Га-Рей Зеро</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Пожиратели Духов: Зеро</title>
<title xml:lang="da" type="synonym">Ga-rei -Zero-</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Екзорсисти: ЗЕРО</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Ga-Rei-Zero</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">garei zero</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Ga-Rei Zero</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">食灵~零</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">GRZ</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">喰霊 -零-</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Ga-Rei-Zero</title>
<title xml:lang="cs" type="official">Ga-Rei: Zero</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="9880" type="Same Setting">Tokyo ESP</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="6036" approval="41" total="49">Shikabane Hime: Aka</anime>
<anime id="3186" approval="24" total="31">Blood+</anime>
<anime id="1536" approval="5" total="14">Bakuretsu Tenshi</anime>
<anime id="13172" approval="2" total="3">Toji no Miko</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="29">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="386407">Very disappointing: primitive animation, enemies, battles, story. Artificial emotions kill the rest. And what was that annoying lip drawing style? Nothing to enjoy at all.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="231672">This series really touched me, would never have guessed how good it would turn after the first episode!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="334694">thanks  for the this serie</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="381646">A+</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="289394">Sad ending :P</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="304206">Bloody good, delightful, don`t watch the last four minutes, ruins the ending</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="111071">Good, demon hunters and angst</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="366008">Great storyline and character development.Recommended, wether you`re a fan of the manga or not.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="120055">While the plot wasn`t mind-blowingly deep, it was well told and had enough substance to keep you watching, and similarly the characters, while not the best developed you`ll ever come across, were likeable and interesting enough to make you care. The show has a nice mixture of plot, action and some more light hearted elements. Aesthetically, I loved it; the character designs and the semi-realistic art style were great, the choreography was pretty well done, and everything was well drawn... the use of 3DCG was a bit jarring at times, but not unforgiveably so. Overall I feel like it was pretty ambitious and by-and-large it delivered... yet it managed to fall down just enough to make it a `recommend` rather than the `must-see` it could`ve been.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="77972">At first I hesitated to watch this knowing it wasn`t complete story but after finished the show it was quite watchable for a standalone.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="424773">A prequel to the manga, Ga-Rei.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="134578">One word: Heart-wrenching

really get the emotions going</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="523721">Very good, dark, dramatic story, which draws you in from the beginning. Nice fighting scenes and good music. Definitely must see.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="244867">Highly recommended! The action scenes will make you OMFG and the plot is really interesting.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="311018">great ending</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="327549">Watched this a long time ago and still 1 of the greatest anime I`ve seen. Dark, ecchi, action, plot, nice animation v...v.. Not many anime nowadays could barely compare with this anime.

Next season is the only thing this anime lacks.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="24713">action, story, character development, emotions. neatly packed in 12 episodes, then wrapped in a ribbon made of love, blood and relentless hate. don`t get fooled by cliffhanger tags, this one is worth the time!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.ga-rei.jp/top.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="1012" type="Animation Work">Asread</name>
<name id="1309" type="Animation Work">AIC Spirits</name>
<name id="4314" type="Character Design">Horiuchi Osamu</name>
<name id="2836" type="Story Composition">Takayama Katsuhiko</name>
<name id="5830" type="Direction">Aoki Ei</name>
<name id="4638" type="Music">Agematsu Noriyasu</name>
<name id="10061" type="Original Work">Segawa Hajime</name>
<name id="4314" type="Chief Animation Direction">Horiuchi Osamu</name>
</creators>
<description>* An anime-only prequel to the Ga-Rei manga by http://anidb.net/cr10061 [Segawa Hajime], serialised in http://anidb.net/cr11434 [Monthly Shounen Ace].
Will you kill someone you love because of love?
An elite squadron trained to combat supernatural forces is called in to investigate reports of invisible monsters terrorising Tokyo, but their mission is complicated by the interference of a rogue exorcist. When the mysterious female slaughters the outmatched attack force, her former comrades are ordered to lock down the crime scene — and forever silence their old friend.
Note: The chronological order of episodes is 3-9, 1-2, and 10-12.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="4544">6.68</permanent>
<temporary count="4596">7.59</temporary>
<review count="5">7.33</review>
</ratings>
<picture>65627.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10052</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4725</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4342</identifier>
<identifier>kktdbw</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.ga-rei.jp/top.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>List_of_Ga-rei:_Zero_episodes</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>喰霊</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1474</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>331513</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10330</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="428" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-12-25">
<name>contractor</name>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1152" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-23">
<name>undead</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1590" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-11">
<name>motorcyclist</name>
<description>A person who is skilled at riding a motorcycle/motorbike and does so on a regular basis.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1616" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-07">
<name>crippled</name>
<description>A person that is partially or totally unable to use one or more limbs, for example a lame.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1632" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-13">
<name>twin -- TO BE DELETED</name>
<description>This tag is meant to be purged in the short term. Please DO NOT assign it to any further characters; add the appropriate char-char relations to them instead.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1645" parentid="2751" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-03">
<name>kendo</name>
<description>Kendo, or kendou in Japanese, is a popular sport from Japan. It consists of swordplay with one or two http://anidb.net/t1817 [shinai], a two-handed bamboo sword which may also be held with one hand only, while wearing armour.</description>
<picurl>163593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1719" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-28">
<name>orphan</name>
<description>The character (in common usage: only a child, or the young of an animal) has lost both parents.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1773" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-12">
<name>tentacle</name>
<description>A tentacle or bothrium (plural: bothria) is one of usually two or more elongated flexible organs present in animals, especially invertebrates. Usually, Tentacles are used for feeding, feeling and grasping.</description>
<picurl>236087.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1955" parentid="2925" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-05-18">
<name>child soldier</name>
<description>Untrained and as yet immature, children are expediently thrust into the role of warriors to protect god, king, and country. Not having even finished school, they are inexplicably designated to elite status or roles, typically requiring months of training and years of experience. All the more so with "experimental" equipment or weapons of mass destruction.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2019" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-09-16">
<name>suicidal</name>
<description>The character has suicidal tendencies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2090" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-17">
<name>trauma</name>
<description>Character with emotional or psychological injury, caused by single or multiple events/experiences in the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2145" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-11-21">
<name>chain</name>
</tag>
<tag id="2253" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-24">
<name>kitsune</name>
<description>Kitsune is the Japanese word for http://anidb.net/t191 [fox], which are a common subject of Japanese folklore. This term in English specifically refers to kitsune as demon foxes or fox spirits. Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t1814 [foxpersons], a http://anidb.net/t7 [juujin] with fox characteristics.
Stories depict them as intelligent beings and as possessing magical abilities that increase with their age and wisdom. Foremost among these is the ability to assume human form.</description>
<picurl>226225.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2257" parentid="1152" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-12">
<name>zombie</name>
<description>A zombie is asserted to be a reanimated corpse, or a human who is being controlled by someone else by use of magic with some media renditions using a pandemic illness to explain their existence.
Stories of zombies originated in the West African spiritual belief system of voodoo, which told of the people being controlled as laborers by a powerful wizard.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2345" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-04-26">
<name>zettai ryouiki</name>
<description>Zettai ryouiki, literally "absolute territory", is an area of exposed skin of a female in the gap between http://anidb.net/t2137 [thigh-high] or over-the-knee http://anidb.net/t6419 [hosiery] and a http://anidb.net/t2451 [miniskirt], http://anidb.net/t2222 [shorts], or on occasion a http://anidb.net/t1200 [minidress]. In addition to the area itself, the term can describe the clothing combination. Please note that zettai ryouiki requires all three components: over-the-knee or thigh-high hosiery, thigh skin, and one of skirt, shorts, or minidress.
The "golden ratio" for the length of the miniskirt, the exposed portion of thigh, and the over-knee part of the hosiery is 4:1:2.5, with a tolerance of 25%. Letter grades have also been assigned for the ratio variants, from E (too much leg is seen, the skirt is too long) to A (short skirt, high socks, short exposed area). A further grade S has been conceived, adding the criteria of a http://anidb.net/t2455 [tsundere] wearing http://anidb.net/t1923 [twintails] to grade A.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>165582.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2467" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-22">
<name>sword</name>
<description>A sword is a long, edged piece of metal, used as a cutting, thrusting, and clubbing weapon in many civilizations throughout the world. Before firearms became commonplace, and fast enough to render other weapons pointless in the battlefield, they were the main kind of weapon for war and duels alike. A sword fundamentally consists of a blade and a hilt, typically with one or two edges for striking and cutting, and a point for thrusting. That aside, however, they may come in all sorts of designs: the medieval European swords used to be big, heavy weapons that did not actually cut but instead broke the enemy`s bones under their armor; conversely, the Chinese jian sword (called "ken" in Japanese) attempted to exploit the armor`s joints and perforate the enemy`s flesh in those places, but was useless against the armor itself, and did not take the strikes, preferring to redirect them, to this day being considered a highly "circular" weapon and associated to taijiquan; on the other hand, the Japanese katana was a balanced all-purposes weapon that could be used even in an axe-like way, but which a master swordsman could use in many other, more elaborate manners.</description>
<picurl>127113.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2535" parentid="1152" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-18">
<name>ghost</name>
<description>In traditional belief, a ghost is the soul or spirit of a deceased person or animal that can appear, in visible form or other manifestation, to the living. Descriptions of the apparition of ghosts vary widely: The mode of manifestation can range from an invisible presence to translucent or wispy shapes, to realistic, life-like visions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2021-07-27">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>For non-porn anime, the fetish must be a major element of the show; incidental appearances of the fetish is not sufficient for a fetish tag. Please do not add fetish tags to anime that do not pander to the fetish in question in any meaningful way. For example, there`s some ecchi in http://anidb.net/a22 [Shinseiki Evangelion], but the fact you get to see http://anidb.net/ch39 [Asuka]`s pantsu is not sufficient to warrant applying the http://anidb.net/t2894 [school girl] fetish tag. See also the http://wiki.anidb.net/Tags#Minimum_Relevance_Rule [minimum relevancy rule].
For porn anime, the application of fetish tags are fairly straightforward, as porn will fully play out most fetishes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2621" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>bullet time</name>
<description>Bullet time refers to a simulation of variable speed (i.e. slow motion, time-lapse, …) and is characterized both by its extreme transformation of time and space to show normally imperceptible and un-filmable events, such as flying bullets.
Most infamous scene using this technique, Neo dodging bullets in The Matrix film.</description>
<picurl>211279.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2636" parentid="2846" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>human enhancement</name>
<description>Human enhancement can take various forms: It can be something comparatively non-intrusive as a power-up drug, a form of machine implantation or cyberization (http://anidb.net/a4414 [SAC Solid State Society]), or outright - possibly atrocious - genetic manipulation (http://anidb.net/a361 [Ao no 6 Gou]). Plot-wise enhanced protagonists in anime usually have to pay a price for their enhancements, be it physical or mental.</description>
<picurl>223945.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2021-04-12">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators. No frontal (visible genitals) = 1.5 stars or less.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2751" parentid="2881" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-27">
<name>combat</name>
<description>Combat involves a violent conflict with the goal to establish dominance over an opponent.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2773" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-18">
<name>magic circles</name>
<description>A magic circle is circle or sphere of space marked out by practitioners of many branches of ritual magic. It may be marked physically, drawn in salt or chalk, for example, or merely visualised.
Traditionally, circles have been used by ritual magicians to form a protective barrier between themselves and what they summoned. Nowadays, circles often have the more benign function of containing and concentrating the energy raised during a ritual. Circles can also be used as barriers for non-magical work such as meditation.
Generally, as with most magical practices, an incantation is recited stating the purpose and nature of the circle, often repeating an assortment of divine and angelic names.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>32800.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2776" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-30">
<name>parasite</name>
<description>Parasites are life forms that feed off other beings in some way. In anime, they are often aliens and usually intelligent. For shock value, and to avoid having to draw aliens all the time, their prey is preferably human; they may see humans as food, as puppets for mind control, or simply as temporary body hosts. In every case, the human is the victim of a "merging", which is not to be confused with the more "amicable" symbiosis.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2830" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>furo scene</name>
<description>Furo (polite: Ofuro) is Japanese for bath, specifically a type of bath which originated as a short, steep-sided wooden bathtub. Baths of this type are found all over Japan in houses, apartments and traditional Japanese inns (Ryokans).
Furo are part of the Japanese ritual of bathing, not used for washing but for relaxing and warming oneself. Washing is carried out separately outside the furo, and only when completely clean does the bather enter the water. Generally Japanese bathrooms are small, so the bathroom is set up much like a walk-in shower area but containing the ofuro.
The cheapest and shortest way to show naked skin on TV, at least as much as allowed. It usually only takes up few minutes at most and as such it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in the nude and raise the DVD sales while still maintaining a "non-filler" episode.
Compare to the big brothers http://anidb.net/t4290 [sentou episode] and http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode].
See also http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode], and http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].</description>
<picurl>160785.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2851" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>horror</name>
<description>The horror cinematic genre is characterized by the attempt to make the viewer experience dread, fear, terror, or horror. Often their plots involve the intrusion of an evil force, event or personage, sometimes of supernatural origin, on the mundane world and the consequences thereof.</description>
<picurl>214682.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2852" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>thriller</name>
<description>The thriller is a genre of fiction in which tough, resourceful, but essentially ordinary heroes are pitted against villains determined to destroy them, their country, or the stability of the free world. The hero of a typical thriller faces danger alone or in the company of a small band of companions. The protagonist may be a law enforcement agent, a journalist, or a soldier, but typically he or she is cut off from the resources of "their" organization. More often the hero is an ordinary citizen drawn into danger and intrigue by circumstances beyond their control.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214683.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2863" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>proxy battles</name>
<description>In our terms, a proxy battle is a battle where humans use creatures/robots to do the fighting for them, either by commanding those creatures/robots or by simply evolving them/changing them into battle mode. Often the training aspect is also involved, or in some cases the proxies are nothing more than holographic representatives of some other variation of competition (like for example a card game). While many popular shounen anime fit under this category, it`s not limited to shounen anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2877" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>revenge</name>
<description>A primary factor that drives the plot forward, is the almost obsessive desire of one of the characters to get back at someone else.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2898" parentid="2885" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>special squads</name>
<description>The Special Squads are called in when the police is completely outclassed, e.g. fighting criminal syndicates. These special forces are trained to combat specific forms of crime, e.g. the anti-cyber-crime division.
There are several such squads: Whereas Section 9 of Ghost in the Shell is an official government organisation, there are also "benevolent" vigilante groups like the Knight Sabers (Bubblegum Crisis).
Criminal syndicates also have their special forces e.g. "death squads".</description>
<picurl>238613.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2979" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-18">
<name>mutilation</name>
<description>Mutilation is an act of physical injury that degrades the appearance or function of any living body. Some ethnic groups practice ritual mutilation, e.g. scarification, burning, flagellation(whipping), tattooing, or wheeling, as part of a rite of passage. In some cases, the term may apply to treatment of dead bodies, such as soldiers mutilated after they have been killed by an enemy. Maiming, or mutilation which involves the loss of, or incapacity to use, a bodily member, is and has been practised by many societies with various cultural and religious significances, and is also a customary form of physical punishment, especially applied on the principle of "an eye for an eye".
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3075" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2013-02-27">
<name>nervous breakdown</name>
<description>A character sees his entire world being destroyed around him, and his brain can`t take it anymore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3314" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-10">
<name>fate</name>
<description>Fate — The predestined path of all things. The outcome is inevitable and the consequences predetermined. Whether or not the protagonist ultimately decides to follow this path shall weigh heavily on their soul.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3513" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-08-10">
<name>special bullet</name>
<description>Custom made bullets that have special effects (and often shapes, too), which take action when hitting the enemy/ally.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3580" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-01-05">
<name>cliffhanger ending</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3795" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>remastered version available</name>
<description>This anime has been remastered in a higher quality format than the original release. The remaster may be a simple upscale, or it could be a full enhancement project from the original frames. This is irrespective of whether specific groups have released rips of such formats to the internet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3809" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-05-24">
<name>character driven</name>
<description>The main appeal of the show is the way the characters are portrayed and interact, focusing on dialogue, spending time together or getting to know each other. These anime are not "story-less" but story is secondary to character development and the characters themselves and what they experience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3953" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-10-04">
<name>in medias res</name>
<description>In medias res, also medias in res (Latin for "into the midst of affairs (lit. into mid-affairs)"), refers to a literary and artistic technique where the narrative starts in the middle of the story instead of from its beginning. It is generally a plot-driven concept rather than a character-driven one; though characters are commonly used to provide the backstory. The characters, setting, and conflict are often introduced through a series of http://anidb.net/t4299 [flashbacks] or through characters relating past events to each other.
Probably originating from an oral tradition, the technique is a convention of epic poetry, one of the earliest and most prominent examples in Western literature being Homer`s Odyssey and Iliad. Virgil`s Aeneid began the tradition in literature of imitating Homer, continued in Torquato Tasso`s Jerusalem Delivered, John Milton`s Paradise Lost and "Inferno" from Dante`s Divine Comedy. George Lucas`s Star Wars saga was told using in medias res.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4057" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-02-19">
<name>magical creatures</name>
<description>Magical creatures are beings associated with a fantasy setting, thus do not exist in reality. Apparently they were "created of" or "powered by" magic. An incantation may have brought them into existence.
Examples: A legendary creature, a mythological or folkloric creature, a fairy or demon, ...</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4073" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-15">
<name>unusual weapons -- TO BE SPLIT AND DELETED</name>
<description>This anime tag is set to be split into multiple character tags. If you are sure of what existing tag to use, please apply it to the relevant characters and remove this one from the anime. On the other hand, if you know why this tag is applied and either expect a new tag will be necessary or don`t know how to handle the retagging, simply remove it from the anime and explain the case to the mod.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4096" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>gore</name>
<description>A Splatter film or Gore film is a sub-genre of horror film that deliberately focuses on graphic portrayals of gore and graphic violence. These films, through the use of special effects and excessive blood and guts, tend to display an overt interest in the vulnerability of the human body and the theatricality of its mutilation. Due to their willingness to portray images society might consider shocking, splatter films share some ideological grounds with the transgressive art movement. The term "splatter cinema" was coined by George A. Romero to describe his film Dawn of the Dead, though Dawn of the Dead is generally considered by critics to have higher aspirations, such as social commentary, than to be simply exploitative for its own sake.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>32491.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4153" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-03-15">
<name>dark</name>
<description>Describes the overall mood in this anime. Dark colours, a non-happy, often tragic story, dark lighting, many night scenes or constantly dark skies, and continuous rain all contribute to setting this mood.
The anime will often be quite depressing to watch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4170" parentid="5626" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-08-08">
<name>police are useless</name>
<description>The civilian law enforcement representatives do not seem to be of much use, when trying to take on the usually vastly superior foes.
The "helpless" and often clumsy antics of the police can be used as a comedy element.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4193" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-03-23">
<name>improbable physics</name>
<description>The physics in this anime have little to do with real-world physics, and are actually very much exaggerated.
Examples: Cars hitting a tiny obstacle, but then flying through the air for no apparent reason, or flimsy bullets slamming heavy characters clear across the room.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4226" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-21">
<name>paradise lost</name>
<description>Derived from the Biblical story of the Fall of Man: the temptation of Adam and Eve by the fallen angel Satan and their expulsion from the Garden of Eden.
This tag is used to demonstrate the unbearable loss, the feeling of losing everything along with every single bit of happiness. It prerequisites a small peaceful period of happiness. The main reason for losing "his/her paradise" can either be the death/sacrifice of an important character or even a betrayal. Usually the anime loses a lot of its former glory afterwards.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4228" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-11-09">
<name>subtle OP ED sequence change</name>
<description>A (small) part of the opening or ending sequence changes after a certain episode, usually to reflect a plot milestone.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4254" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-01-24">
<name>ghost hunting</name>
<description>Ghost Hunting is the process of investigating locations that are reported to be haunted by ghosts. Typically, a ghost hunting team will attempt to collect evidence claimed to be supportive of paranormal activity. Ghost hunters often utilize a variety of electronic equipment.
Traditional techniques such as conducting interviews and researching the history of a site are also employed. Some ghost hunters refer to themselves as a paranormal investigator.
While many groups claim to utilize scientific methods in their search for the ghosts, no scientific body has been able to confirm the existence of ghosts. Ghost hunting can be classified as a pseudoscience.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4314" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-04-11">
<name>psychological</name>
<description>Directed toward dealing with or affecting the mind, especially as a function of awareness, feeling, or motivation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4327" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-18">
<name>be careful what you wish for</name>
<description>Be careful what you wish for... your wish may actually come true. This is an age-old philosophical problem of what human beings think they want and what is actually good for them. The power to wish for anything can be very dangerous and usually — as a moral lesson — yields unexpected / unwanted results.
A contract with the devil is a specific case of this; receiving great power, especially from a devil, is usually a double edged sword.</description>
<picurl>230309.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4340" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-09-26">
<name>suicide</name>
<description>One or several characters in this anime commit suicide.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4386" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-19">
<name>eating Pocky</name>
<description>Pocky (ポッキー) is a Japanese snack food produced by the Ezaki Glico Company of Japan. Pocky was first sold in 1966, and consists of a biscuit stick coated with chocolate. It was named after the Japanese onomatopoetic word for the sound Pocky makes when bitten, pokkin (ポッキン). The original was followed by "Almond Pocky" in 1971, with an almond coating, and "Strawberry Pocky" in 1977. Today, the product line includes such variations as milk, mousse, green tea, honey, banana and coconut flavored coatings, and themed products such as "Decorer Pocky," with colourful decorative stripes in the coating, and "Men`s Pocky," a dark (bittersweet) chocolate and "mature" version.
Source: Wikipedia
It`s marketed in Germany under the name Mikado (Note: NOT the game, the snack).</description>
<picurl>73630.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4460" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-28">
<name>tsuchigumo</name>
<description>Tsuchigumo, literally translated "dirt spider", is the name for a race of spider-like youkai in Japanese folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4520" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>betrayal</name>
<description>Friends become enemies.
Strong bonds of trust receive violations of confidence while friendships are faithlessly given up or revealed to have been false from the start.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4537" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-15">
<name>time skip</name>
<description>The plot features at least one skip or jump in time.
Example: A skip from the present into the past, or time skips in increments, e.g. every hour there is a time skip by a day.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4566" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-05-08">
<name>transforming weapons</name>
<description>This anime features transforming weapons, this can either be cars or household appliances that transform into weapons, such as transformers or weapons that themselves transform into bigger badder shapes to deal more and more damage.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4722" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-07">
<name>omiai</name>
<description>One character promised to marry another one, either by free will (read: love), or due to external interference e.g. by parental "guidance".
This can be a comedy element, especially if both parties are less than thrilled by the prospect of marriage. There is also potential for embarrassment-related humour concerning the emotional interaction between the newly weds.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5626" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>adults are useless</name>
<description>For when adults can`t do anything right.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5638" parentid="5626" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-25">
<name>military is useless</name>
<description>The regular military force per se or certain units thereof are way out of their league when trying to take on the usually vastly superior foes (e.g. powerful aliens). Thus the regular military is completely useless. 
Often, only children (of all people) with special abilities and/or powered suits can defend Earth.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5781" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-08-01">
<name>exorcism</name>
<description>Eviction of demons or other spiritual entities from a person or place which they are believed to have possessed.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5821" parentid="5826" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true">
<name>sibling rivalry</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5826" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-12">
<name>rivalry</name>
<description>Quite broadly used term describing a conflict, contest, struggle, or opposition of some sort.
Typical examples: The mostly comedic rivalry for the love of a protagonist in a harem anime (love polygon), the more "mindless" battles between wannabe delinquents in a school fighting anime, or the struggle between good &amp; evil in an epic conflict for world domination.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5875" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-18">
<name>jealousy</name>
<description>A character is jealous of another character either due to love, or power, or wealth.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5889" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-05">
<name>magic weapons</name>
<description>The characters in this anime wield magic weapons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5935" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-07-06">
<name>ass-kicking girls</name>
<description>The female characters in the anime are very proficient in some form of martial arts, swordplay, or gunfights. They may also have super powers.</description>
<picurl>71307.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5954" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-17">
<name>call my name</name>
<description>"TETSUOOOOOO!!" "KANEDAAAAAA!!"
"TAMAHOMEEEE!!" "MIAKAAAA!!"
Feelings of any kind towards other characters are best shown by calling each other`s name, loud, REALLY LOUD. For better effect at least twice or thrice. For lover`s couples and mortal enemies it is a requirement to run towards each other while calling each other`s name, unaware of the surroundings.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5965" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2015-02-10">
<name>incomplete story</name>
<description>The show does not cover all of the original work (if present) or was cancelled prematurely, leaving plot lines unresolved or aborting character development. Sometimes the show runs through all its initially slotted episodes and adapts all of the original work (if applicable) but fails to present a proper ending, leaving viewers wondering whether they`re missing the final episodes.
In some cases, this may overlap with the studio forging an anime-original ending. Such an ending normally manages to allow the show to "finish", but may still suffer from incomplete story issues.
An incomplete storyline is not to be confused with the sequel bait, which is when the story presented by the show is finished but leaves enough room for a sequel to be produced. Sometimes this goes as far as to present a new potential problem in the last few minutes; that is usual for after-credits footage in movies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6062" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-04-05">
<name>heroic sacrifice</name>
<description>"In order to save the many, the few will need to sacrifice their lives..." or so this character may think. 
In a seemingly hopeless situation, against impossible odds, the character does not choose the path of the coward and run, he or she chooses to bravely face the enemy, fully aware that this will mean death.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6088" parentid="2785" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-01-29">
<name>unrequited shoujo ai</name>
<description>At least one female character has a romantic or sexual interest in another female character, but the feelings are not returned.
This can be because the recipient is oblivious, straight, or simply not interested.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6877" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-05-14">
<name>misleading beginning</name>
<description>The beginning of the show is misleading as to the tone, premise, or story path that the rest of the story will take. Sometimes, it even follows an entirely different cast that never appears again. This may take the form of the first episode or couple of episodes of a series or the first few minutes of e.g. a movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="2978" type="main character in" update="2010-08-21">
<rating votes="112">8.57</rating>
<name>Isayama Yomi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yomi lost her parents at a young age to specters, and was taken in by Isayama Naraku, then head of the Isayama family. Yomi grew to love and respect her foster-father, and polished her skills to repay him for his kindness. Her efforts led to her inheritance of the priced Isayama heirloom, the sword Shishio, which held the spiritual beast Nue in it. Before Naraku`s death, she was betrothed to Izuna Noriyuki and would have succeeded Naraku as the next Isayama head. However, Naraku`s death at the hands of her cousin Mei, who was jealous of her good fortune, and the alteration of Naraku`s will, resulted in her being stripped of her position in the family and therefore her entire inheritance. Yomi eventually found out the truth behind her father`s death, revealed by Mei herself after the latter lured her out in order to kill her. Partly in self-defense, she killed Mei and avenged Naraku, but was ambushed by Mitagawa Kazuhiro, who wounded her so badly that she became hospitalised, her throat and most of the tendons in her body cut and unrepairable, unable to talk or move. This, in addition to the suspicion that she had murdered Mei, led to a series of events that caused her to succumb to Mitagawa`s temptation to accept the sesshouseki. Though Yomi managed to retain some control over her mind, she had nonetheless fallen under the destructive influence of the stone, causing her to kill many many members of the Agency. Ultimately, it was her love and desire to protect Kagura that caused her death at Kagura`s hands, in a desperate wish that she could remove anything that would harm Kagura, including herself.</description>
<picture>18621.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1609" picture="19579.jpg">Mizuhara Kaoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2979" type="main character in" update="2009-02-08">
<rating votes="55">5.47</rating>
<name>Tsuchimiya Kagura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Always smiling, Kagura is the heroine of the story. She is feisty and ambitious and can put up a good fight with her spiritual beast, the Ga-Rei Byakuei, who resembles a large white dragon. She controls Byakuei from the seal on her back and a long chain that connects her soul to his, so any damage Byakuei receives also damages her as well.</description>
<picture>18622.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="245" picture="46862.jpg">Chihara Minori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2980" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-08">
<rating votes="13">3.66</rating>
<name>Izuna Noriyuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Underneath his perverted and cheerfully helpless façade, Izuna is very powerful, able to fight on equal terms with Yomi. He is very knowledgeable on the subject of spirits and is skilled in hojutsu. He treats Kagura like a little sister.</description>
<picture>18623.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1612" picture="129587.jpg">Takahashi Shin`ya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2981" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-08">
<rating votes="7">6.27</rating>
<name>Sakuraba Kazuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An agent of the Ministry. He is a young and sarcastic, annoying yet talented man around the same age as Noriyuki during the events of Ga-Rei -Zero-. Interestingly, his weapons are two suitcases that open up at the bottom to reveal rows of muzzles, a kind of multi-row gatling, which he also uses as melee weapons.</description>
<picture>18624.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="434" picture="41082.jpg">Shiraishi Minoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2982" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-08">
<rating votes="8">6.87</rating>
<name>Iwahata Kouji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An agent of the Ministry who dislikes Izuna. He is very tall and muscular, and a powerful spirit-user. He is an ex-soldier, and was hired by a mercenary corporation until the Agency recruited him for his ability to sense spirits.</description>
<picture>18625.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1616" picture="23191.jpg">Inada Tetsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2983" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-08">
<rating votes="5">4.70</rating>
<name>Nabu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Two large twin brothers who both have the same name, as they come from a culture that give twins the same name. Both brothers tend to finish each other`s sentences. Because they look identical, it leads some of their teammates to confusion.</description>
<picture>18626.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2" picture="16471.jpg">Wakamoto Norio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2984" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-08">
<rating votes="5">5.14</rating>
<name>Nabu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Two large twin brothers who both have the same name, as they come from a culture that give twins the same name. Both brothers tend to finish each other`s sentences. Because they look identical, it leads some of their teammates to confusion.</description>
<picture>18627.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2" picture="16471.jpg">Wakamoto Norio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2985" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-08">
<rating votes="9">5.98</rating>
<name>Jinguuji Ayame</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Minister of Environment during the events of Ga-Rei -Zero- and Fujiko Mine`s other granddaughter. Despite being confined to a wheelchair, she is nice and kind-hearted person with a relaxed air. While likeable, she is very serious and earns her respect from her subordinates. Her personal assistant is Kiri Nikaidou who she affectionately calls "Kiri-chan."</description>
<picture>18628.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="539" picture="228668.jpg">Aizawa Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2986" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-08">
<rating votes="10">6.75</rating>
<name>Nikaidou Kiri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ayame`s personal assistant who helps her in her duties as minister. She has a serious work attitude and is very loyal to her boss, Ayame, and doesn`t hesitate to scold others who disrespect her boss. She serves as the disciplinarian and the harsh voice of the Agency, in contrast to Ayame`s friendly attitude.</description>
<picture>18629.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1618" picture="158557.jpg">Tsuchiya Maki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2987" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-02-28">
<rating votes="6">5.08</rating>
<name>Isayama Naraku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yomi`s father.</description>
<picture>18630.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39" picture="16629.jpg">Mugihito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2988" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-02-28">
<rating votes="6">1.49</rating>
<name>Isayama Yuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Father of Mei.</description>
<picture>18631.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1416" picture="18579.jpg">Ishimori Takkou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2989" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-02-28">
<rating votes="17">3.43</rating>
<name>Isayama Mei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mei is the older cousin of Yomi. She is cool, powerful and is a freelance exorcist. Mei likes calming devil spirits by herself and her weapon is a beautiful spear. She is a bit jealous of Yomi who will be the next head of Isayama family, but she does not show her true feelings to anyone. Mei`s father is Isayama Yuu.
Source: BoxAnimeManga</description>
<picture>18632.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1617" picture="19642.jpg">Tanaka Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2990" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-02-28">
<rating votes="10">6.95</rating>
<name>Tsuchimiya Garaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kagura`s father.</description>
<picture>18633.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1621" picture="28482.jpg">Komura Tetsuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2991" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-09">
<rating votes="8">6.10</rating>
<name>Michael Kohara</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A large man from Australia who speaks bad Japanese with a foreign accent, frequently mixing in some English words. He is Iwahata`s master and the creator of most of the Ministry of Environment`s weapons from the practical guns and swords, to the often bizarre irons and boilers. Because of his appearance, he tends to be arrested by the police for indecent exposure. Despite being outlandish, he is greatly respected in the Agency for his skill, his creations famed for their ability to augment the user`s spiritual output by several times. He possesses mid-tier spiritual abilities.</description>
<picture>18634.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1613" picture="158486.jpg">Hiramatsu Hirokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2992" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-02-28">
<rating votes="7">3.20</rating>
<name>Yanase Chizuru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Classmate of Kagura.</description>
<picture>18635.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1611" picture="70006.jpg">Horikawa Chika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2993" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-02-28">
<rating votes="6">3.83</rating>
<name>Manabe Miku</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Classmate of Kagura.</description>
<picture>18636.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1444" picture="172066.jpg">Masu Nozomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2994" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-09">
<rating votes="10">1.83</rating>
<name>Mitogawa Kazuhiro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A boy who used to belong to the Agency. He was enthralled by the sesshouseki, hoping to use the Kyuubi`s powers to revive his mother, an exorcist who had been previously killed in action. When Lady Tamamo appeared to him in the Vatican`s library, he willingly became one of her minions, sparking off the events in Ga-Rei -Zero- and the first 7 volumes of the manga.</description>
<picture>18637.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="435" picture="188447.jpg">Matsumoto Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47261" type="appears in" update="2013-05-08">
<rating votes="1">1.57</rating>
<name>Nimura Kensuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The protagonist, an ordinary high school student who has had the ability to see ghosts ever since he was a kid. Because of this, he always felt different, but things changed after meeting Kagura. He started practicing kendo from a young age, being the son of a kendo instructor, and utilizes his skills during missions. When fighting, he sometimes dons a pair of sunglasses. The storyline concerns his growth as a spirit-user, his main weapon being swords. He initially wields "Michael #12," but after breaking it in a battle, is given the sword "Michael Revolution" in its place. He supports Kagura during her emotional lows, and a bond develops between them.
Kensuke has the same sesshouseki that transformed Yomi into an evil spirit, embedded near his heart. According to Yomi, the sesshouseki itself wished to be placed there. The stone gifts him with memories, as well as allowing his sword techniques to become radically more powerful. This stone was later removed when Imawano Setsuna forcefully tore it from his body in the Garden of Tamamo, fatally damaging his body in the process. He survived after Kagura defeated Setsuna and revived the Kyuubi, using its powers to restore his body from the brink of death. After firming his resolve to save Kagura from being controlled by the Kyuubi, he unleashes the true power of the Michael Revolution, the ability to cut through dimensions.
Kagura mentions that Kensuke has a unique presence which puts spirits at ease and even Byakuei feels more secure when Kensuke is near.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>91521.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="434" picture="41082.jpg">Shiraishi Minoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47267" type="appears in" update="2013-02-28">
<name>Izuna Norisada</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Noriyuki`s father.</description>
<picture>91506.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3323" picture="24340.jpg">Shiroyama Ken</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47268" type="appears in" update="2013-02-28">
<rating votes="1">2.03</rating>
<name>Nakabayashi Misuzu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>School nurse.</description>
<picture>91508.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="295" picture="25758.jpg">Shinohara Emi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47269" type="appears in" update="2012-07-25">
<rating votes="1">1.57</rating>
<name>Itabashi Kana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91509.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1888" picture="228611.jpg">Masuda Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47270" type="appears in" update="2012-07-25">
<rating votes="2">4.11</rating>
<name>Kanze Tooru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91511.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="612" picture="79531.jpg">Maeno Tomoaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47271" type="appears in" update="2013-02-28">
<rating votes="9">4.87</rating>
<name>Kasuga Natsuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She rides a motorcycle with runes on the wheels.</description>
<picture>91512.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="401" picture="223216.jpg">Kitamura Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47272" type="appears in" update="2012-07-25">
<rating votes="2">4.11</rating>
<name>Shindou Masaki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91513.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="174" picture="41158.jpg">Kakihara Tetsuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47273" type="appears in" update="2012-07-25">
<rating votes="2">4.11</rating>
<name>Kuzuno Kudou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91514.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="244" picture="23860.jpg">Koyama Rikiya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47274" type="appears in" update="2012-07-25">
<rating votes="2">4.11</rating>
<name>Konparu Kiriya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91515.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="398" picture="17243.jpg">Miyamoto Mitsuru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47275" type="appears in" update="2012-07-25">
<rating votes="6">5.26</rating>
<name>Izumi Mami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91517.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="89" picture="148709.jpg">Yahagi Sayuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47276" type="appears in" update="2012-07-25">
<rating votes="1">1.57</rating>
<name>Shouboushi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91518.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="260" picture="17083.jpg">Aizawa Masaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47277" type="appears in" update="2012-07-25">
<name>Sensei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91520.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2501" picture="191381.jpg">Yoshikai Kiyohito</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="93218" update="2011-02-11">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="1">5.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="93320" update="2017-07-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-10-06</airdate>
<rating votes="39">8.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">葵 上 -あおいのうえ-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Above Aoi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aoi no Ue</title>
<summary>An elite squadron trained to combat the supernatural responds to reports of invisible monsters terrorizing Tokyo. Their mission is complicated by the appearance of blue butterflies and a katana-wielding mystery woman.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="93530" update="2017-07-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-10-13</airdate>
<rating votes="25">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">憎 発露 -にくしみのはつろ-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Expression of Hatred</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nikushimi no Hatsuro</title>
<summary>A rival supernatural commando squad, the SDCD, is called in to clean up the mess left behind by their counterparts. What they discover will leave them reeling in disbelief. Could one of their own be responsible for the massacre?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="93531" update="2017-07-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-10-20</airdate>
<rating votes="22">6.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">邂逅 砌 -かいこうのみぎり-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Times of the Chance Encounter</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaikou No Migiri</title>
<summary>As the story reverts to the past, a young Kagura is welcomed to her new home by none other than Yomi. The two girls forge a fast friendship that can only be interrupted by the occasional exorcism.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="93532" update="2017-07-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-10-27</airdate>
<rating votes="21">5.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">務 大義 -つとめのたいぎ-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Cause of the Duty</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsutome no Taigi</title>
<summary>Yomi and Kagura venture into the darkest depths of the subway to exterminate a hoard of evil spirits. When the demons begin to look too human, Kagura hesitates and only an unforgiving ally can save her.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="93723" update="2017-07-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-11-03</airdate>
<rating votes="20">6.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">頑 想 -かたくなのおもい-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Obstinate Feelings</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Katakuna no Omoi</title>
<summary>Kagura and her comrades hatch a scheme that could bring two reluctant lovers together. Meanwhile, a rogue exorcist attempts to steal Yomi’s place in the family business.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="93727" update="2017-07-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-11-10</airdate>
<rating votes="16">7.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">美 敵 -うつくしのてき-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Beautiful Enemy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Utsukushi no Teki</title>
<summary>A flock of mysterious blue butterflies marks the arrival of a white-haired boy with the power to attract evil spirits. Elsewhere, Kagura must overcome her tendency to hesitate in battle if she wants to save her friends.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="95119" update="2017-07-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-11-17</airdate>
<rating votes="14">6.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">呵責連鎖 -かしゃくのれんさ-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Chains of Blame</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kashaku no Rensa</title>
<summary>Kagura is reduced to hysterics after executing the school nurse, and Yomi’s world is shattered by a treacherous act of betrayal. Can the two young exorcists find the strength to resume their duties?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="95158" update="2017-07-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-11-24</airdate>
<rating votes="18">7.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">復讐行方 -ふくしゅうのゆくえ-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Whereabouts of Revenge</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fukushuu no Yukue</title>
<summary>Following the gruesome murder of her father, Yomi is dispossessed by her greedy uncle. Seething with anger, she embarks on a maniacal quest for vengeance that could ruin her forever.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="95592" update="2017-07-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-12-01</airdate>
<rating votes="18">6.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">罪 螺旋 -つみのらせん-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Spiral of Sin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsumi no Rasen</title>
<summary>Yomi lies comatose in a hospital bed, her body broken beyond repair. When she finally wakes, painful truths come to light that threaten to sever any connection to those she once loved.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="95593" update="2017-07-20">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-12-08</airdate>
<rating votes="17">8.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">悲劇 裏 -ひげきのうら-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Other Side of the Tragedy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Higeki no Ura</title>
<summary>The action has come full circle, and the painful truth can no longer be avoided. Yomi’s soul is consumed by evil; Noriyuki and Kagura must stop her murderous rampage - or watch their few remaining friends die in vain.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="95594" update="2017-07-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-12-15</airdate>
<rating votes="20">6.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">運命 乱 -うんめいのみだれ-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Turmoil of Fates</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Unmei no Midare</title>
<summary>When Kagura’s father proves unable to stop Yomi’s killing spree, the director and her dwindling SDCD counterattack unit mobilize in a daring attempt to forever silence their former comrade.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="95595" update="2017-07-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-12-22</airdate>
<rating votes="19">8.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">祈 焦 -いのりのこがれ-</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yearning Prayer</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Inori no Kogare</title>
<summary>The SDCD gets a lock on Yomi’s location, and Kagura sets out to cut down the monster she once considered her sister. Should she fail, the end of the world will surely follow.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="103878" update="2010-05-26">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-10-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="103879" update="2010-08-31">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-10-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="121633" update="2011-02-11">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="2">3.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">TV-CM スポット集</title>
<title xml:lang="en">TV-CM Spot Collection</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">TV-CM Spot Shuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128176" update="2011-02-12">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">5.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">番宣スポット</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV Collection</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bansen Spot</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128177" update="2011-02-12">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2008-12-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223601" update="2019-10-26">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>20</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Location Scouting #1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223602" update="2019-10-26">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Location Scouting #2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223603" update="2019-10-26">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>20</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Location Scouting #3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223604" update="2019-10-26">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>22</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Location Scouting #4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223605" update="2019-10-26">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Location Scouting #5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223606" update="2019-10-26">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>20</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Location Scouting #6</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
