<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="7221" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2010-02-06</startdate>
<enddate>2010-02-06</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Suzumiya Haruhi no Shoushitsu</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">The Vanishment of Haruhi Suzumiya</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Vanishment of Haruhi Suzumiya</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="synonym">La scomparsa di Haruhi Suzumiya</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="synonym">Zniknięcie Haruhi Suzumii</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="synonym">O Desaparecimento de Suzumiya Haruhi</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="synonym">O Desaparecimento de Haruhi Suzumiya</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Зникнення Харухі Судзумії</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">Haruhi Movie</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">涼宮ハルヒの消失</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">The Disappearance of Haruhi Suzumiya</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Das Verschwinden der Haruhi Suzumiya</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">La Disparition de Haruhi Suzumiya</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Исчезновение Харухи Судзумии</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">스즈미야 하루히의 소실</title>
<title xml:lang="et" type="official">Haruhi Suzumiya kadumine</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">凉宫春日的消失</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="6367" type="Prequel">Suzumiya Haruhi no Yuuutsu (2009)</anime>
<anime id="10815" type="Alternative Setting">Nagato Yuki-chan no Shoushitsu</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="7729" approval="14" total="31">Steins;Gate</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="41">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="478043">If you watched the anime, then you definitely need to watch this. It is, simply put, outstanding. The visuals, the music, the story, the characters... everything just blends together perfectly to make one of the best anime movies I`ve seen.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="272736">this is pretty much what fans of original was wondering about or wanting to see. If u did like the tv series but wanted too see characters in different setting i advise to watch this. other than that it dont offer anything else.

p.s. personally i would like to see how their relationships progress.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="63560">Absolutely the best of the Haruhi anime, It`s a Wonderful Life meets Japan</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="337940">Unfortunately this movie doesn`t deserve the high rating it has on this site.  The story isn`t as exciting or intriguing as you`d expect from a movie.  The animation is on par with the series.  And to top it all off, it`s 2.5 hours long.  Definitely worth watching for fans, but terribly overrated.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="548718">If you, like me, were disappointed by the wasted opportunities the series suffered from, watch this. It makes up even for having put up with endless Eight. Honestly, it made putting up with Haruhi at its worst totally worth it. However, make sure you watch the series first or this movie will make little to no sense.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="289922">Overall the Suzumiya Haruhi franchise has had some issues with adaptations from novel to anime form.  This movie has managed to be the best part of the anime franchise to date with the possible exception of the Melancholy episodes of the first series.  It is really worth the watch, though at least some familiarity with the series helps.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="90098">I think this is a movie worth seeing, i dont really get the rating beeing so high but i did enjoy this movie and i do recommend it, but hardly a masterpiece as the rating would suggest. You will have fun watching it though so go for it :)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="432445">Told with a more serious tone compared to the main series, this adventure centers around Yuki and understanding her feelings for Kyon. The focus shifts towards mystery and finding solutions to a sci-fi dilemma, and away from action and comic elements. Nevertheless, fans of the franchise as well as newcomers won`t be disappointed. The score is gold, comprising both the contemporary and classical, and the animation is vivid and exceptional.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="109384">It is simply perfect! you must see it. I am telling you, you must see it!  Also, it is a sequel, so you will appreciate it more if you have seen 2009.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="390668">Except for some minor flaws, it`s absolutely stunning. Recommended to all fans and, why not, to the ones who haven`t seen Haruhi`s series before. I suggest you to watch the series first and then this movie. You wouldn`t regret this.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="366429">Watch it!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="281942">absolutely awesome</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="296063">Forget the "endless eight" fiasco. This movie brings back the awesomeness of the original series, with an improved animation and a great story.

The 160 minutes are well worth it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="126534">Excellent go for it :)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="203171">A must-see for everyone who has seen the series. Only if entire series were THAT epic...</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="491976">Everything about this movie is amazing. A true masterpiece!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="487479">Amazing followup to the perplexing story of Suzumiya Haruhi. This movie is top-notch, with an amazing visuals, plot and overall awesomeness.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="479272">it`s just great. no matter liked u tv series or ot, just watch.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="565692">if you are a fan, see it. if you have no clue what this is about, see the serie then see the movie. 

Best way 2 sum up this movie "M.A.S.T.E.R.P.i.E.C.E"</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="411316">Incredibly well-written story, voice acting and animation. Must see for anyone who enjoys deep story-lines, but I highly recommend watching the original series first, for reasons that will appear obvious once you start watching "Shoushitsu". 
One of my all-time favorite works, including all novels and mangas I`ve read aswell as all animes/films I`ve watched.
PS: Make sure you watch until after the ending credits ;)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="727529">don`t even think about watching this before Suzumiya Haruhi no Yuuutsu (2009) - you will regret it after realizing what kind of experience you`ve missed.

you have been warned.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="367685">You pretty much have to watch the series first, or you will have no clue what`s going on. But it is totally worth it. This movie is awesome. A very deep plot and surprising twists and the animation is top notch. This movie alone makes the entire series worth watching.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="464612">It is a must see for fans! Wonderful animation and voice acting as usual, but even more astounding was the character development in Kyon and Yuki here. Absorbing plot with new insights that will make you want to rewatch some episodes, and made me cry a few times too.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="335160">Classic Haruhi with an edge!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="417094">If you any anyway enjoyed the first two seasons of this anime you owe to yourself to watch this. It will make you both laugh and cry and show some new sides to a few well-known characters. Truly a masterpiece.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="458036">Incredible story telling and nice animation makes it the best of 2010 (imo). Watch it and you won`t be regretted.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="319479">It totally makes up for Endlesssssssssssssss8, 8 times over. For those who had gave up on Haruhi because of the second seasons, this is a must see, your fate will be rekindle.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="296539">A definite must-see for anyone who watched TV series of Haruhi. This movie completely makes up for Endless Eight.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="78827">Don`t miss out on this superb movie - but don`t watch it until you`ve watched the series.  The best anime work of 2010 for me.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="365611">This is the best story about Suzumiya Haruhi. This is the best KyoAni’s amine. What else must I say?</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="478847">Actually my favourite movie, not just anime, but movie in general. I was especially pleased with the length, because I usually feel movies with a complex storyline rush too much, but this one took its time and it ended up being perfect. 

Big warning: dont even think about watching this before seeing the tv show! (at least the 14eps from the first season + Bamboo Leaf Rhapsody from season 2)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="311692">Simply legendary.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.kyotoanimation.co.jp/haruhi/movie/index.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="736" type="Animation Work">Kyoto Animation</name>
<name id="523" type="Character Design">Ikeda Shouko</name>
<name id="536" type="Original Work">Tanigawa Nagaru</name>
<name id="533" type="Direction">Takemoto Yasuhiro</name>
<name id="519" type="Chief Direction">Ishihara Tatsuya</name>
<name id="530" type="Music">Kousaki Satoru</name>
<name id="529" type="Chief Animation Direction">Nishiya Futoshi</name>
<name id="12463" type="Music">Erik Satie</name>
<name id="24464" type="Music">Ishihama Kakeru</name>
<name id="13539" type="Music">Takada Ryuuichi</name>
<name id="14377" type="Music">Hoashi Keigo</name>
<name id="523" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ikeda Shouko</name>
</creators>
<description>* Adaptation of http://anidb.net/cr536 [Tanigawa Nagaru]`s fourth Suzumiya Haruhi light novel.
It is mid-December, and SOS Brigade chief http://anidb.net/ch271 [Suzumiya Haruhi] announces that the brigade is going to hold a Christmas party in their clubroom, with Japanese hotpot for dinner. The brigade members http://anidb.net/ch272 [Kyon], http://anidb.net/ch274 [Nagato Yuki], http://anidb.net/ch278 [Asahina Mikuru] and http://anidb.net/ch349 [Koizumi Itsuki] start preparing everything for the party, such as costumes and decorations. But a couple of days later, Kyon arrives at school only to find that Haruhi is missing. Not only that, but Mikuru claims she has never known Kyon before, Koizumi is also missing, and Yuki has become the sole member of the literature club. The SOS Brigade seems to have never existed, nor has Suzumiya Haruhi. No one in the school has ever heard about her... except for Kyon.
Now it is up to him to travel back through time to find Haruhi and correct the temporal anomaly.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="5967">9.39</permanent>
<temporary count="6021">8.71</temporary>
<review count="5">8.09</review>
</ratings>
<picture>133464.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11120</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7311</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4582</identifier>
<identifier>hkyxwn</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.kyotoanimation.co.jp/haruhi/movie/index.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>The_Disappearance_of_Haruhi_Suzumiya</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>涼宮ハルヒの消失</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2185</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>335453</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12253</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="464" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-01-15">
<name>sarcastic</name>
<description>The character frequently uses sharp, bitter, or cutting expressions or remarks. (From Greek sarcasmos, "to tear flesh, gnash the teeth, speak bitterly".)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2637" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>time travel</name>
<description>In time travel anime characters are transported through time either figuratively or literally to find themselves either in the past or the future</description>
<picurl>210068.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2838" parentid="2628" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>parallel world</name>
<description>A parallel world, parallel universe, or alternative reality is a self-contained separate reality coexisting with our own. Because "alternative reality" sometimes implies that the reality is a variant of our own, like for example a mirror world, we use the term "parallel world/universe" which is more general, without any connotations implying a relationship (or lack thereof) with our own world/universe (meaning a fictional world can just as well have an alternative reality, it doesn`t need to be our reality). To put it more simply, this category is to show if more than 1 world/universe/reality is present in the anime.
Multiple timelines of the same world/universe/reality are NOT considered parallel worlds. For example, in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate] the cast travels through multiple "World Lines", which are defined as parallel timelines of the same universe had various events occurred with differing outcomes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3007" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-07-16">
<name>monologues</name>
<description>This show features a noticeable amount of screen time during which characters talk to themselves. That is usually a way to display to the viewers what the characters are thinking. When used in excess, it may be a sign of poor storytelling, but when done skillfully, it may be excellent comedy fuel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3028" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-17">
<name>real-world location</name>
<description>Places seen in the show exist in reality.
Note: This could be sometime in the future, though names and certain places will still be recognizable.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3314" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-10">
<name>fate</name>
<description>Fate — The predestined path of all things. The outcome is inevitable and the consequences predetermined. Whether or not the protagonist ultimately decides to follow this path shall weigh heavily on their soul.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3795" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>remastered version available</name>
<description>This anime has been remastered in a higher quality format than the original release. The remaster may be a simple upscale, or it could be a full enhancement project from the original frames. This is irrespective of whether specific groups have released rips of such formats to the internet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3813" parentid="6185" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-23">
<name>winter</name>
<description>Coldest season of the year with ice and snow, everything is covered in a blanket of white.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3836" parentid="3314" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-28">
<name>the chosen one!</name>
<description>One of the characters in the anime is the "chosen one", the one to bring about change, the only one to "set things right" in a "good" ending, or bring about complete destruction in a "bad" ending.</description>
<picurl>66957.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4417" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>existentialism</name>
<description>Most commonly defines the rejection of a god and any transcendent will that dictates how humans should live. It rejects any "created" meaning of life and the world, stating a leap of faith is required to live an authentic life. In this existentialism, belief in a god is often considered a form of Bad Faith.
In length, the Absurd contains ideas that there is no meaning in the world beyond what meaning it`s given. Meaninglessness also encompasses amorality or "unfairness" of the world. This contrasts with "karmic" ways of thinking in which "bad things don`t happen to good people"; there is no such thing as a good person or a bad thing; what happens happens, and it may just as well happen to a good person as to a bad person. This contrasts daily experience where most things appear meaningful, and where good people receive a "reward" for goodness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4499" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-07-28">
<name>some weird shit goin` on</name>
<description>Scenes of this show point to insanely strange events which seem to be taking place; throughout its episodes, the show may or may not explain what is going on. Either way, many viewers will find that a succinct and accurate way to describe the show is "WTF?", and the show`s explanations (or lack thereof) to the events will often be subject of heated debate.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4614" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>narration</name>
<description>The most common example is that of a voice, either that of one of the characters or entirely unrelated, that appears at the beginning of an episode to offer a summary or introduction, and at the end of an episode for closure or for a preview to hint upon what to expect next.
Another use of narration comes in the form of a dominant voice belonging to one of the protagonists, intended only for the viewer and revealing the intimate thoughts to whom it belongs. This type of narration occurs frequently throughout the duration of the episode or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5881" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-07">
<name>childhood memory</name>
<description>The childhood memory of one of the protagonists plays an important part as plot device in this anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5980" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-24">
<name>live-action imagery</name>
<description>This anime incorporates still images and/or video footage of real-world objects and locations into the animation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6055" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-15">
<name>time loop</name>
<description>A time loop is a common plot device in science fiction (especially in universes where time travel is commonplace). Events in the story repeat themselves a number of times with or without some variation with each pass. Most characters either do not realise this is occurring or are attempting to break the cycle in some way. 
One well-known example of this is in the 1993 film Groundhog Day, in which the main character is the only one aware of the time loop, although time loops had appeared in many fictional works prior to that. Stories with time loops commonly center on correcting past mistakes or on getting a character to recognise some key truth; escape from the loop may then follow.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="271" type="main character in" update="2015-03-25">
<rating votes="1798">7.02</rating>
<name>Suzumiya Haruhi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>In the beginning of the story, she is initially shown as anti-social and displayed various personality quirks, but as the series progressed, she became more open with her emotions, whilst still remaining highly active. She became the founder of, and recruiter for, the SOS Brigade, forcibly enlisting Kyon, Yuki Nagato (the only member of the Literature Club), Mikuru Asahina, and Itsuki Koizumi. She is responsible for organizing most of their activities as a group.
Unknown to her, she has the power to change, destroy, or create a new reality based on her inner desires and feelings. She is described in various ways; Yuki states that she has `the potential for auto-evolution`, Mikuru believes that she is the originator of a large time-quake and finally Itsuki declares her to be `God`. Due to this, she is the main focus of the Integrated Data Entity, the Organization, and an organization of future humans.</description>
<picture>10490.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="4" picture="177060.jpg">Hirano Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="272" type="main character in" update="2015-03-25">
<rating votes="1318">8.81</rating>
<name>Kyon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kyon is one of Haruhi`s companions, and the second founding member of the SOS Brigade. Upon his entry into high school, he resigns himself to a lifestyle where his adolescent fantasies such as aliens, time travelers, and espers have no place. After one small conversation with him, Haruhi unexpectedly opened up to him and dragged him into her new club. His reputation and fate have since become entangled with Haruhi`s.</description>
<picture>60733.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="45" picture="44970.jpg">Sugita Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="274" type="main character in" update="2015-03-25">
<rating votes="1367">8.80</rating>
<name>Nagato Yuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yuki is initially portrayed as an introverted, taciturn bibliophile. She is actually an artificial human created by the Integrated Data Entity, and possesses supernatural powers as a result. She joins Haruhi Suzumiya`s SOS Brigade in order to observe her on the behalf of the Integrated Data Entity. In addition, she is present to ensure that Haruhi does not use her godlike powers, and aids the other Brigade members in stopping forces that wish her to do so.</description>
<picture>31404.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="245" picture="46862.jpg">Chihara Minori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="278" type="main character in" update="2015-03-25">
<rating votes="498">6.09</rating>
<name>Asahina Mikuru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mikuru is the only character other than Kyon to be brought into the SOS Brigade against her will. She is defined by Kyon to be extremely cute, and is often sexually harassed by Haruhi Suzumiya. She is in fact a time traveler from the future with the purpose of observing Haruhi Suzumiya during the course of the story line.</description>
<picture>168976.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="248" picture="45126.jpg">Gotou Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="280" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-03-25">
<rating votes="379">7.92</rating>
<name>Tsuruya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tsuruya is the hyperactive friend of Mikuru (from the current time plane) notable for her loud voice, knee-length hair, and prominent tooth. She possesses a cheerful and friendly disposition. She is also prone to long fits of unrestrained and intense laughter at things she considers even the slightest bit humorous.</description>
<picture>54844.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="392" picture="17237.jpg">Matsuoka Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="349" type="main character in" update="2015-03-25">
<rating votes="341">4.89</rating>
<name>Koizumi Itsuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Itsuki is the last member to have joined the SOS Brigade, having been recruited by Haruhi as a "mysterious transfer student". Itsuki was sent to observe and keep Haruhi emotionally stable, in order to protect the rest of humanity. Although he is an esper, which is exactly one of the sorts of people Haruhi desires to meet, Itsuki never reveals himself as such, at least, not to her.</description>
<picture>10347.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="250" picture="157976.jpg">Ono Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="361" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-09-11">
<rating votes="252">6.18</rating>
<name>Asakura Ryouko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ryouko appears to be a compassionate and hard-working high school girl. One of Kyon`s friends, Taniguchi, places her in the top three first-year girls in the school with a grade of A++: indicative of her pleasant personality, beauty, and athleticism. Her enormous popularity made her the unanimous choice for class president of Kyon`s homeroom class. She also showed particular concern about how Haruhi had distanced herself from the rest of the class.</description>
<picture>54846.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="328" picture="17164.jpg">Kuwatani Natsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="372" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-03-25">
<rating votes="64">3.75</rating>
<name>Kunikida</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kunikida plays a minor role and does not contribute much dialogue. However since he and Kyon went to the same junior high school, he might know more about Kyon since he once stated that "Kyon likes weird girls," as evidence to support the idea that Kyon is romantically interested in Haruhi. His character is also shown to be smarter than his friends Taniguchi and Kyon, at one time explaining a difficult concept to Taniguchi. Kunikida is also included in certain SOS Brigade activities when there is a shortage of people.</description>
<picture>14656.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="435" picture="188447.jpg">Matsumoto Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="378" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-03-25">
<rating votes="113">4.46</rating>
<name>Taniguchi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Taniguchi is comically lascivious; he gave a `score` of attractiveness to each first-year girl based upon his tastes and preferences. He remembers the full names of everyone receiving an `A` rank, with Ryouko receiving an AA+ and Nagato receiving an A-. As for Mikuru, her mere presence elicits an altered state of adoration for Taniguchi and Kunikida, especially when she was in her soba-serving costume. He also knew Haruhi from back in junior high, and was Kyon`s original source of information on Haruhi before he started conversing with her. It is hinted that he may have been the person that dated Haruhi for the shortest amount of time.</description>
<picture>14661.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="434" picture="41082.jpg">Shiraishi Minoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="422" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-22">
<rating votes="134">6.81</rating>
<name>Kyon no Imouto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Not much is revealed about Kyon`s fifth-grade sister; not even her real name is given. Other characters simply refer to the ten-year-old as Kyon`s (Younger) Sister or Little Sis.
She is carefree, happy and playful and is also the force behind the use of the nickname "Kyon"; after she heard their aunt call her older brother such, she started using the nickname as well in front of his school friends. From there, the name spread and eventually stuck. She seems to get along well with all of the SOS Brigade, especially with Mikuru and Tsuruya, sharing a sister-like relationship with them.</description>
<picture>209815.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="410" picture="228116.jpg">Aoki Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="915" type="appears in" update="2013-06-22">
<rating votes="21">4.40</rating>
<name>Okabe</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The homeroom teacher of Kyon and Haruhi`s class. In charge of the handball club at the school. First name remains unknown.</description>
<picture>60589.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="438" picture="25479.jpg">Yanagisawa Eiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="916" type="appears in" update="2017-12-08">
<rating votes="60">5.51</rating>
<name>Shamisen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A stray cat selected by Haruhi to play the role of Yuki`s familiar for their film The Adventures of Mikuru Asahina, Shamisen is unusual in the sense that he is a male calico cat. During the filming of the movie, Haruhi`s reality-altering powers temporarily give Shamisen the ability to speak. He is adopted by Kyon after the completion of the movie, and is given the nickname "Shami" by his sister.</description>
<picture>210388.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="8633" type="appears in" update="2009-06-06">
<rating votes="105">6.61</rating>
<name>Asahina Mikuru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An older, adult Mikuru from farther into the future traveled back in time to give Kyon some critical information regarding future events relative to his time span.
However, like her younger time-variant, she was still unable to go into much detail and was only able to provide short, rather vague pieces of information. Also, she was strictly prohibited from letting her younger self become aware of her presence in the same time and had to plan accordingly.</description>
<picture>27900.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="111713" update="2015-06-23">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>165</length>
<airdate>2010-02-06</airdate>
<rating votes="23">9.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112200" update="2014-03-21">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2009-12-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">劇場予告</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gekijou Yokoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112204" update="2014-03-21">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<rating votes="1">8.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">特報</title>
<title xml:lang="en">CM (15s)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tokuhou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="128970" update="2014-03-21">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">特報</title>
<title xml:lang="en">CM (30s)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tokuhou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="158532" update="2014-03-21">
<epno type="4">T8</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">商品CM</title>
<title xml:lang="en">DVD/BD CM (15s)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shouhin CM</title>
</episode>
<episode id="158533" update="2014-03-21">
<epno type="4">T7</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">TVスポット</title>
<title xml:lang="en">TV Spot 2 (30s)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">TV Spot</title>
</episode>
<episode id="158534" update="2014-03-21">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">TVスポット</title>
<title xml:lang="en">TV Spot 2 (15s)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">TV Spot</title>
</episode>
<episode id="158535" update="2014-03-21">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">TVスポット</title>
<title xml:lang="en">TV Spot 1 (30s)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">TV Spot</title>
</episode>
<episode id="158536" update="2014-03-21">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">TVスポット</title>
<title xml:lang="en">TV Spot 1 (15s)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">TV Spot</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
