<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8276" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2012-07-02</startdate>
<enddate>2012-09-17</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Jinrui wa Suitai Shimashita</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Mankind Has Fallen</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="synonym">El declive de la humanidad</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Човечеството запада</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="short">人退</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Jintai</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">人類は衰退しました</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Humanity Has Declined</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">인류는 쇠퇴했습니다</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="official">人類衰退之後</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">人类衰退之后</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="9002" approval="4" total="20">Shinsekai yori</anime>
<anime id="10811" approval="1" total="8">Yurikuma Arashi</anime>
<anime id="12007" approval="1" total="6">Flip Flappers</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="17">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="160474">Not too bad. Best is the Time Management and Survival Skills.

Somewhat slow and random. It is worth a watch, but also you do not loose that much if you skip.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="508247">in short words , its an awesome series. but its awesome for those who can appreciate black comedy and dark humor , the execution is brilliant , unmatched in my opinion by any other anime.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="129342">I don`t know why I it`s rated so low.. I really enjoyed the series.. The main character is very unique, interesting and has reflective nature. And a lot whimsical, fun seeking fairies.
It`s a slow paced easy watch.. parodying our society.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="277196">This anime is a parody about our society, its not for everyone, many will not even understand it, and maybe this can be the reason why the rating is so low. its really clever and well presented.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="537553">This anime feels like an adventure with fun oozing of every corner, set in a world where barely anything makes any sense yet has a familiar tone to it. Stuff that happens are intriguing yet comical and funny, all boosted by the main character`s carefree personality (which was voiced by the same voice actor that did Rena from Higurashi). It`s fun because you never know what`ll happen next where you have tiny fairies with no care in the world, skinned chickens trying to take over humanity, a living hair with a mind of its own, glasses that translates everything literally.... etc, you get my point.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="426878">This is a great series. Its funny and dark and crazy and cute and wonderful all at the same time. If you like anime with strange plots then go for this one.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="71577">This anime is awesomely refreshing. Don`t judge a book by its cover - the art-style and the description might not be very convincing about this, but this series relies heavily on dark humor, mind-fuck elements and even some serious philosophical questions (it`s a very interesting combination with that artwork, trust me). The main protagonist and her hilarious remarks make this great series even more awesome, a must see I say.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="200413">Just one word ... AWESOME</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="121887">An intellectual anime with a philosophical bent without all the big words that typically come with that. Clever humor, high in irony, gentle pastel tones pleasing to the eye. Episodic in nature, doesn`t come with an overarching plotline and airs out of chronological order, but works just fine regardless. One of the must see shows of it`s season.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="131503">If you are looking for something new then start to watch it now!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>https://www.marv.jp/special/jintai/</url>
<creators>
<name id="3519" type="Character Design">Sakai Kyuuta</name>
<name id="1540" type="Series Composition">Uezu Makoto</name>
<name id="4489" type="Direction">Kishi Seiji</name>
<name id="3519" type="Chief Animation Direction">Sakai Kyuuta</name>
<name id="910" type="Work">AIC A.S.T.A</name>
<name id="4144" type="Music">Ootani Kou</name>
<name id="1650" type="Chief Animation Direction">Itou Kouji</name>
<name id="23714" type="Original Work">Tanaka Romeo</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on http://anidb.net/cr23714 [Tanaka Romeo]`s light novel series with illustrations by Yamasaki Tooru / http://anidb.net/cr29908 [Tobe Sunaho].
The story is set several centuries into the slow decline of mankind. Earth has now become the realm of "fairies" — 10-centimetre-tall creatures with remarkable intelligence and an appetite for sweets. The human protagonist of the story serves an important duty as the international arbitrator between the fairies and humans, and she returns to her former hometown of Kusunoki. She chose this job because she thought it was an easy job she can do, even when she is as old as her grandfather. However, she learns that her job is anything but simple when she meets the fairies.
Note: The chronological order for the episodes is: 10, S2-S7, 7-8, 5-6, 1-2, 9, 11-12, 3-4. The first episode received a preview screening as part of a special event, which was held at a location in Tokyo revealed only to those that won a lottery, on July 1, 2012. Regular TV broadcast started on July 2, 2012.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2496">7.53</permanent>
<temporary count="2505">7.59</temporary>
<review count="1">8.66</review>
</ratings>
<picture>244953.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13787</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10357</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>16101</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>15617</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5132</identifier>
<identifier>xdheeb</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://www.marv.jp/special/jintai/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Humanity_Has_Declined</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>人類は衰退しました</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2587</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>343087</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15023</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/3376</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2012/jinruihasuitaishimashita</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>humanity-has-declined</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="7" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>juujin</name>
<description>Kemono, "beast", is a genre of Japanese art and character design that prominently features anthropomorphic animal characters. It is used widely in visual arts, especially drawing and painting, and can be found in many manga, anime, and video game.
Anthropomorphic animal characters in the kemono genre are frequently called juujin, "therianthrope"; the kanji for juujin are also sometimes pronounced kemonobito, "beast-human". While their design differs from artist to artist, they generally employ animal traits considered cute and endearing; most kemono characters retain a fundamentally human personality, however, seldom behaving as the actual animals from which they have been anthropomorphized, and as such they are typically depicted living as humans do.
Juujin leans more on the human-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t2857 [anthropomorphism], which leans more on the animal-looking side.
Source: Manga Wikia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="464" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-01-15">
<name>sarcastic</name>
<description>The character frequently uses sharp, bitter, or cutting expressions or remarks. (From Greek sarcasmos, "to tear flesh, gnash the teeth, speak bitterly".)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="587" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-22">
<name>doll</name>
</tag>
<tag id="760" parentid="2274" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>robot helper</name>
<description>In a http://anidb.net/t2846 [science fiction] setting, the robot helper is, in a comedic sense, pretty much equivalent to what the "cute comic relief http://anidb.net/t1835 [animal sidekick]" is in a fantasy setting. The usually small machine has artificial intelligence, enabling it to support their owner / master with advice or help with menial tasks.
http://anidb.net/t1278 [Androids] should not be considered robot helpers since these are far more complex; use the android tag instead.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="780" parentid="2849" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-08-23">
<name>fairy</name>
<description>A fairy is a type of mythical being or legendary creature in European folklore, a form of spirit, often described as metaphysical, supernatural, or preternatural.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>206567.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1063" parentid="2869" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-11">
<name>elementary school</name>
<description>The term elementary school is used in some countries for schools where children from the age of about five receive primary education.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1133" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>otaku</name>
<description>Otaku, derived from a Japanese term for another`s house or family (お宅, otaku), appeared in the 1980s. In the anime http://anidb.net/a77 [Macross], first aired in 1982, the term was used by http://anidb.net/ch7418 [Lynn Minmay] as an honorific term.
In modern Japanese slang, the term otaku refers to a fan of any particular theme, topic, or hobby. Common uses are anime otaku (a fan of anime), cosplay otaku and manga otaku (a fan of Japanese comic books), pasokon otaku (personal computer geeks), geemu otaku (playing video games), and wota (pronounced ota, previously referred to as idol otaku) that are extreme fans of http://anidb.net/t2438 [idols], heavily promoted singing girls. There are also tetsudou otaku or denshamania (railfans) or gunji otaku (military geeks).
While these are the most common uses, the word can be applied to anything (music otaku, martial arts otaku, cooking otaku, etc).
Some of Japan`s otaku use the term to describe themselves and their friends semi-humorously, accepting their position as fans, and some even use the term proudly, attempting to reclaim it from its negative connotations. In general colloquial usage however, most Japanese would consider it undesirable to be described in a serious fashion as otaku; many even consider it to be a genuine insult.
The negativity which modern society shows towards otaku and otaku culture is historically partly attributed to Miyazaki Tsutomu, who became known as The Otaku Murderer in 1989. His bizarre murders fueled a moral panic against otaku. However, the public appearance of most otaku is the major reason for them to be shunned by society today.</description>
<picurl>52482.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1136" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-18">
<name>transfer student</name>
<description>A transfer student is a student who changes from one institution or course to another at the same level. Their arrival, when not at the beginning of the school year, tends to cause a stir.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1759" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>carefree</name>
<description>A [b]carefree[b] person is free of worries, cares or concerns. This does not necessarily imply that they have no responsibilities or are negligent towards them; they are simply able to live out their lives in tranquility regardless of what happens.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2406" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-13">
<name>talking animal</name>
<description>Talking animals are a common theme in mythology and folk tales, as well as children`s literature. Fictional talking creatures often are anthropomorphic, possessing human-like qualities but appearing as a creature. An animal that only knows how to say its name (for example, 99.9% of all http://anidb.net/t2493 [Pokemon]), are not talking animals.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2555" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-07-14">
<name>amnesia</name>
<description>The character suffers from some kind of amnesia (memory disturbance or loss). This may mean inability to memorize new information, or inability to recollect old memories. Since there are many types of memory, the person may e.g. forget who they are but still retain learned skills.
Amnesia is fairly common in fiction as a plot device. In fact, because it allows for major plot changes while requiring little creativity from the author, it may be subject to heavy overuse.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2558" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>catgirl</name>
<description>A catgirl (nekomusume, 猫娘) is a girl that has a cat`s characteristics, a form of zoomorphism.
They can appear either as normal girls without any obvious cat traits —such as eyes, ears, paws, or a tail— or as girls who have one or more of these traits. In the former case they are usually cats that have become human through the means of magic. The feline features are added for moe and/or sexiness appeal, with the most common features being cat ears and tail. Nya~, the Japanese equivalent of meow, is often used by girls acting cute and is not a trait exclusive to catgirls.
Not to be confused with characters who simply are wearing a http://anidb.net/t1622 [cat ears accessory] (nekomimi, 猫耳) as a fashion accessory. Catgirls with cat ears should also be tagged with http://anidb.net/t2541 [animal ears].</description>
<picurl>150775.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2656" parentid="2853" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>satire</name>
<description>In satire, vices, follies, abuses, and shortcomings are held up to ridicule, ideally with the intent of shaming individuals, and society itself, into improvement. Although satire is usually meant to be funny, its greater purpose is often constructive social criticism, using wit as a weapon. (Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2783" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>shounen ai</name>
<description>Shounen Ai means boys love, and thus explores what happens when two boys (or men) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2723 [Yaoi] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphical sex.
The female version is http://anidb.net/t2782 [Shoujo Ai].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2829" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-21">
<name>shower scene</name>
<description>The anime contains a shower scene, obligatory for ecchi anime. The person under the shower will most likely be female — providing "fanservice".</description>
<picurl>208635.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2857" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>anthropomorphism</name>
<description>Anthropomorphism is the attribution of uniquely human characteristics to non-human beings, inanimate objects, or natural or supernatural phenomena. If it`s an animal or an object (AI excluded) and it speaks and/or does other human-like things (dresses up) then we`re dealing with anthropomorphism.
Anthropomorphism leans more on the animal-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t7 [juujin], which leans more on the human-looking side.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2882" parentid="2952" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-17">
<name>dystopia</name>
<description>A dystopia (from Ancient Greek: δυσ-, "bad, ill", and Ancient Greek: τόπος, "place, landscape"; alternatively cacotopia, or anti-utopia) is, in literature, an often futuristic society that has degraded into a repressive and controlled state, often under the guise of being utopian. Dystopian literature has underlying cautionary tones, warning society that if we continue to live how we do, this will be the consequence. A dystopia, thus, is regarded as a sort of negative utopia and is often characterized by an authoritarian or totalitarian form of government. Dystopias usually feature different kinds of repressive social control systems, a lack or total absence of individual freedoms and expressions and constant states of warfare or violence. Dystopias often explore the concept of humans abusing technology and how humans individually and collectively cope with technology that has evolved too quickly such as the car, the flamethrower or the microwave. A dystopian society is also often characterized by widespread poverty and brutal political controls such as a large military-like police.</description>
<picurl>69879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2923" parentid="2874" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-06-25">
<name>post-apocalyptic</name>
<description>An anime that takes place on future Earth (or it could be an alternative universe) after a major cataclysm has occurred. World War III, an alien invasion, plague, global warming or some other general disaster are common themes to build a post-apocalyptic world upon, where the effects were severe enough that mankind barely survived.
The time frame may be immediately after the catastrophe, focusing on the travails or psychology of survivors, or considerably later, often including the theme that the existence of pre-catastrophe civilization has been forgotten (or mythologised). Post-apocalyptic stories often take place in an agrarian, non-technological future world, or a world where only scattered elements of technology remain. There is a considerable degree of blurring between post-apocalyptic fiction and that which deals with false utopias or dystopian societies.</description>
<picurl>42081.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2952" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-06">
<name>rotten world</name>
<description>A rotten world is a setting or situation where the jaded notion that "anything that can go wrong will go horribly wrong" almost always applies. Oppression, perpetual warfare, lawlessness, despair or other forms of mental instability, and other highly undesirable factors tend to be rampant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3007" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-07-16">
<name>monologues</name>
<description>This show features a noticeable amount of screen time during which characters talk to themselves. That is usually a way to display to the viewers what the characters are thinking. When used in excess, it may be a sign of poor storytelling, but when done skillfully, it may be excellent comedy fuel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3092" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-03-02">
<name>important haircut</name>
<description>When a character cuts off his or her hair, it often symbolizes a rite of passage or bout of character growth. A princess striking out on an adventure, or a new recruit at boot camp, for instance. Hair is something that takes time and effort to grow, so parting with it voluntarily can be a powerful act.
This is particularly a big deal when women get haircuts. Yet in fiction, even an accidental hair slicing can leave a character with a surprisingly even cut.
In many religions (Western Christianity, Ancient Egyptian religion, and others) priests and/or monks cut/shave their hair. Roman Catholic nuns also tend to cut and mantain their hair short under their veils when they enter the nunneries. The cutting of one`s own hair is also a part of Buddhist mythology, specifically something done by Siddhartha himself early on in his path to enlightenment, so anime examples might draw from this as an allusion. There are also some cultures, including Native American and many Asians, where a person would cut his or her hair as an act of grief, disgrace, or even rebellion. In the Confucian tradition, hair (like the rest of your body) is considered a gift from your parents and may not be damaged without a very good reason. Furthermore, prisoners and psychiatric patients commonly have their heads shaved, often to prevent the spread of lice, but sometimes also as a demeaning measure.
Source: TVTRope</description>
<picurl>169641.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3185" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-27">
<name>wordplay</name>
<description>The characters play with words. 
E.g. purposely or accidentally use similar-sounding but wrongly applied words in the Japanese original, leading to supposedly funny misunderstandings and confusion.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3546" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-01-08">
<name>experimental animation</name>
<description>This anime uses distinct, alternative animation — much unlike other contemporary anime — either throughout or in individual episodes/sequences.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3741" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-25">
<name>bullying</name>
<description>Bullying is the use of force, threat, or coercion to abuse, intimidate, or aggressively dominate others. One who engages in bullying is known as a bully.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3929" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-09">
<name>sociocultural evolution</name>
<description>Describes how cultures and societies develop over time, based on both cultural evolution and social evolution.
A post-apocalyptic or a Utopian setting would show very interesting changes in human behaviour, mental state, or simply daily life.</description>
<picurl>191062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3934" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-04-10">
<name>non-linear</name>
<description>The story is told achronologically.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3977" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-29">
<name>dialogue driven</name>
<description>A dialogue driven show has its story advanced by dialogue, with action being of much lower priority, and relies heavily on conversations between characters.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4131" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-05-11">
<name>cultural references</name>
<description>The plot of this anime shows signs of cultural references, these are often jokes that make reference to a certain custom, habit or history that is specifically attributed to that culture. Knowledge of the culture itself is needed in order to properly understand these jokes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4222" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>walls of text</name>
<description>Walls of text refers to Japanese text that appears in large quantities within the anime itself. This text is most likely vital to the storyline and may come in the form of charts and diagrams or pieces of paper, notes or even thoughts that are only partially or entirely unspoken.
May also be taken as a fair warning to viewers unable to translate Japanese text on their own, suggesting that thorough subtitle support may be required as well as making use of the pause button on their media players so that all text can be read.
Normally, tags don`t refer to physical translations of text, subtitle appearances and karaoke styling added by 3rd parties. But those who seek to describe an anime that is heavy on SPOKEN dialogue (which may tend to create a large quantity of natural subtitling to read for those not fluent in the language being used) could consider this tag but may make clearer reference with the dialogue driven tag.</description>
<picurl>32534.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4280" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-06-02">
<name>surreal</name>
<description>Refers to things or occurrences that are generally bizarre or dreamlike, with the relentless capability of replacing reality through the eyes of the beholder. Surrealism is boundless, limited only by thought itself.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4340" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-09-26">
<name>suicide</name>
<description>One or several characters in this anime commit suicide.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4386" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-19">
<name>eating Pocky</name>
<description>Pocky (ポッキー) is a Japanese snack food produced by the Ezaki Glico Company of Japan. Pocky was first sold in 1966, and consists of a biscuit stick coated with chocolate. It was named after the Japanese onomatopoetic word for the sound Pocky makes when bitten, pokkin (ポッキン). The original was followed by "Almond Pocky" in 1971, with an almond coating, and "Strawberry Pocky" in 1977. Today, the product line includes such variations as milk, mousse, green tea, honey, banana and coconut flavored coatings, and themed products such as "Decorer Pocky," with colourful decorative stripes in the coating, and "Men`s Pocky," a dark (bittersweet) chocolate and "mature" version.
Source: Wikipedia
It`s marketed in Germany under the name Mikado (Note: NOT the game, the snack).</description>
<picurl>73630.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4499" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-07-28">
<name>some weird shit goin` on</name>
<description>Scenes of this show point to insanely strange events which seem to be taking place; throughout its episodes, the show may or may not explain what is going on. Either way, many viewers will find that a succinct and accurate way to describe the show is "WTF?", and the show`s explanations (or lack thereof) to the events will often be subject of heated debate.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4521" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-28">
<name>lost technology</name>
<description>Any advanced technology or science-related knowledge that was lost for some reason fits the description. This could be technology from a time before a post-apocalyptic cataclysm, knowledge gained a long time ago but forgotten, or the relics of an old alien civilization only recently discovered.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4522" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>social commentary</name>
<description>Social commentary is the act of rebelling against an individual, or a group of people by rhetorical means. This is most often done with the idea of implementing or promoting change by informing the general populace about a given problem and appealing to people’s sense of justice. (Source: Wikipedia)&#13;
&#13;
Since this is anime, usually, the mores of Japan and the Japanese society are scrutinised, but not restricted to that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4570" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-07">
<name>watercolour style</name>
<description>A watercolour or aquarelle is a painting method in which the paints are made of pigments suspended in a water-based solution. Some anime are created in the style of watercolour paintings, the watercolour style, usually with faded pastels that often give the show a warm and friendly visual presentation. In modern anime, this is generally achieved via computer effects that create an imitation of watercolour, rather than by creating real-life watercolour art. While the watercolour style is more commonly used for backgrounds, it is possible to create the entire anime in such a style.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4663" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-31">
<name>tone changes</name>
<description>The anime switches quickly, often rather drastically between different moods or tones, sometimes even on the same scene.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5417" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-22">
<name>mind fuck</name>
<description>A `mind fuck` is a slang term which describes a work that uses literary devices such as nonlinear storytelling and plot twists in order to present convoluted, yet not conflicting, themes.
A creation is usually considered a mind fuck when a casual observer is not able to discern the true meaning of a work without making a serious attempt to unravel the themes presented or when the plot is incredibly difficult to follow.
Special examples of mind fucks involve a single plot twist which completely changes the viewer`s understanding of the events in a film or novel as well as the ideas it presents.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5697" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-02">
<name>randomness</name>
<description>The anime does not follow a predictable storyline. New, strange, obscure, or otherwise unexpected story elements are introduced at a whim.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5805" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-06-11">
<name>post-credits scene</name>
<description>A little bit of the story is found after the credit titles. A little bonus for those patient enough!
This applies regardless of if the credits play over an ED sequence, or over the "regular episode" that continues to air into the credits.
A sequence at the end of an episode, showing what will happen in the next episode, is NOT a post-credits scene; that is a preview.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5993" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-28">
<name>black humour</name>
<description>Sure, it`s funny, but you really shouldn`t be laughing...
In other words, it`s a comedy that employs situations that nice people should not be laughing about.</description>
<picurl>222688.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6030" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-22">
<name>otaku culture</name>
<description>Otaku (おたく/オタク) is a Japanese term used to refer to people with obsessive interests, particularly anime, manga, and video games. A female otaku is occasionally referred to as a fujoshi. (Source: Wikipedia)
Here certain aspects of this "fandom" are presented in more detail, e.g. the creation of doujinshi (self-published amateur manga).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6050" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-02-11">
<name>human - non-human relationship</name>
<description>The relationship between a human and a non-human — be it alien, or artificial — is explored in this anime.
This usually means between a male human and a female (humanoid) alien or AI (avatar).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6055" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-15">
<name>time loop</name>
<description>A time loop is a common plot device in science fiction (especially in universes where time travel is commonplace). Events in the story repeat themselves a number of times with or without some variation with each pass. Most characters either do not realise this is occurring or are attempting to break the cycle in some way. 
One well-known example of this is in the 1993 film Groundhog Day, in which the main character is the only one aware of the time loop, although time loops had appeared in many fictional works prior to that. Stories with time loops commonly center on correcting past mistakes or on getting a character to recognise some key truth; escape from the loop may then follow.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7061" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-27">
<name>the lives of mini-people</name>
<description>The show features the lives of mini-people, characters much shorter than would be natural, and how they interact with a world of things much bigger than themselves. This is not about characters merely being short, but about living in a world of things that, from their perspective, are gigantic.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="40677" type="main character in" update="2012-07-30">
<rating votes="205">9.20</rating>
<name>Watashi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The heroine of the story, who serves an important duty as the international arbitrator between the fairies and humans.</description>
<picture>86039.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6" picture="171987.jpg">Nakahara Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="42848" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-09-03">
<rating votes="12">4.26</rating>
<name>Sofu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>86040.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="339" picture="79312.jpg">Ishizuka Unshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43515" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-16">
<rating votes="17">6.34</rating>
<name>Joshu-san</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>86041.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="14" picture="75503.jpg">Fukuyama Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="43516" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-04-16">
<rating votes="38">9.02</rating>
<name>Yousei-san</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>86042.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="320" picture="66660.jpg">Kobayashi Yumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46809" type="appears in" update="2012-07-11">
<name>Tsugihagi-san</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>90814.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18698" picture="49321.jpg">Nakane Kumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46810" type="appears in" update="2012-07-11">
<rating votes="6">8.67</rating>
<name>Ikkin-san</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>90800.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2766" picture="181834.jpg">Mamiya Kurumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46811" type="appears in" update="2012-07-11">
<name>Koya no Aruji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>90816.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23683" picture="65780.jpg">Gotou Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46812" type="appears in" update="2012-07-11">
<rating votes="2">8.79</rating>
<name>Chicken</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>90810.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11041" picture="82436.jpg">Ooshita Kouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46813" type="appears in" update="2012-07-11">
<rating votes="6">7.90</rating>
<name>Boss Chicken</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>90805.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="340" picture="17176.jpg">Yabe Masahito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46814" type="appears in" update="2012-07-11">
<name>Bunka Kyokuchou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>90811.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2062" picture="188714.jpg">Ichijou Kazuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46815" type="appears in" update="2012-07-11">
<name>Youseisha Uketsuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>90812.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3141" picture="65575.jpg">Tsuruoka Satoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46955" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-08-16">
<rating votes="29">6.87</rating>
<name>Y</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>92505.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38" picture="171532.jpg">Sawashiro Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46981" type="appears in" update="2012-07-24">
<name>Caravan Tai Taichou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91421.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="695" picture="38273.jpg">Ono Atsushi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47430" type="appears in" update="2012-07-30">
<rating votes="9">6.99</rating>
<name>Pion</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>91741.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18" picture="170423.jpg">Mizuki Nana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47558" type="appears in" update="2012-08-05">
<rating votes="5">3.24</rating>
<name>Otarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>92003.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="73" picture="58662.jpg">Hiyama Nobuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47810" type="appears in" update="2012-08-14">
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<name>Joi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>92428.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="328" picture="17164.jpg">Kuwatani Natsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47917" type="appears in" update="2012-08-19">
<name>Yousei-san</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>92648.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="600" picture="148972.jpg">Arai Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="47944" type="appears in" update="2012-08-28">
<rating votes="4">1.92</rating>
<name>Doc</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>92678.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1682" picture="41033.jpg">Matsumoto Rika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48652" type="appears in" update="2012-09-10">
<name>RYOBO230r</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>93829.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="253" picture="222833.jpg">Yuzuki Ryouka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48653" type="appears in" update="2012-09-10">
<rating votes="10">4.71</rating>
<name>Makige</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93832.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12266" picture="56026.jpg">Kanemoto Hisako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48654" type="appears in" update="2012-09-10">
<name>Kyoushi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93831.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18698" picture="49321.jpg">Nakane Kumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48655" type="appears in" update="2012-09-10">
<name>Kouchou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93830.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="289" picture="186204.jpg">Nishimura Tomomichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48656" type="appears in" update="2012-09-10">
<rating votes="4">5.91</rating>
<name>Hana-senpai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93833.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="313" picture="158104.jpg">Nogawa Sakura</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48657" type="appears in" update="2012-09-10">
<rating votes="4">6.76</rating>
<name>Majo-senpai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93834.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="182" picture="226274.jpg">Itou Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="48658" type="appears in" update="2012-09-10">
<name>Yousei-san</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>93828.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="359" picture="65537.jpg">Sanada Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49075" type="appears in" update="2012-09-19">
<name>Sensei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>94459.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11041" picture="82436.jpg">Ooshita Kouta</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="140437" update="2013-03-11">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-07-23</airdate>
<rating votes="13">6.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">妖精さんたちの, さぶかる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Fairies` Subculture</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yousei-san-tachi no, Subcul</title>
<summary>Exploring the strange world they wound up in, the heroine and Y encounter her assistant, who had also gotten himself stuck. They deduce that in order to proceed through the panels, they must do something dramatic enough to make a printed sound effect materialize. They also realize they can draw things into existence, as well as understand that if their manga becomes too boring, they will descend into cancellation. As such, the trio start going through various genres to make it through the manga world. After encountering some fairies, they realize that in order to escape, they need to reach the ending, though a desire for ratings soon leads the stories into a complicated mess. The manga soon becomes unpopular and ends up getting cancelled, but thankfully they manage to end up back in the real world.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>606583</identifier>
<identifier>humanity-has-declined</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="140438" update="2013-03-11">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-07-16</airdate>
<rating votes="15">4.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">妖精さんたちの, さぶかる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Fairies` Subculture</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yousei-san-tachi no, Subcul</title>
<summary>A woman named Y who supposedly works in researching the Human Monument manages to find a disc full of data inside an old mansion, which turns out to be a volume of a yaoi manga. She soon gets into the habit of publishing yaoi manga which she distributes across the country. When the fairies catch wind of the trend and start publishing their own yaoi manga, Y begins to work harder to compete, bringing about a manga renaissance. However, her manga becomes too heavy that the couriers do not want to deliver the boxes themselves, leading her to create a dōjin fair. Some time later, the heroine discovers a mysterious dōjin which traps her and Y inside a blank panel.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>603487</identifier>
<identifier>humanity-has-declined</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="140439" update="2013-03-11">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-07-09</airdate>
<rating votes="18">6.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">妖精さんの, ひみつのこうじょう</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Fairies` Secret Factory</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yousei-san no, Himitsu no Koujou</title>
<summary>The heroine and her assistant become lost after being separated from her grandfather and the receptionist. She soon gets separated from her assistant and comes across the factory`s manager, who directs her to an off-limits area so she can try and find the upper management. She soon discovers the factory is run by a group of intelligent plucked chickens who plan to take over the world. They are soon stopped by the arrival of the assistant and his camcorder, which drives them to commit suicide. After freeing all the trapped fairies, the heroine finds that her hair has been brought to life due to the tonic.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>603485</identifier>
<identifier>humanity-has-declined</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="140440" update="2020-03-12">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-07-02</airdate>
<rating votes="24">4.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">妖精さんの, ひみつのこうじょう</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Fairies` Secret Factory</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yousei-san no, Himitsu no Koujou</title>
<summary>In a world where mankind is nearing extinction, the main character, a girl who acts as a mediator with fairies, is sent to turn butcher chickens, but the chickens escape. After some strange FairyCo products show up in the village, including a tonic that restores her hair, the heroine, her grandfather, and her assistant go to a fairy factory where mass-produced fairy products are made.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>603483</identifier>
<identifier>humanity-has-declined</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="140653" update="2012-07-01">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-07-01</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="140654" update="2012-07-01">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-07-01</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="141231" update="2013-03-11">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-08-20</airdate>
<rating votes="11">4.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">妖精さんたちの, じかんかつようじゅつ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Fairies` Time Management</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yousei-san-tachi no, Jikankatsuyoujutsu</title>
<summary>As the heroine reflects on her multiple timeloops, she focuses on the details about the assistant given to her by her grandfather and the doctor looking after him. During a certain timeloop between the fourth and fifth times, the fairies make a bug which takes the heroine "far away", where she encounters a boy whom she thinks is the assistant, and finds him to be an excitable and lecherous young boy who calls himself the Ringo Kid. It turns out that Ringo Kid was the younger version of the heroine`s grandfather from the distant past. After hearing more about him from her doubles during the fifth time, the heroine meets the assistant on the sixth. She finds him to have a more gentle and plain personality, and believes he had finally found his true personality using doubles to gather opinions from others about how he should be.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>606591</identifier>
<identifier>humanity-has-declined</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="141232" update="2013-03-11">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-08-13</airdate>
<rating votes="12">4.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">妖精さんたちの, じかんかつようじゅつ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Fairies` Time Management</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yousei-san-tachi no, Jikankatsuyoujutsu</title>
<summary>As the heroine is sent by her grandfather to look for his assistant, she encounters someone who looks exactly like her. Things only get stranger as she has déjà vu after déjà vu, encounters various versions of herself, and finds her memory less and less clear. She soon learns it to be the work of the fairies, who are manipulating time in order to get several copies of the heroine to make sweets for them. After several loops resulting in hundreds of clones making sweets, the heroine soon encounters a village full of dogs where the assistant lies.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>606589</identifier>
<identifier>humanity-has-declined</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="141233" update="2013-03-11">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-08-06</airdate>
<rating votes="14">4.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">妖精さんの, おさとがえり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Fairies` Homecoming</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yousei-san no, Osatogaeri</title>
<summary>As Pion, revealed to be a robot who the heroine now calls P-ko, joins the party, they encounter her companion Oyage, a similar robot who calls himself O-taro, who wants to abandon his mission and live in the strange city. As he sends a killer digger truck after them, they all fall down a hole, winding up at an underground castle. The heroine and assistant are confronted by O-taro, who combines with the slimes to become a "Killer Death Cat", though the fairies step in to help them. With help from the fairies, P-ko manages to defeat O-taro using a super-powered microwave, which in turn restores their memories. After the gang manages to escape the city, it is revealed P-ko and O-taro, whose real names are Pioneer and Voyager, were deep space probes that gained humanoid form. O-taro makes P-ko realize that deep inside, like himself, she does not want to leave the warmth of the solar system. Hearing these thoughts, the heroine sabotages the electric generator, stopping P-ko and O-taro from being able to leave before reworking them to become wind-up powered.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>606587</identifier>
<identifier>humanity-has-declined</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="141234" update="2013-03-11">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-07-30</airdate>
<rating votes="14">5.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">妖精さんの, おさとがえり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Fairies` Homecoming</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yousei-san no, Osatogaeri</title>
<summary>As the village prepares an electric-powered festival for the Human Monument Project, the heroine hears from the fairies that they are leaving to avoid the electromagnetic waves from the festival that are deadly to them. They leave behind a good luck charm and a curious manual explaining the dangers that come if no fairies are met during the day. During the festival, the heroine meets a curious girl named Pion, who is searching for her companion. The next day, the heroine and her assistant are sent to explore an underground structure, where they get trapped. As they search for the exit, the charm the heroine received turns into a fairy who tries to lead them towards water but instead comes across a group of acidic slimes. As they face more dangers upon reaching a computer room, they are rescued by Pion.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>606585</identifier>
<identifier>humanity-has-declined</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="142123" update="2013-03-11">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-09-17</airdate>
<rating votes="15">8.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">妖精さんの, ひみつのおちゃかい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Fairies` Secret Tea Party</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yousei-san no, Himitsu no Ochakai</title>
<summary>Whilst spending time having tea parties with the Wildrose Society, the heroine learns that Y was once part of the society. A year later, the heroine moves up to year 4 and becomes Y`s classmate. She soon learns Y had been stealing books to build her own yaoi library. In exchange for not revealing her secret, Y sneaks the heroine into the rooms of the other Wildrose members, revealing their hidden agendas, including how mentally unstable Curly is. After learning all of this, the heroine joins Y in searching for a true fairy tea party, and over the years they rekindle their relationships with the Wildrose Society members. As the heroine, Y and Curly discover a room full of robots, the heroine remembers about the fairy she met years ago. After everyone graduates and the school is torn down, the heroine is visited by Y, who brings her the robot from the school dorms, which is soon revealed to contain the fairy she had met at school.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>606599</identifier>
<identifier>humanity-has-declined</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="142124" update="2013-03-11">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-09-10</airdate>
<rating votes="14">7.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">妖精さんの, ひみつのおちゃかい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Fairies` Secret Tea Party</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yousei-san no, Himitsu no Ochakai</title>
<summary>The heroine thinks back to when she was ten and began attending school, having to start at the lowest grade...  As she decides to remain inconspicuous and focus on skipping through the grades, she finds herself the target of bullying from some of the other students, including a young Y.  Believing her to be the mastermind, she finds herself alienated from a girl called "Curly" who was trying to become her friend. One day, the heroine rescues a fairy from a group of bullies and has it tag along with her. As the stress of her school life leads the heroine to admit to herself that she feels lonely, the fairy does something before disappearing. The heroine finds Curly has joined her in skipping grades, also facing some bullying from jealous peers. As the heroine decides to repay some of her kindness, she finds Curly to be disturbingly affectionate with her. Curly then moves into the heroine`s dorm and invites her to join a secret organization called the Wildrose Society.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>606597</identifier>
<identifier>humanity-has-declined</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="142125" update="2013-03-11">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-09-03</airdate>
<rating votes="12">8.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">妖精さんたちの, ちきゅう</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Fairies` Earth</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yousei-san-tachi no, Chikyuu</title>
<summary>The heroine begins her job as a mediator and finds it not to be what she expected. Whilst observing an abandoned site, she encounters a group of fairies and brings some of them home with her. After getting over their initial worries, the heroine finds the fairies to be quite talkative and curious. She gives them some names, only to be tasked with naming all the other fairies as well. Finding the abandoned site turned into a metropolis overnight, she gives the fairy population a naming dictionary so they can decide on their own names. The next day, the heroine finds herself hailed as a god and ends up causing chaos when she tries to pass the responsibility onto someone else, leading to the city`s destruction.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>606595</identifier>
<identifier>humanity-has-declined</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="142126" update="2013-03-11">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-08-27</airdate>
<rating votes="18">9.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">妖精さんの, ひょうりゅうせいかつ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Fairies` Survival Skills</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yousei-san no, Hyouryuu Seikatsu</title>
<summary>After an increase in fairy population leads to bullying, the heroine is sent to accompany asylum seeking fairies to find a new home for them. Through various circumstances, the heroine ends up stranded on an island in the middle of the ocean, along with a group of pessimistic fairies who declare her the queen of their new nation. The fairies` motivation to work on building their new nation soon increases their population. The nation evolves into a bustling civilization dedicated to serving its queen, who begins living in luxury. Upon cultivating a plant that can produce candy, the fairies` research and development soon turn the nation into a literal candy island. However, after a lapse in judgement causes everyone to build monuments everywhere, the island is soon ruined and made devoid of food and water, sending them into poverty. The heroine feels she and the asylum seeking fairies should leave the island, but they remain trapped by a rainstorm caused by the collective depression of the fairies. After the island ends up collapsing on itself, the heroine returns to dry land and her daily life.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>606593</identifier>
<identifier>humanity-has-declined</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="144026" update="2016-04-25">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2012-09-19</airdate>
<rating votes="5">8.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">人間さんの, じゃくにくきょうしょく #1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Humans` Law of the Jungle #1</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">인간님의 약육강식 #1</title>
<summary>Whilst sorting through a box of curious items left behind by the fairies, the heroine finds a spoon that lets her scoop flour out of her head. However, she ends up overusing it and winds up small.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="144887" update="2020-02-09">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-10-17</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">人間さんの, じゃくにくきょうしょく #2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Humans` Law of the Jungle #2</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">인간님의 약육강식 #2</title>
<summary>Unable to get help from her grandpa, due to the way her miniature form transforms her speech patterns, the heroine searches for the fairies but comes up against a hungry bird.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="145795" update="2016-04-25">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-11-21</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">人間さんの, じゃくにくきょうしょく #3</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Humans` Law of the Jungle #3</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">인간님의 약육강식 #3</title>
<summary>After narrowly escaping the bird, the heroine meets an intelligent hamster named Yameta whose civilization is under threat from weasels.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="146048" recap="true" update="2016-04-25">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2012-10-28</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">人間さんの, ようせいさんめも</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ningen-san no, Yousei-san Memo</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">인간님의 요정님 메모</title>
</episode>
<episode id="146160" update="2016-04-25">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2012-12-19</airdate>
<rating votes="5">2.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">人間さんの, じゃくにくきょうしょく #4</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Humans` Law of the Jungle #4</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">인간님의 약육강식 #4</title>
<summary>The weasels` attack sends the heroine flying into a pond, where she is rescued by a handsome looking fairy.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="146862" update="2020-02-09">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2013-01-16</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">人間さんの, じゃくにくきょうしょく #5</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Humans` Law of the Jungle #5</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">인간님의 약육강식 #5</title>
<summary>The heroine gives up on trying to find a way to change back and enjoys her luxurious new life. However, whilst doing some cooking, she ends up using the spoon on herself again, becoming even smaller. She soon learns that the spoon converts her intelligent thoughts into flour, shrinking her to match her intelligence.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="147876" update="2020-02-09">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2013-02-20</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">人間さんの, じゃくにくきょうしょく #6</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Humans` Law of the Jungle #6</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">인간님의 약육강식 #6</title>
<summary>The heroine arrives at a fantastic god`s home. The god is away, but she finds a massive sack of flour, and with a sense of nostalgia, offers to bake it into cookies. As she does, her last bit of intelligence is fleeting out the window when she bites into a cookie and starts to regain her senses instead. She realizes she must eat all the cookies herself to return to normal, which she does, and returns to everyday life with most of her intelligence restored.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="148924" update="2013-04-07">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">BD-DVD CM</title>
</episode>
<episode id="148925" update="2013-04-07">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="148926" update="2013-04-07">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="148927" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 1</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>602065</identifier>
<identifier>humanity-has-declined</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
