<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8485" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>11</episodecount>
<startdate>2011-10-14</startdate>
<enddate>2011-12-23</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Un-Go</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="synonym">安吾捕物帖</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="synonym">因果日記</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">ungo</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">UN-GO</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">UN-GO</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Un-Go</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="8650" type="Prequel">Un-Go: Inga-ron</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="5416" approval="19" total="20">Majin Tantei Nougami Neuro</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="5">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="548153">I agree with farce and vortex3010 - the show is a mixture of many and not quite good realized/too shallow in many aspects. Overall average show but it just keeps you occupied and interested what will be next.
Unfortunately this show contains many deceit, propaganda aspect correlating to the real world - for example mingling a real history with fake/fictional history(some acts of terrorism etc) - overall the whole concept of a high developed country being overrun, savaged by terrorism is a naive, fictional concept unless the terrorist is the very gov. of the country or the other high developed country hiding in a shadows behind so called extremists.. At least the control of informations are shown nicely.. :P</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="413607">Underrated . ITs a bit hard to watch , but its still a great series .</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="459074">This is a really great detective anime with great characters and a simple plot. I thoroughly enjoyed watching this and am hoping for a second series. :)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="210496">If you want detective, go somewhere else. This show does a terrible job of laying out the facts. What the show DOES do is peek into human nature, as well as various interpretations to life. Decent watch, especially if you like to think about concepts that have no real solutions.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="567284">As I love detective  anime series, I enjoyed watching it but I also think it was a bit complicated. But still recommended.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.un-go.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="10929" type="Animation Character Design">Inadome Kazumi</name>
<name id="21614" type="Animation Character Design">Yaguchi Hiroko</name>
<name id="7487" type="Animation Character Design">Yasaki Yuuko</name>
<name id="10171" type="Original Plan">Sakaguchi Ango</name>
<name id="29050" type="Character Design">Pako</name>
<name id="130" type="Direction">Mizushima Seiji</name>
<name id="10929" type="Chief Animation Direction">Inadome Kazumi</name>
<name id="21614" type="Chief Animation Direction">Yaguchi Hiroko</name>
<name id="7487" type="Chief Animation Direction">Yasaki Yuuko</name>
<name id="755" type="Animation Work">Bones</name>
<name id="951" type="Character Design">Kouga Yun</name>
<name id="670" type="Story Composition">Aikawa Shou</name>
<name id="5042" type="Music">Narasaki</name>
</creators>
<description>* Loosely adapted from http://anidb.net/cr10171 [Sakaguchi Ango]`s novel Meiji Kaika Ango Torimonochou.
A full-fledged detective story about a detective and handsome boy combo who tackle the world`s most difficult crimes together for reasons of their own. The profession of private detective fell out of favor long ago, and yet, that`s how the young man, http://anidb.net/ch34259 [Yuuki Shinjuurou] identifies himself. With his superior deductive powers, Shinjuurou solves various challenging cases. Meanwhile, http://anidb.net/ch34258 [Inga], an attractive young lad, serves as Shinjuurou`s buddy. But contrary to his cute looks, he`s a sharp, arrogant rogue. Why Inga sticks with Shinjuurou is as of yet unknown. The setting of the story is a postwar, future Tokyo that still bears the scars of war. Ruling the land is Media King http://anidb.net/ch35172 [Kaishou Rinroku], who through politics and industry has the communications infrastructure under his thumb. Kaishou has used a clear head and the massive amount of information at his fingertips to lead to the solution of a great number of cases. But there`s an underside to Kaishou`s brilliant deduction work, which is that Yuuki Shinjuurou, the Last Great Detective, is the one who actually uncovered the truth in those cases. However, the public doesn`t know this and thus refers to Shinjuurou as the Defeated Detective. Still, Shinjuurou, together with Inga, can`t help but search for the truth.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2033">6.05</permanent>
<temporary count="2044">7.10</temporary>
<review count="1">3.33</review>
</ratings>
<picture>85906.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13002</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12411</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>10798</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4984</identifier>
<identifier>cpttvi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.un-go.com/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.bones.co.jp/un-go</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.fujicreative.co.jp/intldept/noitamina/UN-GO</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Un-Go</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>UN-GO</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2258</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>340773</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13764</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/2879</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2011/ungo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>un-go</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="308" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>detective</name>
<description>A detective is an investigator, generally either a member of a law enforcement agency or as an individual working in the capacity of private investigators, tasked with solving crimes and other mysteries, such as disappearances, by examining and evaluating clues and records in order to solve the mystery; for a crime, this would mean uncovering the criminal`s identity and/or whereabouts. In some police systems, a detective position is achieved by passing a written test after a person completes the requirements for being a police officer; in others, detectives are college graduates who join directly from civilian life without first serving as uniformed officers.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210906.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1656" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-27">
<name>corrupt</name>
<description>The character is spiritually or morally impure and may accept payment or other benefits for services or material which the recipient is not due, under law.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1760" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-23">
<name>bishounen</name>
<description>Young man whose beauty (and sexual appeal) transcends the boundary of gender or sexual orientation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1876" parentid="2794" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>musical band</name>
<description>A musical ensemble also known as a music(al) group or music(al) band is a group of people who perform instrumental or vocal music, typically known by a distinct name.</description>
<picurl>10249.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2420" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>enigmatic</name>
<description>An enigmatic person is someone with a mysterious personality that is difficult to grasp and/or defies description.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2438" parentid="2794" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-16">
<name>idol</name>
<description>In Japanese culture, idols (アイドル) are media personalities in their teens and early twenties who are considered particularly cute and cuddly and who will, for a period ranging from several months to a few years, regularly appear in the mass media, e.g. as singers for J-pop groups, bit-part actors, TV personalities, models in photo spreads published in magazines, advertisements, etc.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>63097.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2565" parentid="2608" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-14">
<name>cross-dressing</name>
<description>This character sometimes wears clothes traditionally worn by and associated with the opposite sex.
Cross-dressers often hide their cross-dressing identity for a long period of time and thus tend to become adept in accurately portraying the opposite sex in terms of voice, movement, behaviour, temperament, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2566" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-31">
<name>loli</name>
<description>Lolita (often also just abbreviated to loli) refers originally to a novel by Vladimir Nabokov. The book is internationally famous for its controversial subject: the narrator and protagonist, middle aged Humbert Humbert, becomes obsessed and sexually involved with a 12-year-old girl named Dolores Haze.
Nowadays the name "Lolita" describes a sexually precocious young girl.
Related to this is http://anidb.net/t2415 [lolicon], the Japanese abbreviation of the English phrase "Lolita Complex". Sometimes written as "roricon" or "rorikon" due to the inexact mapping between Japanese and English phonemes. This is the term used to describe the fetish/fascination some mature people have for underage girls. There is an entire industry in Japan devoted to providing legal but schoolgirl-themed pornography, taking advantage of the cute childlike appearance some Japanese women maintain well into their twenties.
Because the characters in anime are often young by convention, many fans think that a character can only be Lolicon if she is twelve or younger. Exceptions are granted if the other character in the relationship is a lot older.
One particular device used to skirt the boundaries of taste and legality is the exotic being (alien, creature of magic, robot or the like) which takes the form of an underage human girl, but is in fact for all other practical purposes an adult.
Another reason why lolicon is fetishized by people may be because some of them just view it as a substitute for their fetish for flat-chested, but otherwise well-developed, women.
Source: Wikipedia / TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32760.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2633" parentid="2613" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>prison</name>
<description>A building used to house convicted criminals and accused persons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2654" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-13">
<name>medium awareness</name>
<description>Medium awareness is the situational and generally temporary awareness characters in works of fiction have and display of the very fact that they are characters in works of fiction. For example, they may comment about the background music, quip about the script or narration, complain about the roles given to them by the writer or their lack of screen time, see the subtitles that appear on screen, inform the audience about the arrival of the commercial break, and even use medium effects as tools. The most common form of medium awareness is known as breaking the fourth wall, in which characters speak directly to the audience, either to it as a whole or to specific members of it. The "fourth wall" is the imaginary "wall" at the front of the stage of a proscenium theatre through which the audience sees the play; it is a metaphor for the boundary between what happens inside the work, to the characters, and outside it, to the audience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2726" parentid="2848" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>prostitution</name>
<description>Prostitution is the practice or occupation of engaging in sexual activity with someone for payment.</description>
<picurl>222173.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>sex</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%27Origine_du_monde).
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2793" parentid="2883" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>performance</name>
<description>The song performance on stage or acting in a theatre is a central part of the character`s life in this anime type.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2840" parentid="2872" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>mafia</name>
<description>A mafia is a type of organized crime syndicate whose primary activities are protection racketeering, the arbitration of disputes between criminals, and the organizing and oversight of illegal agreements and transactions. Secondary activities may be practiced such as gambling, drug trafficking, loan sharking, and fraud. The term was originally applied to the Sicilian mafia, but has since expanded to encompass other organizations of similar methods and purpose, such as in "the Russian mafia" or "the Japanese mafia", and is applied informally by the press and public, but the criminal organizations themselves have their own terms; for example, the original Sicilian and Italian-American mafia call themselves "cosa nostra", while the Japanese mafia calls itself "yakuza".
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>211289.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2845" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-04-30">
<name>blackmail</name>
<description>In general usage, blackmail is a crime involving unjustified threats against a person or organization in order to make a gain or harm or cause material loss to them unless a demand is met. It may be considered similar to or a form of extortion, although some jurisdictions will consider them as separate crimes. Most often, blackmail involves the threat of revealing some secret to a given third party, which may be another person, a rival organization, or a state institution such as the police, or to the general public. In anime and related media, and more specifically in pornographic works, blackmail is also a device used to coerce people, generally female and often schoolgirls, into having sex with another or others; in such cases, it may be considered similar to or a form of rape.</description>
<picurl>136031.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2854" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>henshin</name>
<description>Japanese for "transformation" (metamorphosis or disguise).
A "henshin anime" is any anime, where the characters or their costumes transform, such as Sailor Moon. The henshin switches on the character`s special powers, and is frequently accompanied by a costume change. Often the change of clothing is the only outward indicator that the character has changed and yet nobody seems to notice the hero`s true self.
Most henshin heroes have a special item which they use to change into their heroic form. These items are usually activated by a command phrase (which is often in Engrish, for some reason), triggering a transformation sequence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2867" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>politics</name>
<description>From commies to fat capitalist pigs, all the stuff done by the "guys with the power", mainly evil tactics for gaining more power over the masses.
Watching this title may remind you why CNN is boring.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2878" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>conspiracy</name>
<description>The conspiracy thriller (or paranoid thriller) is a sub-genre of the thriller which flourished in the 1970s in the US (and was echoed in other parts of the world) in the wake of a number of high-profile scandals and controversies (most notably Vietnam, the assassination of President Kennedy, Chappaquiddick and Watergate), and which exposed what many people regarded as the clandestine machinations and conspiracies beneath the orderly fabric of political life.
The protagonists of conspiracy thrillers are often journalists or amateur investigators who find themselves (often inadvertently) pulling on a small thread which unravels a vast conspiracy that ultimately goes "all the way to the top".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2879" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>alcohol</name>
<description>Alcohol (or more scientifically, ethanol), is one of the world`s oldest psychoactive substances. It is traditionally found in the form of a beverage such as beer, wine, or liquor, although in some contexts it can be inhaled to produce similar or intoxication, and some people prefer another way of consuming beverage-form alcohol.
Alcoholic beverages are many and varied, due to production methods (fermentation or distillation), source materials (grains, fruits, vegetables, other plants), added substances such as flavorings, and many more ways of defining different forms of alcoholic beverages.
Alcoholic beverages are divided into three general classes: beers, wines, and spirits. They are legally consumed in most countries, and over 100 countries have laws regulating their production, sale, and consumption. In particular, such laws specify the minimum age at which a person may legally buy or drink them. This minimum age varies between 16 and 25 years, depending upon the country and the type of drink. Most nations set it at 18 years of age.</description>
<picurl>70749.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2882" parentid="2952" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-17">
<name>dystopia</name>
<description>A dystopia (from Ancient Greek: δυσ-, "bad, ill", and Ancient Greek: τόπος, "place, landscape"; alternatively cacotopia, or anti-utopia) is, in literature, an often futuristic society that has degraded into a repressive and controlled state, often under the guise of being utopian. Dystopian literature has underlying cautionary tones, warning society that if we continue to live how we do, this will be the consequence. A dystopia, thus, is regarded as a sort of negative utopia and is often characterized by an authoritarian or totalitarian form of government. Dystopias usually feature different kinds of repressive social control systems, a lack or total absence of individual freedoms and expressions and constant states of warfare or violence. Dystopias often explore the concept of humans abusing technology and how humans individually and collectively cope with technology that has evolved too quickly such as the car, the flamethrower or the microwave. A dystopian society is also often characterized by widespread poverty and brutal political controls such as a large military-like police.</description>
<picurl>69879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2885" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>law and order</name>
<description>Where there is "wealth", there are criminals. It is up to the civil law enforcement, i.e. detectives, Police or Special Squads, to keep the lawless activities in the real world or in cyberspace under control.
Note: Do not confuse this with Military presence.</description>
<picurl>238616.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2897" parentid="2885" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>police</name>
<description>The police (civil servants) are the good guys in the battle against crime. Though they try hard, they are usually outclassed by super-criminals or criminal organizations in anime, requiring the help of special units or some lone hero.</description>
<picurl>238615.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2926" parentid="2874" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>post-war</name>
<description>An armed conflict has ended not too long ago, devastation of the world or society is still evident.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2952" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-06">
<name>rotten world</name>
<description>A rotten world is a setting or situation where the jaded notion that "anything that can go wrong will go horribly wrong" almost always applies. Oppression, perpetual warfare, lawlessness, despair or other forms of mental instability, and other highly undesirable factors tend to be rampant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3086" parentid="4316" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-12">
<name>parricide</name>
<description>Parricide, or the murder of family members, is the act of taking the life of of one or more of one`s own close family members, or even one`s entire family; that may include spouses, parents, grandparents, children, grandchildren, siblings, cousins, uncles, aunts, nephews, and nieces, among others.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3132" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-08-11">
<name>helpful couple</name>
<description>This is a very low key type of romance in which the main two characters spend a great deal of time hanging out together just helping other people solve problems. The couple`s personal interaction tends to be subtle.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3149" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-15">
<name>journalism</name>
<description>Journalism is the work and distribution of reports on the interaction of events, facts, ideas, and people that are the "news of the day" and that informs society to at least some degree. The word applies to the occupation (professional or not), the methods of gathering information, and the organizing literary styles. Journalistic media include: print, television, radio, Internet and, in the past, newsreels.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3865" parentid="6153" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-08-07">
<name>noitaminA</name>
<description>noitaminA (ノイタミナ) – Animation written backwards – is a Fuji Television programming block, devoted to anime, broadcast each Thursday night from 00:45 to 1:15. It was launched with the intention of expanding the target audience beyond the typical young male demographic.
The timeslot was expanded from half an hour to a full hour in 2010, and now airs Thursday nights from 00:45 to 1:45.
noitaminA aired its first non-anime series in 2010, with the premiere of the live-action adaptation of Moyashimon. On April 15, 2010, Fuji TV and FUNimation announced an agreement that allows FUNimation to simulcast series from the noitaminA block in North America within an hour of their airing in Japan.</description>
<picurl>36897.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3929" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-09">
<name>sociocultural evolution</name>
<description>Describes how cultures and societies develop over time, based on both cultural evolution and social evolution.
A post-apocalyptic or a Utopian setting would show very interesting changes in human behaviour, mental state, or simply daily life.</description>
<picurl>191062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4096" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>gore</name>
<description>A Splatter film or Gore film is a sub-genre of horror film that deliberately focuses on graphic portrayals of gore and graphic violence. These films, through the use of special effects and excessive blood and guts, tend to display an overt interest in the vulnerability of the human body and the theatricality of its mutilation. Due to their willingness to portray images society might consider shocking, splatter films share some ideological grounds with the transgressive art movement. The term "splatter cinema" was coined by George A. Romero to describe his film Dawn of the Dead, though Dawn of the Dead is generally considered by critics to have higher aspirations, such as social commentary, than to be simply exploitative for its own sake.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>32491.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4170" parentid="5626" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-08-08">
<name>police are useless</name>
<description>The civilian law enforcement representatives do not seem to be of much use, when trying to take on the usually vastly superior foes.
The "helpless" and often clumsy antics of the police can be used as a comedy element.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4335" parentid="2867" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-09">
<name>governmental censorship</name>
<description>Censorship is the suppression of speech or deletion of communicative material which may be considered objectionable, harmful or sensitive, as determined by a censor. In fiction (particularly dystopian sci-fi works) often used by totalitarian regimes to control the people.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4522" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>social commentary</name>
<description>Social commentary is the act of rebelling against an individual, or a group of people by rhetorical means. This is most often done with the idea of implementing or promoting change by informing the general populace about a given problem and appealing to people’s sense of justice. (Source: Wikipedia)&#13;
&#13;
Since this is anime, usually, the mores of Japan and the Japanese society are scrutinised, but not restricted to that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4665" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-26">
<name>propaganda</name>
<description>Propaganda is communication aimed at influencing the attitude of a community toward some cause or position. As opposed to impartially providing information, propaganda in its most basic sense, presents information primarily to influence an audience. Propaganda often presents facts selectively (thus lying by omission) to encourage a particular synthesis, or uses loaded messages to produce an emotional rather than rational response to the information presented. The desired result is a change of the attitude toward the subject in the target audience to further a political agenda.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4952" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true">
<name>nationalism</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5244" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-07-03">
<name>detective agency</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5417" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-22">
<name>mind fuck</name>
<description>A `mind fuck` is a slang term which describes a work that uses literary devices such as nonlinear storytelling and plot twists in order to present convoluted, yet not conflicting, themes.
A creation is usually considered a mind fuck when a casual observer is not able to discern the true meaning of a work without making a serious attempt to unravel the themes presented or when the plot is incredibly difficult to follow.
Special examples of mind fucks involve a single plot twist which completely changes the viewer`s understanding of the events in a film or novel as well as the ideas it presents.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5626" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>adults are useless</name>
<description>For when adults can`t do anything right.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5868" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-14">
<name>rogue artificial intelligence</name>
<description>Artificial intelligence devices may at times act outside their intended parameters. While this normally doesn`t mean much in reality aside from forceful shutdowns and loss of productivity, in fiction this may go as far as turning against their own human creators/masters, and, in extreme cases, even exterminating them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6021" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>gender bender</name>
<description>Term used to refer to a person who takes on the role of their opposite gender. This often only reaches to the extent of cross-dressing (involving physical appearance and clothing only), but in rarer cases, involves a total gender swap (which seems to be more common in anime) - where the willing or unwilling victim receives a body opposite of their original gender (either permanently or temporarily), with all natural parts per their new body fully (or just all-out amply) included.
Example of cross-dressing gender bender: "Maria+Holic"
Examples of body-swap gender bender: "Kashimashi: Girl meets Girl", "Birdy the Mighty Decode"</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6070" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-15">
<name>mystery</name>
<description>The mystery film is a sub-genre of the more general category of crime film. It focuses on the efforts of the detective, private investigator or amateur sleuth to solve the mysterious circumstances of a crime by means of clues, investigation, and clever deduction. (Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6254" parentid="2872" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-23">
<name>terrorism</name>
<description>Terrorism is, in the broadest sense, the use of intentionally indiscriminate violence as a means to create terror among masses of people; or fear to achieve a religious or political aim. It is used in this regard primarily to refer to violence during peacetime or in war against non-combatants (mostly civilians and neutral military personnel). Some definitions now include acts of unlawful violence and war.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>10657.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="29077" type="cameo appearance in" update="2012-03-21">
<rating votes="407">7.44</rating>
<name>Hatsune Miku</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hatsune Miku is a singing synthesizer application and its female character, developed by Crypton Future Media. It uses Yamaha Corporation`s Vocaloid 2 synthesizing technology. The name of the character comes from a fusion of the Japanese for first (初 hatsu), sound (音 ne) and future (Miku (ミク) sounds like a nanori reading of future, 未来, normally read as mirai), referring to her position as the first of Crypton`s Character Vocal Series. She was the second Vocaloid to be sold using the Vocaloid 2 engine and the first Japanese Vocaloid to use the Japanese version of the Vocaloid 2 engine. Her voice is sampled from Japanese voice actress, http://anidb.net/cr1673 [Fujita Saki]. Hatsune Miku has performed onstage as a projection.
Miku`s popularity has seen various references to her in anime. During an episode of http://anidb.net/a5576 [Zoku Sayonara Zetsubou Sensei], Miku is seen auditioning for the voice of http://anidb.net/ch13125 [Otonashi Meru] (Kagamine Rin and Len are referenced in the same episode). Miku`s voice is used in the last http://anidb.net/s10696 [ending theme] for the anime series http://anidb.net/a6182 [Akikan!]. In the http://anidb.net/a5932 [Lucky Star OVA], http://anidb.net/ch32 [Hiiragi Kagami] gets magically transformed into Miku cosplay. http://anidb.net/ch11062 [Kondou Mikoto] in the anime http://anidb.net/a6685 [Kampfer] appears dressed as Miku in episode seven. Miku also makes a cameo appearance in the anime http://anidb.net/a6176 [Sora o Kakeru Shoujo] as well as getting cosplayed by http://anidb.net/ch2254 [Kannagi Itsuki] in the second picture drama.</description>
<picture>84342.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="34258" type="main character in" update="2011-08-05">
<rating votes="46">6.73</rating>
<name>Inga</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76476.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1438" picture="69192.jpg">Toyosaki Aki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34259" type="main character in" update="2017-06-14">
<rating votes="45">6.73</rating>
<name>Yuuki Shinjuurou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76477.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="15592" picture="76468.jpg">Katsuji Ryou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35171" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-05">
<rating votes="42">7.12</rating>
<name>Kaishou Rie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76470.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="25804" picture="71817.jpg">Yamamoto Nozomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35172" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-05">
<rating votes="25">3.84</rating>
<name>Kaishou Rinroku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76473.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="233" picture="228661.jpg">Miki Shin`ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35173" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-05">
<rating votes="19">4.23</rating>
<name>Koyama Izumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76474.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="442" picture="187043.jpg">Honda Takako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35174" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-08-05">
<rating votes="19">2.03</rating>
<name>Hayami Seigen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76475.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="470" picture="17419.jpg">Irino Miyu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37731" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-13">
<rating votes="60">8.18</rating>
<name>Inga</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68805.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1438" picture="69192.jpg">Toyosaki Aki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37732" type="appears in" update="2011-10-13">
<rating votes="1">2.39</rating>
<name>Kanou Atsuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68806.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="166" picture="23196.jpg">Kuwashima Houko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37733" type="appears in" update="2011-10-13">
<rating votes="1">1.18</rating>
<name>Ono Ittou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68807.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6345" picture="30893.jpg">Kouno Tomoyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37734" type="appears in" update="2011-10-13">
<rating votes="1">1.56</rating>
<name>Kanou Nobuzane</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68808.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="409" picture="24867.jpg">Arimoto Kinryuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37735" type="appears in" update="2011-10-13">
<rating votes="1">2.39</rating>
<name>Terada Ryouko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68816.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12672" picture="42847.jpg">Ozaki Reina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37736" type="appears in" update="2011-10-13">
<rating votes="1">1.56</rating>
<name>Kanda Masahiko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68817.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="264" picture="228626.jpg">Ogata Mitsuru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37890" type="appears in" update="2011-10-20">
<rating votes="3">4.22</rating>
<name>Osada An</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70818.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27357" picture="75009.jpg">Yasuno Kiyono</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37891" type="appears in" update="2011-10-20">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Oyamada Arata</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70819.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10190" picture="48563.jpg">Higuchi Tomoyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37892" type="appears in" update="2011-10-20">
<rating votes="2">3.16</rating>
<name>Tsunemi Kumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70888.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="641" picture="31202.jpg">Katou Emiri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37893" type="appears in" update="2011-10-20">
<name>Nakahashi Eitarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70889.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2071" picture="74324.jpg">Oohata Shintarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37894" type="appears in" update="2011-10-20">
<rating votes="2">3.16</rating>
<name>Umezawa Yumeno</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70896.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="475" picture="17433.jpg">Makino Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37895" type="appears in" update="2011-10-20">
<rating votes="2">4.89</rating>
<name>Nakahashi Sumika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70897.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10759" picture="38748.jpg">Anzai Chika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37896" type="appears in" update="2011-10-20">
<rating votes="2">3.97</rating>
<name>Tsunemi Kumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70898.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="641" picture="31202.jpg">Katou Emiri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37897" type="appears in" update="2011-10-20">
<rating votes="2">3.16</rating>
<name>Umezawa Yumeno</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70927.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="475" picture="17433.jpg">Makino Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37898" type="appears in" update="2011-10-20">
<rating votes="2">3.16</rating>
<name>Nakahashi Sumika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70928.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10759" picture="38748.jpg">Anzai Chika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37899" type="appears in" update="2011-10-20">
<rating votes="2">2.50</rating>
<name>Osada Hisako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>70929.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30024" picture="79284.jpg">Matsuzawa Chiaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37900" type="appears in" update="2011-10-20">
<rating votes="1">1.04</rating>
<name>Yonagahime 3+1</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>70950.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="37913" type="appears in" update="2011-10-21">
<rating votes="1">1.18</rating>
<name>Aramaki Toshiji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="37914" type="appears in" update="2011-10-21">
<rating votes="2">4.89</rating>
<name>Anzai Eri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="38166" type="appears in" update="2011-10-27">
<rating votes="1">1.04</rating>
<name>Sasa Itoji</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>74184.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4020" picture="28744.jpg">Matsuoka Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38167" type="appears in" update="2011-10-27">
<rating votes="1">1.04</rating>
<name>Sasa Fumihiko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>74186.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3130" picture="186156.jpg">Watanabe Kumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38168" type="appears in" update="2011-10-27">
<rating votes="1">1.18</rating>
<name>Sasa Kigihiko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>74199.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="177" picture="170981.jpg">Hoshino Takanori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38169" type="appears in" update="2011-10-27">
<rating votes="1">2.39</rating>
<name>Taku Hidenobu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>74209.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4039" picture="91415.jpg">Mogami Tsuguo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38170" type="appears in" update="2011-10-27">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Sasa Mitsuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>74195.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2142" picture="170565.jpg">Shiina Hekiru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38171" type="appears in" update="2011-10-27">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Sasa Kazamori</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>74260.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="38172" type="appears in" update="2011-10-27">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Sasa Komamori</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>74323.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4039" picture="91415.jpg">Mogami Tsuguo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38173" type="appears in" update="2011-10-27">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Sasa Kazamori</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>74334.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="38352" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-11-03">
<rating votes="8">4.69</rating>
<name>Sasa Kazamori</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76693.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5700" picture="172104.jpg">Matsumoto Marika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38361" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-11-10">
<rating votes="22">7.96</rating>
<name>Sasa Kazamori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76942.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5700" picture="172104.jpg">Matsumoto Marika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38582" type="appears in" update="2011-11-10">
<rating votes="1">2.39</rating>
<name>Shimada Jirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76930.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="454" picture="17354.jpg">Furuya Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38583" type="appears in" update="2011-11-10">
<rating votes="3">2.75</rating>
<name>Hirata Youko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76931.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3830" picture="25450.jpg">Terasaki Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38584" type="appears in" update="2011-11-10">
<rating votes="1">2.39</rating>
<name>Yamamoto Teishin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76934.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="178" picture="228660.jpg">Miyake Kenta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38585" type="appears in" update="2011-11-10">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Ootsubo Tetsuya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76935.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="214" picture="238138.jpg">Nojima Hirofumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38586" type="appears in" update="2011-11-10">
<rating votes="1">1.18</rating>
<name>Shimada Hakurou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76936.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="284" picture="225436.jpg">Tanaka Masahiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38587" type="appears in" update="2011-11-10">
<rating votes="1">1.56</rating>
<name>Mitsuhisa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76941.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="38588" type="appears in" update="2011-11-10">
<rating votes="1">1.56</rating>
<name>Gomi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76940.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="38813" type="appears in" update="2011-11-17">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Yajima</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>77257.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="168" picture="246304.jpg">Fujiwara Keiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38814" type="appears in" update="2011-11-17">
<rating votes="1">2.39</rating>
<name>Yajima Akio</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>77258.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32669" picture="87955.jpg">Toba Tsukiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38815" type="appears in" update="2011-11-17">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Yajima Takako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>77259.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="447" picture="224407.jpg">Tsunematsu Ayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38816" type="appears in" update="2011-11-17">
<rating votes="3">4.71</rating>
<name>Shousetsuka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>77260.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1678" picture="68277.jpg">Kaji Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38817" type="appears in" update="2011-11-17">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Yajima Kazuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>77261.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="31646" picture="85192.jpg">Satou Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38818" type="appears in" update="2011-11-17">
<rating votes="2">4.61</rating>
<name>Kaishou Maid</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>77262.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="157" picture="42784.jpg">Orikasa Fumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38991" type="appears in" update="2011-11-24">
<rating votes="4">4.85</rating>
<name>Izawa Sayo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>77539.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1798" picture="20493.jpg">Kotobuki Minako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38992" type="appears in" update="2011-11-24">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Tanimura Motoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>77540.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="411" picture="17475.jpg">Takagaki Ayahi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38993" type="appears in" update="2011-11-24">
<rating votes="2">4.89</rating>
<name>Yada Sumie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>77541.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1438" picture="69192.jpg">Toyosaki Aki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38994" type="appears in" update="2011-11-24">
<rating votes="1">1.18</rating>
<name>Mitaka Kichitarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>77542.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4742" picture="54426.jpg">Fukumatsu Shin`ya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39195" type="appears in" update="2011-12-01">
<rating votes="1">1.56</rating>
<name>Okamoto Kankichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>77896.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="455" picture="17356.jpg">Matsumoto Yasunori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39196" type="appears in" update="2011-12-02">
<rating votes="6">1.87</rating>
<name>Bettenou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>77897.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="40132" type="appears in" update="2012-01-02">
<rating votes="2">1.99</rating>
<name>Kuramitsu Mine</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>79349.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1662" picture="25819.jpg">Kouda Mariko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40133" type="appears in" update="2012-01-02">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Fuwa Juujirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>79350.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3185" picture="171529.jpg">Terasoma Masaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40134" type="appears in" update="2012-01-02">
<rating votes="1">1.04</rating>
<name>Motoyama Minami</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>79351.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="382" picture="228600.jpg">Ookawa Tooru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40135" type="appears in" update="2012-01-02">
<rating votes="1">1.04</rating>
<name>Mizuno Sakon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>79353.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="7432" picture="69009.jpg">Horikawa Jin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="40136" type="appears in" update="2012-01-02">
<rating votes="1">1.56</rating>
<name>Mihara Yasutarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>79354.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2225" picture="192115.jpg">Kimura Ryouhei</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="133203" update="2012-05-27">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="133204" update="2012-05-27">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="133659" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-12-23</airdate>
<rating votes="11">7.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">私はただ探している</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`m Just Searching</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Je ne fais que chercher</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Watashi wa Tada Sagashiteiru</title>
<summary>A mysterious invitation has been delivered to Shinjurou and several other people who have a connection to Chairman Kaishou. It contains the message, "An invitation to a party, in which the real person behind the bombing will be discovered" and seemingly bears the personal seal of Kaishou himself. And so, the people concerned gather together in the TV studio that had recently been bombed. A furious Izumi suspects Shinjurou of setting up the "farce", to which he responds, "I was called here, too. In other words, a crime is going to occur. And a major crime at that..." Was Kaishou behind the bombing? Shinjurou`s final deductions begin and along the way, Inga and Bettenou`s true identities are revealed. It culminates in a showdown between the two entities, but once everything is laid bare, what will be the relationship between Shinjurou, Inga and Rie?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>586026</identifier>
<identifier>un-go</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="133660" update="2011-12-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-12-16</airdate>
<rating votes="9">5.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">海勝麟六の葬送</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kaishou Rinroku`s Funeral</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les funérailles de Rinroku Kaishô</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaishou Rinroku no Sousou</title>
<summary>Inga has disappeared, but Shinjurou continues to search for the truth alone. While investigating the TV station bombing, Shinjurou, who suspects that Kaishou used Bettenou to do it, devises a plan to uncover the truth. Kaishou is requested to testify at a budget committee, but if done via video monitor while he`s in his hospital bed, Bettenou`s ability to manipulate people through a person`s words should be blocked. Kaishou, who easily deflects the rigorous interrogation, says, "There are an innumerable amount of truths. Being satisfied with just one truth is no more than ceasing to think about it beyond that point." Angered at the words, Shinjurou questions Kaishou without thinking and asks Rie to testify as his trump card. Rie explains, "Right after the explosion at the TV station, I saw my father at home." Was the Kaishou at the TV station an illusion produced by Bettenou? Then Inga appears in womanly form to ask the truth of an unexpected person!</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>586024</identifier>
<identifier>un-go</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="133661" update="2011-12-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-12-09</airdate>
<rating votes="9">7.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">海勝麟六の犯罪</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kaishou Rinroku`s Crime</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le crime de Rinroku Kaishô</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaishou Rinroku no Hanzai</title>
<summary>A group of crackers calling themselves "Full Circle" fix on JJ Systems as their target and begin attacking by leaking the company`s data as well as revealing Rinroku Kaishou`s private life. Amid those unfavorable winds, Kaishou appears on a TV talk show. The other participants, a politician, the president of a rival company, and the writer of a tell-all book are all critical of Kaishou. Just before, Full Circle spread the rumor across the net that Kaishou intends to gather together everyone who is hostile towards him and murder them. Then, right after the program starts, there is an explosion at the TV station. Eight people are dead or missing, including the participants on the program. Kaishou himself is seriously injured and taken to a hospital, but word spreads that he`s the one behind the blast. Meanwhile, Shinjurou is on the trail of Bettenou when he gets called to the hospital by Rie, who requests that he prove Kaishou`s innocence. Shinjurou is surprised by the irony, yet begins investigating...</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>586022</identifier>
<identifier>un-go</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="133662" update="2011-12-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-12-02</airdate>
<rating votes="11">5.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">楽園の王</title>
<title xml:lang="en">King of Paradise</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le roi du paradis</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rakuen no Ou</title>
<summary>After searching for the missing Shinjurou on the net, Kazamori discovers that he`s in the East Kantou Social Rehabilitation Program Center, a prison. Shinjurou`s objective in going to this privately-run prison was to interview the criminal who calls himself "The Novelist" regarding a previous case. Through Rie, Rinroku, Koyama and Hayami also learn of Shinjurou`s whereabouts. Rie tags along as Koyama heads to the prison, where they first meet the Novelist, the last person to see Shinjurou before his disappearance...</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>586020</identifier>
<identifier>un-go</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="133663" update="2011-12-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-11-25</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ハクチユウム</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Daydream</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Rêverie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hakuchiyuumu</title>
<summary>Shinjurou Yuuki is working as a movie cameraman. His current project is "The Retard", a film set in a fictionalized modern-day Japan that is embroiled in war, though the story focuses on three young women who escape from different places only to wind up living together in the closet of a ramshackle house and being loved by the same man. The seeming disinterest of the director, Kichitarou Mitaka, is balanced by the passion of the three lead actresses. Their enthusiasm rubs off on Shinjurou, who becomes inspired to do the best work he`s ever done. But then, one day, Director Mitaka is murdered and the prime suspect is Shinjurou himself, apparently the last person to see the director alive...</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>586018</identifier>
<identifier>un-go</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="133664" update="2011-12-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-11-18</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あまりにも簡単な暗号</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Code Too Simple</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un code trop simple</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Amarini mo Kantan`na Angou</title>
<summary>Yajima, a man who has just gotten out of prison, pays Shinjurou a visit. It turns out that he`s an old friend of Kaishou and he asks the young detective to break a secret code. Folded inside of a purloined book from Kaishou`s library is a piece of paper from Yajima`s own personalized manuscript paper with a series of numbers written on it. The decoded message indicates a planned rendezvous, which leads to the suspicion that Kaishou and Yajima`s wife had an affair while Yajima was incarcerated. But where are the Yajima children, who suddenly disappeared one day?</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>586016</identifier>
<identifier>un-go</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="133665" update="2011-12-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-11-11</airdate>
<rating votes="13">5.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">幻の像</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Statue of Illusion</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La statue fantôme</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maboroshi no Zou</title>
<summary>During the war, three students bravely volunteered to prevent a terrorist bombing . After the war, it became taboo to speak of their actions, but the unveiling of a bronze statue is held to praise the three young heroes. The sponsor is Hakurou Shimada, the leader of the "Rising Sun Party", a political organization the three students had been involved in. But then, during the ceremony, two corpses are discovered inside a hidden cavity in the statue. Shinjurou had been invited to the unveiling, so with two murder victims right in front of him, he gets caught up in the puzzling case.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>586014</identifier>
<identifier>un-go</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="133666" update="2011-12-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-11-04</airdate>
<rating votes="13">6.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">素顔の家</title>
<title xml:lang="en">House, Unmasked</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La famille démasquée</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sugao no Ie</title>
<summary>The former head of the Sasa family, Komamori Sasa, developed a groundbreaking artificial intelligence known as RAI (Real A.I.), but the technology was banned by the government and consigned to oblivion. Shinjurou`s brilliant reasoning follows a trail to the past and exposes the Sasa family`s hidden truth. But even then, a mystery remains, until a certain event provides the young detective with a hint, dispelling all of his doubts!</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>586012</identifier>
<identifier>un-go</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="133667" update="2011-12-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-10-28</airdate>
<rating votes="13">4.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">覆面屋敷</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Masked Mansion</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La famille résidence sans visage</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fukumen Yashiki</title>
<summary>Rie pays Shinjurou a visit, thinking he`ll be able to solve the mystery that occurs at the Sassa house. The deceased is the head of the Sassa household, Kazamori Sassa. Kazamori`s father, Komamori, was a brilliant researcher in the field of artificial intelligence, but during the war, his research was suppressed and he was subsequently killed in an explosion. Seven years later, his son, Kazamori, also dies suddenly in an explosion. Is it murder, suicide, or perhaps a curse...?</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>586010</identifier>
<identifier>un-go</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="133668" update="2011-12-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-10-21</airdate>
<rating votes="13">3.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">無情のうた</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Pitiless Song</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le chant impitoyable</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mujo no Uta</title>
<summary>A trunk is delivered to a mansion by an unlicensed taxi driver. Inside is the corpse of the mansion`s owner, Osada Hisako. Based on Kaishou Rinraku`s deductions, a manhunt begins for the suspect, Aramaki. But An, the daughter of Osada Hisako, tells Shinjurou that Aramaki isn`t the killer. This leads the "Defeated Detective" into a search for the real murderer as well as the secret behind wartime pop group Yonagahime.</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>586008</identifier>
<identifier>un-go</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="133669" update="2011-12-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-10-14</airdate>
<rating votes="13">3.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">舞踏会の殺人</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Murder at the Ball</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Meurtre au bal</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Butoukai no Satsujin</title>
<summary>In a near-future, post-war Tokyo, the war hero president of a major corporation is murdered at his own party. Will the brilliant, young Shinjurou prove his self-proclaimed title as "the last great detective" by solving the case, or will devious "Media King" Rinroku Kaishou beat him to it, leading to a questionable outcome and the branding of Shinjurou as the "Defeated Detective" once again?</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>586006</identifier>
<identifier>un-go</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="133962" update="2011-10-13">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-10-14</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="133963" update="2011-10-13">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-10-14</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134729" update="2011-11-08">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2011-11-08</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="x-unk">Inga Nikki</title>
<title xml:lang="ja">因果日記</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Inga`s Diary - 01</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Inga Nikki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134889" update="2011-11-20">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2011-11-20</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">因果日記</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Inga`s Diary - 02</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Inga Nikki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="135249" update="2011-12-10">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2011-12-10</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">因果日記</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Inga`s Diary - 03</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Inga Nikki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136370" update="2012-01-15">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2012-01-15</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">因果日記</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Inga`s Diary - 04</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Inga Nikki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136847" update="2012-02-04">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2012-02-04</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">因果日記</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Inga`s Diary - 05</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Inga Nikki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="138190" update="2012-03-27">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2012-03-27</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">因果日記</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Inga`s Diary - 06</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Inga Nikki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="138507" update="2012-04-13">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2012-04-06</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">因果日記</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Inga`s Diary - 07</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Inga Nikki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="138865" update="2012-04-13">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2012-04-13</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">因果日記</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Inga`s Diary - 08</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Inga Nikki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="138989" update="2012-04-19">
<epno type="2">S9</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2012-04-19</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">因果日記</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Inga`s Diary - 09</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Inga Nikki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139094" update="2012-04-24">
<epno type="2">S10</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2012-04-24</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">因果日記</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Inga`s Diary - 10</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Inga Nikki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139830" update="2012-05-27">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139832" update="2012-05-27">
<epno type="6">O10</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2011-12-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 11 Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139833" update="2012-05-27">
<epno type="6">O9</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2011-12-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 10 Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139834" update="2012-05-27">
<epno type="6">O8</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2011-12-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 09 Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139835" update="2012-05-27">
<epno type="6">O7</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2011-11-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 08 Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139836" update="2012-05-27">
<epno type="6">O6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2011-11-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 07 Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139837" update="2012-05-27">
<epno type="6">O5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2011-11-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 06 Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139838" update="2012-05-27">
<epno type="6">O4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2011-11-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 05 Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139839" update="2012-05-27">
<epno type="6">O3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2011-10-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 04 Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139840" update="2012-05-27">
<epno type="6">O2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2011-10-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 03 Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="139841" update="2012-05-27">
<epno type="6">O1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2011-10-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 02 Preview</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
