<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8552" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2012-01-06</startdate>
<enddate>2012-03-30</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Kill Me Baby</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Прикончи меня, детка</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Baby, Please Kill Me</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">爱杀宝贝</title>
<title xml:lang="x-kot" type="synonym">킬 미 베이비</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">kmb</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">キルミーベイベー</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Kill Me Baby</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">啾咪BABY</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="10025" type="Other">Kill Me Baby (2013)</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="8168" approval="29" total="44">Nichijou</anime>
<anime id="8729" approval="6" total="20">Danshi Koukousei no Nichijou</anime>
<anime id="4777" approval="6" total="15">Lucky Star</anime>
<anime id="5335" approval="5" total="13">Suzumiya Haruhi-chan no Yuuutsu</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="7">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="540154">It´s the funniest anime I`ve ever seen, and I`ve seen loads of!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="85123">entertaining for what it is</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="523039">Funny as hell</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="69845">Simply put, one of best anime ever. Hahahhahahahaha. The reason why JCStaff is still around is because they put out shows like Kill Me Baby.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="461271">Totally adorable and cute! Loved it from the start and in the end I was sad it was over so quickly. The ending song with its canon is also super addictive!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="174082">If you like watching shows with no plot and just in it for the laughs i recommend this one.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="222294">fakin hilarious xD</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.tbs.co.jp/anime/kmb/</url>
<creators>
<name id="28217" type="Original Work">Kazuho</name>
<name id="720" type="Animation Work">J.C.Staff</name>
<name id="3391" type="Character Design">Hasegawa Shin`ya</name>
<name id="4637" type="Series Composition">Shirane Hideki</name>
<name id="1521" type="Direction">Yamakawa Yoshiki</name>
<name id="29611" type="Music">Expo</name>
<name id="4386" type="Chief Animation Direction">Andou Masahiro</name>
<name id="3391" type="Chief Animation Direction">Hasegawa Shin`ya</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a http://anidb.net/t2805 [4-koma] manga by http://anidb.net/cr28217 [Kazuho], serialised in Manga Time Kirara Carat.
The life of the naive school girl http://anidb.net/ch35928 [Yasuna] and her no-nonsense assassin classmate http://anidb.net/ch35927 [Sonya] knows no dull moments. Sonya`s attempt to fit in often fails when her natural assassin instincts kick in and Yasuna`s attempt to be more friendly with Sonya often gets her hurt or intimidated, but she does not give up...</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1626">3.89</permanent>
<temporary count="1644">6.17</temporary>
<review count="1">6.66</review>
</ratings>
<picture>77865.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13289</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11079</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5017</identifier>
<identifier>ovjxtk</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://killmebaby.tv/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tbs.co.jp/anime/kmb/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Baby,_Please_Kill_Me!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>キルミーベイベー</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2372</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>341347</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14190</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2012/killmebaby</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="204" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-06-19">
<name>violent</name>
</tag>
<tag id="569" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-11-18">
<name>clumsy</name>
<description>A clumsy person is one lacking in coordination, and as such prone to often having accidents such as tripping, bumping into objects, or dropping things. In female characters, this is often thought of as endearing.</description>
<picurl>63355.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1032" parentid="2881" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-08-10">
<name>fishing</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1283" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-06-24">
<name>tsukkomi</name>
<description>A tsukkomi is a comedy duo stock character in a traditional Japanese slapstick stand-up comedy style known as manzai. Tsukkomi characters are the smart, reasonable, and down-to-earth half of the unit; their simple-minded counterparts are the http://anidb.net/t1399 [boke] characters. As a result of their boke counterparts` simple mistakes and gross exaggerations, tsukkomi berate and abuse them both verbally and physically; a very common example of tsukkomi physical abuse is a paper fan slap, which is generally accompanied by a sound effect. Their approximate equivalent in Western culture is the comedy role of straight man.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2665" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-16">
<name>school sports festival</name>
<description>To show off the students in sports clothing — in ecchi anime the female students in particular — a sports festival (or athletic meet) is quite popular in your typical anime with school setting. Here the protagonists can show their skills in diverse athletic competitions.
Note: This festival may also, though very rarely, take place at a kindergarten or preschool.</description>
<picurl>161025.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2770" parentid="2653" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>violent retribution for accidental infringement</name>
<description>A comedy / slapstick element often found in Ecchi anime: The hilarity derives from spontaneous embarrassment, overreaction of the "victim" (girl), immediate retribution for a seemingly inappropriate act, and a sense of pity with the supposed "aggressor" (boy).
Typically a boy will - through no fault of his own - stumble into a girl, thus invading her personal space. In the process the boy may e.g. pull down her skirt, grab the girl`s breasts, or accidentally kiss her. Any level-headed girl would see the accident just for what it is. Not so the girl with an overly developed sense of modesty, and a thing for violence. She - often a tsundere - will clobber the boy with excessive brutality.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2805" parentid="2798" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>4-koma manga</name>
<description>Yonkoma manga (4コマ漫画, four cell manga, or 4-koma for short), a comic-strip format, generally consists of gag comic strips within four panels of equal size ordered from top to bottom. (They also sometimes run right-to-left horizontally or use a hybrid 2x2 style, depending on the layout requirements of the publication in which they appear.) Though the word yonkoma comes from the Japanese, the style also exists outside of Japan in other Asian countries as well as in the English-speaking market.</description>
<picurl>70558.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2830" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>furo scene</name>
<description>Furo (polite: Ofuro) is Japanese for bath, specifically a type of bath which originated as a short, steep-sided wooden bathtub. Baths of this type are found all over Japan in houses, apartments and traditional Japanese inns (Ryokans).
Furo are part of the Japanese ritual of bathing, not used for washing but for relaxing and warming oneself. Washing is carried out separately outside the furo, and only when completely clean does the bather enter the water. Generally Japanese bathrooms are small, so the bathroom is set up much like a walk-in shower area but containing the ofuro.
The cheapest and shortest way to show naked skin on TV, at least as much as allowed. It usually only takes up few minutes at most and as such it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in the nude and raise the DVD sales while still maintaining a "non-filler" episode.
Compare to the big brothers http://anidb.net/t4290 [sentou episode] and http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode].
See also http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode], and http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].</description>
<picurl>160785.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2865" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-16">
<name>summer festival</name>
<description>The summer festival is used to show off the female protagonists in traditional Japanese clothing — the yukata — a casual form of kimono.
The festivities include food stalls (cotton candy, candy apples, choco bananas, taiyaki), various games (scoop goldfishes), and a fireworks display.</description>
<picurl>161023.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2880" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-01">
<name>Christmas</name>
<description>Christmas, also referred to as Christmas Day, is an annual holiday celebrated on December 25 that commemorates the birth of Jesus of Nazareth. The day marks the beginning of the larger season of Christmastide, which lasts twelve days. The nativity of Jesus, which is the basis for the Anno Domini system of dating, is thought to have occurred between 7 and 2 BC. December 25 is not known to be Jesus` actual date of birth, and the date may have been chosen to correspond with either a Roman festival or the winter solstice.
On the Julian calendar, followed by most Orthodox churches, Christmas Day also falls on O.S. December 25th; this corresponds to N.S. January 7th on the Gregorian calendar, followed by Western churches.
Modern customs of the holiday include gift-giving, Church celebrations, and the display of various decorations—including the Christmas tree, lights, mistletoe, nativity scenes, and holly. Santa Claus (also referred to as Father Christmas, although the two figures have different origins) is a popular mythological figure often associated with bringing gifts at Christmas for children. Santa is generally believed to be the result of a syncretization between Saint Nicholas and elements from pagan Nordic and Christian mythology, and his modern appearance is believed to have originated in 19th century media.
Christmas is celebrated throughout the Christian population, but is also celebrated by many non-Christians as a secular, cultural festival. Because gift-giving and several other aspects of the holiday involve heightened economic activity among both Christians and non-Christians, Christmas has become a major event for many retailers.</description>
<picurl>160837.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2886" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-16">
<name>New Year`s Day</name>
<description>It is tradition in Japan to celebrate the new year at a Shinto shrine (hatsumode). The protagonists will offer some money, ring a bell at the end of a thick rope, and then pray for good fortune.
This usually goes along with gorging yourself at the many temporary food stalls, playing various games, and drawing a fortune.
The female characters in the anime will usually dress up in a kimono, to show off their traditional Japanese clothing, while watching the fireworks.</description>
<picurl>161028.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4290" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>bath house visit</name>
<description>A sentou is a type of Japanese communal bath house where customers pay for entrance. Some Japanese find social importance in going to public baths, out of the theory that physical intimacy brings emotional intimacy, which is termed skinship in Japanese. Traditionally it is gender-segregated — men usually bathe only with men, and women with women. 
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in the nude and raise the DVD sales.
See also http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode], http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode], and http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].</description>
<picurl>160783.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4570" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-07">
<name>watercolour style</name>
<description>A watercolour or aquarelle is a painting method in which the paints are made of pigments suspended in a water-based solution. Some anime are created in the style of watercolour paintings, the watercolour style, usually with faded pastels that often give the show a warm and friendly visual presentation. In modern anime, this is generally achieved via computer effects that create an imitation of watercolour, rather than by creating real-life watercolour art. While the watercolour style is more commonly used for backgrounds, it is possible to create the entire anime in such a style.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5840" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-16">
<name>birthday</name>
<description>All about the birthday celebration of at least one of the protagonists in this anime.
This includes a birthday party with a birthday cake and other food and presents — lots of them.</description>
<picurl>161031.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5846" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-26">
<name>beach visit</name>
<description>Every anime has to have them, episodes in which the characters for whatever reason end up going to the sea, ocean, random island or the local pond.
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in swimsuits and raise the DVD sales.
The cheap version is the http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].
Other marginally less used variants of this are the http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode] and the http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], used when it is too cold for a beach/pool episode.
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene].</description>
<picurl>160805.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="35927" type="main character in" update="2011-11-10">
<rating votes="33">6.89</rating>
<name>Sonya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76924.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3712" picture="240126.jpg">Tamura Mutsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35928" type="main character in" update="2011-11-10">
<rating votes="37">7.57</rating>
<name>Oribe Yasuna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76923.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18198" picture="228672.jpg">Akasaki Chinatsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35929" type="main character in" update="2011-11-10">
<rating votes="34">7.65</rating>
<name>Goshiki Agiri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76925.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5220" picture="29211.jpg">Takabe Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="39198" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-12-02">
<rating votes="9">4.13</rating>
<name>Botsu Chara</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>77903.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3" picture="44969.jpg">Kugimiya Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="132618" update="2011-08-24">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2011-08-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">PV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="135222" update="2012-02-08">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-01-06</airdate>
<rating votes="12">4.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">いぬをしのびてさくらさく</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sneaking Dog, Blossoming Cherry</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Inu o Shinobite Sakura Saku</title>
<summary>Yasuna Oribe gets a lot of injuries from classmate and hired assassin, Sonya. When a dog wanders into the classroom, the two think of a way to get rid of it. Later, Yasuna meets a self-proclaimed ninja named Agiri Goshiki who tries to sell her some `ninjitsus`.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="135946" update="2011-12-31">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">ED PV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="135947" update="2011-12-31">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="135948" update="2011-12-31">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136187" update="2012-02-08">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-01-27</airdate>
<rating votes="8">3.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あいするすいかよがしかく</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ice Cream Scream Watermelon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ai Suru Suika Yoga Shikaku</title>
<summary>On a hot summer`s day, Yasuna and Sonya buy some ice cream, where Yasuna becomes obsessed with finding a winning stick. The next day, they head to the beach to try and break open a watermelon. Later, Sonya is targeted by another assassin, who is eventually stopped by Agiri. On another day, more assassins disguised as Yasuna target Sonya, which becomes more confusing when the real Yasuna shows up and plays along.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="136188" update="2012-02-08">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-01-20</airdate>
<rating votes="9">3.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">えすぱのろえばあめずもう</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cursed Psychic Rain Wrestling</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Esper Noroeba Amezumou</title>
<summary>Yasuna tries her hand at psychic powers and voodoo curses, before finding some activities to do on a rainy day. Later, a red haired girl who was rejected from the main cast tries to take revenge on Yasuna and Sonya, but keeps missing them.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="136189" update="2012-02-08">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-01-13</airdate>
<rating votes="11">3.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">わざぬんちゃくでくまふうせん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nunchaku Skills Bear Balloon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Waza Nunchaku de Kuma Fuusen</title>
<summary>Yasuna tries and fails to learn to use nunchuks before she and Sonya encounter an escaped bear. The next day, a little girl gets Sonya and Yasuna to play with her.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="136196" update="2012-01-06">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-01-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136197" update="2012-01-06">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2012-01-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136651" update="2012-02-13">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-02-10</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">へそからくりでてるごおり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Navel Mechanism Paper Doll Ice</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Heso Karakuri de Terugoori</title>
<summary>As summer ends, Yasuna gets a craving for shaved ice and asks Agiri for help. Later, Yasuna and Sonya go to Agiri`s house, filled with hidden mechanisms, before later having to deal with a stormy day.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="136652" update="2012-02-08">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-02-03</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">むしをまつりてうみにんぎょう</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Buggy Festival Sea Dolls</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mushi o Matsurite Umi Ningyou</title>
<summary>Yasuna`s attempt to get Sonya interested in bug catching goes awry when she attracts a lot of bees. Later, Yasuna and Sonya go to a festival and try out all the stalls. Whilst at the beach, Yasuna and Sonya deal with a loose dog and get stranded at sea. Later, Yasuna practises a puppet routine, which just annoys Sonya.
Source: Wikipedia</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="137054" update="2012-02-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-02-17</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ぶんかおてだまできばせん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Culture Beanbag Jousting Duel</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bunka Otedama de Kibasen</title>
<summary>As Yasuna tries to come up with a project for the upcoming culture festival, Sonya demonstrates how long she is able to hold her breath. At a sports festival, the girls debate who should be on top in a tower battle. Later, Yasuna becomes irritated when Sonya trumps her at juggling. Afterwards, both Yasuna and Sonya become engaged in a battle against a mosquito.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="137249" update="2012-02-17">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-03-09</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さんたつららてゆきだるむ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Santa Icicle Snow Mantra</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Santa Tsurara te Yukidaruma</title>
</episode>
<episode id="137250" update="2012-02-17">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-03-02</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">つりつちのこしわすれえだ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fishing Hammer`s Spawn Branch Forgotten</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsuri Tsuchinokoshi Wasure Eda</title>
</episode>
<episode id="137251" update="2012-02-29">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-02-24</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">はまりかなでりつきささり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sticking, Strumming, Stabbing</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hamari Kanaderi Tsukisasari</title>
<summary>Whilst trying to play a prank on Sonya, Yasuna gets a bin stuck on her head. Later, Yasuna has Sonya try out various musical instruments before roping her into a game of darts.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="137677" update="2012-03-09">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-03-30</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">きるがみーしてべいべする</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Make the Kill Me and Make Me Your Baby</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kill ga Me Shite Baby Suru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="137678" update="2012-03-09">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-03-23</airdate>
<rating votes="5">2.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ちょこがねむけてけがしっぷ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Drowsy Chocolate Injury Compress</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Choco ga Nemuke te Kega Shippu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="137679" update="2012-03-09">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2012-03-16</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ふろたこもちてはつゆめし</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bath Kite Rice Cake New Year`s First Dream</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Furo Tako Mochi te Hatsuyume shi</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
