<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="9366" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2013-04-10</startdate>
<enddate>2013-06-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Yuyushiki</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ゆゆ式</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Yuyushiki</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Yuyushiki</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">悠悠式</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="12036" type="Sequel">Yuyushiki: Komarasetari, Komarasaretari</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="8107" approval="40" total="46">A Channel: The Animation</anime>
<anime id="8353" approval="30" total="32">Yuru Yuri</anime>
<anime id="9722" approval="25" total="32">Non Non Biyori</anime>
<anime id="9418" approval="18" total="20">Aiura</anime>
<anime id="9857" approval="17" total="24">Kitakubu Katsudou Kiroku</anime>
<anime id="8899" approval="12" total="22">Joshiraku</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="3">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="477642">One of the best comedies around. There is no actual storyline, character development, etc. whatsoever but you can`t just get enough of these characters doing stupid things. Especially Yui and Yukari`s relentless efforts to get in Yui`s pants and the painful tsukkomi they recieve in return. :D</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="257071">Must-see for slice-of-life comedy (dialogue and situational- not slapstick)- up there with the best in the genre, and one of the examples of the recent CGDCT trend in anime and manga that manages to avoid being shamefully generic and soulless. Some of the jokes rely heavily on language usage and aren`t going to translate very well- pick your translation group wisely if you need that sort of thing.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.yuyushiki.net/</url>
<creators>
<name id="33641" type="Original Work">Mikami Komata</name>
<name id="2950" type="Animation Work">Kinema Citrus</name>
<name id="6257" type="Character Design">Tabata Hisayuki</name>
<name id="1465" type="Series Composition">Takahashi Natsuko</name>
<name id="29512" type="Direction">Kaori</name>
<name id="36647" type="Music">Sakai Asuka</name>
<name id="11592" type="Chief Animation Direction">Akiya Yukie</name>
<name id="6257" type="Chief Animation Direction">Tabata Hisayuki</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the http://anidb.net/t2805 [4-koma] manga by http://anidb.net/cr33641 [Mikami Komata].
It is the first day of high school for the level-headed http://anidb.net/ch51761 [Yui]. Wearing her new school uniform for the first time, she does not look forward to the anticipated teasing by her best friends: the mischievous energetic http://anidb.net/ch51760 [Yuzuko] and the sleepy-head http://anidb.net/ch51762 [Yukari].
About to attend the enrolment ceremony at school, the first-year high school students are delighted to discover that they made it into the same class. But as freshmen they are expected to take part in club activities, but what club should they choose? They note that the Data Processing Club has zero members, situated in a small cosy room with two workstations. Their teacher and also the DPC`s club advisor is http://anidb.net/ch53531 [Matsumoto Yoriko], who the girls lovingly call Mom, even though she is not even 30 years old yet.
The girls decide to join the Data Processing Club, giving them many strange topics to look up and talk about. No wordplay can be too strange not to be enjoyed by this close group of friends.
— written by foo2</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1268">6.05</permanent>
<temporary count="1271">7.01</temporary>
<review count="1">8.50</review>
</ratings>
<picture>134595.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>14576</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19029</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>15911</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.yuyushiki.net/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Yuyushiki</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ゆゆ式</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2943</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>344840</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15947</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="26">
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=d_ECoowxvdA</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=qRlnz6FR9GI</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>yuyushiki</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="920" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-03-22">
<name>perverted</name>
<description>Is a concept describing those types of human behavior that are excessive or deviated from what is considered to be orthodox or normal.</description>
<picurl>245189.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1018" parentid="2869" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-25">
<name>middle school</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1279" parentid="2869" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-18">
<name>all-girls school</name>
<description>This school is only for female students. There may be a few male teachers though.</description>
<picurl>70853.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1446" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-15">
<name>energetic</name>
<description>An energetic character, often also called a genki character, shows great, often excessive levels of activity or vitality, and seems to always be doing everything extra fast. Genki characters are often slightly, or sometimes very, eccentric, and are filled with confidence and determination, regardless of whether they are competent or not; in fact, they often have little to no actual competence at whatever they generally do. Although genki characters are usually played exclusively for comedy effect, sometimes they may slow down for a serious or introspective moment. The most common genki character archetype is the genki schoolgirl, who will often be late to school and run with a toast in her mouth.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2396" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-08">
<name>swimsuit</name>
<description>A swimsuit is one of several kinds of garments designed to be worn by people engaging in water-based activities or sports or during certain activities under sunlight. Most kinds of swimsuit reveal a large portion of the body surface area, but exceptions exist. The more revealing kinds may also be worn as undergarment in sports that require wetsuits, or when there is a need to display the body, as in the case of beauty pageants or bodybuilding contests.
There is a very wide range of styles of modern swimsuits, which vary in relation to body coverage and materials. The choice of style of swimsuit is dependent on current fashions, community standards of modesty, and plain personal preference. Swimsuits for men usually expose the chest, while those for women do not usually do so; however, many women prefer to engage in water or sun activities with their torso uncovered, in a practice commonly described as toplessness or topfreedom. Since the early twentieth century a naturist movement has developed in western countries that seeks a return to non-sexual nakedness when swimming and during other appropriate activities; in some places around the world, nude beaches have been set aside for people who choose to engage in normal beach activities in the nude, and such beaches may or may not enforce nudity onto their goers.
In anime, it is common for at least one episode to feature the characters in swimsuits, usually as an excuse for gratuitous fanservice; when that happens, the episode is usually labeled a pool or beach episode, after the place the characters went to. Swimsuits, and in particular one-piece swimsuits, are a very common fetish in Japan; while the reason for that is uncertain, a common folk explanation is the fact that boys throughout their entire adolescence are commonly exposed to their female classmates wearing them, in what might be called an experiment in sexual discovery waiting to happen.</description>
<picurl>149786.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2805" parentid="2798" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>4-koma manga</name>
<description>Yonkoma manga (4コマ漫画, four cell manga, or 4-koma for short), a comic-strip format, generally consists of gag comic strips within four panels of equal size ordered from top to bottom. (They also sometimes run right-to-left horizontally or use a hybrid 2x2 style, depending on the layout requirements of the publication in which they appear.) Though the word yonkoma comes from the Japanese, the style also exists outside of Japan in other Asian countries as well as in the English-speaking market.</description>
<picurl>70558.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2815" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>boobs in your face</name>
<description>Boobs in your face: the character`s face is pressed into a female`s cleavage. This may be accidental or actually intended by the female character, or even a result of a device by the other character. This action is generally seen as sexually charged by the viewers and often also by the cast, so it will usually happen in an ecchi context; as such, something such as a mother hugging her child won`t generally count.</description>
<picurl>230160.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2830" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>furo scene</name>
<description>Furo (polite: Ofuro) is Japanese for bath, specifically a type of bath which originated as a short, steep-sided wooden bathtub. Baths of this type are found all over Japan in houses, apartments and traditional Japanese inns (Ryokans).
Furo are part of the Japanese ritual of bathing, not used for washing but for relaxing and warming oneself. Washing is carried out separately outside the furo, and only when completely clean does the bather enter the water. Generally Japanese bathrooms are small, so the bathroom is set up much like a walk-in shower area but containing the ofuro.
The cheapest and shortest way to show naked skin on TV, at least as much as allowed. It usually only takes up few minutes at most and as such it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in the nude and raise the DVD sales while still maintaining a "non-filler" episode.
Compare to the big brothers http://anidb.net/t4290 [sentou episode] and http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode].
See also http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode], and http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].</description>
<picurl>160785.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2865" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-16">
<name>summer festival</name>
<description>The summer festival is used to show off the female protagonists in traditional Japanese clothing — the yukata — a casual form of kimono.
The festivities include food stalls (cotton candy, candy apples, choco bananas, taiyaki), various games (scoop goldfishes), and a fireworks display.</description>
<picurl>161023.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2880" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-01">
<name>Christmas</name>
<description>Christmas, also referred to as Christmas Day, is an annual holiday celebrated on December 25 that commemorates the birth of Jesus of Nazareth. The day marks the beginning of the larger season of Christmastide, which lasts twelve days. The nativity of Jesus, which is the basis for the Anno Domini system of dating, is thought to have occurred between 7 and 2 BC. December 25 is not known to be Jesus` actual date of birth, and the date may have been chosen to correspond with either a Roman festival or the winter solstice.
On the Julian calendar, followed by most Orthodox churches, Christmas Day also falls on O.S. December 25th; this corresponds to N.S. January 7th on the Gregorian calendar, followed by Western churches.
Modern customs of the holiday include gift-giving, Church celebrations, and the display of various decorations—including the Christmas tree, lights, mistletoe, nativity scenes, and holly. Santa Claus (also referred to as Father Christmas, although the two figures have different origins) is a popular mythological figure often associated with bringing gifts at Christmas for children. Santa is generally believed to be the result of a syncretization between Saint Nicholas and elements from pagan Nordic and Christian mythology, and his modern appearance is believed to have originated in 19th century media.
Christmas is celebrated throughout the Christian population, but is also celebrated by many non-Christians as a secular, cultural festival. Because gift-giving and several other aspects of the holiday involve heightened economic activity among both Christians and non-Christians, Christmas has become a major event for many retailers.</description>
<picurl>160837.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2886" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-16">
<name>New Year`s Day</name>
<description>It is tradition in Japan to celebrate the new year at a Shinto shrine (hatsumode). The protagonists will offer some money, ring a bell at the end of a thick rope, and then pray for good fortune.
This usually goes along with gorging yourself at the many temporary food stalls, playing various games, and drawing a fortune.
The female characters in the anime will usually dress up in a kimono, to show off their traditional Japanese clothing, while watching the fireworks.</description>
<picurl>161028.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3185" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-27">
<name>wordplay</name>
<description>The characters play with words. 
E.g. purposely or accidentally use similar-sounding but wrongly applied words in the Japanese original, leading to supposedly funny misunderstandings and confusion.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3191" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-14">
<name>ohanami</name>
<description>Hanami (花見, lit. "flower viewing") is the Japanese traditional custom of enjoying the beauty of flowers, "flower" in this case almost always meaning cherry blossoms or ume blossoms. 
From the end of March to early May, sakura bloom all over Japan, and around the first of February on the island of Okinawa. The blossom forecast (桜前線 sakurazensen, literally cherry blossom front) is announced each year by the weather bureau, and is watched carefully by those planning hanami as the blossoms only last a week or two. 
In modern-day Japan, hanami mostly consists of having an outdoor party beneath the sakura during daytime or at night. Hanami at night is called yozakura (夜桜, literally night sakura). 
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
<picurl>160895.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3868" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-14">
<name>sleepover</name>
<description>A sleepover, also known as a pyjama party or a slumber party, is a party where a guest or guests are invited to stay overnight.
Typical participant activities include staying up late, talking, eating and playing until falling asleep, which sometimes never happens for a few high energy guests. Sleepovers are usually held at one participant`s house, with other guests sometimes bringing their bedtime things, such as pillows or sleeping bags. Common activities include playing board games or video games, having pillow fights, watching movies, ordering pizza, eating sweets and playing party games such as Truth or Dare. 
While sleepovers are practised by both girls and boys, in anime it is an almost girls-exclusive event and a good excuse for more fanservice.</description>
<picurl>160892.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3977" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-29">
<name>dialogue driven</name>
<description>A dialogue driven show has its story advanced by dialogue, with action being of much lower priority, and relies heavily on conversations between characters.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4116" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-13">
<name>eternal blush</name>
<description>It is no ordinary blush it is a blush that does not disappear.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4228" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-11-09">
<name>subtle OP ED sequence change</name>
<description>A (small) part of the opening or ending sequence changes after a certain episode, usually to reflect a plot milestone.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4386" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-19">
<name>eating Pocky</name>
<description>Pocky (ポッキー) is a Japanese snack food produced by the Ezaki Glico Company of Japan. Pocky was first sold in 1966, and consists of a biscuit stick coated with chocolate. It was named after the Japanese onomatopoetic word for the sound Pocky makes when bitten, pokkin (ポッキン). The original was followed by "Almond Pocky" in 1971, with an almond coating, and "Strawberry Pocky" in 1977. Today, the product line includes such variations as milk, mousse, green tea, honey, banana and coconut flavored coatings, and themed products such as "Decorer Pocky," with colourful decorative stripes in the coating, and "Men`s Pocky," a dark (bittersweet) chocolate and "mature" version.
Source: Wikipedia
It`s marketed in Germany under the name Mikado (Note: NOT the game, the snack).</description>
<picurl>73630.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4498" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-20">
<name>heart-warming</name>
<description>The story and its characters give off good vibes — includes elevated feelings of affection such as tenderness, sympathy and love, all in one package.
The kind of anime which leaves you with a warm feeling inside and you can not stop smiling while watching it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4570" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-07">
<name>watercolour style</name>
<description>A watercolour or aquarelle is a painting method in which the paints are made of pigments suspended in a water-based solution. Some anime are created in the style of watercolour paintings, the watercolour style, usually with faded pastels that often give the show a warm and friendly visual presentation. In modern anime, this is generally achieved via computer effects that create an imitation of watercolour, rather than by creating real-life watercolour art. While the watercolour style is more commonly used for backgrounds, it is possible to create the entire anime in such a style.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4576" parentid="6185" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-03">
<name>summer</name>
<description>At least one of the episodes takes place in summer. Think oppressively warm weather, summer vacation, summer school, summer festival, or a visit to the beach.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5515" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>faceless background characters</name>
<description>Unimportant random/extra characters that appear mostly as part of the background are often drawn without much facial details, normally to save money, effort and manpower for more important parts of the show. Sometimes, they have almost or no facial details, meaning their heads only have indications of the presence of parts such as hair or mouth, or not even that. This can go as far as only drawing an abstracted silhouette of the whole body.</description>
<picurl>233515.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5697" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-02">
<name>randomness</name>
<description>The anime does not follow a predictable storyline. New, strange, obscure, or otherwise unexpected story elements are introduced at a whim.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5763" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-19">
<name>rock-paper-scissors</name>
<description>Whenever a decision has to be made in anime, the Japanese protagonists seem to be awfully fond of playing rock-paper-scissors (or jan-ken-pon) to determine the outcome.</description>
<picurl>62869.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5846" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-26">
<name>beach visit</name>
<description>Every anime has to have them, episodes in which the characters for whatever reason end up going to the sea, ocean, random island or the local pond.
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in swimsuits and raise the DVD sales.
The cheap version is the http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].
Other marginally less used variants of this are the http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode] and the http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], used when it is too cold for a beach/pool episode.
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene].</description>
<picurl>160805.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6046" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>pool episode</name>
<description>An episode playing at the pool, mostly in school, sometimes outside of it when the cast does not have a chance for a beach episode.
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in swimsuits and raise the DVD sales.
The cheap version of the http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode].
Other variants are the http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode] and the http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], used when it is too cold for a beach/pool episode.
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene].</description>
<picurl>160904.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6137" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-09">
<name>catchphrase</name>
<description>A catchphrase is a sound, word or phrase commonly used by a person. That may be simply out of habit, or in an attempt to deliver some form of image, like that of cuteness. In fiction, characters often use catchphrases as a way to deliver specific personality traits. Examples include Otohime Mutsumi`s "ara ara" in Love Hina, Yang Wenli`s "yare yare" in Legend of the Galactic Heroes, Misuzu`s "gao" in AIR, Sakura`s "hoe" in Card Captor Sakura, Suiseiseki`s "desu" in Rozen Maiden, and Ayu`s "uguu" in Kanon (as well as several other characters in the same show).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="51760" type="main character in" update="2017-02-20">
<rating votes="46">7.43</rating>
<name>Nonohara Yuzuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>133661.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10973" picture="78574.jpg">Ookubo Rumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51761" type="main character in" update="2017-02-20">
<rating votes="53">8.15</rating>
<name>Ichii Yui</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>133662.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21823" picture="131326.jpg">Tsuda Minami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="51762" type="main character in" update="2017-02-20">
<rating votes="46">7.00</rating>
<name>Hinata Yukari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>133663.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32750" picture="227075.jpg">Taneda Risa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53528" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-03-15">
<rating votes="22">6.59</rating>
<name>Aikawa Chiho</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>133664.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20497" picture="62433.jpg">Kayano Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53529" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-03-15">
<rating votes="15">4.68</rating>
<name>Okano Kei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>133667.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27977" picture="76416.jpg">Han Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53530" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-03-15">
<rating votes="12">5.43</rating>
<name>Hasegawa Fumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>133665.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="35408" picture="142481.jpg">Shimizu Mana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="53531" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-02-20">
<rating votes="30">8.24</rating>
<name>Matsumoto Yoriko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>133666.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="61" picture="58663.jpg">Horie Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54911" type="appears in" update="2013-05-08">
<name>Yui no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>136397.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="223" picture="228520.jpg">Kakazu Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54919" type="appears in" update="2013-04-10">
<name>Shoten Ten`in</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>135084.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1918" picture="225099.jpg">Sakurai Harumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="54920" type="appears in" update="2013-04-10">
<name>Kouchou-sensei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>135083.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="494" picture="17485.jpg">Ichijou Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55547" type="appears in" update="2013-05-02">
<name>Hoken no Sensei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>136152.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9124" picture="186845.jpg">Hayama Ikumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="55929" type="appears in" update="2013-05-19">
<name>Kami</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>136803.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3093" picture="38195.jpg">Nojima Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="56383" type="appears in" update="2013-05-30">
<name>Konbini Ten`in</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>137360.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1918" picture="225099.jpg">Sakurai Harumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57143" type="appears in" update="2013-06-12">
<name>Long T no Kamisama</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138408.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="694" picture="52187.jpg">Choo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57144" type="appears in" update="2013-06-12">
<rating votes="1">2.34</rating>
<name>Bijutsubu Senpai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>138407.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12598" picture="74984.jpg">Miyake Marie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57497" type="appears in" update="2013-06-26">
<name>Okano no Otouto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>139105.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="641" picture="31202.jpg">Katou Emiri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="57498" type="appears in" update="2013-06-26">
<name>Aikawa no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>139106.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="210" picture="71057.jpg">Ueda Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="148751" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-05-01</airdate>
<rating votes="8">3.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">いいんちょう</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Chairman</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Présidente</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Iinchou</title>
<summary>Aikawa looks back on her first time meeting Yui and observes the trio and Yukari’s lack of motivation.  Later, the girls research Whales while their teacher comes to terms with her “Mom” nickname.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>622857</identifier>
<identifier>yuyushiki</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="148752" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-04-24</airdate>
<rating votes="9">3.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夏休みじゃーい!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It`s Summer Vacation!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les vacances d`été !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Natsuyasumi Jaai!</title>
<summary>Summer vacation finds the girls visiting the pool, having a sleep over, and bugging Yui.
Yukari goes on an island vacation and sends her friends unique videos.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>622855</identifier>
<identifier>yuyushiki</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="148753" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-04-17</airdate>
<rating votes="9">3.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">情報処理部</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Data Processing Club</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le club d`informatique</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jouhou Shoribu</title>
<summary>As the newly formed Data Processing Club, the conversations rage from how to grow your chest to ice cream.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>622853</identifier>
<identifier>yuyushiki</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="148754" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-04-10</airdate>
<rating votes="11">2.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">高校生になりました</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Now We`re High School Students</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">On est au lycée !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koukousei ni Narimashita</title>
<summary>Yuzuko, Yukari, and Yui explore their new high school for the perfect club to join.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>622851</identifier>
<identifier>yuyushiki</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="149082" update="2013-04-10">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-04-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="149083" update="2013-04-10">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-04-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="149856" update="2013-04-21">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-03-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">ACE 2013 PV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="149857" update="2013-04-21">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2013-01-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">コミックマーケット83公開PV</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Comiket 83 PV</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Comic Market 83 Koukai PV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150210" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-05-29</airdate>
<rating votes="10">5.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">2年生になりました</title>
<title xml:lang="en">We`re in Our Second Year Now</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">On est en 2e année !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">2-nensei ni Narimashita</title>
<summary>Okano is a little jealous of Aikawa`s admiration of Yui. Yuzo and Yukari are desperate to see Mom cry.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>622865</identifier>
<identifier>yuyushiki</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="150211" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-05-22</airdate>
<rating votes="9">4.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">3学期っ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">3rd Semester!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le 3ème trimestre !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">3-gakki!</title>
<summary>Yukari and Yuzuko enjoy the last days of their vacation at Yui’s, again.  And the subject of chocolates leads to today’s topic: eyes.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>622863</identifier>
<identifier>yuyushiki</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="150212" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-05-15</airdate>
<rating votes="8">4.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">初雪なべ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">First Snow Hotpot</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Première fondue hivernale</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hatsuyuki Nabe</title>
<summary>Po-ta-to.  After discussing the theme of “Days of the week”, the club approaches Mom in hopes of having a hotpot.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>622861</identifier>
<identifier>yuyushiki</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="150213" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-05-08</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">唯と縁とゆずこ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yui and Yukari and Yuzuko</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Yui et Yukari et Yuzuko</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yui to Yukari to Yuzuko</title>
<summary>Yui and Yukari share stories of their first meeting in elementary school, Yuzuko listens with jealously.   The conversation shifts from first meetings to death and memories.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>622859</identifier>
<identifier>yuyushiki</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="150700" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-06-26</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ノーイベント グッドライフ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Uneventful Good Life</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une vie bien ordinaire</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">No Event Good Life</title>
<summary>As summer vacation begins again, the girls spend most of their days at Yui`s house, before later going to the beach.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>622873</identifier>
<identifier>yuyushiki</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="150701" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-06-19</airdate>
<rating votes="9">4.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">こーゆー時間</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Times Like These</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ces moments-là</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kouyuu Jikan</title>
<summary>The girls look into the various aspects of time, before pondering what they`d like to do in the future.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>622871</identifier>
<identifier>yuyushiki</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="150702" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-06-12</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">楽しいから</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Because It`s Fun</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Parce que c`est amusant</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tanoshii kara</title>
<summary>Yukino makes popping sounds with her mouth, Yuzuko hops on the pop train. The girls have fun in cooking class and Yuzuko brings a surprise from art class.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>622869</identifier>
<identifier>yuyushiki</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="150703" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2013-06-05</airdate>
<rating votes="8">4.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">まじゃりんこ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mishmash</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Fréquentations</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Majarinko</title>
<summary>These cutie pies are up to the same old shenanigans!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>622867</identifier>
<identifier>yuyushiki</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="150984" update="2013-06-14">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2013-05-29</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">にゃにゃ式 予告編 『猫ににゃりました』</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nyanyashiki Yokokuhen: Neko ni Nyarimashita</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150985" update="2013-06-03">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-04-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151524" update="2013-07-02">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2013-06-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">にゃにゃ式 猫ににゃりました</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nyanyashiki: Neko ni Nyarimashita</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151536" update="2013-07-02">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-05-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1d</title>
</episode>
<episode id="151537" update="2013-07-02">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-04-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1c</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152266" update="2013-07-31">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2013-07-24</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">にゃにゃ式 にゃんつってっつっちゃった</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nyanyashiki: Nyantsutte ttsucchatta</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152267" update="2013-07-31">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-05-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1f</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152268" update="2013-07-31">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-05-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1e</title>
</episode>
<episode id="154028" update="2013-09-12">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2013-08-28</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">にゃにゃ式 せーにょっ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nyanya Shiki senyo!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="154029" update="2013-09-12">
<epno type="3">C9</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-05-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1h</title>
</episode>
<episode id="154030" update="2013-09-12">
<epno type="3">C8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-05-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1g</title>
</episode>
<episode id="154403" update="2013-09-28">
<epno type="3">C11</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-06-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1j</title>
</episode>
<episode id="154404" update="2013-09-28">
<epno type="3">C10</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-06-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1i</title>
</episode>
<episode id="154405" update="2013-09-28">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2013-09-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">にゃにゃ式 ごめん寝</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 5</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nyanyashiki: Gomenne</title>
</episode>
<episode id="155331" update="2013-10-28">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2013-10-23</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">にゃにゃ式 ♡♡♡</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Special 6</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nyanya Shiki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="155766" update="2013-11-03">
<epno type="3">C12</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2013-06-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1k</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
