<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="99" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>1998-07-07</startdate>
<enddate>1998-09-29</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Serial Experiments Lain</title>
<title xml:lang="lt" type="synonym">Serijiniai Eksperimentai Lain</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Серійні експерименти Лейн</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Lain</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">SE Lain</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">SEL</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="short">Лейн</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">シリアルエクスペリメンツレイン</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Serial Experiments Lain</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Serial Experiments Lain</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Serial Experiments Lain</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Serial Experiments Lain</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">Serial Experiments Lain</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Эксперименты Лэйн</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">Wirtualna Lain</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="official">Serial Experiments Lain</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">玲音</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA" type="official">Lain</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="673" approval="106" total="129">Texhnolyze</anime>
<anime id="179" approval="84" total="94">Boogiepop wa Warawanai: Boogiepop Phantom</anime>
<anime id="1265" approval="57" total="92">Mousou Dairinin</anime>
<anime id="3302" approval="34" total="52">Ergo Proxy</anime>
<anime id="4345" approval="32" total="70">Dennou Coil</anime>
<anime id="61" approval="30" total="56">Ghost in the Shell</anime>
<anime id="28" approval="8" total="17">Akira</anime>
<anime id="575" approval="5" total="17">Kino no Tabi: The Beautiful World</anime>
<anime id="9357" approval="5" total="13">Aku no Hana</anime>
<anime id="22" approval="4" total="12">Shinseiki Evangelion</anime>
<anime id="24" approval="3" total="14">.hack//Sign</anime>
<anime id="6088" approval="1" total="9">Chaos;Head</anime>
<anime id="6267" approval="1" total="4">Shangri-La</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="34">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="312775">Mesmerizing, with an unforgettable animation that creates a psych feeling throughout the series. Highly recommended!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="248327">the best seinen ever</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="237158">Quite twisted, very psychological, worth  of analyzing. Hard to comprehend.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="403799">A great series with the strange capacity&lt;br /&gt;that everything gets sense after episode 11.&lt;br /&gt;Una gran serie con la extraña capcidad de que todo tiene sentido despeus del episodio 11.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="479578">A bit confusing for some people, I might need a second watch, but I did enjoy watching it non-the less</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="670085">Lain iwakura life alone, but very fantastic</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="516146">Perhaps only for ABe fans... I loved the atmosphere of this anime, the look and the sound of it.  OK, the animation isn`t fantastic, but if you find fault in that, you definitely missed the point. Yes, the plot is dense at times, but overall this is an experience in anime that you may never find again. Try it if you`re up for something unique.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="495882">If you have seen a lot of anime, and yet to see this, get to it. You will not see anything like it, and it is definitely something new. Some episodes are kinda slow and you will ask a lot of questions that won`t be answered until the end, or near the end. If you can`t stand these kind of things, you probably will not like Serial Experiments Lain, otherwise, give it a watch.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="697647">I... [i]think[/i] this was a good show. The atmosphere and sound design was top notch. As for the story... uhhhhhhhhh... profound? Is that the right word? They certainly don`t do a lot of hand-holding along the way, but if you can wrap your head around it, then it`s a must watch. And if you can actually wrap your head around all the philosophical stuff too, then you`re a better man than me. Hell, you could probably make a half-decent religion off this stuff, it`s that sort of show.

Definitely watch this at some point, just don`t worry too much if you get lost along the way, it`ll make sense eventually, or not, I`m still not too sure (and I`m half convinced anyone who says otherwise is a liar).</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="54185">Simply beautiful, setting, story, animation. Makes you think, and I always find that good in an anime.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="78827">Essential viewing - well-written, thought-provoking, ahead of it`s time, beautifully animated, great soundtrack, oh and Yoshitoshi ABe.  I think that covers it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="124124">After being hooked on anime by the all time classic FullMoon, it was another year before i saw Lain, and i found it to be one of the only animes that i enjoy as much as FullMoon.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="481527">A piece of Art!
It`s like "Das Kapital" from Karl Marx. Very view understand it but nevertheless it`s a big contribution to the understanding of human pschology and communication.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="235114">... for cyberpunk fans and lost, bored souls.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="303392">Classic. If Cowboy Bebop is THE best action anime series out there, this is Cowboy Bebop of cyberpunk in anime. Comparable to the Ghost in the Shell movie.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="518865">*jedi mind trick* you -must- watch this if you are an anime fan!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.geneon-ent.co.jp/rondorobe/anime/lain/</url>
<creators>
<name id="789" type="Animation Work">Triangle Staff</name>
<name id="9609" type="Music">Nakaido Reichi</name>
<name id="4147" type="Character Design">Kishida Takahiro</name>
<name id="4184" type="Direction">Nakamura Ryuutarou</name>
</creators>
<description>The first episode opens with the mysterious suicide of a junior high school girl, http://anidb.net/ch2408 [Yomoda Chisa]. She was a classmate of http://anidb.net/ch2338 [Iwakura Lain], a quiet, 14-year-old junior high school girl. One of the other girls in the class has been receiving e-mail messages from Chisa, and Lain discovers she also has mail from Chisa.
She explains in the mail to Lain that she just abandoned her flesh. She assures Lain that she still is alive in the `wired` world. After getting a new `navi` and adding a `psyche` circuit, Lain spends more and more time in the wired. It seems that Lain has at least two personalities, and Lain`s first personality is changing even now. Who is Lain? Who are the `knights`? Can the wired influence the real world with a prophecy? Is the real world nothing but a hologram of the information in the wired?</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="8598">7.34</permanent>
<temporary count="8705">7.91</temporary>
<review count="13">8.22</review>
</ratings>
<picture>221666.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>166</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>339</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>371</identifier>
<identifier>nxigxj</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://www.nbcuni.co.jp/rondorobe/anime/lain/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Serial_Experiments_Lain</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Serial_experiments_lain</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>442</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>88879</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1710</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="19">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Serial_experiments_lain</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="20">
<externalentity>
<identifier>玲音</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6458</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="7" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>juujin</name>
<description>Kemono, "beast", is a genre of Japanese art and character design that prominently features anthropomorphic animal characters. It is used widely in visual arts, especially drawing and painting, and can be found in many manga, anime, and video game.
Anthropomorphic animal characters in the kemono genre are frequently called juujin, "therianthrope"; the kanji for juujin are also sometimes pronounced kemonobito, "beast-human". While their design differs from artist to artist, they generally employ animal traits considered cute and endearing; most kemono characters retain a fundamentally human personality, however, seldom behaving as the actual animals from which they have been anthropomorphized, and as such they are typically depicted living as humans do.
Juujin leans more on the human-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t2857 [anthropomorphism], which leans more on the animal-looking side.
Source: Manga Wikia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1018" parentid="2869" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-25">
<name>middle school</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1152" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-23">
<name>undead</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1528" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-12">
<name>artificial intelligence</name>
<description>Artificial intelligence (AI) is the intelligence of machines and the branch of computer science that aims to create it. AI textbooks define the field as "the study and design of intelligent agents" where an intelligent agent is a system that perceives its environment and takes actions that maximize its chances of success. John McCarthy, who coined the term in 1956, defines it as "the science and engineering of making intelligent machines."
The field was founded on the claim that a central property of humans, intelligence—the sapience of Homo sapiens—can be so precisely described that it can be simulated by a machine. This raises philosophical issues about the nature of the mind and the ethics of creating artificial beings, issues which have been addressed by myth, fiction and philosophy since antiquity. Artificial intelligence has been the subject of optimism, but has also suffered setbacks and, today, has become an essential part of the technology industry, providing the heavy lifting for many of the most difficult problems in computer science.
AI research is highly technical and specialized, and deeply divided into subfields that often fail to communicate with each other. Subfields have grown up around particular institutions, the work of individual researchers, the solution of specific problems, longstanding differences of opinion about how AI should be done and the application of widely differing tools. The central problems of AI include such traits as reasoning, knowledge, planning, learning, communication, perception and the ability to move and manipulate objects. General intelligence (or "strong AI") is still among the field`s long term goals.</description>
<picurl>71305.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2535" parentid="1152" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-18">
<name>ghost</name>
<description>In traditional belief, a ghost is the soul or spirit of a deceased person or animal that can appear, in visible form or other manifestation, to the living. Descriptions of the apparition of ghosts vary widely: The mode of manifestation can range from an invisible presence to translucent or wispy shapes, to realistic, life-like visions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2839" parentid="2628" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-05">
<name>virtual world</name>
<description>A virtual world is a place where the character interacts with a computer (or some other device)-simulated environment, be it real or imagined. The condition for a virtual reality to exist is the existence of an originating "real" (source/anchor) world for the character. In some cases, a virtual reality where characters can get harmed physically is depicted.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2861" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>cyberpunk</name>
<description>Cyberpunk focuses on computers or information technology, usually coupled with some degree of breakdown in social order. The plot often centres on a conflict among hackers, artificial intelligences, and mega corporations, tending to be set within a near-future dystopian Earth.</description>
<picurl>211264.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3227" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-06-24">
<name>introspection</name>
<description>The characters in this anime do not walk through life simply accepting how they are, but quite on the contrary constantly try to understand their own motives, feelings and reactions to the other protagonists. 
This self-searching included the questions: "Who am I?", "What makes me tick?", "What do I want?", "What do others expect of me?", etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3313" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-09">
<name>evolution</name>
<description>Evolution is change in the heritable characteristics of biological populations over successive generations. Evolutionary processes give rise to biodiversity at every level of biological organisation, including the levels of species, individual organisms, and molecules.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>64170.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3369" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-06-23">
<name>human psyche</name>
<description>How that grey mass inside the skulls of us earthlings works.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3795" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>remastered version available</name>
<description>This anime has been remastered in a higher quality format than the original release. The remaster may be a simple upscale, or it could be a full enhancement project from the original frames. This is irrespective of whether specific groups have released rips of such formats to the internet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4084" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-03-20">
<name>dark atmosphere</name>
<description>Usually metaphorical. Sometimes literal. At times both!
Typically this refers to the fact that the story is set in a grim, dog eat dog milieu — for example a decaying city.
Often the characters are just doing what they need to do to survive, with little or no expectation that their lives can be better. And often characters may feel they do not have any real choice in what they do.
And yes, occasionally the setting is actually dark — be it night or perpetually heavy cloudy sky and rain. It all adds to the oppressive, hopeless feeling of the show.
You probably will not feel uplifted or happy after watching this anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4153" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-03-15">
<name>dark</name>
<description>Describes the overall mood in this anime. Dark colours, a non-happy, often tragic story, dark lighting, many night scenes or constantly dark skies, and continuous rain all contribute to setting this mood.
The anime will often be quite depressing to watch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4280" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-06-02">
<name>surreal</name>
<description>Refers to things or occurrences that are generally bizarre or dreamlike, with the relentless capability of replacing reality through the eyes of the beholder. Surrealism is boundless, limited only by thought itself.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4314" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-04-11">
<name>psychological</name>
<description>Directed toward dealing with or affecting the mind, especially as a function of awareness, feeling, or motivation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4340" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-09-26">
<name>suicide</name>
<description>One or several characters in this anime commit suicide.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4417" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>existentialism</name>
<description>Most commonly defines the rejection of a god and any transcendent will that dictates how humans should live. It rejects any "created" meaning of life and the world, stating a leap of faith is required to live an authentic life. In this existentialism, belief in a god is often considered a form of Bad Faith.
In length, the Absurd contains ideas that there is no meaning in the world beyond what meaning it`s given. Meaninglessness also encompasses amorality or "unfairness" of the world. This contrasts with "karmic" ways of thinking in which "bad things don`t happen to good people"; there is no such thing as a good person or a bad thing; what happens happens, and it may just as well happen to a good person as to a bad person. This contrasts daily experience where most things appear meaningful, and where good people receive a "reward" for goodness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4499" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-07-28">
<name>some weird shit goin` on</name>
<description>Scenes of this show point to insanely strange events which seem to be taking place; throughout its episodes, the show may or may not explain what is going on. Either way, many viewers will find that a succinct and accurate way to describe the show is "WTF?", and the show`s explanations (or lack thereof) to the events will often be subject of heated debate.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4522" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>social commentary</name>
<description>Social commentary is the act of rebelling against an individual, or a group of people by rhetorical means. This is most often done with the idea of implementing or promoting change by informing the general populace about a given problem and appealing to people’s sense of justice. (Source: Wikipedia)&#13;
&#13;
Since this is anime, usually, the mores of Japan and the Japanese society are scrutinised, but not restricted to that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4715" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-07-01">
<name>dementia</name>
<description>Serious emotional and mental deterioration of organic or functional origin, often age-related.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4811" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-01-30">
<name>internet</name>
<description>It`s not a big truck. It`s a series of tubes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5417" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-22">
<name>mind fuck</name>
<description>A `mind fuck` is a slang term which describes a work that uses literary devices such as nonlinear storytelling and plot twists in order to present convoluted, yet not conflicting, themes.
A creation is usually considered a mind fuck when a casual observer is not able to discern the true meaning of a work without making a serious attempt to unravel the themes presented or when the plot is incredibly difficult to follow.
Special examples of mind fucks involve a single plot twist which completely changes the viewer`s understanding of the events in a film or novel as well as the ideas it presents.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5768" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>intact family</name>
<description>The main character`s family is a so-called "nuclear family". Wherein both parents are alive and present in his or her life. This is actually relatively rare for anime, where "parental abandonment" is the norm.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5773" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-14">
<name>secret organisation</name>
<description>A secret organisation or secret society is an organisation whose activities and inner functioning are concealed from non-members. The society may or may not attempt to conceal its existence itself. Examples of historical and existing secret societies include Freemasonry, the Knights Templar, the Rosicrucians, Skull and Bones, the Thule Society, and the Illuminati.</description>
<picurl>192876.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5788" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-10-03">
<name>experiments</name>
<description>Involves (para-)scientific experiments.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5824" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-23">
<name>god is a girl</name>
<description>In storylines where many or all gods are portrayed as goddesses (female gods), "The God of all Gods", or the Number-One-God so to speak, is also female.
In other instances, such may just refer to a girl with god-like powers.</description>
<picurl>215285.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5980" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-24">
<name>live-action imagery</name>
<description>This anime incorporates still images and/or video footage of real-world objects and locations into the animation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5991" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-07-04">
<name>dark mood</name>
<description>Similar to `Dark Atmosphere`, but more focused on the actual characters rather than the setting. A dark mood can easily result from a dark atmosphere.
A dark mood is more than just occasionally feeling angry or down, it`s usually a permanent character trait that sours the character`s relationships with others.
However it arises, at least one character in this anime can see little good in the world or the people in it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="2338" type="main character in" update="2009-01-13">
<rating votes="143">9.09</rating>
<name>Iwakura Lain</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Iwakura Lain is the main protagonist of Serial Experiments Lain. She is a 14 year old, shy girl.</description>
<picture>2404.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="56" picture="16651.jpg">Shimizu Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2339" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-13">
<rating votes="9">5.71</rating>
<name>Eiri Masami</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Masami Eiri is the former Chief Researcher of Tachibana Labs and mastermind of Protocol 7. He believes that humans must get rid of their physical limitations and exist as purely digital entities if they are to evolve.</description>
<picture>2405.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="27" picture="26123.jpg">Hayami Shou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2340" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-13">
<rating votes="6">8.12</rating>
<name>Iwakura Yasuo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>As the father of Lain, Yasuo Iwakura pushes her towards the Wired and when she asks for it, he buys her a new NAVI that becomes an entry point for Lains endavours in the Wired. He is also a collegue of Masami Eiri.</description>
<picture>2406.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="3383" picture="24325.jpg">Oobayashi Ryuusuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2341" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-07-04">
<rating votes="14">8.10</rating>
<name>Mizuki Arisu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mizuki Arisu is a classmate of Lain; Arisu is her only real friend in the series. Arisu helps Lain socialising by pushing her into going to the Cyberia nightclub. She is protective of Lain and takes care of her.</description>
<picture>2407.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="3503" picture="222796.jpg">Asada Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2406" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-04-30">
<rating votes="7">6.21</rating>
<name>Iwakura Mika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Iwakura Mika is Lain`s apathetic older sister.</description>
<picture>2410.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="12" picture="184301.jpg">Kawasumi Ayako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2408" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-14">
<rating votes="4">4.87</rating>
<name>Yomoda Chisa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yomoda Chisa is Lain`s classmate. She`s the one that initially gets Lain involved with the Wired.
She commits suicide at the beginning of the story and later contacts Lain from within the Wired saying "There was no reason for me to stay in the real world any longer. In the real world, it didn`t matter if I was there or not. When I realized that, I was no longer afraid of losing my body".</description>
<picture>2411.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="429" picture="17306.jpg">Mutou Sumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2419" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-18">
<rating votes="4">5.37</rating>
<name>Tarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tarou is a member-to-be of the Knights and he works for them. He hangs out with his friends Masayuki and Myu-myu at the Cyberia night club where he meets Lain.</description>
<picture>2412.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="3504">Takimoto Keito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="2421" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-14">
<rating votes="4">1.32</rating>
<name>Iwakura Miho</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Lain`s mother in the Iwakura family. She is quiet and expressionless through most of the anime, except when she is with Iwakura Yasuo</description>
<picture>2413.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="693" picture="226546.jpg">Igarashi Rei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7251" type="appears in" update="2009-05-25">
<rating votes="2">1.96</rating>
<name>Kuchi</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A low level wired user that is only able to form a mouth and gives some information to Lain so that he/she can gain reputation.</description>
<picture>2884.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="20242" picture="69015.jpg">Matsuo Takashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46536" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-07-01">
<rating votes="3">5.43</rating>
<name>Yamamoto Reika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>90299.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16799" picture="186162.jpg">Tezuka Chiharu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46537" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-07-01">
<rating votes="1">7.18</rating>
<name>Katou Juri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>90300.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3294" picture="223278.jpg">Mizuno Manabi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46539" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-07-01">
<rating votes="1">4.27</rating>
<name>Lin Sui-Xi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>90301.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="374" picture="17220.jpg">Yamazaki Takumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46540" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-07-01">
<rating votes="2">7.34</rating>
<name>Karl Haushofer</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>90302.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="226" picture="17045.jpg">Nakata Jouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="46541" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-07-01">
<rating votes="1">1.74</rating>
<name>Miumiu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>90303.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="46543" type="secondary cast in" update="2012-07-01">
<rating votes="1">4.27</rating>
<name>Masayuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>90304.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37762" picture="138699.jpg">Touma Sora</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="1976" update="2017-06-03">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-09-08</airdate>
<rating votes="16">8.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">LOVE</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Love</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Layer 10: Love</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Amour</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Любовь</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Love</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA">Estrato 10: Amor</title>
<summary>Lain encounters a man who call himself the “god” of the wired, and members of the Knights all across the world log on to participate in a cryptic mass suicide.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="1977" update="2017-06-03">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-08-04</airdate>
<rating votes="18">8.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">DISTORTION</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Distortion</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Layer 05: Distortion</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Distorsion</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Искажение</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Distortion</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA">Estrato 05: Distorsión</title>
<summary>Lain’s friends suspect her involvement in a series of computer errors that caused a lethal traffic accident. Meanwhile, her sister is haunted by mysterious messages demanding that she “fulfill the prophecy”.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="1978" update="2017-06-03">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-07-28</airdate>
<rating votes="19">7.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">RELIGION</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Religion</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Layer 04: Religion</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Religion</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Религия</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Religion</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA">Estrato 04: Religión</title>
<summary>The more involved with computers she becomes, the more Lain begins to transform. In the cybernetic cocoon that was once her room, she’s hard at work blurring the lines between reality and the wired.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="1979" update="2017-06-03">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-07-21</airdate>
<rating votes="20">7.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">PSYCHE</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Psyche</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Layer 03: Psyche</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Psyché</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Псише</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Psyche</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA">Estrato 03: Psique</title>
<summary>Lain has questions about a computer chip someone left in her locker, and her Dad’s not talking. Some kids at the club say they know all about it - but they want a piece of Lain’s wired wild side.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="1980" update="2017-06-03">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-07-14</airdate>
<rating votes="27">7.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">GIRLS</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Girls</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Layer 02: Girls</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Filles</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Девочки</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Girls</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA">Estrato 02: Chicas</title>
<summary>Accela - a designer drug born of nanotechnology - is a big hit with the club kids, but what’s that got to do with Lain? Only a madman who painted the dance floor with blood can answer that question - and he’s dead.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="1981" update="2017-06-02">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-07-07</airdate>
<rating votes="36">6.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">WEIRD</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Weird</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Layer 01: Weird</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Étrange</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Странно</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Weird</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA">Estrato 01: Raro</title>
<summary>Lain wasn’t interested in computers until she received her first email from a formerly suicidal classmate. Her newfound desire to connect with the dead will lead her into the twisted maze of the “wired world.”
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="1982" update="2017-06-03">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-09-01</airdate>
<rating votes="17">8.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">PROTOCOL</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Protocol</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Layer 09: Protocol</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Protocole</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Протокол</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Protocol</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA">Estrato 09: Protocolo</title>
<summary>A DJ at the club passes Lain a plain brown envelope containing a computer chip of unknown origins. Hoping to learn more about the clandestine technology, Lain abducts a young boy for a “date.”
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="1983" update="2017-06-02">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-09-29</airdate>
<rating votes="23">8.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">EGO</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ego</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Layer 13: Ego</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Égo</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Эго</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ego</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA">Estrato 13: Ego</title>
<summary>Lain’s guilt over the havoc caused by her interaction within the wired provokes her to take drastic - and irreversible - action.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="1984" update="2017-06-03">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-08-25</airdate>
<rating votes="18">8.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">RUMORS</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rumors</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Layer 08: Rumors</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Rumeurs</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Слухи</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rumors</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA">Estrato 08: Rumores</title>
<summary>Lain’s unsavory behavior within the wired turns her into an outcast at school. Confused and alone, Lain investigates her own cyber-lifestyle only to be shocked by a voyeuristic incarnation of herself.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="1985" update="2017-06-03">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-09-22</airdate>
<rating votes="18">7.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">LANDSCAPE</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Landscape</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Layer 12: Landscape</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Paysage</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Ландшафт</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Landscape</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA">Estrato 12: Paisaje</title>
<summary>“God” preaches that our bodies are simply an obstacle preventing the evolution of mankind. An exhausted Lain appears willing to sacrifice her own flesh and blood until Alice convinces her to take a stand against the digitalized deity.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="1986" update="2017-06-03">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-08-18</airdate>
<rating votes="18">7.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">SOCIETY</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Society</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Layer 07: Society</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Société</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Общество</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Society</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA">Estrato 07: Sociedad</title>
<summary>Covert agents in black suits take Lain in for questioning. When the interrogation hits too close to home, Lain flips from real to wired in the blink of an eye.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="1987" update="2017-06-03">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-09-15</airdate>
<rating votes="17">6.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">INFORNOGRAPHY</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Infornography</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Layer 11: Infornography</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Infornographie</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Инфорнография</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Infornography</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA">Estrato 11: Infornografía</title>
<summary>Lain risks a meltdown by uploading a Navi clone into her own brain. Later, the border between reality and the wired is threatened when Lain forces the world to forget a secret that never should have been revealed.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="1988" update="2017-06-03">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-08-11</airdate>
<rating votes="18">8.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">KIDS</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kids</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Layer 06: Kids</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Enfants</title>
<title xml:lang="ru">Дети</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kids</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA">Estrato 06: Niños</title>
<summary>When an image of herself appears in the clouds, the “real” Lain enters the wired on a search for answers. Her quest leads to a “child-killer” scientist whose devious work is being exploited by the Knights.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="16847" update="2007-05-06">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 00 - Series Intro</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39993" update="2005-08-22">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="6">9.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39994" update="2010-07-26">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="4">3.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120404" update="2010-07-26">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Italian Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="126191" update="2010-12-13">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer &amp; Commercial Collection 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="126192" update="2010-12-13">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer &amp; Commercial Collection 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="126193" update="2010-12-13">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer &amp; Commercial Collection 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="126194" update="2010-12-13">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer &amp; Commercial Collection 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="126195" update="2010-12-13">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer &amp; Commercial Collection 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="126196" update="2010-12-13">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="en">LPR-309 Clip The wired world - 13th Floor Elevator / Laugh Out Version</title>
</episode>
<episode id="126197" update="2010-12-13">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="en">LPR-309 Clip The invisible bridge - 13th Floor Elevator / Be Funny To.... Version</title>
</episode>
<episode id="126198" update="2010-12-13">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="en">LPR-309 Clip The real world -13th Floor Elevator / Smile Back Version</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
