<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="10352" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2018-07-14</startdate>
<enddate>2018-09-29</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">High Score Girl</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Hiscore Girl</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Hi-Score Girl</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ハイスコアガール</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Hi Score Girl</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">하이 스코어 걸</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">高分少女</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="14418" type="Sequel">High Score Girl: Extra Stage</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="13270" approval="7" total="14">Karakai Jouzu no Takagi-san</anime>
<anime id="12494" approval="1" total="7">Gamers!</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="528918">I thought that I`ll watch this because it sounded fun. But I was suprised, because I got totally hooked from start to finish and couldn`t wait what was going to happen next.

I think that the character development was great and I loved to watch relationships slowly form between the main characters. It was really fun, but also touching at times. The animation was awesome and game history was really interesting.

If you love games and romance, this is a must see! I have high expectations of the 2nd season.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://hi-score-girl.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="720" type="Animation Work">J.C.Staff</name>
<name id="38526" type="Character Design">Kuwabata Mitsuru</name>
<name id="3405" type="Series Composition">Urahata Tatsuhiko</name>
<name id="38832" type="Original Work">Oshikiri Rensuke</name>
<name id="1521" type="Direction">Yamakawa Yoshiki</name>
<name id="16092" type="Music">Shimomura Youko</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a manga written and illustrated by http://anidb.net/cr38832 [Oshikiri Rensuke], serialised in Gekkan Big Gangan.
1991. The year of the Gulf War. The year Mount Unzen erupted. The year the Ten-Day War in Slovenia broke out. The year the world wavered.
http://anidb.net/ch96703 [Yaguchi Haruo], a 6th grader, is not only the least popular in his school, but also has the worst grades, a bad attitude towards others, and cannot be called attractive either. The only thing he lives for are video games, and this happens to be the only thing he is really good at. Until one day, he plays Street Fighter II against http://anidb.net/ch96694 [Oono Akira], a well-off female classmate, who proves to him that she is not only more popular, intelligent, attractive, and lucky than he is, but also... better than him at playing video games!
Haruo`s small world wavers...
Source: Batoto
Note: Due to a then-ongoing legal dispute concerning http://anidb.net/cr1225 [SNK Playmore]`s intellectual property, the manga`s publisher http://anidb.net/cr1130 [Square Enix] voluntarily recalled its volumes from the stores, also suspending serialization, further publication and digital sales of volumes, and development of the anime adaptation. The two companies eventually settled out of court and Square Enix resumed the previously halted activities.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="870">7.24</permanent>
<temporary count="872">7.51</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>221463.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20797</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21877</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://hi-score-girl.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>High_Score_Girl</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ハイスコアガール</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4968</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>347985</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>hi_score_girl</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="26">
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=S51PKANf92c</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="34">
<externalentity>
<url>https://www.netflix.com/title/80997338</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="601" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-29">
<name>bicycle</name>
<description>A bicycle, often called a bike or cycle, is a human-powered, pedal-driven, single-track vehicle, having two wheels attached to a frame, one behind the other. A bicycle rider is called a cyclist, or bicyclist.
Souce: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>172772.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2538" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-02">
<name>playing video games</name>
<description>Video games are electronic games played on a video screen, normally a television or a built-in screen when played on a handheld machine.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2770" parentid="2653" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>violent retribution for accidental infringement</name>
<description>A comedy / slapstick element often found in Ecchi anime: The hilarity derives from spontaneous embarrassment, overreaction of the "victim" (girl), immediate retribution for a seemingly inappropriate act, and a sense of pity with the supposed "aggressor" (boy).
Typically a boy will - through no fault of his own - stumble into a girl, thus invading her personal space. In the process the boy may e.g. pull down her skirt, grab the girl`s breasts, or accidentally kiss her. Any level-headed girl would see the accident just for what it is. Not so the girl with an overly developed sense of modesty, and a thing for violence. She - often a tsundere - will clobber the boy with excessive brutality.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3007" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-07-16">
<name>monologues</name>
<description>This show features a noticeable amount of screen time during which characters talk to themselves. That is usually a way to display to the viewers what the characters are thinking. When used in excess, it may be a sign of poor storytelling, but when done skillfully, it may be excellent comedy fuel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3610" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-12-19">
<name>game references</name>
<description>Be it the sound of a 1-up being grabbed, three golden triangles appearing on someones shirt or a blatant parody portraying a monkey throwing barrels down a poorly constructed facility, this anime contains characteristics dedicated to the remembrance/worship of an actual video game.</description>
<picurl>166123.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4542" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-04-25">
<name>no dialogue</name>
<description>The anime either has no spoken dialogue or no dialogue at all.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5515" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>faceless background characters</name>
<description>Unimportant random/extra characters that appear mostly as part of the background are often drawn without much facial details, normally to save money, effort and manpower for more important parts of the show. Sometimes, they have almost or no facial details, meaning their heads only have indications of the presence of parts such as hair or mouth, or not even that. This can go as far as only drawing an abstracted silhouette of the whole body.</description>
<picurl>233515.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6004" parentid="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>development hell</name>
<description>Due to unforeseen circumstances, the production or release of this anime has been pushed back, stalled, or cancelled one or more times from when it was first announced.
While some of them have eventually been completed, others might have only had a trailer released or have been changed into another format (e.g. a TV series turned into an OVA).
Common reasons for a work to become stuck in development hell include creative differences, legal issues, financial problems, scheduling conflicts or the death of an involved creator.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>origin</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="13767" type="appears in" update="2009-12-26">
<rating votes="86">7.92</rating>
<name>Chun-Li</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>40630.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="157" picture="42784.jpg">Orikasa Fumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85068" type="appears in" update="2016-09-24">
<rating votes="3">5.66</rating>
<name>Blanka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Blanka is a fighter from Brazil. He was once human, but after being struck by a lightning during the plane crash he mutated, resulting in his green colouring and his ability to generate electricity.
Blanka fights in a self-taught, animalistic style. In several of his special moves he rolls into a ball, launching himself at an opponent. In Blanka`s signature attack, he crouches and emits an electric current shocking anything it touches.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>191726.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="316" picture="25472.jpg">Ueda Yuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96691" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-07-14">
<rating votes="10">8.82</rating>
<name>Jiiya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>220377.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="694" picture="52187.jpg">Choo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96692" type="appears in" update="2018-08-24">
<rating votes="8">7.88</rating>
<name>Guile-san</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>222685.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="64" picture="173421.jpg">Yasumoto Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96693" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-07-14">
<rating votes="8">5.31</rating>
<name>Doi Genta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>220373.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34784" picture="129957.jpg">Yamashita Daiki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96694" type="main character in" update="2018-07-14">
<rating votes="42">5.79</rating>
<name>Oono Akira</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>220370.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="55692" picture="224737.jpg">Suzushiro Sayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96695" type="appears in" update="2019-09-08">
<rating votes="9">8.61</rating>
<name>Oono Makoto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238099.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18198" picture="228672.jpg">Akasaki Chinatsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96696" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-07-14">
<rating votes="8">6.26</rating>
<name>Miyao Koutarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>220372.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1692" picture="224934.jpg">Okitsu Kazuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96697" type="appears in" update="2018-07-14">
<rating votes="6">3.26</rating>
<name>Shougakkou no Tannin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>220378.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45" picture="44970.jpg">Sugita Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96698" type="appears in" update="2018-07-14">
<rating votes="4">5.86</rating>
<name>Koharu no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>220381.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2339" picture="151715.jpg">Taketora</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96699" type="main character in" update="2018-07-14">
<rating votes="60">8.04</rating>
<name>Hidaka Koharu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>220371.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="47407" picture="252729.jpg">Hirose Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96700" type="appears in" update="2018-07-14">
<rating votes="5">2.75</rating>
<name>Gouda Moemi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>220376.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="182" picture="226274.jpg">Itou Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96701" type="appears in" update="2018-07-14">
<rating votes="4">3.31</rating>
<name>Numata-sensei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>220379.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="345" picture="84834.jpg">Nakamura Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96702" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-07-14">
<rating votes="24">8.18</rating>
<name>Yaguchi Namie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>220375.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="600" picture="148972.jpg">Arai Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96703" type="main character in" update="2018-07-14">
<rating votes="18">6.71</rating>
<name>Yaguchi Haruo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>220369.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40642" picture="62085.png">Amasaki Kouhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96704" type="appears in" update="2018-07-14">
<rating votes="5">4.55</rating>
<name>Toono Reiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>220380.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="210" picture="71057.jpg">Ueda Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96705" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-07-14">
<rating votes="8">2.43</rating>
<name>Onizuka Chihiro</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>220374.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="55691" picture="223219.jpg">Midou Daria</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="202350" update="2018-06-30">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-08-04</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="202351" update="2018-06-30">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-07-28</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="202352" update="2018-06-30">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-07-21</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="202353" update="2018-06-30">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-07-14</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="202821" update="2018-10-17">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-07-14</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="202822" update="2018-07-14">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-07-14</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="203492" update="2018-07-28">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-09-01</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 8</title>
</episode>
<episode id="203493" update="2018-07-28">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-08-25</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="203494" update="2018-07-28">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-08-18</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="203495" update="2018-07-28">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-08-11</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="204602" update="2018-08-25">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-09-08</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 9</title>
</episode>
<episode id="204603" update="2018-08-25">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-09-15</airdate>
<rating votes="4">7.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 10</title>
</episode>
<episode id="204604" update="2018-08-25">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-09-22</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 11</title>
</episode>
<episode id="204605" update="2018-08-25">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-09-29</airdate>
<rating votes="4">6.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 12</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
