<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="106" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>26</episodecount>
<startdate>2002-04-09</startdate>
<enddate>2002-10-01</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Azumanga Daiou The Animation (2002)</title>
<title xml:lang="zh" type="synonym">阿滋漫画大王</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Адзуманга Дайо</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="synonym">أزومانجا دايوه</title>
<title xml:lang="vi" type="synonym">AZ Manga King</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Азуманга Дайо: Анимацията (2002)</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Азуманґа даійо</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="short">Адзуманга</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">AD</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">AzuDai</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">azu</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Azumanga</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Azudai TV</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="short">Азуманґа</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">あずまんが大王 THE ANIMATION (2002)</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Azumanga Daioh</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Azumanga Daioh: The Animation</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Azu Manga Daioh</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">아즈망가 대왕</title>
<title xml:lang="th" type="official">อสึมังกะ โรงเรียนป่วน นักเรียนเป๋อ</title>
<title xml:lang="vi" type="official">Nữ Sinh Trung Học</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="8792" type="Side Story">Azumanga Web Daiou</anime>
<anime id="8793" type="Side Story">Azumanga Daiou The Animation</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="4777" approval="188" total="227">Lucky Star</anime>
<anime id="8168" approval="148" total="180">Nichijou</anime>
<anime id="2787" approval="92" total="107">Ichigo Marshmallow</anime>
<anime id="8729" approval="71" total="93">Danshi Koukousei no Nichijou</anime>
<anime id="2165" approval="42" total="82">School Rumble</anime>
<anime id="3298" approval="42" total="60">PaniPoni Dash!</anime>
<anime id="4309" approval="27" total="48">Minami-ke</anime>
<anime id="5910" approval="27" total="43">Hyakko</anime>
<anime id="6257" approval="9" total="23">K-On!</anime>
<anime id="8107" approval="9" total="18">A Channel: The Animation</anime>
<anime id="1099" approval="5" total="22">Sakigake!! Cromartie Koukou</anime>
<anime id="1697" approval="5" total="7">Sensei no Ojikan: Doki Doki School Hours</anime>
<anime id="7224" approval="4" total="13">Mitsudomoe</anime>
<anime id="370" approval="3" total="13">Hoohokekyo Tonari no Yamada-kun</anime>
<anime id="8890" approval="3" total="12">Acchi Kocchi</anime>
<anime id="228" approval="2" total="9">Jungle wa Itsumo Hare Nochi Guu</anime>
<anime id="2435" approval="2" total="8">Gakuen Alice</anime>
<anime id="5356" approval="1" total="12">Bamboo Blade</anime>
<anime id="6646" approval="1" total="8">Hanamaru Youchien</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="43">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="652565">It is not THAT good, but still manages to steal a smile from you once a while. At some point, I felt that the jokes are getting repetitive and unappealing to say the least, but at the end of the day, I wouldn`t say you`d regret watching it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="419308">This is freaking fantastic. I watched most of it at work (yay dual monitors :U) and I loved it!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="447359">it`s a light-hearted anime with little to no shock value so it`s an excellent choice for any one looking to get into anime</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="61291">Very fun and it will make you laugh for sure.

Anyway, even if I loved it when I started to watch this, jokes and events become too repetitive through the 26 episodes.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="547775">Slice of life school comedy. Very interesting and likeable characters, as well as slightly quirky humour.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="80032">The humor is very mild but can still be exagerated at times, and yet in perfectly balanced manner. 
For a taste I`d recommend searching the tube for "best of kimmura sensei"</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="140987">One of my all time favorite.&lt;br /&gt;Comedy in a the cutest way.&lt;br /&gt;You cannot not love Osaka!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="321031">SHIKARI! SHIKARI! SHIKARI! SHIKARI!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="89822">Good anime</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="201226">A defining anime series. Well liked by just about anyone.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="241728">One of the best comedies that I`ve ever seen, even 6 years later. There`s many characters that are timeless and will be imitated for years to come.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="53116">Classic.  I`ve never met anyone who didn`t enjoy it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="69464">best anime ever</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="359130">I loved this anime!  It`s really funny haha and sometimes completely random! You need to see this if you haven`t already.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="412867">Azumanga Daiou is a show that you will remember!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="495882">Azumanga is an anime that came from a series of 4 panel comics. Which is very hard to make, but it was done amazingly. The humor comes from how the girls interact and makes for great situations and memorable events.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="129243">This is the series you need to blame if you hate or love slice of life, easy-going, gakuen boke-tsukkomi comedy.

Seriously, at this point, if you haven`t watched this yet, you don`t know comedy.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="537611">A definitely must see comedy. Most of the gags works and characters are lovable. It has a strong cast of female characters, which is a rarity in anime.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="446193">One of the many gems of anime that serves as one of the many precursors to its genre, Azumanga Daioh set the precedents of moe, "cute girls doing cute things," and character archetypes that have evolved into what anime is today in the moe genre.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="332307">Why must see? Because its the funniest and cutest anime I have ever seen. The humor is not in actions but in dialogues. SO can be hard for little ones. Leaves a taste of enjoyment and fulfillment at the end is awesome. #1 for me.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="432445">This is hands-down the funniest anime I`ve ever seen! Hilarious classic from an era before fanservice invaded the whole cute-girls-doing-cute-things genre (and made it somewhat distasteful, which is the opposite of what Azumanga represents). The characters may follow the typical formula, but they are lovable and the comedy is superb and artfully executed. Rewatching short clips on youtube always warms my heart a bit.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://king-cr.jp/special/azuma/</url>
<creators>
<name id="720" type="Animation Work">J.C.Staff</name>
<name id="3525" type="Character Design">Katou Yasuhisa</name>
<name id="1603" type="Direction">Nishikiori Hiroshi</name>
<name id="7832" type="Chief Animation Direction">Wada Takashi</name>
<name id="8212" type="Music">Kurihara Masaki</name>
<name id="1857" type="Series Composition">Ookouchi Ichirou</name>
<name id="3939" type="Original Work">Azuma Kiyohiko</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the 4-koma manga by http://anidb.net/cr3939 [Azuma Kiyohiko], originally serialised in Electric Shock Daiou.
A lively group of six high school girls, with colourful personalities, tries to master their daily life at school: there is the gifted 10-year-old http://anidb.net/ch7243 [Chiyo], the carefree klutz http://anidb.net/ch7429 [Ayumu], the shy but kind http://anidb.net/ch7480 [Sakaki], the mischievous http://anidb.net/ch7478 [Tomo], the short-tempered glasses-wearing http://anidb.net/ch7479 [Koyomi], and the extroverted tomboy http://anidb.net/ch7482 [Kagura]. Together with their quirky teachers http://anidb.net/ch7484 [Kurosawa Minamo] and http://anidb.net/ch7483 [Tanizaki Yukari] not a day passes without some minor incident occurring.
— written by foo2</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="9569">7.92</permanent>
<temporary count="9735">8.25</temporary>
<review count="19">7.91</review>
</ratings>
<picture>221656.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>799</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>66</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>857</identifier>
<identifier>rtsmeg</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.jcstaff.co.jp/sakuhin/nenpyo/2002/01_azumanga/azumanga.htm</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://king-cr.jp/special/azuma/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Azumanga_Daioh#Anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>あずまんが大王</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>184</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>238149</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5283</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/117</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2002/azumanga</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7899</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="798" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>moe</name>
<description>Moe is a Japanese slang loanword that refers to feelings of strong affection mainly towards characters in anime, manga, and video games. Moe, however, has also gained usage to refer to feelings of affection towards any subject. Moe can be related to lust; however, pure lust without other feelings is considered outside its scope. The word Moe originated in the late 1980s and early 1990s in Japan and is of uncertain origin, although there are several theories on how it came into use.
At the anime level, the http://anidb.net/t7146 [cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] tag may also apply.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2461" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>domestic cat</name>
<description>The cat (Felis catus or Felis silvestris catus), also known as the domestic cat to distinguish it from other felines and felids, is a small, usually furry, domesticated, and carnivorous mammal. Cats are valued by humans for companionship and their ability to hunt vermin and household pests, and are often kept as indoor pets, in which case they are also called housecats; they have been associated with humans for at least 9,500 years and are currently the most popular pet in the world, being found almost everywhere on Earth.
Cats are similar in anatomy to the other felids, with light, strong and flexible bodies, excellent hearing, sense of smell, and near darkness eyesight, quick reflexes, sharp retractable claws, and teeth adapted to killing small prey. They are skilled predators and hunt over 1,000 species for food. Despite being solitary hunters, cats are a social species, with communication means that include pheromones, body language and a variety of vocalizations, such as meowing, purring, trilling, hissing, growling and grunting.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>41283.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2677" parentid="2672" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Osaka</name>
<description>Osaka Prefecture is a prefecture located in the Kansai region on Honshu, the main island of Japan. The capital is the city of Osaka. It is the center of Osaka-Kobe-Kyoto area.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214384.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2681" parentid="2672" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Okinawa</name>
<description>Okinawa Prefecture is the southernmost prefecture of Japan. It encompasses two thirds of the Ryukyu Islands in a chain over 1,000 kilometreslong. The Ryukyu Islands extend southwest from Kyushu (the southwesternmost of Japan`s four main islands) to Taiwan. Naha, Okinawa`s capital, is located in the southern part of Okinawa Island.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214299.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2805" parentid="2798" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>4-koma manga</name>
<description>Yonkoma manga (4コマ漫画, four cell manga, or 4-koma for short), a comic-strip format, generally consists of gag comic strips within four panels of equal size ordered from top to bottom. (They also sometimes run right-to-left horizontally or use a hybrid 2x2 style, depending on the layout requirements of the publication in which they appear.) Though the word yonkoma comes from the Japanese, the style also exists outside of Japan in other Asian countries as well as in the English-speaking market.</description>
<picurl>70558.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3185" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-27">
<name>wordplay</name>
<description>The characters play with words. 
E.g. purposely or accidentally use similar-sounding but wrongly applied words in the Japanese original, leading to supposedly funny misunderstandings and confusion.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3809" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-05-24">
<name>character driven</name>
<description>The main appeal of the show is the way the characters are portrayed and interact, focusing on dialogue, spending time together or getting to know each other. These anime are not "story-less" but story is secondary to character development and the characters themselves and what they experience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4223" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>running gag</name>
<description>(Bit) character(s) play out a short skit several times during the course of the anime. The skit may or may not be exactly the same but does tend to have the same theme throughout.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4323" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-04">
<name>spacing out</name>
<description>A comedy element: The character starts to daydream or fantasize about some topic. The typical complete lack of reality makes the spacing out funny. Especially when the protagonist mumbles to himself / herself and friends hear this. Promptly teasing the possibly lovestruck and very embarrassed protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5697" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-02">
<name>randomness</name>
<description>The anime does not follow a predictable storyline. New, strange, obscure, or otherwise unexpected story elements are introduced at a whim.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6034" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>Engrish</name>
<description>Engrish is actually a mispronunciation of English, as can be the result of someone, who does not have English as their primary language of origin (such as Japanese or Chinese). Occasionally characters in the original Japanese dialogue version of an anime will speak in English... however; this often still requires the assistance of subtitles, for while the words are meant to be said in English, the sentence structure and letter pronunciation may still be strongly related to the person’s primary language.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6088" parentid="2785" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-01-29">
<name>unrequited shoujo ai</name>
<description>At least one female character has a romantic or sexual interest in another female character, but the feelings are not returned.
This can be because the recipient is oblivious, straight, or simply not interested.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6349" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-13">
<name>multi-segment episodes</name>
<description>Multi-segment episodes are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t5852 [short episodes], which are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length (up to and including 10 minutes).
Also not to be confused with an OVA or music video with multiple (otherwise unrelated) full-length http://anidb.net/t7241 [bundled episodes] consolidated into a single episode video track.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7146" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-14">
<name>cute girls doing cute things</name>
<description>Cute girls doing cute things with each other (CGDCT): when girls are super friendly with each other and do all sorts of http://anidb.net/t798 [cute/moe] things with each other, but there is no yuri or shoujo ai subtext -- more specifically, there is no romantic subtext.

* CGDCT applies where the main focus is on moe/cute girls and their interactions with each other. Good examples include http://anidb.net/a9722 [Non Non Biyori] (600 weight / 3.0 stars) and http://anidb.net/a9579 [Kin`iro Mosaic] (600 weight / 3.0 stars).
* Generally, CGDCT is applicable only if the anime is also tagged predominantly female cast or all female cast.
* CGDCT does not apply if girls doing cute things is incidental to a larger motive/theme/meta. For example, in http://anidb.net/a8168 [Nichijou] the focus is comedy, using cute girls; the tag would not apply.

CGDCT is often mistaken as low level yuri or shoujo ai. If there is also actual romantic subtext, use the http://anidb.net/t2695 [yuri (18+)] and http://anidb.net/t2782 [shoujo ai] tags as well. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>223153.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="7243" type="main character in" update="2009-05-27">
<rating votes="145">7.11</rating>
<name>Mihama Chiyo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chiyo is a child prodigy, Chiyo has skipped five grades to tenth grade (the first grade in Japanese high school) at the start of the series and is still at the top of the class. This type of grade-skipping is normally unthinkable in Japan, and the series humorously explores its consequences. She is extremely smart and responsible for her age—for example, she is the class representative and packs her own bento box every morning. However, Chiyo-chan (as she is usually called) still has the naivety, desires, and fears of a child.</description>
<picture>25610.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="553" picture="170553.jpg">Kaneda Tomoko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7429" type="main character in" update="2009-07-27">
<rating votes="359">9.12</rating>
<name>Kasuga Ayumu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ayumu "Osaka" Kasuga, commonly known as Osaka, is a transfer student from Osaka. Tomo, expecting her to act like the stereotypical Osakan (loud, exuberant and fond of bawdy jokes), quickly chose for her the nickname "Osaka", although Ayumu`s behavior could not be more different from the "typical" Osakan. Ayumu considers her label "too simple" and "icky," but she lacks the energy or motivation to dispute it. Unlike the stereotypical Osakan, she seems slow and easily distracted, but she merely has a mind that works quite differently than most people. This makes her prone to daydreaming, absentmindedness, and non-sequiturs, but it also makes her unusually good at answering very specific types of riddles. She is also easily amused by things that most people would consider bizarre.</description>
<picture>25973.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="392" picture="17237.jpg">Matsuoka Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7478" type="main character in" update="2015-09-18">
<rating votes="141">6.64</rating>
<name>Takino Tomo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tomo Takino is extremely energetic and competitive, despite being nonathletic and a slacker at the same time. She tends to irritate everyone around her, especially Yomi, who has been her classmate since elementary school. Tomo`s character is extremely impulsive and never considers nor cares about the consequences of anything she says or does. During the second trip to Chiyo`s summer house, Tomo actually grabbed Chiyo`s house keys and threw them into the forest because she wanted to see what would happen if they had lost them which, of course, was a very bad idea. However, on the occasions when Tomo has actually been inspired to concentrate on something, she has demonstrated that she is quite capable.</description>
<picture>26119.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2140" picture="21615.jpg">Higuchi Chieko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7479" type="main character in" update="2009-07-27">
<rating votes="104">6.06</rating>
<name>Mizuhara Koyomi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Koyomi Mizuhara, commonly known as Yomi, is a grade-school friend and general antithesis of Tomo. She is the voice of reason of the series, carrying herself as the most mature and serious of the group. Though smart and athletic, she is constantly dissatisfied with herself due to her weight and is always trying various diets in an effort to become thinner. She can never seem to stick to these diets however, as she finds herself constantly tempted by her favorite foods. Another weakness of Yomi`s character is that while she is above average in everything else, she is an awful singer, yet karaoke is one of her favorite pastimes. While usually functioning as Tomo`s "straight man", she sometimes manifests a rather cruel sense of humor.</description>
<picture>26121.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="135" picture="16884.jpg">Tanaka Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7480" type="main character in" update="2009-07-27">
<rating votes="227">8.77</rating>
<name>Sakaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sakaki is a tall, soft-spoken girl uncomfortable with her height and busty physique. Because she is so shy, she seldom speaks, and her reticence is misinterpreted as mysterious, or cool. This reputation has been compounded by the fact that most of the school`s sports teams try to recruit her every year in the story because of her natural athletic ability (she`s usually stronger and faster than most of the male students in school), but, for the most part, she has no real interest in sports. In contrast to what the other students think of her, Sakaki is in reality a very emotionally sensitive person who holds a secret longing for all things cute.</description>
<picture>2133.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="82" picture="216596.jpg">Asakawa Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7482" type="main character in" update="2009-07-27">
<rating votes="135">6.29</rating>
<name>Kagura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kagura is a later acquaintance, joining Yukari`s class in the 2nd year (Yukari selects her as a ringer to win the school athletic competitions). She was originally in Nyamo`s class and displays a very competitive spirit with her peers in all things (though with little success in studies). She devotes most of her time to the swim team but is an all-around good athlete, and genuinely nice to her classmates. She has a slight obsession with Sakaki, with whom she sees as an athletic rival. This is mostly due to the fact that while Kagura trains constantly to stay in shape, Sakaki is a naturally gifted athlete with no training at all. Like Tomo, Kagura tends to be quite impulsive in her actions (although unlike Tomo, Kagura is consciously aware of this and makes a genuine effort to try and keep it under control)</description>
<picture>26120.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="166" picture="23196.jpg">Kuwashima Houko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7483" type="main character in" update="2009-05-27">
<rating votes="147">7.90</rating>
<name>Tanizaki Yukari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>2913.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="692" picture="188445.jpg">Hiramatsu Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7484" type="main character in" update="2009-06-05">
<rating votes="86">6.59</rating>
<name>Kurosawa Minamo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>26212.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="360" picture="171401.jpg">Hisakawa Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7485" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-05-28">
<rating votes="64">7.70</rating>
<name>Kimura-sensei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>26218.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="67" picture="25195.jpg">Ishii Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10330" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-12">
<rating votes="71">4.26</rating>
<name>Kaori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Usually adressed by her nickname, Kaorin, she firstly appears in the show as a student in Yukari-sensei`s class. She is a member of the Astronomic Club, and is obliged to take part in its activities, thus she is often unable to spend vacations with her classmates. Kaori`s respect for Sakaki intentionally develops into love interest. Also, Kaorin becomes the main aim of Kimura-sensei`s attention. Her character is usually calm and shy, however, it drastically changes when Sakaki gets involved.</description>
<picture>30877.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="313" picture="158104.jpg">Nogawa Sakura</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10669" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-07-22">
<rating votes="20">4.69</rating>
<name>Chihiro</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Chihiro is one of the students in Yukari-sensei`s class. She is Kaorin`s friend, and they combine their artistic skills in order to create human-sized animal suits. She is also bad at English and has a fear of cockroaches.</description>
<picture>31745.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1879" picture="20977.jpg">Oomae Akane</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11320" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-08-23">
<rating votes="33">7.63</rating>
<name>Chiyo Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>33754.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2" picture="16471.jpg">Wakamoto Norio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68784" type="appears in" update="2015-09-18">
<rating votes="5">5.48</rating>
<name>Kimura no Tsuma</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch7485 [Kimura-sensei]`s wife. She has a good heart and a kind personality.</description>
<picture>158420.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="74" picture="84835.jpg">Oohara Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92021" type="appears in" update="2017-11-14">
<rating votes="2">8.04</rating>
<name>Maya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Maya (マヤー Mayā) is Sakaki`s pet Iriomote Mountain Cat. They met on Iriomote Island (Episode 21 of the anime; Volume 4 in the manga) when he was a kitten during the class trip to Okinawa, and he was the first cat to ever let Sakaki pet it. They were together all the time during Class 3`s visit to Iriomote, but they had to be separated when the class left from there. However, later on, Sakaki read online about the death of an Iriomote Cat that had been run over by a car and strongly resembled Maya`s mother. After this, Maya somehow followed Sakaki home. Because of her parent`s allergies, Sakaki cannot keep pets at her house and because of this, it was decided that Maya should stay at Chiyo`s house until Sakaki went to college and had her own house or apartment.
Maya tends to scare off the neighborhood cats and protecting Sakaki from Kamineko. After his attack on said cat when he had just found Sakaki after travelling all the way from Iriomote Island, Maya was physically weakened – probably due to exhaustion from having travelled so far. He was taken to Dr. Ishihara, who was suspicious because of Maya`s obvious resemblance to an Iriomote Cat (that are not recommended for keeping as pets), but Sakaki and Chiyo convinced him that Maya was a crossbreed and they were thus allowed to take him home. Sakaki decided to name her new pet Maya. In spite of being a wildcat, Maya is comfortable around people and even Tadakichi-san. He also lets Sakaki bathe him. Maya once scratched Tomo because she was taunting him, but Sakaki tapped him on the head and told him not to scratch people. Before graduation, Sakaki often visited Chiyo-chan`s house so that she could be with Maya, even spending the night there where she rolled around on the floor holding her cat, only to be confronted by Chiyo-chan in doing so. He tends to keep a serious look on his face, and is nearly identical to his deceased mother (apart from his size).
Trivia
- His name is derived from Yamamayaa, a name in Okinawan language for his species.
- Osaka refers him as "Pikameowmeow", or "Pikanyaa", from a corruption of Yamapikarya, another Okinawan name for the species. Chiyo made many attempts to teach Osaka the proper way to say his name, but it was impossible for her.
Source: http://azumanga.wikia.com/wiki/Maya</description>
<picture>208982.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="97623" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-08-23">
<rating votes="3">7.50</rating>
<name>Kamineko</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kamineko (「噛み猫」, "Biting Cat", or "Evil Cat" in Japanese) is a gray cat that http://anidb.net/ch7480 [Sakaki] occasionally sees on the way to and from school. Having a great soft spot for cats, Sakaki tries to pet it, but it ends up latching its huge, beartrap-like teeth onto her hand.
Source: http://azumanga.wikia.com/wiki/Kamineko</description>
<picture>66529.png</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="562" update="2011-11-13">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-07-16</airdate>
<rating votes="24">8.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">木村家の人々 / みたみた? / 未確認奥さん / ガチガチ / 結果発表</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Members of the Kimura Family / Did You See? Did You See? / Unidentified Wife / Nervous Wreck / The Numbers Are In</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Familie Kimura / Hast du das gesehen? / Unerkannte Ehefrau / Sieg um jeden Preis / Nur die Zahlen zählen</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Kimuran perheen jäsenet - Näitkö tuon? - Salaperäinen vaimo - Jäätynyt - Päätösilmoitus</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kimura Ke no Hitobito / Mita Mita? / Mikakunin Oku-san / Gachi Gachi / Kekka Happyou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="563" update="2011-11-13">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-05-21</airdate>
<rating votes="28">7.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">おとぎの組 / 人格者 / のりのりゴー! / マスコット / 敵?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fairyland Class / Man of Character / Go With Enthusiasm! / The Mascot / Enemy?</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die märchenhafte Klasse / Jemand mit gutem Charakter / Legt euch ins Zeug und legt los! / Das Maskottchen / Ein Feind?</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Keijukaisten luokka - Luonteen mies - Pää pystyyn ja menoksi! - Maskotti - Vihollinen?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Otogi no Gumi / Jinkakusha / Nori Nori Go! / Mascot / Teki?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="564" update="2011-11-13">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-06-18</airdate>
<rating votes="24">8.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">国際都市 / 対決 / たたかなくても / ねこまみれ / 逃げないで</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cosmopolitan City / Showdown / You Didn`t Have to Hit Him / Covered In Cats / Don`t Run Away</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Eine internationale Stadt / Wettkampf / Ihn zu schlagen war nicht nötig / Katzen über Katzen / Lauf nicht weg</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Kansainvälinen kaupunki - Kilpailu - Ei tarvitse lyödä - Täynnä kissoja - Älä pakene</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kokusai Toshi / Taiketsu / Tatakanakute mo / Neko Mamire / Nigenai de</title>
</episode>
<episode id="565" update="2016-03-13">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-04-23</airdate>
<rating votes="31">5.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">にゃも / 派閥闘争 / ゆかりがきた / 悪くないもん / どこまでも</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nyamo / Factional Rivalry / Yukari`s Here / Not My Fault / Forever and Ever</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Nyamo / Rivalinnen / Yukaris Überraschungsbesuch / Nicht meine Schuld / Für immer und ewig</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Nyamo - Kilpailua omasta edusta - Yukari ilmestyi - Se ei ole minun vikani - Minne ikinä menemmekin</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nyamo / Habatsu Tousou / Yukari ga Kita / Warukunaimon / Dokomademo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="566" update="2011-11-13">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-07-23</airdate>
<rating votes="31">9.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">くみあわせ / 降臨 / かわいい / 注文 / 宣伝効果</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Combinations / Epiphany / Cute / Ordering / Advertising Reach</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Kombinationen / Die Eingebung / So niedlich / Bestellungen / Werbekampagne</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Yhdistelmä - Laskeutuminen - Söpö - Määräys - Mainostuksen vaikutus</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kumiawase / Kourin / Kawaii / Chuumon / Senden Kouka</title>
</episode>
<episode id="567" update="2011-11-13">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-05-28</airdate>
<rating votes="32">4.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大阪の初夢 / ともちゃんの場合 / 榊の場合 / ようこそ / かおりんの場合</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Osaka`s New Year`s Dream / In Tomo-chan`s Case / In Sakaki`s Case / Welcome / In Kaorin`s Case</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Osakas Neujahrstraum / Bei Tomo-chan dagegen... / Bei Sakaki dagegen... / Willkommen / Bei Kaorin dagegen...</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Osakan vuoden ensimmäinen uni - Tomon versio - Sakakin versio - Tervetuloa - Kaorinin versio</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oosaka no Hatsuyume / Tomo-chan no Baai / Sakaki no Baai / Youkoso / Kaorin no Baai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="568" update="2011-11-13">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-06-25</airdate>
<rating votes="24">8.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ちよちゃんの一日 / 高校のともだち / お昼 / ごご / なわとび</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Chiyo-chan`s Day / High School Friends / Lunch / Afternoon / Jump Rope</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Chiyo-chans Tag / Oberschulkameraden / Mittagspause / Nachmittag / Seilspringen</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Chiyon päivä - Lukiokaverit - Päivällinen - Iltapäivä - Hyppynaru</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chiyo-chan no Ichinichi / Koukou no Tomodachi / Ohiru / Gogo / Nawatobi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="569" update="2011-11-13">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-04-30</airdate>
<rating votes="29">6.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">楽しい職業 / プールプールプール / りぼん / ふたりっきり / いいひと?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Fun Profession / Pool, Pool, Pool / Ribbon / Just the Two of Them / A Good Person?</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ein Beruf, der Spaß macht / Pool, Pool, Pool! / Das Band / Nur die beiden / Ein guter Mensch</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Kiva työ - Uima-allas x3 - Nauha - Vain me kaksi - Hyvä ihminen?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tanoshii Shokugyou / Pool Pool Pool / Ribbon / Futarikkiri / Ii Hito?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="570" update="2011-11-13">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-06-04</airdate>
<rating votes="24">7.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">触れないなら / 11才 / ねこさん... / 設定 / なんで?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">If I Can`t Pet One... / 11 Years Old / Mr. Kitty Cat... / Premise / Why?</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Wenn ich keine streicheln kann / Elf Jahre alt / Neko-san / Aufbau / Warum?</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Jos et päästä irti - 11 vuotta vanha - Kissa - Ansa - Miksi?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Furenai Nara / 11 Sai / Neko-san... / Settei / Nande?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="571" update="2011-11-13">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-07-02</airdate>
<rating votes="24">8.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ノーガード戦法 / S / 中間テスト / 結成 / 能力</title>
<title xml:lang="en">No Guard Strategy / S / Exams / Formation / Abilities</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Keine funktionierende Schutzstrategie / S / Zwischenprüfungen / Formation / Fähigkeiten</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">"Ei suojausta"-strategia - S - Lukukauden välikokeet - Muodostelma - Kyky</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">No Guard Senpou / S / Chuuken Test / Kessei / Nouryoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="572" update="2011-11-13">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-05-07</airdate>
<rating votes="28">8.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">なつやすみ / ようこそちよの部屋へ / ご招待 / 経験者語って / もうだめ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Summer Break / Welcome to Chiyo`s Room / Invitation / Someone with Experience, Speak / Done For</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Sommerferien / Willkommen in Chiyos Zimmer / Einladung / Jemand mit Erfahrung soll reden / Erledigt</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Kesäloma - Tervetuloa Chiyon huoneeseen - Kutsu - Kokemuksen äänellä - Ei enempää</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Natsuyasumi / Youkoso Chiyo no Heya e / Goshoutai / Keikensha Katatte / Mou Dame</title>
</episode>
<episode id="573" update="2011-11-13">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-04-09</airdate>
<rating votes="46">6.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">こども高校生 / 天才です / こわいかな? / 爆走ともちゃん! / 大阪人や</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Child High School Student / She`s a Prodigy / Scary Maybe? / Wildcat Tomo-chan! / The Osakan Gal</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Eine Oberschülerin im Grundschulalter / Ein Wunderkind / Unheimlich? / Tobsüchtige Tomo-chan! / Sie kommt aus Osaka</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Lapsi lukiolaisena - Nero - Pelottava? - Riehuva Tomo-chan - Se on Osakalainen</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kodomo Koukousei / Tensai Desu / Kowai ka na? / Bakusou Tomo-chan / Oosakajin ya</title>
</episode>
<episode id="574" update="2011-11-13">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-07-09</airdate>
<rating votes="26">9.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">おかいもの / 集合 / うみー! / 捕獲作戦 / 大人の世界</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shopping / Meeting Up / The Ocean! / Capture Operation / The Adult World</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Shopping / Sich treffen / Das Meer! / Gefangennahme / Die Welt der Erwachsenen</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Ostoksilla - Tapaaminen - Valtameri! - Kiinniotto-operaatio - Aikuisten maailma</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Okaimono / Shuugou / Umi! / Hokaku Sakusen / Otona no Sekai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="575" update="2011-11-13">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-05-14</airdate>
<rating votes="28">8.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">勝利の方程式 / 三組の榊, 五組の神楽 / ぶっちぎり / わーい / 踊る大団円</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Equation For Victory / Sakaki of Class 3, Kagura of Class 5 / Runaway Victory / Yay / Dancing the Grand Finale</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Siegesformel / Sakaki aus Klasse drei - Kagura aus Klasse fünf / Es geht um den Sieg! / Hurra! / Großes Finale mit Tanz</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Voiton yhtälö - Luokka 3:n Sakaki - Luokka 5:n Kagura - Näytä niille! - Jee! - Tanssiva finaali</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shouri no Houteishiki / Sangumi no Sakaki Gokumi no Kagura / Bucchigiri / Waai / Odoru Daidenen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="576" update="2011-11-13">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-06-11</airdate>
<rating votes="24">8.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ドラフト指名 / クラス替え / おおかみ / 先輩風ぴゅーぴゅー / マルコ...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Draft Picks / Class Shuffle / Wolf / Putting On Senior Airs / Marco...</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Einberufung / Klassenwechsel / Wolf / Die Marotten der Älteren annehmen / Marco</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Ehdokasvalinnat - Luokkamuutokset - Susi - "Olen vanhempi"-asenne jyrää - Marco...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Draft Shimei / Classgae / Ookami / Senpai Kaze Pyuu Pyuu / Marco...</title>
</episode>
<episode id="577" update="2016-11-14">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-04-16</airdate>
<rating votes="32">7.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">今日も大阪 / 体育・バレーボール / しゃっくり / 脳が / おにゅー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Osaka Today As Well / P.E. - Volleyball / Hiccups / The Brain... / Brand New</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Osaka, auch heute wieder / Sportstunde - Volleyball / Schluckauf / Das Gehirn / Brandneu</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Tänään on taas Osaka - Lentopalloa liikuntatunnilla - Hikka - Aivot - Tulokas</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyou mo Oosaka / Taiiku Volleyball / Shakkuri / Nou ga / Onyuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1453" update="2011-11-13">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-07-30</airdate>
<rating votes="25">8.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大阪の怪談 / 気分転換 / 師走 / すごいサンタ / クリスマス会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Osaka`s Horror Story / Change of Pace / Yule / Amazing Santa / Christmas Party</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Osakas Gruselgeschichte / Tempowechsel / Dezember / Der Wahnsinns-Weihnachtsmann / Weihnachtsparty</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Osakan kauhutarinat - Mielialan muutokset - Joulukuu - Mahtava joulupukki - Joulubileet</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Osaka no Kaidan / Kibun Tenkan / Shiwasu / Sugoi Santa / Christmas Kai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="1681" update="2011-11-13">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-08-06</airdate>
<rating votes="24">8.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">うきよみ / 裏切り / ワクワクワクワク / 仲間はずれ / ゴー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yomi`s Exposure to the World / Betrayal / Excited, Excited, Excited, Excited / Left Out / Go!</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Yomis Ausflug in die weite Welt / Betrug / Aufregend, aufregend, aufregend / Zuhause gelassen / Los!</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Lumoutunut Yomi - Petos - Innostunut - Ulkopuolinen - Mene!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ukiyomi / Uragiri / Wakuwaku Wakuwaku / Nakama Hazure / Go</title>
</episode>
<episode id="2207" update="2011-11-13">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-08-13</airdate>
<rating votes="24">7.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あくび名人 / なんだか青春 / 大人の花見 / 子供の花見 / 桜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yawn Master / Vaguely Youth / Adults` Flower Gazing / Children`s Flower Gazing / Cherry Blossoms</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Gähn-Champion / Flüchtige Jugend / Kirschblüten gucken für Erwachsene / Kirschblüten gucken für Kinder / Kirschblüten</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Haukottelemisen mestari - Nuoruuden kevät - Aikuisten juhla - Lasten juhla - Kirsikankukka</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akubi Meijin / Nandaka Seishun / Otona no Hanami / Kodomo no Hanami / Sakura</title>
</episode>
<episode id="2208" update="2011-11-13">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-08-20</airdate>
<rating votes="24">8.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">別離 / ゆかりの誕生日 / はばたけちよ / こども大統領 / 強く生きて下さい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Separation / Yukari`s Birthday / Flap Your Wings, Chiyo / Child President / Please Be Strong</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Trennung / Yukaris Geburtstag / Schlag mit den Flügeln, Chiyo / Kinderpräsident / Du musst stark sein</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Eroaminen - Yukarin synt.p. - Lennä tulevaisuuteen, Chiyo! - Lapsipresidentti - Elä täysillä</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Betsuri / Yukari no Tanjoubi / Habatake Chiyo / Kodomo Daitouryou / Tsuyoku Ikite Kudasai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="2209" update="2011-11-13">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-08-27</airdate>
<rating votes="25">9.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">期待 / いてもたっても / 海の藻屑 / 夢の島 / 山にすむネコ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Anticipation / Can`t Stand Still / Watery Grave / Island of Dreams / Cat of the Mountains</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Vorfreude / Stillstehen unmöglich / Ein nasses Grab / Trauminsel / Bergkatze</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Toivo - En vain voinut - Vetinen hauta - Unelmasaari - Vuoristokissat</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kitai / Itemo Tattemo / Umi no Mokuzu / Yume no Shima / Yama ni Sumu Neko</title>
</episode>
<episode id="2336" update="2011-11-13">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-10-01</airdate>
<rating votes="30">9.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">初めての卒業 / 万感 / 悲しみ / 母校 / みんな</title>
<title xml:lang="en">First Graduation Ever / A Thousand Emotions / Sorrow / Alma Mater / Everyone</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Erste Abschlussfeier / Tausend Gefühle / Trauer / Alma Mater / Alle gemeinsam</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Ensimmäiset valmistujaiset - Tuhat tunnetta - Suru - Vanha koulumme - Me kaikki</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajimete no Sotsugyou / Bankan / Kanashimi / Bokou / Minna</title>
</episode>
<episode id="2337" update="2011-11-13">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-09-03</airdate>
<rating votes="29">9.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ナイスですよ / だまされた / 黒沢先生 / 未遂 / まだ終わってない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It`s Nice / Fooled / Miss Kurosawa / An Attempt / It`s Not Over Yet</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Einfach schön / Reingelegt / Kurosawa-san / Ein Versuch / Es ist noch nicht vorbei</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Hienoa - Tuli huijatuksi - Kurosawa - Yritetty - Se ei ole vielä ohi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nice Desu yo / Damasareta / Kurosawa-sensei / Misui / Mada Owattenai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="2338" update="2011-11-13">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-09-10</airdate>
<rating votes="24">8.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">かんだ / もりあげ役 / 考えてなかった / みんなで走ります / 一丸</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Got a Bite / Motivator / Hadn`t Thought Of That / We`ll All Run Together / United</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Darf ich mal abbeißen? / Anfeuerungen / Das hab ich nicht bedacht / Wir laufen alle zusammen / Vereint</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Pureskeltu - Cheerleaderit - En ajatellut - Juoksemme yhdessä - Yhdistyneet</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanda / Moriageyaku / Kangaetenakatta / Minna de Hashirimasu / Ichigan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="2339" update="2011-11-13">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-09-17</airdate>
<rating votes="31">9.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">進路 / 対決 / はやく行こう / 人望 / マヤーと一緒</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Career Paths / Showdown / Let`s Go Quickly / Popularity / Together with Mayaa</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Berufswahl / Finale / Beeilen wir uns / Popularität / Zusammen mit Maya</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Urapolku - Viimeinen taistelu - Pidetään kiirettä - Suosio - Mayan kanssa</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinro / Taiketsu / Hayaku Ikou / Jinbou / Mayaa to Issho</title>
</episode>
<episode id="2340" update="2011-11-13">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2002-09-24</airdate>
<rating votes="23">9.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">進路相談 / 合格祈願 / ファイト / 勉強会 / ともと大阪 運命の日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Career Path Discussion / Prayers For Acceptance / Fight / Study Group / Tomo and Osaka, the Fateful Day</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Berufsdebatte / Beten fürs Bestehen / Kampf / Arbeitsgruppe / Tomo und Osaka, der Schicksalstag</title>
<title xml:lang="fi">Kurssikeskustelu - Rukoile menestystä - Taistele! - Opiskelutuokio - Tomon ja Osakan kohtalon pv.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinro Soudan / Goukaku Kigan / Fight / Benkyoukai / Tomo to Oosaka Unmei no Hi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27789" update="2014-03-19">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2002-04-09</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="27790" update="2014-03-19">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2002-04-09</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="75347" update="2011-11-14">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<rating votes="1">3.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Movie Character Art Gallery</title>
</episode>
<episode id="75348" update="2011-11-14">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">2.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Production Sketches Part 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="75349" update="2011-11-14">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">3.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Production Sketches Part 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="75350" update="2011-11-14">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>3</length>
<rating votes="1">2.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Production Sketches Part 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="75351" update="2011-11-14">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">3.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Production Sketches Part 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="75352" update="2011-11-14">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">2.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Production Sketches Part 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="75353" update="2011-11-14">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">3.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Production Sketches Part 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="226895" update="2020-02-14">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2009-06-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">アイキャッチ集</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Eyecatch Collection</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Eyecatch Shuu</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
