<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="10886" restricted="false">
<type>Movie</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2015-02-20</startdate>
<enddate>2015-02-20</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Hana to Alice: Satsujin Jiken</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">花とアリス殺人事件</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">花とアリス 殺人事件</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">The Case of Hana &amp; Alice</title>
</titles>
<recommendations total="3">
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="461271">What a surprise! 
This movie went from awkward, over sweet to sad and back to heartwarming.
It had sad moments but also great comedy without getting too ridiculous. 
A sweet melodrama with fantastic, calming soundtrack. The characters felt so lively and real. And most importantly, it leaves you with positivism.
I loved it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="106205">Very good comedy!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="340713">I loved it! I think the best part is that the girls talk and act like normal kids, I`m so used to middle/high school anime characters being like little adults (or super geniuses protecting the universe with their super powers) that this felt like a real breath of fresh air. Very funny and cute. The animation looks like rotoscoping to me, it might seem a little strange at first but I feel it helps it stand out from the crowd in the end.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://hana-alice.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="41065" type="Original Work">Iwai Shunji</name>
<name id="41065" type="Music">Iwai Shunji</name>
<name id="41065" type="Direction">Iwai Shunji</name>
<name id="42835" type="Work">Steve N` Steven</name>
<name id="51110" type="Work">Rockwell Eyes</name>
<name id="51112" type="Music">Hekuto Pascal</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch70676 [Arisugawa Tetsuko] has just moved to a new house with her recently divorced mother. She becomes a transfer student at a school where a strange rumour lingers among the students. When she starts to investigate into it, she ends up meeting http://anidb.net/ch70677 [Arai Hana], her young strange neighbour who rarely leaves the house.
Source: ANN
Note: Prequel to 2004 coming-of-age live-action film Hana &amp; Alice.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="335">7.11</permanent>
<temporary count="335">7.13</temporary>
<review count="2">8.33</review>
</ratings>
<picture>177706.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16600</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>27969</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://hana-alice.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>The_Case_of_Hana_&amp;_Alice</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>花とアリス#.E8.8A.B1.E3.81.A8.E3.82.A2.E3.83.AA.E3.82.B9.E6.AE.BA.E4.BA.BA.E4.BA.8B.E4.BB.B6</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>350630</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>17977</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="125" parentid="362" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>ballet</name>
</tag>
<tag id="308" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>detective</name>
<description>A detective is an investigator, generally either a member of a law enforcement agency or as an individual working in the capacity of private investigators, tasked with solving crimes and other mysteries, such as disappearances, by examining and evaluating clues and records in order to solve the mystery; for a crime, this would mean uncovering the criminal`s identity and/or whereabouts. In some police systems, a detective position is achieved by passing a written test after a person completes the requirements for being a police officer; in others, detectives are college graduates who join directly from civilian life without first serving as uniformed officers.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210906.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="362" parentid="2793" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-09-24">
<name>dancing</name>
<description>Dance is when people move their body to music. There are many kinds of dance, like ballet or waltz. Dancing can be done for fun but can be also an art.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1637" parentid="2565" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-09">
<name>reverse trap</name>
<description>A reverse trap is a plot device where a female character is mistaken for a male, with the intention of sexually deceiving other characters and/or the viewer. This behavior does not need to be intentional by the female (it is often not intentional) or continually maintained by the female, but the occurrence is common enough to deserve this fetish-specific tag.
This is often achieved by portraying the female character as a male; primarily via their clothing and physical appearance, but also through her behaviour, and/or language. A female character misinterpreted by others as male, without action from the female (explicitly masculine dress or behaviour), is generally not considered a reverse trap; instead they are likely just http://anidb.net/t2561 [androgynous].
The reverse case is known as a http://anidb.net/t618 [trap].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2565" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-14">
<name>cross-dressing</name>
<description>This character sometimes wears clothes traditionally worn by and associated with the opposite sex.
Cross-dressers often hide their cross-dressing identity for a long period of time and thus tend to become adept in accurately portraying the opposite sex in terms of voice, movement, behaviour, temperament, etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2614" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>josei</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, the word josei refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 15 and 44. In Japanese, the word means simply "woman", and has no anime/manga-related connotations at all. It does not comprise a style or a genre per se, but rather indicates the publisher`s intended target demographic.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2793" parentid="2883" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>performance</name>
<description>The song performance on stage or acting in a theatre is a central part of the character`s life in this anime type.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2796" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>movie</name>
<description>Based on a live action film, Japanese or otherwise.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3146" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-04-29">
<name>divorce</name>
<description>The parents depicted in this anime have divorced, usually upsetting the life of their children.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3741" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-25">
<name>bullying</name>
<description>Bullying is the use of force, threat, or coercion to abuse, intimidate, or aggressively dominate others. One who engages in bullying is known as a bully.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4298" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-04-07">
<name>rotoscoping</name>
<description>Rotoscoping is an animation technique in which animators trace over footage, frame by frame, for use in live-action and animated films.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="70676" type="main character in" update="2014-10-16">
<rating votes="5">7.54</rating>
<name>Arisugawa Tetsuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>162799.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9703" picture="36416.jpg">Aoi Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70677" type="main character in" update="2014-10-16">
<rating votes="5">6.93</rating>
<name>Arai Hana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>162800.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11258" picture="40674.jpg">Suzuki An</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71964" type="appears in" update="2015-10-03">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Tsutsumi Yuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ballet teacher.</description>
<picture>178203.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="41622" picture="165823.jpg">Kimura Tae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71965" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-10-03">
<rating votes="2">5.34</rating>
<name>Arisugawa Kayo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>178199.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="41620" picture="165821.jpg">Aida Shouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71966" type="appears in" update="2015-10-03">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Tomonaga-sensei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>178206.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="41624" picture="165825.jpg">Kaku Tomohiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71967" type="appears in" update="2015-10-03">
<rating votes="1">1.56</rating>
<name>Yuda Koutarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>178197.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="15592" picture="76468.jpg">Katsuji Ryou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71968" type="appears in" update="2015-10-03">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Arai Tomomi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>178202.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="41621" picture="165822.jpg">Kimura Midoriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71969" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-10-03">
<rating votes="2">4.38</rating>
<name>Ogino Satomi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>178198.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33548" picture="216939.jpg">Kuroki Haru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71970" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-10-03">
<rating votes="2">2.79</rating>
<name>Mutsu Mutsumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>178196.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34113" picture="94845.jpg">Suzuki Lanlan</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="71971" type="appears in" update="2015-10-03">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Kuroyanagi Kenji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>178201.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="41626" picture="165827.jpg">Hiraizumi Sei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="77650" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-10-03">
<rating votes="2">2.36</rating>
<name>Fuuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>178204.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="77651" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-10-03">
<rating votes="1">1.18</rating>
<name>Chiba Yuuya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>178205.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="77652" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-10-03">
<rating votes="1">7.63</rating>
<name>Watanabe</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>178200.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="166594" update="2015-03-11">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>100</length>
<airdate>2015-02-20</airdate>
<rating votes="5">8.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
