<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="11321" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2016-04-07</startdate>
<enddate>2016-06-23</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Anne Happy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Anne Happy♪</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Anhapi</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="synonym">Unhappy♪</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">あんハピ♪</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Anne-Happy</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">Anne Happy♪</title>
</titles>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="510875">I picked this up expecting it to be worse but honestly was surprised - it`s not bad at all. Characters are cute, the plot is just random things happening at random times and the OP/ED songs are great. Don`t expect too much though, however there is drama and tension thrown in at various intervals just to add some spice to the mix.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="179476">I wasn`t planning on watching this, but very happy I did!  It`s a great slice-of-life/comedic show.  

If you like adapted 4-komas, this one isn`t one to miss!  It has an interesting set of characters.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://anne-happy.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1564" type="Direction">Oonuma Shin</name>
<name id="3779" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ooshima Miwa</name>
<name id="3020" type="Music">Monaca</name>
<name id="44241" type="Original Work">Kotoji</name>
<name id="3779" type="Character Design">Ooshima Miwa</name>
<name id="37823" type="Series Composition">Tanaka Jin</name>
<name id="2900" type="Animation Work">Silver Link</name>
</creators>
<description>All the students with "negative karma" or misfortune seem to have been gathered in class 1-7 at the elite school of the Tennomifune Academy. Since, as it turns out, the classes 1-(1-3) specialize in academics, and the classes 1-(4-6) in sports, this leaves class 7 with only one goal: happiness.
http://anidb.net/ch78942 [Hibarigaoka Ruri], a level-headed high school student in this special class, meets the unlucky yet energetic http://anidb.net/ch78940 [Hanakoizumi An] and the frail http://anidb.net/ch78938 [Kumegawa Botan] on her first day of school. Together with the emotionally stunted http://anidb.net/ch78939 [Ekoda Ren], and the often spatially disoriented http://anidb.net/ch78941 [Hagyuu Hibiki], they try to find a way to turn their school life into a happy one.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="730">4.79</permanent>
<temporary count="735">6.45</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>228832.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>17372</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>31080</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://anne-happy.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Anne_Happy</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>あんハピ♪</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4096</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>354827</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18987</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>annehappy_anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>anne-happy</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="31">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20235</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="798" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>moe</name>
<description>Moe is a Japanese slang loanword that refers to feelings of strong affection mainly towards characters in anime, manga, and video games. Moe, however, has also gained usage to refer to feelings of affection towards any subject. Moe can be related to lust; however, pure lust without other feelings is considered outside its scope. The word Moe originated in the late 1980s and early 1990s in Japan and is of uncertain origin, although there are several theories on how it came into use.
At the anime level, the http://anidb.net/t7146 [cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] tag may also apply.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1279" parentid="2869" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-18">
<name>all-girls school</name>
<description>This school is only for female students. There may be a few male teachers though.</description>
<picurl>70853.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2839" parentid="2628" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-05">
<name>virtual world</name>
<description>A virtual world is a place where the character interacts with a computer (or some other device)-simulated environment, be it real or imagined. The condition for a virtual reality to exist is the existence of an originating "real" (source/anchor) world for the character. In some cases, a virtual reality where characters can get harmed physically is depicted.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2854" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>henshin</name>
<description>Japanese for "transformation" (metamorphosis or disguise).
A "henshin anime" is any anime, where the characters or their costumes transform, such as Sailor Moon. The henshin switches on the character`s special powers, and is frequently accompanied by a costume change. Often the change of clothing is the only outward indicator that the character has changed and yet nobody seems to notice the hero`s true self.
Most henshin heroes have a special item which they use to change into their heroic form. These items are usually activated by a command phrase (which is often in Engrish, for some reason), triggering a transformation sequence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3092" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-03-02">
<name>important haircut</name>
<description>When a character cuts off his or her hair, it often symbolizes a rite of passage or bout of character growth. A princess striking out on an adventure, or a new recruit at boot camp, for instance. Hair is something that takes time and effort to grow, so parting with it voluntarily can be a powerful act.
This is particularly a big deal when women get haircuts. Yet in fiction, even an accidental hair slicing can leave a character with a surprisingly even cut.
In many religions (Western Christianity, Ancient Egyptian religion, and others) priests and/or monks cut/shave their hair. Roman Catholic nuns also tend to cut and mantain their hair short under their veils when they enter the nunneries. The cutting of one`s own hair is also a part of Buddhist mythology, specifically something done by Siddhartha himself early on in his path to enlightenment, so anime examples might draw from this as an allusion. There are also some cultures, including Native American and many Asians, where a person would cut his or her hair as an act of grief, disgrace, or even rebellion. In the Confucian tradition, hair (like the rest of your body) is considered a gift from your parents and may not be damaged without a very good reason. Furthermore, prisoners and psychiatric patients commonly have their heads shaved, often to prevent the spread of lice, but sometimes also as a demeaning measure.
Source: TVTRope</description>
<picurl>169641.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3751" parentid="6243" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-02">
<name>grandiose displays of wealth</name>
<description>Some of the characters in this anime come from very wealthy families. A huge estate with large mansion or castle, a flotilla of expensive cars, private jets or islands, and many servants will impress the viewer profoundly.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3867" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>ED variety</name>
<description>Several ED sequences in this anime have either a different song or different animation, maybe even to the point of having a unique ED for each episode.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4090" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-08">
<name>cardiopulmonary resuscitation</name>
<description>Cardiopulmonary resuscitation, commonly known as CPR, is an emergency procedure that combines chest compression often with artificial ventilation in an effort to manually preserve intact brain function until further measures are taken to restore spontaneous blood circulation and breathing in a person who is in cardiac arrest. It is indicated in those who are unresponsive with no breathing or abnormal breathing. CPR involves chest compressions at a rate of at least 100 to 120 per minute. The rescuer may also provide artificial ventilation by either exhaling air into the subject`s mouth or nose (mouth-to-mouth resuscitation) or using a device that pushes air into the subject`s lungs (mechanical ventilation).
CPR alone is unlikely to restart the heart; its main purpose is to restore partial flow of oxygenated blood to the brain and heart. The objective is to delay tissue death and to extend the brief window of opportunity for a successful resuscitation without permanent brain damage. Administration of an electric shock to the subject`s heart, termed defibrillation, is usually needed in order to restore a viable heart rhythm. In general, CPR is continued until the person has a return of spontaneous circulation or is declared dead.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>68242.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4227" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-03">
<name>detailed landscapes</name>
<description>An amazing view of nature, of artificially sculpted landscapes (i.e. gardens), or of a cityscape.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4498" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-20">
<name>heart-warming</name>
<description>The story and its characters give off good vibes — includes elevated feelings of affection such as tenderness, sympathy and love, all in one package.
The kind of anime which leaves you with a warm feeling inside and you can not stop smiling while watching it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4570" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-07">
<name>watercolour style</name>
<description>A watercolour or aquarelle is a painting method in which the paints are made of pigments suspended in a water-based solution. Some anime are created in the style of watercolour paintings, the watercolour style, usually with faded pastels that often give the show a warm and friendly visual presentation. In modern anime, this is generally achieved via computer effects that create an imitation of watercolour, rather than by creating real-life watercolour art. While the watercolour style is more commonly used for backgrounds, it is possible to create the entire anime in such a style.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5515" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>faceless background characters</name>
<description>Unimportant random/extra characters that appear mostly as part of the background are often drawn without much facial details, normally to save money, effort and manpower for more important parts of the show. Sometimes, they have almost or no facial details, meaning their heads only have indications of the presence of parts such as hair or mouth, or not even that. This can go as far as only drawing an abstracted silhouette of the whole body.</description>
<picurl>233515.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5872" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-14">
<name>bad luck</name>
<description>You are living a blessed life far from any troubles. Your sister is a famous reporter, you have a good looking girlfriend and you excel in your studies aiming to be a scientist. Your future is looking bright. But reality is, fate hates you. Your sister is killed, your girlfriend breaks up with you after being crippled in a terrorist attack and finally you end up as a pizza delivery boy.
And just when you thought it can`t get worse, it does. Your former girlfriend turns into a Darth Vader knock-off, tries to impose her world view on others by force and is out there to kill you. Yes, your life does truly suck.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5900" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-13">
<name>casino</name>
<description>A casino is a facility that houses and accommodates certain types of gambling activities. Casinos are most commonly built near or combined with hotels, restaurants, retail shopping, cruise ships and other tourist attractions. Some casinos are known for hosting live entertainment events, such as stand-up comedy, concerts, and sporting events. (Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6186" parentid="6185" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-29">
<name>spring</name>
<description>During spring, the axis of the Earth is increasing its tilt relative to the Sun, and the length of daylight rapidly increases for the relevant hemisphere. The hemisphere begins to warm significantly causing new plant growth to spring forth, giving the season its name. Snow, if a normal part of winter, begins to melt, and streams swell with runoff. Frosts, if a normal part of winter, become less severe. In climates that have no snow and rare frosts, the air and ground temperatures increase more rapidly. Many flowering plants bloom this time of year, in a long succession sometimes beginning when snow is still on the ground, continuing into early summer. In normally snowless areas spring may begin as early as February (Northern Hemisphere) heralded by the blooming of deciduous magnolias, cherries and quince, or August (Southern Hemisphere) in the same way. Many temperate areas have a dry spring, and wet autumn (fall), which brings about flowering in this season more consistent with the need for water as well as warmth. Subarctic areas may not experience spring at all until May or even June.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>161969.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6243" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-29">
<name>money</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7146" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-14">
<name>cute girls doing cute things</name>
<description>Cute girls doing cute things with each other (CGDCT): when girls are super friendly with each other and do all sorts of http://anidb.net/t798 [cute/moe] things with each other, but there is no yuri or shoujo ai subtext -- more specifically, there is no romantic subtext.

* CGDCT applies where the main focus is on moe/cute girls and their interactions with each other. Good examples include http://anidb.net/a9722 [Non Non Biyori] (600 weight / 3.0 stars) and http://anidb.net/a9579 [Kin`iro Mosaic] (600 weight / 3.0 stars).
* Generally, CGDCT is applicable only if the anime is also tagged predominantly female cast or all female cast.
* CGDCT does not apply if girls doing cute things is incidental to a larger motive/theme/meta. For example, in http://anidb.net/a8168 [Nichijou] the focus is comedy, using cute girls; the tag would not apply.

CGDCT is often mistaken as low level yuri or shoujo ai. If there is also actual romantic subtext, use the http://anidb.net/t2695 [yuri (18+)] and http://anidb.net/t2782 [shoujo ai] tags as well. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>223153.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="78938" type="main character in" update="2016-09-19">
<rating votes="12">4.99</rating>
<name>Kumegawa Botan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>180720.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27357" picture="75009.jpg">Yasuno Kiyono</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="78939" type="main character in" update="2016-09-19">
<rating votes="12">5.05</rating>
<name>Ekoda Ren</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>180722.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38299" picture="222837.jpg">Yoshioka Mayu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="78940" type="main character in" update="2016-09-19">
<rating votes="16">6.77</rating>
<name>Hanakoizumi An</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>180718.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38634" picture="144425.jpg">Hanamori Yumiri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="78941" type="main character in" update="2016-09-19">
<rating votes="14">5.70</rating>
<name>Hagyuu Hibiki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>180721.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17149" picture="174125.jpg">Yamamura Hibiku</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="78942" type="main character in" update="2016-09-19">
<rating votes="19">6.25</rating>
<name>Hibarigaoka Ruri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>180719.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33578" picture="225440.jpg">Shiraishi Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80431" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-19">
<rating votes="5">1.96</rating>
<name>Timothy</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>191445.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40739" picture="186144.jpg">Morinaga Chitose</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80432" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-19">
<rating votes="11">3.05</rating>
<name>Kodaira-sensei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>191443.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23483" picture="85663.jpg">Hara Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84889" type="appears in" update="2016-09-19">
<name>Hoikushi 1</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>191453.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38296" picture="228671.jpg">Aoyama Yoshino</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84890" type="appears in" update="2016-09-19">
<name>Hoikushi 2</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>191452.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10384" picture="188515.jpg">Takahashi Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84891" type="appears in" update="2016-09-19">
<name>Ume Baa-san</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>191447.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="600" picture="148972.jpg">Arai Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84892" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-09-19">
<name>Sayama Tsubaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>191455.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40739" picture="186144.jpg">Morinaga Chitose</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84893" type="appears in" update="2016-09-19">
<name>Ren no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>191449.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36498" picture="223591.jpg">Kaiden Michiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84894" type="appears in" update="2016-09-19">
<name>Kainushi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>191446.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43444" picture="186203.jpg">Noguchi Ruriko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84895" type="appears in" update="2016-09-19">
<rating votes="1">4.17</rating>
<name>Saginomiya-sensei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>191454.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="51" picture="39247.jpg">Koshimizu Ami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84896" type="appears in" update="2016-09-19">
<name>Hanakoizumi Sakura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>191444.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2228" picture="21776.jpg">Gibu Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84897" type="appears in" update="2016-09-19">
<name>Hibiki no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>191448.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2228" picture="21776.jpg">Gibu Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84898" type="appears in" update="2016-09-19">
<rating votes="1">7.45</rating>
<name>Hagyuu Hibiki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>191450.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17149" picture="174125.jpg">Yamamura Hibiku</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84899" type="appears in" update="2016-09-19">
<rating votes="1">7.45</rating>
<name>Ekoda Ren</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>191451.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38299" picture="222837.jpg">Yoshioka Mayu</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="176243" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-04-28</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">4月29日 ナゾナゾな罰ゲーム</title>
<title xml:lang="en">April 29: A Mysterious Penalty</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">29 avril, un mystérieux gage</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">4-gatsu 29-nichi: Nazonazo na Batsu Game</title>
<summary>After losing the dice game that was part of happiness training, the girls are assigned to take pictures of their "lucky items" as homework. Hanako, Hibari, and Botan try to get together over the weekend to finish their assignment, but from the moment they meet, they experiencec misfortune after misfortune. For some reason Hibiki seems strangely competitive, and a sleepy-looking Ren begins following them as welll...
Will the girls be able to complete their homework?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>702667</identifier>
<identifier>anne-happy</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="176244" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-04-21</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">4月28日 はじめての幸福実技</title>
<title xml:lang="en">April 28: My First Happiness Training</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">28 avril, bonheur, travaux pratiques, première séance</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">4-gatsu 28-nichi: Hajimete no Koufuku Jitsugi</title>
<summary>Today`s lesson for class 1-7 of Tennomifune Academy is a dice game?!
Hanako, Hbari, and Botan form a team and set out for the finish line, but at this rate they`ll finish last. Meanwhile, their competitive classmate Hagyu Hibiki is determined to win as she drags along her childhood friend Ekoda Ren with her.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>702665</identifier>
<identifier>anne-happy</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="176245" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-04-14</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">4月11日 ハイテクな身体測定</title>
<title xml:lang="en">April 11: The High-Tech Physical Exam</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">11 avril, un examen médical high-tech</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">4-gatsu 11-nichi: High-Tech na Shintai Sokutei</title>
<summary>It`s been a week since the entrance ceremony.
In class 1-7, the students` misfortune shines through in interviews and physical exams, causing quite the uproar.
After school, Hanako, Hibari, and Botan go on a tour of the school`s clubs with academy guide robot Timothy to find one right for themselves...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>702663</identifier>
<identifier>anne-happy</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="176246" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-04-07</airdate>
<rating votes="8">4.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">四月七日 不幸な入学初日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">April 7: An Unfortunate First Day of School</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">7 avril, jour de rentrée des pas de chance</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shigatsu Nanoka: Fukou na Nyuugaku Shonichi</title>
<summary>On the day of the Tennomifune Academy entrance ceremony, in the class 1-7 classroom, Hanakoizumi Anne (Hanako), Hibarigaoka Ruri (Hibar), and Kumegawa Botan (Botan) are told by their homeroom teacher Kodaira-sensei that they are unfortunate and unhappy students.
The goal of the students of class 1-7, who are burdened by a variety of forms of misfortune, is to become happy.
The three girls have trouble accepting their circumstances, but they`re immediately given an unexpected assignment...!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>702661</identifier>
<identifier>anne-happy</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="176772" update="2016-04-07">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-04-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="176773" update="2016-04-07">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-04-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="177119" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-05-26</airdate>
<rating votes="6">2.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">7月11日 戦う期末試験</title>
<title xml:lang="en">July 11: Fighting Final Exams</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">11 juillet, une fin de trimestre très mouvementée</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">7-gatsu 11-nichi: Tatakau Kimatsushiken</title>
<summary>After finishing their final exams in the basic subjects, the girls are only allowed a moment`s relief before being told they`re taking a "special happiness test!" Even farther underground the gym`s basement facility they once visited, the girls are subjected to a virtual exam!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>702675</identifier>
<identifier>anne-happy</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="177120" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-05-19</airdate>
<rating votes="5">3.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">6月28日 はなこのお見舞い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">June 28: Visiting Hanako</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">28 juin, visite à Hanako</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">6-gatsu 28-nichi: Hanako no Omimai</title>
<summary>Hanako gets a fever and leaves class early. Hibari and Botan go to visit her at home with gifts and the day`s homework. When Hanako misses school the next day, the four girls of class 7 begin creating something that makes wishes come true...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>702673</identifier>
<identifier>anne-happy</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="177121" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-05-12</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">5月30日 みんなで遠足</title>
<title xml:lang="en">May 30: A Field Trip with Everyone</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">30 mai, la course d`orientation</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">5-gatsu 30-nichi: Minna de Ensoku</title>
<summary>The subject of today`s happiness training is "Good Luck Orienteering!"
Lead by the assistant Timothy, Hanako and her friends arrive at a mountain near school.
While experiencing typical levels of misfortune, the girls have a picnic, and Hibari realizes the true meaning of the happiness training.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>702671</identifier>
<identifier>anne-happy</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="177122" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-05-05</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">5月9日 迷子の登校風景</title>
<title xml:lang="en">May 9: Getting Lost on the Way to School</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">9 mai, jour de classe d`une fille perdue</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">5-gatsu Kokonoka: Maigo no Toukou Fuukei</title>
<summary>Hibiki gets lost when she`s forced to walk to school alone. While angrily thinking about how Ren refuses to accompany her, she begins reminscing about how they first met and became friends...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>702669</identifier>
<identifier>anne-happy</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="177502" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-06-23</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">8月19日 幸せな林間学校</title>
<title xml:lang="en">August 19: A Happy Outdoor School</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">19 août, une classe de montagne heureuse</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">8-gatsu 19-nichi: Shiawase na Rinkangakkou</title>
<summary>A game of Miniature Garden Tag abruptly begins at the outdoor school.
Will Hanako, Hibari, Botan, Hibiki, and Ren of "Team Four Leaf Clover" be able to find the wooden statues they carved and safely make it to the end of the game?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>702683</identifier>
<identifier>anne-happy</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="177503" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-06-16</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">8月18日 嵐の林間学校</title>
<title xml:lang="en">August 18: A Stormy Outdoor School</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">18 août, une classe de montagne dans la tourmente</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">8-gatsu 18-nichi: Arashi no Rinkangakkou</title>
<summary>Outdoor School is the big event of the summer! At first glance, it seems like an ordinary overnight trip, but the girls find themselves confronted by another "happiness training." When a game of "Miniature Garden Tag" suddenly begins, Hanako and her friends are attacked by a giant Timothy!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>702681</identifier>
<identifier>anne-happy</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="177504" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-06-09</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">7月20日~ 私たちの夏休み</title>
<title xml:lang="en">July 20: Our Summer Vacation</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">20 juillet, nos vacances d`été</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">7-gatsu Hatsuka: Watashitachi no Natsuyasumi</title>
<summary>Summer vacation has finally begun. Botan records the fun days she is having with her friends from class 7 in her journal. Going to karaoke on the way home from school, swimming at the beach by the Kumegawa villa... As they describe their summers filled with "happiness," she smiles.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>702679</identifier>
<identifier>anne-happy</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="177505" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-06-02</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">7月13日 波乱の合同授業</title>
<title xml:lang="en">July 13: A Stormy Group Lesson</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">13 juillet, un cours en commun du tonnerre</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">7-gatsu 13-nichi: Haran no Goudou Jugyou</title>
<summary>Class 7 has its first joint lesson with another class. Washinomiya-sensei, the other class` homeroom teacher teaching the cooking lesson, accuses Hibari and her friends of lacking awareness. Refusing to allow her comment to discourage them, the girls continue with the class, but...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>702677</identifier>
<identifier>anne-happy</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="209165" update="2018-10-13">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2016-06-23</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 12 Ending</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
