<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="11601" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2016-01-08</startdate>
<enddate>2016-04-01</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Dagashi Kashi</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Магазинчик сладостей</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">だがしかし</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Dagashi Kashi</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">다가시카시</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">粗点心战争</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="13355" type="Sequel">Dagashi Kashi 2</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="13053" approval="8" total="11">Ramen Daisuki Koizumi-san</anime>
<anime id="13376" approval="7" total="14">Takunomi.</anime>
<anime id="9722" approval="1" total="14">Non Non Biyori</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="510875">The show has some rather fun moments and it`s full of candy knowledge. If you never tried Japanese candy, or you have but don`t know the origins of some of them, then this anime will teach you the origins in a fun, enjoyable and humorous manner.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.tbs.co.jp/anime/dagashi/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1006" type="Animation Work">Feel</name>
<name id="7012" type="Series Composition">Takayanagi Shigehito</name>
<name id="43813" type="Original Work">Kotoyama</name>
<name id="9387" type="Character Design">Kamimoto Kanetoshi</name>
<name id="35599" type="Series Composition">Kamo Yasuko</name>
<name id="23377" type="Music">Oosumi Tomotaka</name>
<name id="40986" type="Music">Nobusawa Nobuaki</name>
<name id="7012" type="Direction">Takayanagi Shigehito</name>
<name id="9387" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kamimoto Kanetoshi</name>
<name id="8546" type="Chief Animation Direction">Masuda Kuniaki</name>
<name id="10932" type="Chief Animation Direction">Yamazaki Masakazu</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a manga by http://anidb.net/cr43813 [Kotoyama] serialized in http://anidb.net/cr23232 [Shuukan Shounen Sunday].
http://anidb.net/ch78088 [Shikada You] owns a rural sweets shop, and his plan is for his son http://anidb.net/ch78085 [Kokonotsu] to take it over one day, but Kokonotsu wants to be a manga author instead. One day, the heir to the well-known sweets maker Shidare Company, the cute but weird http://anidb.net/ch78084 [Shidare Hotaru], pays them a visit. Apparently, You is famous, and she wants him to join her father`s company, but he will agree only if she can convince Kokonotsu to inherit the shop and continue the family business.
Source: MU</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1882">4.13</permanent>
<temporary count="1890">6.26</temporary>
<review count="1">4.83</review>
</ratings>
<picture>225156.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>17723</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>31636</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tbs.co.jp/anime/dagashi/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Dagashi_Kashi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>だがしかし</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4030</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>354179</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18781</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B01GEZ1IBO</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="627" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-15">
<name>lingerie</name>
<description>Lingerie is a term for fashionable and alluring women`s undergarments.</description>
<picurl>238327.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1157" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>horny nosebleed</name>
<description>In Japanese media, healthy young men who have no other sexual outlet will often suffer nosebleeds upon seeing the naked female body, or even just a pair of well-filled panties.
The nosebleed is, of course, a visual shorthand/euphemism for sexual arousal. It is commonly interpreted that way for males and females, with little trickles of blood indicating mild arousal, and gushing fountains of blood indicating erection/extreme arousal in both sexes. It can also be interpreted as shorthand strictly for erections in males. In that case, when blood shoots from the nose explosively, and in ridiculous quantity, the implication would be an ejaculation.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>233513.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2634" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>countryside</name>
<description>The anime takes place far from the any densely populated areas like cities, i.e. out in the suburbs, in the countryside with many fields and forests.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3305" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-05-14">
<name>light-hearted</name>
<description>Not being burdened by trouble, worry, or care; happy and carefree.
Just a casual and feel-good watch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3792" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-06">
<name>iyashi-kei</name>
<description>A feel good, "no true conflict within story" type of plot, instead about the daily musings and activities of the characters with an overall tranquil mood. Similar to "Slice of Life", but much more relaxed, peaceful and "zen".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4570" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-07">
<name>watercolour style</name>
<description>A watercolour or aquarelle is a painting method in which the paints are made of pigments suspended in a water-based solution. Some anime are created in the style of watercolour paintings, the watercolour style, usually with faded pastels that often give the show a warm and friendly visual presentation. In modern anime, this is generally achieved via computer effects that create an imitation of watercolour, rather than by creating real-life watercolour art. While the watercolour style is more commonly used for backgrounds, it is possible to create the entire anime in such a style.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4576" parentid="6185" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-03">
<name>summer</name>
<description>At least one of the episodes takes place in summer. Think oppressively warm weather, summer vacation, summer school, summer festival, or a visit to the beach.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5276" parentid="2874" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-25">
<name>typhoon</name>
<description>A typhoon is a mature tropical cyclone that develops in the north-western part of the Pacific Ocean between 180° and 100°E. This region is referred to as the north-west Pacific basin. Identical phenomena in the eastern north Pacific are called hurricanes, with tropical cyclones moving into the western Pacific re-designated as typhoons.
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5518" parentid="7199" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-03">
<name>flat chest jokes</name>
<description>Jokes about the (supposedly or actually) flat chest of a character.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5626" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>adults are useless</name>
<description>For when adults can`t do anything right.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5790" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-30">
<name>family without mother</name>
<description>For some reason, the protagonist`s mother is no longer among the living. The much-too-early death was due to sickness or accident.
This plot device adds a certain degree of tragedy to the anime, and usually has repercussions on the rest of the family. For example: the grief-stricken father and children barely function as humans; the oldest daughter has an extra burden of raising the other children, additional emphasis is given to the only female child in the family, i.e. with bishounen brother and dad in a shoujo setting.
In rare cases the mother may still be alive, just not living with the rest of the family presently, i.e. on some quest or job and gone for a long time.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5916" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-26">
<name>product placement</name>
<description>Otherwise known as a "plug" or "writing commercials right into a show". The practice of prominently displaying or talking about a recognizable product in a program, in exchange for some consideration from the manufacturer, usually monetary. (Source: TV Tropes)
Particularly notorious example, Pizza Hut for the involvement with Code Geass, Darker than Black and other series.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6029" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-04-08">
<name>mundane made awesome</name>
<description>Sometimes normal just doesn`t cut it. Eating: you put food in your mouth and chew. Playing sports: you throw a ball around. You need to make it awesome, no matter how mundane it is.
Let`s throw in some gripping orchestral music, lighting changes, different camera angles, something! Don`t write like a man, write like an evil overlord! Exaggerate your expressions and gestures, speak with excessive intonation, and if all else fails, throw in some close-ups, slow motion, and ominous Latin chanting! With practice, even you can turn something like eating chips into an epic battle of light and dark, blinding the viewer with sheer awesomeness.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>149443.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6442" parentid="2798" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-09">
<name>Weekly Shounen Sunday</name>
<description>Weekly Shounen Sunday is a weekly shounen manga magazine published in Japan by Shogakukan since 1959. Contrary to its title, Weekly Shounen Sunday issues are released on Wednesdays.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>175276.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7199" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-12">
<name>sexual humour</name>
<description>Sexual humour is prevalent in this anime. It often involves cheeky or crude sexual language, with innuendos and jokes about the female or male genitalia. Often, such anime also have http://anidb.net/t2856 [ecchi] elements to them.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="78084" type="main character in" update="2018-06-21">
<rating votes="91">8.22</rating>
<name>Shidare Hotaru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>219414.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="590" picture="242467.jpg">Taketatsu Ayana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="78085" type="main character in" update="2018-06-21">
<rating votes="30">3.95</rating>
<name>Shikada Kokonotsu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>219415.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="545" picture="188506.jpg">Abe Atsushi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="78086" type="main character in" update="2018-06-21">
<rating votes="102">8.44</rating>
<name>Endou Saya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>219416.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17069" picture="80944.jpg">Numakura Manami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="78087" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-06-21">
<rating votes="26">3.98</rating>
<name>Endou Tou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>219417.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="644" picture="205640.jpg">Suzuki Tatsuhisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="78088" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-06-21">
<rating votes="25">3.41</rating>
<name>Shikada You</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>219418.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="168" picture="246304.jpg">Fujiwara Keiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80581" type="appears in" update="2016-02-26">
<rating votes="6">3.29</rating>
<name>Tamai Tamako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>183489.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43378" picture="175210.jpg">Hara Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="80582" type="appears in" update="2016-02-26">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Katanuki-ya no Shujin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>183490.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="289" picture="186204.jpg">Nishimura Tomomichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81190" type="appears in" update="2016-03-25">
<name>Perry</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>184520.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45" picture="44970.jpg">Sugita Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81191" type="appears in" update="2016-03-25">
<name>Yakunin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>184521.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3186" picture="171957.jpg">Tone Kentarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81436" type="appears in" update="2016-04-01">
<name>Fukuzawa Yukichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>184985.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="168" picture="246304.jpg">Fujiwara Keiji</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="174089" update="2015-12-26">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-01-29</airdate>
<rating votes="9">4.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ふがしとふがしと... / グリコとグリコと...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fugashi, Fugashi, And... / Glico, Glico, And...</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Gâteaux au gluten / Caramels Glico</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">후가시와 후가시와... / 글리코와 글리코와...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fugashi to Fugashi to... / Glico to Glico to...</title>
</episode>
<episode id="174090" update="2015-12-26">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-01-22</airdate>
<rating votes="11">3.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ブタメンとくるくるぼーゼリーと... / ボンタンアメとセブンネオンと...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Buta-men, Kuru Kuru Bou Jelly, And... / Bontan-ame, Seven Neon, And...</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Butamen et vis en pâte de fruits / Bonbons au pamplemousse et Seven Neon</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">부타멘과 쿠루쿠루보 젤리와... / 보탄아메와 세븐네온과...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Butamen to Kurukuru Bou Jelly to... / Bontan`ame to Seven Neon to...</title>
</episode>
<episode id="174091" update="2015-12-26">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-01-15</airdate>
<rating votes="17">2.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">きなこ棒と生いきビールと... / フエラムネとめんこと...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kinako-bou, Namaiki Beer, And... / Fue Ramune, Menko, And...</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Kinako-bô et Mousse / Ramune-Flûtes et cartes Menko</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">키나코봉과 나마이키 맥주와... / 후에 라무네와 멘코와...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kinako Bou to Nama Iki Beer to... / Fue Ramune to Menko to...</title>
</episode>
<episode id="174092" update="2015-12-26">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-01-08</airdate>
<rating votes="20">5.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">うまい棒とポテフと... / コーヒー牛乳キャンディとヤングドーナツと...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Umai-bou, Fries, And... / Milk Coffee Candies, Young Donuts, And...</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Bâton des Délices et Potato Fry / Bonbon au café au lait et Young Doughnuts</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">우마이봉과 포테프와... / 커피우유캔디와 영도나츠와...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Umaibou to Potefu to... / Coffee Gyuunyuu Candy to Young Doughnut to...</title>
</episode>
<episode id="174330" update="2016-11-23">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-01-08</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="174331" update="2016-11-23">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-01-08</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="174666" update="2016-02-07">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-03-04</airdate>
<rating votes="8">4.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">超怖い話ガムと台風と... / けん玉とプチプチ占いチョコと...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Super Scary Story Gum, Typhoon, And... / Kendama, Popping Fortune-Telling Chocolate, And...</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le chewing-gum kifépeur et la tempête / Des bilboquets et des Petits-Petits Chocoroscopes</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">엄청 무서운 이야기 껌과 태풍과... / 켄다마와 톡톡 운수쵸코와</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chou Kowai Hanashi Gum to Taifuu to... / Kendama to Puchipuchi Uranai Choco to...</title>
</episode>
<episode id="174667" update="2016-02-07">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-02-26</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夏祭りとほたると... / 夏祭りとサヤと...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Summer Festival, Hotaru, And... / Summer Festival, Saya, And...</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La fête de l`été, et Hotaru / La fête de l`été et Saya</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">여름 축제와 호타루와... / 여름축제와 사야와...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Natsumatsuri to Hotaru to... / Natsumatsuri to Saya to...</title>
</episode>
<episode id="174668" update="2016-02-07">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-02-19</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">超ひもQとおはじきとときどきまけんグミ... / ヨーグレットとココナツと...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Super Himo Q, Ohajiki, and Sometimes Maken Gumi... / Yoguret, Coconuts, And...</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Super Lacets Q, Billes Plates et Maken Gummi / Des Yoglets et Coconuts</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">초히모Q와 구슬치기와 때때로 마켄구미... / 요구렛과 코코넛과...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chou Himo Q to Obajiki to Tokidoki Maken Gumi... / Yogurette to Coconuts to...</title>
</episode>
<episode id="174669" update="2016-02-06">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-02-05</airdate>
<rating votes="8">4.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ビンラムネとベビースターラーメンと... / ヤッターめんとすっぱいぶどうにご用心!と...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bottle Ramune, Baby-Star Ramen, And... / Yatta Men, Watch Out for the Sour Grape, And...</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Bouteilles Ramune et Baby Star Ramen / Yattamen et Raisins Acides</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">병 라무네와 베이비스타 라면과... / 얏타멘과 새콤 포도에 주의! 와...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bin Ramune to Baby Star Ramen to... / Yattamen to Suppai Budou ni Goyoushin! To...</title>
</episode>
<episode id="175753" update="2016-02-27">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-04-01</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">食べるんですHiとさくらんぼの詩と... / 森永ミルクキャラメルとサクマ式ドロップスと...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`m Gonna Eat It-Hi, Poem of Cherries, And... / Morinaga Milk Caramel, Sakuma Drops, And...</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Des "Je mange, Hi" et des Poèmes de Cerises / Des caramels au lait de Morinaga et des Gouttes de Sakuma</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">먹을래요! Hi와 버찌의 노래와... / 모리나가 밀크 캐러멜과 사쿠마시키 드롭스와...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Taberundesu Hi to Sakuranbo no Uta to... / Morinaga Milk Caramel to Sakuma Drops to...</title>
</episode>
<episode id="175754" update="2016-02-27">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-03-25</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">コーラガムとヨウと... / 都こんぶとラムネと...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cola Gum, Yo, And... / Miyako Kombu, Ramune, And...</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les Chewing-Gums Cola et Yô / Des algues Miyako et du Ramune</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">콜라껌과 요우와... / 미야코 다시마와 라무네와...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Cola Gum to You to... / Miyako Konbu to Ramune to...</title>
</episode>
<episode id="175755" update="2016-02-27">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-03-18</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">駄菓子じゃねえか!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">That`s Dagashi!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">C`est des bonbons, quoi !</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">막과자잖아!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dagashi ja Neeka!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="175756" update="2016-02-27">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2016-03-11</airdate>
<rating votes="8">3.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">わたパチとうんチョコと... / さくら大根とたまごアイスと...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wata-pachi, Lucky Choco-Droppings, And... / Sakura Daikon, Egg Ice Cream, And...</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Des Cotons Pops et des Chocrottes / Un Radis Cerise et des Œufs de Glace</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">와타파치와 응가초콜릿과... / 벚꽃무와 계란아이스와...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Wada Pachi to Un Choco to... / Sakura Daikon to Tamago Ice to...</title>
</episode>
<episode id="182513" update="2016-11-23">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-01-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1c</title>
</episode>
<episode id="182514" update="2016-11-23">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-01-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="182515" update="2016-11-23">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-01-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1c</title>
</episode>
<episode id="182516" update="2016-11-23">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-01-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1b</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
