<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="11822" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2017-04-07</startdate>
<enddate>2017-06-23</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Ren`ai Boukun</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">The very lovely tyrant of love ♥</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Renai Boukun</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">恋愛暴君</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Love Tyrant</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Love Tyrant</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">연애폭군</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">恋爱暴君</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="2820" approval="11" total="13">Bokusatsu Tenshi Dokuro-chan</anime>
<anime id="4563" approval="3" total="11">Death Note</anime>
</similaranime>
<url>http://renaiboukun.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="48084" type="Original Work">Mihoshi Megane</name>
<name id="43522" type="Animation Work">EMT Squared</name>
<name id="11283" type="Character Design">Itou Mariko</name>
<name id="1465" type="Series Composition">Takahashi Natsuko</name>
<name id="19341" type="Direction">Nigorikawa Atsushi</name>
<name id="15955" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kitamura Jun`ichi</name>
<name id="6577" type="Chief Animation Direction">Yatsu Miyako</name>
<name id="3020" type="Music">Monaca</name>
</creators>
<description>A Kiss Note is a powerful notebook that makes anyone who have their names written together instantly fall in love if they kiss each other. This magical item belongs to an angel named Guri whose job as cupid is to create couples. However, she accidentally writes down Aino Seiji, a regular high school student, and unless he kisses someone in the course of 24 hours, Guri will die, and Seiji will remain a virgin for the rest of his life.
Eventually, Guri convinces Seiji to kiss his crush, Hiyama Akane, the school`s popular girl who turns out to be a http://anidb.net/t1208 [yandere], with her feelings for Seiji bordering on obsessive and psychotic. To make the matters worse, after Akane and Seiji become a couple, Guri decides that she likes Seiji as well. Now, what seems awesome to most guys becomes hell for Seiji who just wants a normal relationship with a girl.
Source: MangaHelpers</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1194">3.84</permanent>
<temporary count="1198">6.12</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>198211.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18906</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>32262</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://renaiboukun.com/</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tv-tokyo.co.jp/anime/renaiboukun/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Ren'ai_Bōkun</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>恋愛暴君</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4505</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>359036</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20094</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>boukun_PR</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>love-tyrant</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B07SPC88PB</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2346" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-09-14">
<name>angel</name>
<description>An angel is a supernatural being, said to be the messenger of God. They are often depicted as human beings with a pair of white feathered wings and sometimes with a halo.
In contrast, a fallen angel who has turned evil will be depicted with black wings.</description>
<picurl>35521.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2632" parentid="6563" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>hell</name>
<description>"Abandon hope all ye who enter here"
You been a sinner? Welcome to Hell, where you will suffer for all eternity for your sins. The devils with pitchforks will take good care of you there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2770" parentid="2653" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>violent retribution for accidental infringement</name>
<description>A comedy / slapstick element often found in Ecchi anime: The hilarity derives from spontaneous embarrassment, overreaction of the "victim" (girl), immediate retribution for a seemingly inappropriate act, and a sense of pity with the supposed "aggressor" (boy).
Typically a boy will - through no fault of his own - stumble into a girl, thus invading her personal space. In the process the boy may e.g. pull down her skirt, grab the girl`s breasts, or accidentally kiss her. Any level-headed girl would see the accident just for what it is. Not so the girl with an overly developed sense of modesty, and a thing for violence. She - often a tsundere - will clobber the boy with excessive brutality.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2783" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>shounen ai</name>
<description>Shounen Ai means boys love, and thus explores what happens when two boys (or men) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2723 [Yaoi] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphical sex.
The female version is http://anidb.net/t2782 [Shoujo Ai].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2793" parentid="2883" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>performance</name>
<description>The song performance on stage or acting in a theatre is a central part of the character`s life in this anime type.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2822" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-06">
<name>skirt flipping</name>
<description>Naughty characters — usually boys — flip the skirts of female protagonists to ascertain what panties they are wearing (also see Pantsu category).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2851" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>horror</name>
<description>The horror cinematic genre is characterized by the attempt to make the viewer experience dread, fear, terror, or horror. Often their plots involve the intrusion of an evil force, event or personage, sometimes of supernatural origin, on the mundane world and the consequences thereof.</description>
<picurl>214682.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4055" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-10-12">
<name>facial distortion</name>
<description>The characters face are exaggerated into a misshape, deformed, and almost warped. Used as comedy element to express extreme mood swings.
Differing from "http://anidb.net/t2652 [super deformed]", here only the face changes to an extreme degree, not the whole body of the protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4083" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-04">
<name>drastic change of life</name>
<description>One or more characters in this series go through an event that makes them change their way of life drastically and permanently. This change might be voluntary, or against the character`s will.
Some examples might be an accident, the gaining of superpowers, or simply graduating.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4413" parentid="6563" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-16">
<name>heaven</name>
<description>Heaven, the Heavens or Seven Heavens, is a common religious, cosmological or transcendent place from which heavenly beings (such as a God, angels, the jinn, and sky deities like King or Queen of Heaven, Heavenly Father, Heavenly Mother, Son of Heaven, heavenly saints or venerated ancestors) originate, are enthroned or inhabit.
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4440" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>boy meets girl</name>
<description>A classical type of plot in story writing, where the story begins with a boy meeting a girl leading to romantic development between the two. More often than not the boy loses the girl later on and has to find her again.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5794" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-04-01">
<name>forbidden love</name>
<description>This anime contains characters pursuing a romantic interest that their parents, grandparents, the police, the fire department, the neighbourhood watch association and local politicians do not approve of.
Potential relationships defined as such may be ones that are incestuous, violations of caste systems, or socially unsanctioned.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6030" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-22">
<name>otaku culture</name>
<description>Otaku (おたく/オタク) is a Japanese term used to refer to people with obsessive interests, particularly anime, manga, and video games. A female otaku is occasionally referred to as a fujoshi. (Source: Wikipedia)
Here certain aspects of this "fandom" are presented in more detail, e.g. the creation of doujinshi (self-published amateur manga).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6088" parentid="2785" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-01-29">
<name>unrequited shoujo ai</name>
<description>At least one female character has a romantic or sexual interest in another female character, but the feelings are not returned.
This can be because the recipient is oblivious, straight, or simply not interested.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6349" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-13">
<name>multi-segment episodes</name>
<description>Multi-segment episodes are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t5852 [short episodes], which are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length (up to and including 10 minutes).
Also not to be confused with an OVA or music video with multiple (otherwise unrelated) full-length http://anidb.net/t7241 [bundled episodes] consolidated into a single episode video track.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6563" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-23">
<name>spirit realm</name>
<description>A spirit realm is a place where inhabited by the spirits of the dead, deities, demons, and other such entities. Examples would be Heaven and Hell in Christianity, the Elysium in Greek mythology, and so on.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6730" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-11">
<name>torture</name>
<description>Torture involves the deliberate act of inflicting pain, to either fulfill a desire of the torturer, or apply coercion to compel action from the victim. Torture, by definition, is a knowing and intentional act; deeds which unknowingly or negligently inflict pain without a specific intent to do so are not typically considered torture.
This is distinct from http://anidb.net/t2905 [erotic torture], which is generally for the purpose of using (almost) any form of physical or excessive psychological abuse to inflict physical and/or mental pain, with the goal of inducing sexual pleasure.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="87708" type="main character in" update="2017-02-18">
<rating votes="21">4.97</rating>
<name>Guri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>198391.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38296" picture="228671.jpg">Aoyama Yoshino</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="87709" type="main character in" update="2017-02-18">
<rating votes="25">3.08</rating>
<name>Shiramine Shikimi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>198395.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23483" picture="85663.jpg">Hara Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="87710" type="main character in" update="2017-02-18">
<rating votes="36">7.08</rating>
<name>Hiyama Akane</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>198393.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17069" picture="80944.jpg">Numakura Manami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="87711" type="main character in" update="2017-02-18">
<rating votes="8">3.31</rating>
<name>Aino Seiji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>198392.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4755" picture="183070.jpg">Ono Kenshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="87712" type="main character in" update="2017-02-18">
<rating votes="19">5.51</rating>
<name>Kichougasaki Yuzu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>198394.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="48909" picture="223240.jpg">Nagano Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88205" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-03-14">
<rating votes="5">3.46</rating>
<name>Coraly</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199622.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="73" picture="58662.jpg">Hiyama Nobuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88206" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-03-14">
<rating votes="6">3.71</rating>
<name>Stolas</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199626.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2037" picture="244859.jpg">Horiuchi Ken`yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88207" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-03-14">
<rating votes="5">2.12</rating>
<name>Kamisama</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199623.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="297" picture="233915.jpg">Ootsuka Houchuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88208" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-03-14">
<rating votes="15">4.58</rating>
<name>Aino Akua</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199621.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38380" picture="224406.jpg">Takahashi Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88209" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-03-14">
<rating votes="4">2.33</rating>
<name>Maou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199624.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88210" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-03-14">
<rating votes="1">4.18</rating>
<name>Tsuruoka Tarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199625.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10130" picture="151714.jpg">Takumi Yasuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89809" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-06-06">
<rating votes="10">4.83</rating>
<name>Shiina Mari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203620.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27218" picture="223318.jpg">Ootsubo Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89810" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-06-06">
<rating votes="5">3.46</rating>
<name>Kusunoki Nagito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203621.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1680" picture="132752.jpg">Tachibana Shinnosuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89811" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-06-06">
<rating votes="6">5.08</rating>
<name>Tiara</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203622.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="401" picture="223216.jpg">Kitamura Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89812" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-06-06">
<rating votes="10">5.25</rating>
<name>Suou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203623.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="74" picture="84835.jpg">Oohara Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89813" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-06-06">
<rating votes="14">5.56</rating>
<name>Ameisha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203624.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="97" picture="222166.jpg">Satou Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90820" type="appears in" update="2017-08-06">
<name>Mavuro</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>205856.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="350" picture="20063.jpg">Tamura Yukari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90821" type="appears in" update="2017-08-06">
<name>Guri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>205857.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38296" picture="228671.jpg">Aoyama Yoshino</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="186358" update="2017-05-08">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-04-28</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">絶対負けませんから! × もしかしてお仲間ですか?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`m Not Going to Lose! x Are You Like Me?</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Je ne perdrai pas ! × Serais-tu une camarade ?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zettai Makemasen kara! x Moshikashite Onakama Desuka?</title>
<summary>Yuzu will go to great lengths for her beloved older sister, Akane, even skipping her own lessons 
to watch over her. Despite harsh words from Akane, Yuzu refuses to relinquish her forbidden love even for someone like Seiji, who she may care about more than she realizes. Meanwhile, on the hunt for a new couple to match, fortune smiles upon Seiji and Guri when a classmate approaches them saying she has a crush she would like paired with. The request turns complicated when the classmate, Shikimi, doesn`t seem to know the name of her intended partner. While helping Shikimi find this mystery boy Seiji finds that this meek bespectacled girl is not quite what she appears to be...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>734107</identifier>
<identifier>love-tyrant</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="186359" update="2017-04-22">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-04-21</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">私一人でなんとか出来る! × チョリーッス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Can Handle This Myself! x Wassup</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Je peux me débrouiller seule ! × Yo !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Watashi Hitori de Nantoka Dekiru! x Choriissu</title>
<summary>Guri finally meets Seiji`s younger sister, Akua and is surprised by her rather cold attitude towards her big brother. The cupid decides to learn more about what changed this once loving sister, and Yuzu is right there to help (or make things worse...). But while the girls are getting acquainted the demon Stolas appears and a panick ensues! The strangely psychotic penguin seems to have a special affinity for Akua and sends her running. It`s up to her big brother Seiji to save her like he used to.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>734105</identifier>
<identifier>love-tyrant</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="186360" update="2017-04-22">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-04-14</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">くんすかくんすか × 青司くんを傷つけていいのは... 私だけなの</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sniff Sniff x The Only One Who May Hurt Seiji-kun... Is Me</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Snif, snif × La seule autorisée à toucher à seiji... c`est moi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kunsuka Kunsuka x Seiji-kun o Kizutsukete Ii no wa... Watashi dake na no</title>
<summary>During Yuzu`s daily routine of stalking through her sister, Akane`s trash, Guri suddenly appears and the two girls begin taking love consultations at school. Seiji and Akane reluctantly agree to help look for coupling candidates and soon the group thinks they have found a pair of ideal targets. However, things get much more complicated when no one can agree if the intended couple really share each other`s feelings. In the midst of all this Yuzu and Guri scheme an elaborate plan to prove their instincts are right.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>734103</identifier>
<identifier>love-tyrant</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="186361" update="2017-04-12">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-04-07</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">私も, 参戦します × ほぁー!! 禁断の愛ですか!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`m Getting In on This, Too x Whoa! Forbidden Love?!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Je me suis rajoutée ! × Oh ! Un amour interdit ?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Watashi mo, Sansen Shimasu x Hoa!! Kindan no Ai Desuka!!</title>
<summary>Aino Seiji is your typical male high school student when he meets Guri, who is a shinigami? No, a pervert--no! An angel?! Guri introduces him to the Kiss Note and explains that if he doesn`t kiss someone within 24 hours, she will die. So it`s off to Seiji`s school to find his school crush, his classmate, Hiyama Akane, but of course nothing is ever so simple...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>734101</identifier>
<identifier>love-tyrant</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="186790" update="2017-04-06">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-04-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="186791" update="2017-04-06">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-04-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="187265" update="2017-05-31">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-05-26</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さよなら × 恋敵でしょ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Farewell x We`re Rivals, Obviously!!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Adieu × On est rivales !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sayonara x Koigataki Desho!!</title>
<summary>Yuzu and Guri are off to save Akane! Several obstacles are placed in their path but the girls overcome them with ease, only to find that Akane is not herself. A happy reunion quickly turns to shock as Akane turns her blade on her sister. Yuzu tries desperately to reach her beloved sister but nothing seems to get through. When Seiji finally appears Akane`s love is put to the test, will she do as her mother commands and get rid of Seiji once and for all?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>734115</identifier>
<identifier>love-tyrant</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="187266" update="2017-05-30">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-05-19</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">お祭りじゃーい × どうしてこうなったぁ!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It`s a Festival x How Did It Come to This?!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le festival bat son plein × Pourquoi on en est là ?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Omatsuri jaai x Doushite Kou Nattaa!!</title>
<summary>After an argument with Seiji, Guri goes wandering the city on her own. During a stop at the bookstore for the latest volume from her favorite manga artist, a handsome stranger stops to talk to her. When the unknown young man invites Guri out on a date she can`t bring herself to refuse. Getting to experience a date with someone other than Seiji seemed like a good idea but Guri can`t help be feel something isn`t quite right. Meanwhile, things have gotten more complicated in Akane`s family and she`s suddenly under house-arrest!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>734113</identifier>
<identifier>love-tyrant</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="187267" update="2017-05-16">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-05-12</airdate>
<rating votes="5">4.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">一緒に海に行かないか? × わかるわからないの問題じゃないでしょ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Go to the Beach with Me? x It`s Not a Matter of Knowing or Not</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">On va à la mer ensemble ? × Ce n’est pas quelque chose de rationnel</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Issho ni Umi ni Ikanaika? x Wakaru Wakaranai no Mondai ja Nai Desho</title>
<summary>Summer vacation! Seiji, Guri, Akane and Yuzu have invited Akua to go with them to the beach. Akane tries to get Akua to go swimming with her in attempt to get closer to Seiji`s little sister, but Akua gives her the cold shoulder. Pouting at her brother and his harem Akua goes to swim by herself but a dark shadow looms beneath her. Meanwhile, summer also means tests of courage! Guri suddenly invites Seiji, Akane, and Yuzu to the school after dark for a test of courage but her real motives are to pair another young couple who have asked for her help. Seiji thinks something isn`t quite right about the pair though...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>734111</identifier>
<identifier>love-tyrant</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="187268" update="2017-05-08">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-05-05</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">`愛`って何かにゃー × 神土下座なうww</title>
<title xml:lang="en">What Is Love? x Kami Is Prostrating Himself Now lolol</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">C’est quoi, l’amour ? × Prosternation divine en direct LOL</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">`Ai`tte Nanika Nya x Kami Dogeza nau ww</title>
<summary>In a desperate struggle to find Seiji, Akane and Yuzu seem oddly worried when Guri tells them that he is off with Shikimi searching for her crush. The concern seems warranted when Seiji finds himself in the midst of a torture session with Shikimi. According to this mistress of disguise her ultimate goal isn`t just Seiji, but Akane and Yuzu. What is her link to the two sisters and what is it that she`s after? And just what has Seiji been dragged into this time? Akane fights Shikimi fiercely to keep the truth hidden. Just when everything seems resolved, Seiji has stopped breathing!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>734109</identifier>
<identifier>love-tyrant</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="187846" update="2017-10-07">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-06-23</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">そうだ, 死にましょう! × 私やっとわかりました</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Right, Let`s All Die! x I Finally Understand</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Bonne idée ! Mourez ! × Je l’ai enfin compris</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sou Da, Shinimashou! x Watashi Yatto Wakarimashita</title>
<summary>With some divine intervention, Seiji and Yuzu are off to hell to see if they can return Guri to normal. With Coraly`s help they attempt to disguise themselves as demons but the jig is up when they happen to run into Shikimi as she wanders the streets. As they are chased by the demon police, Akane shows up to makes a half-hearted attempt to return Guri to her senses. When that fails, she attempts to drag Seiji back home. Yuzu finally convinces Seiji to talk to Guri to let prove to her that he does actually care about her but will it be enough? Will the real Guri ever come back?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>734123</identifier>
<identifier>love-tyrant</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="187847" update="2017-10-07">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-06-16</airdate>
<rating votes="6">2.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">どこ行ったんだ あいつ × 今まで大変お世話になりました</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Where Did She Go? x I Apologize for Troubling You Until Now</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Elle est passée où ? × Merci pour tout</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Doko Ittanda Aitsu x Ima made Taihen Osewa ni Narimashita</title>
<summary>Guri has gone missing. Seiji seems unphased while Akane is thrilled but Yuzu is deeply concerned for her friend and begs Seiji to seriously look for Guri. Meanwhile, Shikimi is up to no good and Seiji catches her in the midst of trying to trick Kusunoki-sensei. Seiji drags Shikimi away to save the hapless teacher, but winds up having the tables turned on him when she traps him. A confrontation boils up and Guri finally falls from the sky, literally, to ask Seiji how he truly feels about her.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>734121</identifier>
<identifier>love-tyrant</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="187848" update="2017-06-13">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-06-09</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">お泊まりに来ちゃいました × 私だって... 成長するんだよ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`m Here to Stay the Night x I`m... Growing Up, Too</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Je viens passer la nuit × Moi aussi, j’ai grandi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Otomari ni Kichaimashita x Watashi Datte... Seichou Surunda yo</title>
<summary>As his family takes off for a few days, Seiji finds himself home alone. Well, except for Guri, of course. But the peace of the moment is short-lived when Akane shows up at his door saying she`s there to spend the night while his family is away and to claim the kiss that Seiji had promised her. Things only get more complicated as usual when Yuzu and Shikimi show up as well. Things seem to go rather okay until Seiji`s younger sister Akua returns home early to find Seiji surrounded by all four girls in a compromising situation and proceeds to scold her brother for his behavior. Curious about the siblings` relationship, Guri drags Akua out shopping to get to the bottom of her brother-complex.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>734119</identifier>
<identifier>love-tyrant</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="187849" update="2017-06-13">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-06-02</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">全然... 何も... × ちょっと, どうかしていました...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Absolutely... Nothing... x There`s Just Something Wrong with Me...</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Absolument... rien × Je dois avoir un problème</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zenzen... Nanimo... x Chotto, Douka Shiteimashita...</title>
<summary>It`s time for the school cultural festival! Excitement is in the air as life seems to be back to normal for Seiji, Akane, and the rest, but all is not what it seems. Shikimi suddenly has transferred into Seiji`s class and it now has Akane on edge. When its decided that their class will be putting on a play with Shikimi in the leading role of the princess Akane is roped into playing the prince while Guri gets to play the rival pirate to the prince. On top of all this even Yuzu has started acting strangely and Seiji finds himself stuck in the middle, as always.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>734117</identifier>
<identifier>love-tyrant</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
