<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="12234" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2017-01-05</startdate>
<enddate>2017-03-23</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Masamune-kun no Revenge</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">政宗くんのリベンジ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Masamune-kun`s Revenge</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">마사무네의 리벤지</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">政宗君的复仇</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="13840" type="Sequel">Masamune-kun no Revenge (2018)</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="3">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="301225">This show is bit of a let down because it doesn`t really move anywhere in the end. There`s tons of cliché`s and some fanservice episodes which seems weird considering they could`ve crammed more material in it. I suppose they chose to cover only the first volume of the manga which has 10 btw. I also didn`t really care for any of the characters other than, at times, the main protagonist. Consider this series a teaser for the manga. Interesting concept, but it doesn`t live up to my expectations. [4/10]</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="725935">As already noted by others, it`s a typical High school romantic comedy anime. Considering that this genre is not my cup of tea, I still think Masamune-kun no Revenge highly underrated.  There are serious revenge undertones and the pain of young relationships (or lack there of), by the MC and side-character which make it worth while and interesting to watch.  

Maybe I enjoyed more than most people, since I could relate to the MC in more than one way as this show reminded me of my early dating experience.  I really like how the MC grew as a man and how he matured in his thinking.  I`d like to expand on these thoughts, but I`d give too much of the story away...  

As others also noted, it lacks a concise ending, as it sets itself up pretty open for a continuation of the story (which I hope will come soon).</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="24572">Gotta warn you, I`m a fan of the genre... After the promising first 7-8 eps I thought this anime would be on my 2017 top animes, maybe even alltime fav. Believe me, this is a great romcom, at times Masamune is just so hilarious I literary was ROFLMAO. The revenge plot is simply genius, great cast and good animation. Yet, as utterly frustrated I was when it went into the typical school life routine filled with uninventive genre clichés. Then an important event happened which of course there was not enough eps and time to elaborate upon! The ending is so rushed and lackluster IMO it almost ruined everything.  

Will there be a 2nd season? Don`t get your hopes up. Sadly this genre is in most cases cut down to 12 eps over 1 season only. Even when the original manga or light novel has tons of published material and volume. Let us all hope more of those great romcom mangas become lengthy animes in the future!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://masamune-tv.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="46106" type="Original Work">Takeoka Hazuki</name>
<name id="2900" type="Animation Work">Silver Link</name>
<name id="38385" type="Direction">Minato Mirai</name>
<name id="27370" type="Character Design">Sawairi Yuuki</name>
<name id="3465" type="Series Composition">Yokote Michiko</name>
<name id="41078" type="Original Work">Tiv</name>
<name id="27370" type="Chief Animation Direction">Sawairi Yuuki</name>
<name id="10106" type="Music">Katou Tatsuya</name>
</creators>
<description>As an overweight child, http://anidb.net/ch85801 [Makabe Masamune] was mercilessly teased and bullied by one particular girl, http://anidb.net/ch85798 [Adagaki Aki]. Determined to one day exact his revenge upon her, Makabe begins a rigorous regimen of self-improvement and personal transformation.
Years later, Masamune re-emerges as a new man. Handsome, popular, with perfect grades and good at sports, Masamune-kun transfers to Aki`s school, and is unrecognizable to her. Now, Masamune-kun is ready to confront the girl who bullied him so many years ago and humiliate her at last. But will revenge be as sweet as he thought?
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1959">3.94</permanent>
<temporary count="1966">6.18</temporary>
<review count="3">4.49</review>
</ratings>
<picture>191671.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>18749</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>33487</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://masamune-tv.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Masamune-kun's_Revenge</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>政宗くんのリベンジ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4385</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>357139</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19766</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>masamune_tv</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>masamune-kuns-revenge</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="627" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-15">
<name>lingerie</name>
<description>Lingerie is a term for fashionable and alluring women`s undergarments.</description>
<picurl>238327.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2631" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-02-11">
<name>island</name>
<description>Part of this anime takes place on an island, a small landmass that is surrounded by the sea. Generally, an island setting involves interaction with "island" elements. Such elements could include (but is not limited towards): riding on a boat, fishing, foraging/hunting, beach scene, "peaceful island life", being "shipwrecked", island fever, lamenting isolation from the mainland, etc.
An island or isle is any piece of sub-continental land that is surrounded by water. Very small islands such as emergent land features on atolls can be called islets, cays or keys. An island in a river or lake may be called an eyot (also ait), or holm. A grouping of geographically or geologically related islands is called an archipelago.
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2676" parentid="2672" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo</name>
<description>Tokyo, officially Tokyo Metropolis, is the capital city of Japan and one of its 47 prefectures. The Greater Tokyo Area is the most populous metropolitan area in the world. It is the seat of the Emperor of Japan and the Japanese government. Tokyo is in the Kantou region on the southeastern side of the main island Honshu and includes the Izu Islands and Ogasawara Islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214311.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2752" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tennis</name>
<description>Tennis is yet another sport involving hitting a ball. Were it not for the copious amounts of grass involved in certain varieties, it seems hard to imagine that people would pay it any attention at all.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2784" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>sudden girlfriend appearance</name>
<description>Sudden Girlfriend Appearance anime involve a sudden change in the main character`s life where (s)he suddenly gets confronted with an individual (s)he`s sexually attracted to, the two of them inevitably becoming a couple.</description>
<picurl>210066.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2793" parentid="2883" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>performance</name>
<description>The song performance on stage or acting in a theatre is a central part of the character`s life in this anime type.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2822" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-06">
<name>skirt flipping</name>
<description>Naughty characters — usually boys — flip the skirts of female protagonists to ascertain what panties they are wearing (also see Pantsu category).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2877" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>revenge</name>
<description>A primary factor that drives the plot forward, is the almost obsessive desire of one of the characters to get back at someone else.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3028" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-17">
<name>real-world location</name>
<description>Places seen in the show exist in reality.
Note: This could be sometime in the future, though names and certain places will still be recognizable.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3734" parentid="5826" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-03-14">
<name>school rivalry</name>
<description>Simple description for a "School vs School in all-out physical-combat" series.
No matter how geographically close or far apart the schools are, students from different schools are enemies by default and are likely to engage in physical fights on sight (except on the occasion that certain schools form pacts of alliance or peace).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3741" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-25">
<name>bullying</name>
<description>Bullying is the use of force, threat, or coercion to abuse, intimidate, or aggressively dominate others. One who engages in bullying is known as a bully.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3831" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-13">
<name>training</name>
<description>Training is extensive, serious practising a person undergoes in order to develop skills and abilities, such as handling weapons, playing instruments, playing sports, and so on.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4479" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-03">
<name>sense of foreboding</name>
<description>The anime starts off quietly, everything seems to be fine, but from episode to episode the signs that something ominous is about to happen increase. E.g. a typical mystery setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4614" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>narration</name>
<description>The most common example is that of a voice, either that of one of the characters or entirely unrelated, that appears at the beginning of an episode to offer a summary or introduction, and at the end of an episode for closure or for a preview to hint upon what to expect next.
Another use of narration comes in the form of a dominant voice belonging to one of the protagonists, intended only for the viewer and revealing the intimate thoughts to whom it belongs. This type of narration occurs frequently throughout the duration of the episode or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4761" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-02-11">
<name>love letter</name>
<description>One of the characters in the anime receives a love letter, usually stashed away in their school shoe locker. Or in other cases a girl might directly give the love letter to the boy she loves.
Plot device to further the relationship between characters, may also be used as comedic element creating awkward situations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5518" parentid="7199" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-03">
<name>flat chest jokes</name>
<description>Jokes about the (supposedly or actually) flat chest of a character.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5826" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-12">
<name>rivalry</name>
<description>Quite broadly used term describing a conflict, contest, struggle, or opposition of some sort.
Typical examples: The mostly comedic rivalry for the love of a protagonist in a harem anime (love polygon), the more "mindless" battles between wannabe delinquents in a school fighting anime, or the struggle between good &amp; evil in an epic conflict for world domination.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7199" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-12">
<name>sexual humour</name>
<description>Sexual humour is prevalent in this anime. It often involves cheeky or crude sexual language, with innuendos and jokes about the female or male genitalia. Often, such anime also have http://anidb.net/t2856 [ecchi] elements to them.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="85797" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-01-14">
<rating votes="34">6.74</rating>
<name>Futaba Tae</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>196952.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33509" picture="204529.jpg">Tadokoro Azusa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85798" type="main character in" update="2017-01-14">
<rating votes="54">6.54</rating>
<name>Adagaki Aki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>196949.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30554" picture="81681.jpg">Oohashi Ayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85799" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-01-14">
<rating votes="53">5.79</rating>
<name>Koiwai Yoshino</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>196950.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21013" picture="201781.jpg">Minase Inori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85800" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-01-14">
<rating votes="17">5.01</rating>
<name>Shuri Kojuurou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>196953.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2296" picture="189623.jpg">Hayami Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85801" type="main character in" update="2017-01-14">
<rating votes="31">5.12</rating>
<name>Makabe Masamune</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>196948.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="31313" picture="84218.jpg">Hanae Natsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="85802" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-01-14">
<rating votes="43">7.01</rating>
<name>Fujinomiya Neko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>196951.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20025" picture="132938.jpg">Mimori Suzuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86325" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-03-05">
<rating votes="19">5.51</rating>
<name>Hayase Chinatsu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199261.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2345" picture="22115.jpg">Oogame Asuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86326" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-03-05">
<rating votes="21">6.26</rating>
<name>Hayase Kinue</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199260.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16794" picture="214757.jpg">Ogura Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86327" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-01-14">
<rating votes="13">2.71</rating>
<name>Kiba Kikune</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>196957.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1443" picture="23192.jpg">Itou Kanae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86328" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-01-14">
<rating votes="11">1.95</rating>
<name>Mizuno Mari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>196958.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="162" picture="23208.jpg">Satou Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="86329" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-01-14">
<rating votes="13">2.59</rating>
<name>Kaneko Sonoka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>196956.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="101" picture="16709.jpg">Ise Mariya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="87316" type="appears in" update="2017-01-30">
<rating votes="2">1.81</rating>
<name>Tanabe Akio</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>197628.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="41754" picture="181639.jpg">Kobayashi Daiki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="87317" type="appears in" update="2017-01-30">
<rating votes="2">1.81</rating>
<name>Yamada Shigeo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>197627.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32533" picture="236058.jpg">Lounsbery Arthur</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="87318" type="appears in" update="2017-01-30">
<rating votes="2">3.13</rating>
<name>Eiji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>197621.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="351" picture="132760.jpg">Okiayu Ryoutarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="87319" type="appears in" update="2017-01-30">
<rating votes="3">3.45</rating>
<name>Momo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>197622.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1662" picture="25819.jpg">Kouda Mariko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="87320" type="appears in" update="2017-01-30">
<rating votes="6">2.39</rating>
<name>Makabe Masamune</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>197619.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="31313" picture="84218.jpg">Hanae Natsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="87321" type="appears in" update="2017-01-30">
<rating votes="2">3.94</rating>
<name>Koubaibu Ten`in</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>197626.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="48573" picture="197395.jpg">Hirose Saya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="87322" type="appears in" update="2017-01-30">
<rating votes="2">1.40</rating>
<name>Otaku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>197623.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="44361" picture="226057.jpg">Kiuchi Tarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="87323" type="appears in" update="2018-10-20">
<rating votes="8">5.26</rating>
<name>Koiwai Naruno</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>225806.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9510" picture="185781.jpg">Shimizu Ayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="87324" type="appears in" update="2017-01-30">
<rating votes="2">3.94</rating>
<name>Kyoushi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>197624.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34519" picture="128555.jpg">Maeda Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="87385" type="appears in" update="2017-01-30">
<rating votes="5">3.59</rating>
<name>Adagaki Aki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>197620.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30554" picture="81681.jpg">Oohashi Ayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="87846" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-03-05">
<rating votes="13">1.66</rating>
<name>Gasou Kanetsugu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>199259.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="180" picture="249038.jpg">Saiga Mitsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92557" type="appears in" update="2017-11-30">
<rating votes="7">7.44</rating>
<name>Yuizaki Midori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>210057.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="51" picture="39247.jpg">Koshimizu Ami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92561" type="appears in" update="2017-12-01">
<rating votes="1">6.79</rating>
<name>Shidou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>210104.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34504" picture="200900.jpg">Taichi You</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="183183" update="2017-01-26">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-01-26</airdate>
<rating votes="13">6.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">今そこにある危機</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Clear and Present Danger</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un danger immédiat</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Imakoso ni Aru Kiki</title>
<summary>Masamune is planning his strategy to get revenge on Aki by reading the shojo manga, "Barasute," but Yoshino, aka Master, tells him he`s doing it wrong. Rather than the aggressive approach he`s been using, Masamune tries to get Aki to pay more attention to him by ignoring her, but...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>728187</identifier>
<identifier>masamune-kuns-revenge</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="183184" update="2017-01-19">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-01-19</airdate>
<rating votes="12">6.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">吉乃のマジックショー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yoshino`s Magic Show</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le spectacle de magie de Yoshino</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yoshino no Magic Show</title>
<summary>In order to try to get Aki to promise to go on a date with him, Masamune teams up with Kojuurou and challenges Aki and Yoshino to see who can get a better score on a test. If he wins, he gets a date with Aki. If he loses, he`ll have to live with the nickname Aki gave him until he graduates. How will this end up?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>728185</identifier>
<identifier>masamune-kuns-revenge</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="183185" update="2017-01-19">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-01-12</airdate>
<rating votes="14">6.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">シンデレラは笑わない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cinderella Doesn`t Smile</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Cendrillon ne se moque pas</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Cinderella wa Warawanai</title>
<summary>Masamune recieves a letter with the words "Pig`s Foot" written on it and realizes someone knows about his past. Masamune tries to find the person who sent the letter, and it ends up being someone rather surprising.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>728183</identifier>
<identifier>masamune-kuns-revenge</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="183186" update="2017-01-19">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-01-05</airdate>
<rating votes="15">5.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">豚足と呼ばれた男</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Boy Who Was Called Pig`s Foot</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Celui qu`on appelait Porcelet</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tonsoku to Yobareta Otoko</title>
<summary>Makabe Masamune was a chubby little kid but after years of training, he manages to lose weight and becomes a hot guy. This was all so he could get revenge on a girl who called him Pig`s Foot as a child by making her fall in love with him and dumping her in return.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>728181</identifier>
<identifier>masamune-kuns-revenge</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="183461" update="2018-09-23">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-01-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="183462" update="2017-01-05">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-01-05</airdate>
<rating votes="3">3.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="183526" update="2018-09-23">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-01-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending (AT-X)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="183821" update="2017-02-27">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-02-23</airdate>
<rating votes="13">8.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">君じゃないんだ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It`s Not You</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ce n`est pas toi que je désire</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kimi ja Nainda</title>
<summary>Masamune suddenly gets a call from Aki on his cellphone. Masamune then realizes that the picture of him and Aki when they were children that was in his room is gone, and he’s certain that Neko is the one who took it. Masamune sneaks into Neko’s room to try to find out the truth, but is found by Neko. And then, Neko does something rather surprising...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>728195</identifier>
<identifier>masamune-kuns-revenge</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="183822" update="2017-02-27">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-02-16</airdate>
<rating votes="13">7.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">綱手島事件</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Tsunade Island Incident</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`affaire de l`île Tsunade</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsunade Tou Jiken</title>
<summary>After finishing their exams, summer vacation finally begins. Masamune plans his next move to get closer to Aki, and heads to Tsunade Island along with the others to spend time at Aki’s summer villa. Yoshino tells Masamune that if he’s not able to make any progress with Aki there, she would tell Aki everything that’s been going on. Once they get to the island, they meet the secretary of the Adagaki family, Yuigasaki, and Masamune tells her that he’s dating Aki. This leads to the two having to pretend that they are a couple...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>728193</identifier>
<identifier>masamune-kuns-revenge</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="183823" update="2017-02-27">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-02-09</airdate>
<rating votes="13">6.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">突撃! お宅訪問戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Attack! Battle of the Home Visits</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Chargez ! La pagaille s`invite à la maison</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Totsugeki! Otaku Houmen Sen</title>
<summary>Neko tries desperately to try to win Masamune`s affection. However, Masamune seems rather oblivious to this fact and when he gets home, he finds Yoshino and Neko there, making him food. Masamune panics because there are various things from his past that he doesn`t want to be seen...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>728191</identifier>
<identifier>masamune-kuns-revenge</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="183824" update="2017-02-07">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-02-02</airdate>
<rating votes="13">5.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ミステリアス・キャット</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mysterious Cat</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Mysterious cat</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mysterious Cat</title>
<summary>Masamune saves Aki as she was about to be hit by a car, when the mysterious beautiful girl who was riding in the car comes out and says that she was waiting to see Masamune and hugs him. A few days later, a girl named Fujinomiya Neko transfers into Masamune`s class, and Aki`s mood has been worse ever since...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>728189</identifier>
<identifier>masamune-kuns-revenge</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="184652" update="2017-03-23">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-03-23</airdate>
<rating votes="13">2.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">死んでもマイクを手放すな</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Don`t Let Go of the Mic, Even If You Die</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Même si tu y passes, ne lâche pas le micro</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shindemo Mic o Tebanasuna</title>
<summary>Despite all the trouble, the cultural festival is now over. They all end up having an after party at karaoke and battle it out there. What will become of Masamune’s revenge?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>728203</identifier>
<identifier>masamune-kuns-revenge</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="184653" update="2017-03-17">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-03-16</airdate>
<rating votes="10">4.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">八坂祭の白雪姫</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Snow White of the Yasaka Festival</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Blanche-Neige au festival du lycée</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yasaka Matsuri no Shirayukihime</title>
<summary>Whoever gets more votes for their production of “Snow White” for the cultural fair, get to dance with Aki afterwards. The battle has begun between Masamune and Kanetsugu. Suddenly, something rather unexpected happens to the both of them...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>728201</identifier>
<identifier>masamune-kuns-revenge</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="184654" update="2017-03-09">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-03-09</airdate>
<rating votes="10">3.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">疑惑の新学期</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The New School Term Filled with Doubts</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une rentrée douteuse</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Giwaku no Shingakki</title>
<summary>Another Masamune appears in front of Aki named Gasou Kanetsugu. Summer break ends and Masamune continues his approach on Aki but he learns that he is Aki’s betrothed. Masamune sees that Aki’s attitude toward Kanetsugu is completely different from how she treats him, so he panics and goes to Yoshino to figure out what to do, but...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>728199</identifier>
<identifier>masamune-kuns-revenge</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="184655" update="2017-03-02">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-03-02</airdate>
<rating votes="11">7.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛とも恋ともいうけれど</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It`s Been Called Love and Affection</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`amour et l`affection</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ai to mo Koi to mo Iu keredo</title>
<summary>After being rejected by Masamune, Neko disappears, and they all go to search for her. Aki seems to feel sorry for Neko since she was rejected, and then Masamune asks her if she remembers the nickname “Pig’s Foot.” When they finally find Neko, she starts talking about the past...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>728197</identifier>
<identifier>masamune-kuns-revenge</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="185554" update="2017-03-13">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>50</length>
<airdate>2017-03-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">政宗くんのリベンジ オリジナル特番~政宗くんの予習復讐~ 復讐編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Masamune-kun no Revenge Original Tokuban: Masamune-kun no Yoshuu Fukushuu - Fukushuu Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="185555" update="2019-06-06">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2017-03-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">政宗くんのリベンジ オリジナル特番~政宗くんの予習復讐~ 予習編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Masamune-kun no Revenge Original Tokuban: Masamune-kun no Yoshuu Fukushuu - Yoshuu Hen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="186702" update="2017-04-05">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2016-11-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">PV第2弾 (2:23)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 2 (2:23)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="186703" update="2017-04-05">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2016-10-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">PV第1弾 (1:27)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 1 (1:27)</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
