<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="12494" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2017-07-13</startdate>
<enddate>2017-09-28</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Gamers!</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">게이머즈!</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ゲーマーズ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Gamers!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Gamers!</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Геймеры!</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">GAMERS电玩咖</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="11735" approval="5" total="15">Kono Bijutsubu ni wa Mondai ga Aru!</anime>
<anime id="10011" approval="4" total="13">D-Frag!</anime>
<anime id="7568" approval="2" total="14">Kami nomi zo Shiru Sekai</anime>
<anime id="10352" approval="1" total="7">High Score Girl</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="8">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="430699">Expected a lot less from this one but enjoyed it very much in the end. The story is pretty cliche with a non-ending but there are many (predictable) twists in the romance. Everything is done with an appropriate amount of comedy. I loved it.
If you`re a fan of light-hearted romcom, this is perfect for you.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="421763">This has a hilariously convoluted love-polygon as the main theme. Simply put, fun to watch.

edit: 8 episodes in and it still manages to deliver. Most works of this genre get old quick, but this doesn`t - might even get better. This is how good love-polygons are made; partly unpredictable and absolutely hilarious.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="109723">Went in expecting a love polygon related to a club, but thank god the club was just a plot device to get characters to meet. Great story about love misunderstandings the hilarity that ensues.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="212512">This isn`t a club anime about gaming (although that does exist, just as an initial plot element.)  Instead this is a light hearted RomCom with lots of exaggerated humour i.e. synchronized reactions and goofy face animations often during said reactions.  Also there is one almost love triangle between the protagonist and two of the female leads, but it is never heavy emotionally because of it.  What I enjoy about the light romance of this show is the multiple imagined love triangles/affairs that are made by all the characters at different points manifesting from the constant misconceptions they all make, which is the main source of comedy in this show. If you like a show with a lot of silly comedy and a soft romance element, this a perfect show for you.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="491381">gamers isn`t all about games. it has a weird charm that make you want to watch it. i`am glad i didn`t dropped this anime.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="728225">Best episode 1 twist ever! Good Anti Cliche! I love it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="317942">So this show is crazy fun. It`s not so much about games as the name would imply but rather an off the rails story about misunderstanding upon misunderstanding. With some fun deconstructions of games and gamers in general.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="678374">This had some moments of clever execution and creative transitions for a show with a generic sounding premise. Dare I say it, it doesn`t have the right to be so good. While you get pulled into the story by baiting you with familiar games it at least makes sure you stay for its love polygon filled with misunderstandings.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.gamers-anime.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="44448" type="Animation Work">Pine Jam</name>
<name id="1553" type="Character Design">Satou Tenshou</name>
<name id="44249" type="Direction">Okamoto Manabu</name>
<name id="49364" type="Series Composition">Uchida Hiroki</name>
<name id="9950" type="Original Work">Aoi Sekina</name>
<name id="8977" type="Music">Dewa Yoshiaki</name>
<name id="1553" type="Chief Animation Direction">Satou Tenshou</name>
<name id="10690" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ikegami Tarou</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on light novel series written by http://anidb.net/cr9950 [Aoi Sekina] and and illustrated by http://anidb.net/cr50271 [Saboten].
"Would you like to be with me... in the Gamers Club?"
Amano Keita is a perfectly mediocre loner with no particular distinguishing features other than his love for games. One day, his school`s prettiest girl and Gamer Club President Tendo Karen suddenly calls out to him. That moment changes Keita`s life forever, as he now finds himself in the midst of a romcom with beautiful girl gamers... or, well, that`s how it usually goes. Not with him, however.
Source: crunchyroll</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1715">4.91</permanent>
<temporary count="1724">6.62</temporary>
<review count="1">4.33</review>
</ratings>
<picture>65172.png</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19399</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>34280</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.gamers-anime.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Gamers!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ゲーマーズ!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4613</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>358558</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20370</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>gamers_tvanime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>gamers</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B07G5MQS1N</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="774" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-03-27">
<name>billiards</name>
<description>Billiards are a wide variety of games of skill generally played with a cue stick which is used to strike billiard balls, moving them around a cloth-covered billiards table bounded by rubber cushions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2756" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>board games</name>
<description>People here play a board game. It can vary from chess and Go, to Monopoly, to Dungeons and Dragons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2779" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>multiple couples</name>
<description>More than one couple is developed in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3092" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-03-02">
<name>important haircut</name>
<description>When a character cuts off his or her hair, it often symbolizes a rite of passage or bout of character growth. A princess striking out on an adventure, or a new recruit at boot camp, for instance. Hair is something that takes time and effort to grow, so parting with it voluntarily can be a powerful act.
This is particularly a big deal when women get haircuts. Yet in fiction, even an accidental hair slicing can leave a character with a surprisingly even cut.
In many religions (Western Christianity, Ancient Egyptian religion, and others) priests and/or monks cut/shave their hair. Roman Catholic nuns also tend to cut and mantain their hair short under their veils when they enter the nunneries. The cutting of one`s own hair is also a part of Buddhist mythology, specifically something done by Siddhartha himself early on in his path to enlightenment, so anime examples might draw from this as an allusion. There are also some cultures, including Native American and many Asians, where a person would cut his or her hair as an act of grief, disgrace, or even rebellion. In the Confucian tradition, hair (like the rest of your body) is considered a gift from your parents and may not be damaged without a very good reason. Furthermore, prisoners and psychiatric patients commonly have their heads shaved, often to prevent the spread of lice, but sometimes also as a demeaning measure.
Source: TVTRope</description>
<picurl>169641.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3191" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-14">
<name>ohanami</name>
<description>Hanami (花見, lit. "flower viewing") is the Japanese traditional custom of enjoying the beauty of flowers, "flower" in this case almost always meaning cherry blossoms or ume blossoms. 
From the end of March to early May, sakura bloom all over Japan, and around the first of February on the island of Okinawa. The blossom forecast (桜前線 sakurazensen, literally cherry blossom front) is announced each year by the weather bureau, and is watched carefully by those planning hanami as the blossoms only last a week or two. 
In modern-day Japan, hanami mostly consists of having an outdoor party beneath the sakura during daytime or at night. Hanami at night is called yozakura (夜桜, literally night sakura). 
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
<picurl>160895.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3209" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>table tennis</name>
<description>Table tennis (also called ping pong) is a sport in which two or four players hit a lightweight ball back and forth using a table tennis racket. The game takes place on a hard table divided by a net. Except for the initial serve, players must allow a ball played toward them only one bounce on their side of the table and must return it so that it bounces on the opposite side. Points are scored when a player fails to return the ball within the rules. Play is fast and demands quick reactions.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>163036.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3610" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-12-19">
<name>game references</name>
<description>Be it the sound of a 1-up being grabbed, three golden triangles appearing on someones shirt or a blatant parody portraying a monkey throwing barrels down a poorly constructed facility, this anime contains characteristics dedicated to the remembrance/worship of an actual video game.</description>
<picurl>166123.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3842" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-31">
<name>TV censoring</name>
<description>The TV version is censored and later DVD/BD releases are uncensored, so the money-grubbing capitalists can make a couple more bucks at our expense.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3867" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>ED variety</name>
<description>Several ED sequences in this anime have either a different song or different animation, maybe even to the point of having a unique ED for each episode.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3953" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-10-04">
<name>in medias res</name>
<description>In medias res, also medias in res (Latin for "into the midst of affairs (lit. into mid-affairs)"), refers to a literary and artistic technique where the narrative starts in the middle of the story instead of from its beginning. It is generally a plot-driven concept rather than a character-driven one; though characters are commonly used to provide the backstory. The characters, setting, and conflict are often introduced through a series of http://anidb.net/t4299 [flashbacks] or through characters relating past events to each other.
Probably originating from an oral tradition, the technique is a convention of epic poetry, one of the earliest and most prominent examples in Western literature being Homer`s Odyssey and Iliad. Virgil`s Aeneid began the tradition in literature of imitating Homer, continued in Torquato Tasso`s Jerusalem Delivered, John Milton`s Paradise Lost and "Inferno" from Dante`s Divine Comedy. George Lucas`s Star Wars saga was told using in medias res.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4223" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>running gag</name>
<description>(Bit) character(s) play out a short skit several times during the course of the anime. The skit may or may not be exactly the same but does tend to have the same theme throughout.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4522" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>social commentary</name>
<description>Social commentary is the act of rebelling against an individual, or a group of people by rhetorical means. This is most often done with the idea of implementing or promoting change by informing the general populace about a given problem and appealing to people’s sense of justice. (Source: Wikipedia)&#13;
&#13;
Since this is anime, usually, the mores of Japan and the Japanese society are scrutinised, but not restricted to that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4576" parentid="6185" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-03">
<name>summer</name>
<description>At least one of the episodes takes place in summer. Think oppressively warm weather, summer vacation, summer school, summer festival, or a visit to the beach.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5205" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-09-18">
<name>dungeon</name>
<description>A dungeon is a closed environment in RPG terminology. Dungeons are usually full of enemies and loot, which corresponds to items and money that may be either lying around or dropped by enemies killed by the player. Caves and ruins are among the most common forms of dungeons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5697" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-02">
<name>randomness</name>
<description>The anime does not follow a predictable storyline. New, strange, obscure, or otherwise unexpected story elements are introduced at a whim.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5862" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-08">
<name>melodrama</name>
<description>A melodrama is a dramatic work that exaggerates plot and characters in order to appeal to the emotions, often with strongly stereotyped characters. Language, behaviour, or events which resemble melodramas are also called melodramatic. In scholarly and historical musical contexts melodramas are dramas of the 18th and 19th centuries in which orchestral music or song was used to accompany the action.
Melodrama is a style of drama that has been applied on the stage, in movies and television, and radio formats, from the 18th century to the present. Because of the long timeframe in which the style has existed, it is difficult to derive a precise definition. The term melodrama is most often used pejoratively, to suggest that the work to which the term is applied lacks sophistication or subtlety.
The term originated from the early 19th-century French word mélodrame, which is derived from Greek melos, music, and French drame, drama (from Late Latin drāma, which in turn derives from Greek drān, to do, perform).
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5916" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-26">
<name>product placement</name>
<description>Otherwise known as a "plug" or "writing commercials right into a show". The practice of prominently displaying or talking about a recognizable product in a program, in exchange for some consideration from the manufacturer, usually monetary. (Source: TV Tropes)
Particularly notorious example, Pizza Hut for the involvement with Code Geass, Darker than Black and other series.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5943" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-06-14">
<name>misunderstanding</name>
<description>Suggests that a large portion of storyline revolves around a rather large misunderstanding between two or more characters, usually forming long lasting situations of separation or hostility between all those involved.
A large portion of the story may be dedicated to gradually working all parties into a mutual understanding to true intentions or changes of heart.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6030" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-22">
<name>otaku culture</name>
<description>Otaku (おたく/オタク) is a Japanese term used to refer to people with obsessive interests, particularly anime, manga, and video games. A female otaku is occasionally referred to as a fujoshi. (Source: Wikipedia)
Here certain aspects of this "fandom" are presented in more detail, e.g. the creation of doujinshi (self-published amateur manga).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6186" parentid="6185" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-29">
<name>spring</name>
<description>During spring, the axis of the Earth is increasing its tilt relative to the Sun, and the length of daylight rapidly increases for the relevant hemisphere. The hemisphere begins to warm significantly causing new plant growth to spring forth, giving the season its name. Snow, if a normal part of winter, begins to melt, and streams swell with runoff. Frosts, if a normal part of winter, become less severe. In climates that have no snow and rare frosts, the air and ground temperatures increase more rapidly. Many flowering plants bloom this time of year, in a long succession sometimes beginning when snow is still on the ground, continuing into early summer. In normally snowless areas spring may begin as early as February (Northern Hemisphere) heralded by the blooming of deciduous magnolias, cherries and quince, or August (Southern Hemisphere) in the same way. Many temperate areas have a dry spring, and wet autumn (fall), which brings about flowering in this season more consistent with the need for water as well as warmth. Subarctic areas may not experience spring at all until May or even June.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>161969.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6191" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-05">
<name>card games</name>
<description>A card game is any game using playing cards as the primary device with which the game is played, be they traditional or game-specific. Countless card games exist, including families of related games (such as poker). A small number of card games played with traditional decks have formally standardized rules, but most are folk games whose rules vary by region, culture, and person.
Many games that are not generally placed in the family of card games do in fact use cards for some aspect of their gameplay. Similarly, some games that are placed in the card game genre involve a board. The distinction is that the gameplay of a card game primarily depends on the use of the cards by players (the board is simply a guide for scorekeeping or for card placement), while board games (the principal non-card game genre to use cards) generally focus on the players` positions on the board, and use the cards for some secondary purpose.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6408" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-17">
<name>bowling</name>
<description>Bowling refers to a series of sports or leisure activities in which a player rolls or throws a bowling ball towards a target.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>173577.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="89388" type="main character in" update="2018-06-02">
<rating votes="15">5.32</rating>
<name>Uehara Tasuku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>202769.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="303" picture="166016.jpg">Toyonaga Toshiyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89389" type="main character in" update="2017-05-23">
<rating votes="33">6.99</rating>
<name>Aguri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>202765.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10973" picture="78574.jpg">Ookubo Rumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89390" type="main character in" update="2018-06-02">
<rating votes="47">7.19</rating>
<name>Tendou Karen</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>202768.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12266" picture="56026.jpg">Kanemoto Hisako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89391" type="main character in" update="2018-06-02">
<rating votes="36">7.03</rating>
<name>Hoshinomori Chiaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>202767.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="49536" picture="228921.jpg">Iwami Manaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89392" type="main character in" update="2018-06-02">
<rating votes="20">2.66</rating>
<name>Amano Keita</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>202766.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27977" picture="76416.jpg">Han Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90428" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-08-04">
<rating votes="4">5.43</rating>
<name>Misumi Eiichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>205767.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="31313" picture="84218.jpg">Hanae Natsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90429" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-08-04">
<rating votes="2">3.58</rating>
<name>Kase Gakuto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>205766.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10130" picture="151714.jpg">Takumi Yasuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90430" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-08-04">
<rating votes="8">6.69</rating>
<name>Ooiso Niina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>205768.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42648" picture="207956.jpg">Yoshino Yuna</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91244" type="main character in" update="2018-06-02">
<rating votes="23">6.27</rating>
<name>Hoshinomori Konoha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>206823.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38354" picture="150733.jpg">Kuwahara Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91440" type="appears in" update="2017-09-16">
<rating votes="1">4.09</rating>
<name>Sarina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>207189.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3830" picture="253506.jpg">Terasaki Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91606" type="appears in" update="2017-09-30">
<rating votes="1">4.09</rating>
<name>Misumi Riki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>207751.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38380" picture="224406.jpg">Takahashi Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95000" type="appears in" update="2018-04-11">
<rating votes="1">4.09</rating>
<name>Masaya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>216085.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39260" picture="150015.jpg">Ishiya Haruki</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="188581" update="2017-08-24">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-08-03</airdate>
<rating votes="10">5.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">INTERMISSION 天道花憐とスランプ・デイズ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Intermission: Karen Tendo and Slump Days</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Tendou Karen und die Krisentage</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Karen Tendô dans la tourmente</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">Intermission: 텐도 카렌과 슬럼프 데이즈</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Intermission: Tendou Karen to Slump Days</title>
<summary>Tendou Karen has been out-of-it ever since Chiaki and Keita have become friends. She runs into Keita in town, and so they go on a "walk" together.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742415</identifier>
<identifier>gamers</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="188582" update="2017-08-24">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-07-27</airdate>
<rating votes="10">5.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">星ノ守千秋とすれ違い通信</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Chiaki Hoshinomori and StreetPass Communication</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Chiaki Hoshinomori und StreetPass Kontakt</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Chiaki Hoshinomori et le StreetPass</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">호시노모리 치아키와 엇갈림 통신</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hoshinomori Chiaki to Surechigai Tsuushin</title>
<summary>Tasuku tries to set Keita up to be friends with Chiaki, another gamer. They hit it off, leading to great misery for Tendou Karen.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742413</identifier>
<identifier>gamers</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="188583" update="2017-07-23">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-07-20</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">上原祐と強くてニューゲーム</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tasuku Uehara and New Game +</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Tasuku Uehara und New Game +</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Tasuku Uehara et le New Game +</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">우에하라 타스쿠와 뉴 게임</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uehara Tasuku to Tsuyokute New Game</title>
<summary>Keita takes flak for rejecting Karen`s invitation to the game club. For a moment, it looks like Keita had made the entire class his enemy, but Tasuku doesn`t seem to want to board that bandwagon.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742411</identifier>
<identifier>gamers</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="188584" update="2017-07-23">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-07-13</airdate>
<rating votes="11">5.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">雨野景太と導かれし者達</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Keita Amano and Chapters of the Chosen</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Amano Keita und die Erwählten</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Keita Amano et l`épopée des élus</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">아마노 케이타와 이끌린 사람들</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Amano Keita to Michibikareshi Mono-tachi</title>
<summary>Gaming enthusiast Amano Keita is invited by the cutest girl at school, Tendo Karen,  to join the game club. The people in the club seem cool, but...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742409</identifier>
<identifier>gamers</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="189230" update="2017-07-20">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-07-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="189231" update="2017-07-20">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-07-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="189526" update="2017-10-09">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-08-31</airdate>
<rating votes="9">8.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">エロゲーマーと観戦モード / ゲーマーズと半生ゲーム</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Erogamer and Watching Mode / Gamers and Half Their Life Game</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Erogamer und Zuschauermodus / Gamers und Spiel des halben Lebens</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Jeux érotiques et mode spectateur – Les gamers et le jeu du destin</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">에로게이머와 관전모드 / 게이머즈와 반생게임</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Erogame to Kansen Mode / Gamers to Hansei Game</title>
<summary>The Gamers Meet-up gets together at Chiaki’s place to play a board game. The seems to reveal – or maybe even predict – something about the gang’s relationship with each other.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742423</identifier>
<identifier>gamers</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="189527" update="2017-10-09">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-08-24</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">雨野景太と天道花憐の最高の娯楽</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Keita Amano and Karen`s Best Entertainment</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Keita Amano und Karen, bestens unterhalten</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le divertissement préféré de Keita Amano et Karen Tendô</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">아마노 케이타와 텐도 카렌의 최고의 오락</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Amano Keita to Tendou Karen no Saikou no Goraku</title>
<summary>Karen invites Keita out to a date. It takes a long time.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742421</identifier>
<identifier>gamers</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="189528" update="2017-08-24">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-08-17</airdate>
<rating votes="11">8.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天道花憐と不意打ちハッピーエンド (ゲーマーズと全滅ゲームオーバー)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Karen Tendo and Surprise "Happy End" (Gamers and Wipeout "Game Over")</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Gamers und das vernichtende „Game Over“</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les gamers et le game over total</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">텐도카렌과 깜짝 해피엔드 (게이머즈와 전멸 게임오버)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tendou Karen to Fuiuchi Happy End (Gamers to Zenmetsu Game Over)</title>
<summary>Aguri and Keita discover Chiaki and Tasuku on what appears to be a date. Aguri is devastated, but both she and Tasuku decide independently to help Keita move things along with Karen.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742419</identifier>
<identifier>gamers</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="189529" update="2017-08-24">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-08-10</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">亜玖璃と通信エラー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Aguri and Communication Error</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Aguri und Kommunikationsversagen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Aguri et l`erreur de communication</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">아구리와 통신에러</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aguri to Tsuushin Error</title>
<summary>Tasuku pieces together the surprising connections between Chiaki and Keita. Chiaki and Keita, meanwhile, not even aware that they`d had those connections, discover that they have some seemingly irreconcilable differences.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742417</identifier>
<identifier>gamers</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="190377" update="2017-10-09">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-09-28</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">INTERMISSION ゲーマーズと課金トーク</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Intermission: Gamers and Billing System Talk</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Gamers und Verkaufssystem-Diskussionen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les gamers et les achats in-game</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">Intermission: 게이머즈와 현질 토크</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Intermission: Gamers to Kakin Talk</title>
<summary>The gang heads to the hot springs. Aguri has some piercing criticisms of gamers and the gaming industry.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742431</identifier>
<identifier>gamers</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="190378" update="2017-10-09">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-09-21</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゲーマーズと青春コンティニュー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gamers and Youth Continue</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Gamers und Youth Continue</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les gamers et le continu de la jeunesse</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">게이머즈와 청춘 컨티뉴</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gamers to Seishun Continue</title>
<summary>Tasuku and Karen hatch a double-date plot to try to ease apart Aguri and Keita, whose friendship they fear has the potential to become something more.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742429</identifier>
<identifier>gamers</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="190379" update="2017-10-09">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-09-14</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゲーマーズとネクストステージ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gamers and Next Stage</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Gamers und Next Stage</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les gamers et le niveau supérieur</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">게이머즈와 넥스트 스테이지</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gamers to Next Stage</title>
<summary>Chiaki is led to believe that Tasuku had confessed to her. With the tensions becoming overwhelming, Keita gathers the Meet-up gang to announce his intention to finally set everything straight, but he Keitas it up.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742427</identifier>
<identifier>gamers</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="190380" update="2017-10-09">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-09-07</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">星ノ守千秋とアカウントハック</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Chiaki Hoshinomori and Account Hack</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Chiaki Hoshinomori und der Account-Hack</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Chiaki Hoshinomori et le compte piraté</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">호시노모리 치아키와 계정 해킹</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hoshinomori Chiaki to Account Hack</title>
<summary>Having learned that, all along, Keita was the number-one fan of her games, as well as her best buddy in an MMO, Chiaki’s feelings for him become more than just a little bit complicated.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>742425</identifier>
<identifier>gamers</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="190767" update="2017-09-16">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-09-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
