<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="12743" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2018-01-04</startdate>
<enddate>2018-03-22</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Yuru Camp</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Yurukyan</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Yurucamp</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ゆるキャン△</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Laid-Back Camp</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">유루 캠프</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="official">مخيم الاسترخاء</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">摇曳露营△</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="14437" type="Sequel">Yuru Camp Season 2</anime>
<anime id="14438" type="Other">Eiga Yuru Camp</anime>
<anime id="14439" type="Other">Heya Camp</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="9257" approval="41" total="42">Yama no Susume</anime>
<anime id="10293" approval="4" total="5">Yama no Susume: Second Season</anime>
<anime id="13756" approval="2" total="8">Anima Yell!</anime>
<anime id="424" approval="1" total="7">Yokohama Kaidashi Kikou</anime>
<anime id="468" approval="1" total="6">Yokohama Kaidashi Kikou: Quiet Country Cafe</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="736643">Beautiful sceneries. Liked the background music alot.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>https://yurucamp.jp/first/</url>
<creators>
<name id="48518" type="Original Work">Afro</name>
<name id="21794" type="Animation Work">C-Station</name>
<name id="2458" type="Character Design">Sasaki Mutsumi</name>
<name id="37823" type="Series Composition">Tanaka Jin</name>
<name id="11931" type="Direction">Kyougoku Yoshiaki</name>
<name id="38165" type="Music">Tateyama Akiyuki</name>
<name id="2458" type="Chief Animation Direction">Sasaki Mutsumi</name>
<name id="25888" type="Work">Iwata Masahiro</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on http://anidb.net/cr48518 [Afro]`s slow outdoor seinen manga.
http://anidb.net/ch90090 [Rin] likes to go camping by herself along the lakes that provide a scenic view of Mt. Fuji. http://anidb.net/ch90089 [Nadeshiko] loves to take cycling trips by herself to places where she can see Mt. Fuji. After they meet, Rin and Nadeshiko take camping trips, eat cup ramen together, and enjoy the scenery.
Source: ANN
Note: The first episode received an early screening at a special event held at TOHO Cinemas Shinjuku Screen 7 on 10.12.2017.
Note: The DVD/BD special http://anidb.net/e197669 [Heya Camp: Episode 0] was released on YouTube on 12.12.2019.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1580">8.16</permanent>
<temporary count="1586">7.92</temporary>
<review count="2">8.00</review>
</ratings>
<picture>221874.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20010</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>37341</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>34798</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://yurucamp.jp/first/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Laid-Back_Camp</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ゆるキャン△</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4783</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>367473</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>359503</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>367475</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>367472</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20714</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>yurucamp_anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="26">
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=RceflGi1cuQ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>laid-back-camp</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2634" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>countryside</name>
<description>The anime takes place far from the any densely populated areas like cities, i.e. out in the suburbs, in the countryside with many fields and forests.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2875" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>ecology</name>
<description>Nature and ecology are a central theme of this anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2879" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>alcohol</name>
<description>Alcohol (or more scientifically, ethanol), is one of the world`s oldest psychoactive substances. It is traditionally found in the form of a beverage such as beer, wine, or liquor, although in some contexts it can be inhaled to produce similar or intoxication, and some people prefer another way of consuming beverage-form alcohol.
Alcoholic beverages are many and varied, due to production methods (fermentation or distillation), source materials (grains, fruits, vegetables, other plants), added substances such as flavorings, and many more ways of defining different forms of alcoholic beverages.
Alcoholic beverages are divided into three general classes: beers, wines, and spirits. They are legally consumed in most countries, and over 100 countries have laws regulating their production, sale, and consumption. In particular, such laws specify the minimum age at which a person may legally buy or drink them. This minimum age varies between 16 and 25 years, depending upon the country and the type of drink. Most nations set it at 18 years of age.</description>
<picurl>70749.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3028" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-17">
<name>real-world location</name>
<description>Places seen in the show exist in reality.
Note: This could be sometime in the future, though names and certain places will still be recognizable.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3185" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-27">
<name>wordplay</name>
<description>The characters play with words. 
E.g. purposely or accidentally use similar-sounding but wrongly applied words in the Japanese original, leading to supposedly funny misunderstandings and confusion.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3191" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-14">
<name>ohanami</name>
<description>Hanami (花見, lit. "flower viewing") is the Japanese traditional custom of enjoying the beauty of flowers, "flower" in this case almost always meaning cherry blossoms or ume blossoms. 
From the end of March to early May, sakura bloom all over Japan, and around the first of February on the island of Okinawa. The blossom forecast (桜前線 sakurazensen, literally cherry blossom front) is announced each year by the weather bureau, and is watched carefully by those planning hanami as the blossoms only last a week or two. 
In modern-day Japan, hanami mostly consists of having an outdoor party beneath the sakura during daytime or at night. Hanami at night is called yozakura (夜桜, literally night sakura). 
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
<picurl>160895.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3217" parentid="2864" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-17">
<name>working life</name>
<description>The life of someone actually working on a often less than glamorous job is depicted in this anime. The job is taxing and the pay is low, not really the dream job one would choose to work in.
Examples: Working as salesperson in a department store, or as a waitress in a family restaurant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3285" parentid="2850" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true">
<name>journey</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3772" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-09-03">
<name>library</name>
<description>In a traditional sense, a library is a large collection of books, and can refer to the place in which the collection is housed.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3792" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-06">
<name>iyashi-kei</name>
<description>A feel good, "no true conflict within story" type of plot, instead about the daily musings and activities of the characters with an overall tranquil mood. Similar to "Slice of Life", but much more relaxed, peaceful and "zen".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3809" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-05-24">
<name>character driven</name>
<description>The main appeal of the show is the way the characters are portrayed and interact, focusing on dialogue, spending time together or getting to know each other. These anime are not "story-less" but story is secondary to character development and the characters themselves and what they experience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3813" parentid="6185" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-23">
<name>winter</name>
<description>Coldest season of the year with ice and snow, everything is covered in a blanket of white.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3869" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-12">
<name>mono no aware</name>
<description>Literally "the pathos of things", also translated as "an empathy toward things," or "a sensitivity of ephemera"; a Japanese term used to describe the awareness of the transience of things and a gentle sadness (or wistfulness) at their passing.
Also frequently been translated as "the `ahh-ness` of things".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4030" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-04-13">
<name>mental cinema</name>
<description>The ability to imagine all kinds of things, as if they were real.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4055" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-10-12">
<name>facial distortion</name>
<description>The characters face are exaggerated into a misshape, deformed, and almost warped. Used as comedy element to express extreme mood swings.
Differing from "http://anidb.net/t2652 [super deformed]", here only the face changes to an extreme degree, not the whole body of the protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4150" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-02-01">
<name>everybody is nice</name>
<description>All characters are nice in their own way; nobody has ill intentions to others. Even if a secondary character appears to be bad at the beginning, they will redeem themselves or become tamed/pacified/neutralized swiftly.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4222" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>walls of text</name>
<description>Walls of text refers to Japanese text that appears in large quantities within the anime itself. This text is most likely vital to the storyline and may come in the form of charts and diagrams or pieces of paper, notes or even thoughts that are only partially or entirely unspoken.
May also be taken as a fair warning to viewers unable to translate Japanese text on their own, suggesting that thorough subtitle support may be required as well as making use of the pause button on their media players so that all text can be read.
Normally, tags don`t refer to physical translations of text, subtitle appearances and karaoke styling added by 3rd parties. But those who seek to describe an anime that is heavy on SPOKEN dialogue (which may tend to create a large quantity of natural subtitling to read for those not fluent in the language being used) could consider this tag but may make clearer reference with the dialogue driven tag.</description>
<picurl>32534.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4227" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-03">
<name>detailed landscapes</name>
<description>An amazing view of nature, of artificially sculpted landscapes (i.e. gardens), or of a cityscape.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4498" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-20">
<name>heart-warming</name>
<description>The story and its characters give off good vibes — includes elevated feelings of affection such as tenderness, sympathy and love, all in one package.
The kind of anime which leaves you with a warm feeling inside and you can not stop smiling while watching it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4614" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>narration</name>
<description>The most common example is that of a voice, either that of one of the characters or entirely unrelated, that appears at the beginning of an episode to offer a summary or introduction, and at the end of an episode for closure or for a preview to hint upon what to expect next.
Another use of narration comes in the form of a dominant voice belonging to one of the protagonists, intended only for the viewer and revealing the intimate thoughts to whom it belongs. This type of narration occurs frequently throughout the duration of the episode or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4729" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-07-06">
<name>colour coded</name>
<description>Every single character on the main cast has a unique hair colour to help less perceptive viewers distiguish between them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5768" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>intact family</name>
<description>The main character`s family is a so-called "nuclear family". Wherein both parents are alive and present in his or her life. This is actually relatively rare for anime, where "parental abandonment" is the norm.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6034" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>Engrish</name>
<description>Engrish is actually a mispronunciation of English, as can be the result of someone, who does not have English as their primary language of origin (such as Japanese or Chinese). Occasionally characters in the original Japanese dialogue version of an anime will speak in English... however; this often still requires the assistance of subtitles, for while the words are meant to be said in English, the sentence structure and letter pronunciation may still be strongly related to the person’s primary language.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6075" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-12">
<name>educational</name>
<description>The entire series (at least a major part of it) is centred on a particular subject. Information is fed to the audience in a sublime manner. Most of the time an on-screen written comment by the narrator (or translator) can be seen, e.g. biological specimen, medicine, process, etc. Sometimes at the end of every episode’s closing song, a 20 seconds educational clip is presented.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6186" parentid="6185" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-29">
<name>spring</name>
<description>During spring, the axis of the Earth is increasing its tilt relative to the Sun, and the length of daylight rapidly increases for the relevant hemisphere. The hemisphere begins to warm significantly causing new plant growth to spring forth, giving the season its name. Snow, if a normal part of winter, begins to melt, and streams swell with runoff. Frosts, if a normal part of winter, become less severe. In climates that have no snow and rare frosts, the air and ground temperatures increase more rapidly. Many flowering plants bloom this time of year, in a long succession sometimes beginning when snow is still on the ground, continuing into early summer. In normally snowless areas spring may begin as early as February (Northern Hemisphere) heralded by the blooming of deciduous magnolias, cherries and quince, or August (Southern Hemisphere) in the same way. Many temperate areas have a dry spring, and wet autumn (fall), which brings about flowering in this season more consistent with the need for water as well as warmth. Subarctic areas may not experience spring at all until May or even June.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>161969.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6399" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-25">
<name>episodic</name>
<description>An episodic anime consists of many successive short arcs that are generally 1-2 episodes in length, with strong plot continuity within each arc but generally little continuity from one arc to the next. For long shows (well upwards of 50 episodes), the episode count constraint is less tight; for example, a show with close to 250 episodes would also be considered episodic if it consisted of a majority of arcs of up to 3 or maybe 4 episodes and possibly also very few slightly longer arcs.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7146" parentid="2607" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-14">
<name>cute girls doing cute things</name>
<description>Cute girls doing cute things with each other (CGDCT): when girls are super friendly with each other and do all sorts of http://anidb.net/t798 [cute/moe] things with each other, but there is no yuri or shoujo ai subtext -- more specifically, there is no romantic subtext.

* CGDCT applies where the main focus is on moe/cute girls and their interactions with each other. Good examples include http://anidb.net/a9722 [Non Non Biyori] (600 weight / 3.0 stars) and http://anidb.net/a9579 [Kin`iro Mosaic] (600 weight / 3.0 stars).
* Generally, CGDCT is applicable only if the anime is also tagged predominantly female cast or all female cast.
* CGDCT does not apply if girls doing cute things is incidental to a larger motive/theme/meta. For example, in http://anidb.net/a8168 [Nichijou] the focus is comedy, using cute girls; the tag would not apply.

CGDCT is often mistaken as low level yuri or shoujo ai. If there is also actual romantic subtext, use the http://anidb.net/t2695 [yuri (18+)] and http://anidb.net/t2782 [shoujo ai] tags as well. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>223153.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="90089" type="main character in" update="2017-12-12">
<rating votes="41">6.37</rating>
<name>Kagamihara Nadeshiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>206403.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38634" picture="144425.jpg">Hanamori Yumiri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90090" type="main character in" update="2017-12-12">
<rating votes="81">8.49</rating>
<name>Shima Rin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>206402.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21312" picture="232438.jpg">Touyama Nao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91021" type="main character in" update="2017-08-19">
<rating votes="24">6.31</rating>
<name>Oogaki Chiaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>206405.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10951" picture="222825.jpg">Hara Sayuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91022" type="main character in" update="2017-12-12">
<rating votes="19">6.17</rating>
<name>Saitou Ena</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>206404.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38380" picture="224406.jpg">Takahashi Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91023" type="main character in" update="2017-12-12">
<rating votes="28">6.97</rating>
<name>Inuyama Aoi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>206406.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1438" picture="69192.jpg">Toyosaki Aki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92740" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-12-16">
<rating votes="20">7.32</rating>
<name>Kagamihara Sakura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>210814.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11" picture="32253.jpg">Inoue Marina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93969" type="appears in" update="2018-02-24">
<rating votes="2">5.01</rating>
<name>Shima Saki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>213482.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="591" picture="226209.jpg">Mizuhashi Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94161" type="appears in" update="2018-03-02">
<rating votes="1">2.04</rating>
<name>Kagamihara Shizuka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>213952.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="25804" picture="71817.jpg">Yamamoto Nozomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94162" type="appears in" update="2018-03-02">
<name>Kagamihara Shuichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>213953.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2071" picture="74324.jpg">Oohata Shintarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94291" type="appears in" update="2018-03-06">
<rating votes="1">5.81</rating>
<name>Ocha no Onee-san</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>214286.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12" picture="184301.jpg">Kawasumi Ayako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94566" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-03-15">
<rating votes="13">4.10</rating>
<name>Toba Minami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>214862.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="182" picture="226274.jpg">Itou Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94568" type="appears in" update="2018-03-16">
<rating votes="3">5.16</rating>
<name>Inuyama Akari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>214879.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="41504" picture="178543.jpg">Matsuda Risae</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94839" type="appears in" update="2018-03-26">
<name>Itou-san</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>215501.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2192" picture="248128.jpg">Kashii Shouto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94840" type="appears in" update="2018-03-26">
<name>Kanrinin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>215502.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6082" picture="222919.jpg">Hirano Toshitaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94848" type="appears in" update="2018-03-28">
<name>Tenshu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>215552.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3098" picture="248136.jpg">Ugaki Hidenari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94858" type="appears in" update="2018-03-29">
<name>Kanrinin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>215604.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1683" picture="248129.jpg">Kanemitsu Nobuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94861" type="appears in" update="2018-03-30">
<name>Part no Josei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>215617.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32534" picture="222839.jpg">Yano Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94862" type="appears in" update="2018-03-30">
<rating votes="1">7.19</rating>
<name>Camper no Roujin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>215619.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="286" picture="17117.jpg">Ootsuka Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94863" type="appears in" update="2018-03-30">
<name>Kanrinin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>215620.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34508" picture="211755.jpg">Tokuishi Katsuhiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94865" type="appears in" update="2018-03-31">
<name>Caribou Ten`in</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>215663.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43748" picture="222817.jpg">Eguchi Nako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94866" type="appears in" update="2018-03-31">
<name>Wakashiya Ten`in</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>215664.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="54648" picture="216306.jpg">Mochida Himari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94868" type="appears in" update="2018-03-31">
<name>Yuujin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>215672.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17069" picture="80944.jpg">Numakura Manami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94874" type="appears in" update="2018-04-01">
<name>Oomachi-sensei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>215694.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4726" picture="248131.jpg">Kawamoto Kunihiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94875" type="appears in" update="2018-04-01">
<name>Inuyama Mineko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>215695.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="252" picture="149852.jpg">Shindou Naomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108558" type="appears in" update="2020-03-03">
<name>Toba Ryouko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244748.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9365" picture="34581.jpg">Kokuryuu Sachi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="194077" update="2018-01-29">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-01-25</airdate>
<rating votes="12">7.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">野クルとソロキャンガール</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Outdoor Activities Club and the Solo Camping Girl</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le cercle de plein air et la solitaire</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">야외 활동 서클과 솔로 캠핑 걸</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">نادي النشاطات في الهواء الطلق وفتاة التّخييم الانفرادي</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nokuru to Solo Camp Girl</title>
<summary>The Outdoor Activities Club prepares for their first camping trip. They may have to improvise a little. Meanwhile, Rin sets out to camp in Nagano.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>758791</identifier>
<identifier>laid-back-camp</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="194078" update="2018-01-29">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-01-18</airdate>
<rating votes="13">7.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ふじさんとまったりお鍋キャンプ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mount Fuji and Relaxed Hot Pot Camp</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Fondue relax au pied du mont Fuji</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">후지산과 유유자적 찌개 캠프</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">جبل فوجي وتخييم كسرولة هادئ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fujisan to Mattari Onabe Camp</title>
<summary>Nadeshiko gets wind that Shima Rin is camping at Fumoto Campgrounds. She invites herself to join, bringing a basket of hot pot supplies for them to enjoy.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>758789</identifier>
<identifier>laid-back-camp</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="194079" update="2018-01-29">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-01-11</airdate>
<rating votes="14">7.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ようこそ 野クルへ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Welcome to the Outdoor Activities Club!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Bienvenue au cercle de plein air !</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">야외 활동 서클에 오신 걸 환영합니다!</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">أهلاً بكم في نادي النشاطات في الهواء الطلق</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Youkoso Nokuru e!</title>
<summary>Kagamihara Nadeshiko joins the Outdoor Activites Club. Shima Rin finds out that they go to the same school, but avoids her, preferring to camp alone.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>758787</identifier>
<identifier>laid-back-camp</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="194080" update="2018-01-29">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-01-04</airdate>
<rating votes="20">7.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ふじさんとカレーめん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mount Fuji and Curry Noodles</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Nouilles au curry face au mont Fuji</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">후지산과 카레라면</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">جبل فوجي ومعكرونة بالكاري</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fuji-san to Kare-man</title>
<summary>Shima Rin goes solo camping at Motosuko Lake, where she encounters an odd girl sleeping on a bench.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>758785</identifier>
<identifier>laid-back-camp</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="194767" update="2018-01-04">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-01-04</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195114" update="2018-08-09">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-01-11</airdate>
<rating votes="3">7.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195235" update="2018-04-10">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-02-22</airdate>
<rating votes="12">5.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">テスト, カリブー, まんじゅううまい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Exams, Caribou, Steamed Buns, Yum!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Contrôles, Caribou, délicieux gâteaux</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">시험, 카리부, 만쥬 맛있어</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">امتحانات وكاريبو وكعك مُبخّر، لذيذ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Test, Caribou, Manjuu Umai</title>
<summary>Despite upcoming exams, the OutClub continues to obsess about camping, doing maintenance on a bowl and skillet that Chiaki and Aoi had bought. Another camping trip is in the works.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>758799</identifier>
<identifier>laid-back-camp</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="195236" update="2018-04-10">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-02-15</airdate>
<rating votes="12">9.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">湖畔の夜とキャンプの人々</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Night on the Lake Shore and Campers</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une nuit au bord du lac et des campeuses</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">호반의 밤과 캠핑장 사람들</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">ليلة في شاطئ البحيرة ومُخيّمون</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kohan no Yoru to Camp no Hitobito</title>
<summary>At Lake Shibire, Rin gives Nadeshiko a scare with the story of a monster that may or may not live in the water. They have trouble starting the fire for the barbecue.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>758797</identifier>
<identifier>laid-back-camp</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="195237" update="2018-04-10">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-02-08</airdate>
<rating votes="12">7.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">お肉と紅葉と謎の湖</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Meat and Fall Colors and the Mystery Lake</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Viande, couleurs automnales et lac mystérieux</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">고기랑 홍차랑 수수께끼 호수</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">لحم وألوان الخريف وبحيرة الغموض</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oniku to Kouyou to Nazo no Mizuumi</title>
<summary>Rin buys a portable grill online, which Nadeshiko discovers. They decide to go on a weekend camping barbecue.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>758795</identifier>
<identifier>laid-back-camp</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="195238" update="2018-04-10">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-02-01</airdate>
<rating votes="13">8.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">二つのキャンプ, 二人の景色</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Two Camps, Two Campers` Views</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Deux campings, deux paysages</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">두 개의 캠핑, 두 사람의 풍경</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">مُخيَّمان ومنظر مُخيِّمتَين</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Futatsu no Camp, Futari no Keshiki</title>
<summary>After a courageous battle against the temptations of the hot springs, the OutClub makes it to their campsite. Meanwhile, Shima Rin arrives at Takabotchi Highlands by herself.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>758793</identifier>
<identifier>laid-back-camp</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="196125" update="2018-04-10">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-03-22</airdate>
<rating votes="11">9.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ふじさんとゆるキャンガール</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mount Fuji and the Laid-Back Camp Girls</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le mont Fuji et les filles au grand air</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">후지산과 유루 캠핑 걸</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">جبل فوجي وفتيات التخييم المسترخيات</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fuji-san to Yuru Camp Girl</title>
<summary>Rin gets back from buying extra supplies, and the gang hangs out for a while longer before going to bed. They’ll be watching the sun rise over Mount Fuji the next morning.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>758807</identifier>
<identifier>laid-back-camp</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="196126" update="2018-04-10">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-03-15</airdate>
<rating votes="11">9.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">クリキャン!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Christmas Camp!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Au grand air pour Noël !</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">크리스마스 캠핑!</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">مخيّم الكريسماس</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kuri Camp!</title>
<summary>Rin and the OutClub arrive early for their Christmas camping trip. They have ice cream, play with Saitou’s chihuahua, and decorate their teacher, who is already smashed.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>758805</identifier>
<identifier>laid-back-camp</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="196127" update="2018-04-10">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-03-08</airdate>
<rating votes="11">8.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">旅下手さんとキャンプ会議</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Clumsy Travelers and Camp Meetings</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La voyageuse pas douée et la réunion de camping</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">여행 하수 씨와 캠프 회의</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">مسافِرات خرقاوات واجتماعات تخييم</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tabi Heta-san to Camp Kaigi</title>
<summary>With Chiaki and Nadeshiko’s help, Rin makes it to her campsite. The OutClub begins making plans for a Christmas camping trip.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>758803</identifier>
<identifier>laid-back-camp</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="196128" update="2018-04-10">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-03-01</airdate>
<rating votes="11">8.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">なでしこナビと湯けむりの夜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Night of Navigator Nadeshiko and Hot Spring Steam</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Nadeshiko guide et la nuit de vapeur</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">나데시코 내비게이션과 온천 수증기가 있는 밤</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">ليلة الملّاحة ناديشيكو وبخار نبع ساخن</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nadeshiko Navi to Yukemuri no Yoru</title>
<summary>The exams are over, and Rin invites Nadeshiko out camping again, but she’s fallen ill. Rin heads out to Nagano again, while Chiaki hangs out with Nadeshiko.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>758801</identifier>
<identifier>laid-back-camp</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="197669" update="2020-06-14">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2018-03-28</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">へやキャン△episode0</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Room Camp: Episode 0</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Heya Camp Episode 0</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198524" update="2018-07-13">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2018-05-23</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ほらキャン△</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ruse Camp</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hora Camp</title>
</episode>
<episode id="203770" update="2018-08-07">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2018-07-25</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">サバキャン△</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Survival Camp</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saba Camp</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
