<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="12803" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2017-07-04</startdate>
<enddate>2017-09-19</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Aho Girl</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Ahogaru: Clueless Girl</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Дурочка</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">바보 걸</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Aho-Girl</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">アホガール</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Aho-Girl</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">笨女孩</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="4381" approval="7" total="8">Muteki Kanban Musume</anime>
<anime id="11908" approval="2" total="7">Handa-kun</anime>
<anime id="12112" approval="1" total="7">Saiki Kusuo no Sainan (2016)</anime>
<anime id="14467" approval="1" total="6">Tejina Senpai</anime>
<anime id="11219" approval="1" total="5">Kare Baka: Wagahai no Kare wa Baka de R</anime>
</similaranime>
<url>http://ahogirl.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="7430" type="Character Design">Ishikawa Masakazu</name>
<name id="6742" type="Series Composition">Aoshima Takashi</name>
<name id="12023" type="Direction">Tamaki Shingo</name>
<name id="3422" type="Chief Direction">Kusakawa Keizou</name>
<name id="1789" type="Animation Work">Diomedea</name>
<name id="783" type="Work">NAS</name>
<name id="9111" type="Original Work">Hiroyuki</name>
<name id="43533" type="Music">Gin</name>
</creators>
<description>* Base on the 4-koma slice of life comedy shounen manga series written and illustrated by http://anidb.net/cr9111 [Hiroyuki].
Yoshiko is a genuinely stupid girl (she can even manage to get all 0`s on multiple choice tests). She hangs out at school with her childhood friend, who she claims to like, and he has to put up with all her ridiculous behavior!
Source: M-U</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1712">5.02</permanent>
<temporary count="1723">6.64</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>221563.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19022</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>34881</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://ahogirl.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Aho-Girl</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>アホガール</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4604</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>359675</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20246</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ahogirl_anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>aho-girl</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="627" parentid="2856" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-15">
<name>lingerie</name>
<description>Lingerie is a term for fashionable and alluring women`s undergarments.</description>
<picurl>238327.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1157" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>horny nosebleed</name>
<description>In Japanese media, healthy young men who have no other sexual outlet will often suffer nosebleeds upon seeing the naked female body, or even just a pair of well-filled panties.
The nosebleed is, of course, a visual shorthand/euphemism for sexual arousal. It is commonly interpreted that way for males and females, with little trickles of blood indicating mild arousal, and gushing fountains of blood indicating erection/extreme arousal in both sexes. It can also be interpreted as shorthand strictly for erections in males. In that case, when blood shoots from the nose explosively, and in ridiculous quantity, the implication would be an ejaculation.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>233513.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1482" parentid="2751" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-09-08">
<name>wrestling</name>
<description>Wrestling is a fight between two people without weapons, in which each person tries to beat their opponent. Wrestlers use clinching, holding, locking, and leverage. It resembles ritual fighting as it avoids things that will likely lead to serious injury. It is similar to military hand-to-hand combat or self-defence systems.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2634" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>countryside</name>
<description>The anime takes place far from the any densely populated areas like cities, i.e. out in the suburbs, in the countryside with many fields and forests.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2676" parentid="2672" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo</name>
<description>Tokyo, officially Tokyo Metropolis, is the capital city of Japan and one of its 47 prefectures. The Greater Tokyo Area is the most populous metropolitan area in the world. It is the seat of the Emperor of Japan and the Japanese government. Tokyo is in the Kantou region on the southeastern side of the main island Honshu and includes the Izu Islands and Ogasawara Islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214311.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2751" parentid="2881" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-27">
<name>combat</name>
<description>Combat involves a violent conflict with the goal to establish dominance over an opponent.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2805" parentid="2798" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>4-koma manga</name>
<description>Yonkoma manga (4コマ漫画, four cell manga, or 4-koma for short), a comic-strip format, generally consists of gag comic strips within four panels of equal size ordered from top to bottom. (They also sometimes run right-to-left horizontally or use a hybrid 2x2 style, depending on the layout requirements of the publication in which they appear.) Though the word yonkoma comes from the Japanese, the style also exists outside of Japan in other Asian countries as well as in the English-speaking market.</description>
<picurl>70558.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2816" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>sexual fantasies</name>
<description>One or more characters in this anime let their imaginations run wild thinking about another character.
Yes, they are thinking about sex, and in an ecchi anime these thoughts are often perverted, leading to a nosebleed. But it may also be romanticising simply being husband and wife, and everything that implies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2822" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-06">
<name>skirt flipping</name>
<description>Naughty characters — usually boys — flip the skirts of female protagonists to ascertain what panties they are wearing (also see Pantsu category).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2964" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>OP variety</name>
<description>Several OP sequences in this anime have either a different song or different animation, maybe even to the point of having a unique OP for each episode.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3028" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-17">
<name>real-world location</name>
<description>Places seen in the show exist in reality.
Note: This could be sometime in the future, though names and certain places will still be recognizable.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3356" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-12-20">
<name>banana peel</name>
<description>Used as slapstick comedy element in this anime: At least one of the characters in this anime will slip on a banana peel, leading to humorous or even ecchi situations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3842" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-31">
<name>TV censoring</name>
<description>The TV version is censored and later DVD/BD releases are uncensored, so the money-grubbing capitalists can make a couple more bucks at our expense.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4055" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-10-12">
<name>facial distortion</name>
<description>The characters face are exaggerated into a misshape, deformed, and almost warped. Used as comedy element to express extreme mood swings.
Differing from "http://anidb.net/t2652 [super deformed]", here only the face changes to an extreme degree, not the whole body of the protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4151" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-11-15">
<name>German suplex</name>
<description>A wrestling move commonly used in a slapstick manner by one of the more unique characters in a series. The move typically signals a strong and coordinated individual (who may or may not actually be a wrestler). Often the move will be deployed on the same person over and over again as part of a running gag.</description>
<picurl>253242.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4522" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>social commentary</name>
<description>Social commentary is the act of rebelling against an individual, or a group of people by rhetorical means. This is most often done with the idea of implementing or promoting change by informing the general populace about a given problem and appealing to people’s sense of justice. (Source: Wikipedia)&#13;
&#13;
Since this is anime, usually, the mores of Japan and the Japanese society are scrutinised, but not restricted to that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4576" parentid="6185" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-03">
<name>summer</name>
<description>At least one of the episodes takes place in summer. Think oppressively warm weather, summer vacation, summer school, summer festival, or a visit to the beach.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5485" parentid="7199" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-28">
<name>penis jokes</name>
<description>A penis or other phallic object is used as a device to elicit laughter from the viewer. This also includes indirect references to such objects provided the intent is clearly the same.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5943" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-06-14">
<name>misunderstanding</name>
<description>Suggests that a large portion of storyline revolves around a rather large misunderstanding between two or more characters, usually forming long lasting situations of separation or hostility between all those involved.
A large portion of the story may be dedicated to gradually working all parties into a mutual understanding to true intentions or changes of heart.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6349" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-13">
<name>multi-segment episodes</name>
<description>Multi-segment episodes are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t5852 [short episodes], which are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length (up to and including 10 minutes).
Also not to be confused with an OVA or music video with multiple (otherwise unrelated) full-length http://anidb.net/t7241 [bundled episodes] consolidated into a single episode video track.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6494" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>half-length episodes</name>
<description>Half-length episodes are regular episodes that are somewhat shorter than the standard length. This includes episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length; shows with episodes up to and including 10 minutes are http://anidb.net/t5852 [short episodes] instead.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7199" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-12">
<name>sexual humour</name>
<description>Sexual humour is prevalent in this anime. It often involves cheeky or crude sexual language, with innuendos and jokes about the female or male genitalia. Often, such anime also have http://anidb.net/t2856 [ecchi] elements to them.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="89066" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-09-06">
<rating votes="12">8.82</rating>
<name>Inu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He is a big dog that http://anidb.net/ch89068 [Yoshiko] takes a liking to and would like to ride like a horse. http://anidb.net/ch89069 [Akuru] likes him too as he seems to understand his feelings.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>204646.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="265" picture="25730.jpg">Namikawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89067" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-09-06">
<rating votes="20">6.35</rating>
<name>Hanabatake Yoshie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hanabatake Yoshie is http://anidb.net/ch89068 [Yoshiko]`s mother, who is constantly worrying about her daughter, but brightens up that http://anidb.net/ch89069 [Akuru] pays attention to her and secretly hopes he and Yoshiko can marry. She hatches several schemes to have Yoshiko flirt with Akuru but they often backfire. At first she perceives http://anidb.net/ch89070 [Sayaka] to be a threat to marry Akuru but after checking her panties are that of a child, she deems her safe.
Source: Wikipedia, edited.</description>
<picture>206807.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1799" picture="156027.jpg">Hikasa Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89068" type="main character in" update="2017-10-25">
<rating votes="27">6.51</rating>
<name>Hanabatake Yoshiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hanabatake Yoshiko is a high school girl who is stupid both academically and socially. She even gets zeroes on multiple choice tests. However what she lacks intellectual capacity she makes up with lots of spunk, ridiculous audacity and lots of energy when it comes to what she wants.
She frequently hangs out with her neighbor, childhood best friend and classmate http://anidb.net/ch89069 [Akutsu Akuru] whom she calls "Akkun", profiles much to his annoyance. Her favorite food is bananas, where she can tell every bit of detail about its variety, texture and how it`s grown.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>202293.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1625" picture="226033.jpg">Yuuki Aoi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89069" type="main character in" update="2017-09-06">
<rating votes="19">6.37</rating>
<name>Akutsu Akuru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Akutsu Akuru is a smart and serious high school student who is constantly annoyed by http://anidb.net/ch89068 [Yoshiko]`s antics. The reason he and Yoshiko are classmates is because he chose to attend a local high school as the really academic schools were too far away for him to study properly. He scolds Yoshiko for her idiotic behavior, even resorting to punches. He prefers to study, and does not have a girlfriend or any friends besides Yoshiko, although http://anidb.net/ch89070 [Sayaka] agrees to be his friend out of pity. A recurring gag is that he is never able to get a perfect score on any exam.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>202294.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45" picture="44970.jpg">Sugita Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89070" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-09-06">
<rating votes="30">8.10</rating>
<name>Sumino Sayaka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sumino Sayaka is http://anidb.net/ch89069 [Akuru]`s and http://anidb.net/ch89068 [Yoshiko]`s classmate who ends up becoming friends with the two. She too is level-headed and assumes the straight-man role, often moderating interactions between Yoshiko and others. She is also kind and worries about being boring, very sensitive, especially when others point out her small chest.
Source: Wikipedia, edited.</description>
<picture>202296.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="47245" picture="224994.jpg">Harada Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89071" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-06-07">
<rating votes="29">7.32</rating>
<name>Fuuki Iinchou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She is an unnamed high school upperclassman who is the president of disciplinary committee. She cannot stand http://anidb.net/ch89068 [Yoshiko]`s idiocy. When http://anidb.net/ch89069 [Akuru] starts complimenting her by accident, she develops a major crush on Akuru - she starts stalking him, and often has lewd fantasies about him.
Yoshiko considers her a rival because of the girl`s large breast size. In many instances she tries to reach out to Akuru but her interactions give her a reputation of being just as weird, even though she is unaware of that. She is fairly smart academically, placing in the top 5 of her class.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>202297.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28602" picture="131381.jpg">Uesaka Sumire</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89851" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-09-06">
<rating votes="11">7.13</rating>
<name>Oshieda Atsuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Oshieda Atsuko is http://anidb.net/ch89068 [Yoshiko]`s homeroom and math. Although passionate about teaching, she is serious and overthinks about things. Because of this, she is unable to accept Yoshiko`s stupid actions head-on. She has always been in an all girls school, so she has had no experience in love. Up until today, she never cared about it either...</description>
<picture>206804.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="97" picture="222166.jpg">Satou Rina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89852" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-09-06">
<rating votes="9">5.02</rating>
<name>Hiiragi Kii</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>206808.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29667" picture="223460.jpg">Maeda Rena</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89853" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-10-25">
<rating votes="14">5.97</rating>
<name>Eimura Akane</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Eimura Akane is the leader of a trio of gyaru classmates whom http://anidb.net/ch89068 [Yoshiko] starts interacting with later in the series. They do not really like her, but they are just as dumb as Yoshiko in school.
Akane is the most antagonistic of the three against Yoshiko. However, she tends to listen and participate in Yoshiko`s schemes, and is sometimes unwillingly manipulated by her. She dislikes http://anidb.net/ch89069 [Akuru], who calls her ugly. She also wants to be more popular and have a boyfriend.
Source: Wikipedia, edited.</description>
<picture>206806.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36368" picture="224755.jpg">Mao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89854" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-09-06">
<rating votes="8">5.48</rating>
<name>Shiina Kuroko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shiina Kuroko is one of http://anidb.net/ch89068 [Yoshiko]`s classmates, usually seen with http://anidb.net/ch89853 [Eimura Akane] and http://anidb.net/ch89852 [Hiiragi Kii]. She is only one of the three who has a boyfriend, although she is extremely shy about it.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>206805.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="516" picture="34813.jpg">Iguchi Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89855" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-09-06">
<rating votes="20">6.91</rating>
<name>Akutsu Ruri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Akutsu Ruri is http://anidb.net/ch89069 [Akuru]`s little sister who is in the 5th grade. She is worried she will become an idiot like http://anidb.net/ch89068 [Yoshiko] as she struggles academically, and that even her brother tells her to give up - even giving her a guidebook on how to get through life without a degree. She admires http://anidb.net/ch89070 [Sayaka] because she helps tutor her a little bit.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>65222.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="38108" picture="172027.jpg">Senbongi Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89856" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-09-06">
<rating votes="10">4.13</rating>
<name>Kurosaki Ryuuichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kurosaki Ryuuichi is a delinquent guy whom http://anidb.net/ch89068 [Yoshiko] interacts with, he becomes Yoshiko`s disciple. He tries to become friends with http://anidb.net/ch89069 [Akuru] but fails because of his shyness, and ends up acting more like his underling.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>206809.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38431" picture="224824.jpg">Yashiro Taku</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90606" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-02-13">
<rating votes="9">7.04</rating>
<name>Nozomi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212954.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29667" picture="223460.jpg">Maeda Rena</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91127" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-02-13">
<rating votes="3">5.29</rating>
<name>Tadashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212953.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="516" picture="34813.jpg">Iguchi Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91128" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-02-13">
<rating votes="4">4.97</rating>
<name>Mamoru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212952.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10410" picture="223211.jpg">Izawa Shiori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91454" type="appears in" update="2017-09-19">
<rating votes="2">6.23</rating>
<name>Akutsu Akuru (Kodomo Jidai)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>207265.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="44112" picture="225552.jpg">Koichi Makoto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91455" type="appears in" update="2017-09-19">
<rating votes="2">8.12</rating>
<name>Hanabatake Yoshiko (Kodomo Jidai)</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>207266.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1625" picture="226033.jpg">Yuuki Aoi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92304" type="appears in" update="2017-11-14">
<rating votes="1">2.16</rating>
<name>Male Student</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>209679.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38360" picture="239389.jpg">Sawashiro Chiharu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93141" type="appears in" update="2018-01-03">
<rating votes="1">4.09</rating>
<name>Pome-chan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211573.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10410" picture="223211.jpg">Izawa Shiori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93149" type="appears in" update="2018-01-03">
<rating votes="1">4.09</rating>
<name>Akuru no Hahaoya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211594.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="54272" picture="223458.jpg">Kowaka Wakana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96706" type="appears in" update="2018-07-14">
<rating votes="1">4.09</rating>
<name>Satou-san</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>220384.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="46416" picture="233690.jpg">Akasaka Masayuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96721" type="appears in" update="2018-07-15">
<rating votes="1">2.16</rating>
<name>Sudou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>220413.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40701" picture="159873.jpg">Hashinaka Yuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="188485" update="2017-10-06">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2017-07-25</airdate>
<rating votes="11">6.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">突入! アホガール</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Charge! Aho Girl!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Aho Girl! L’irruption!</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">돌입! 바보 걸</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Totsunyuu! Aho Girl</title>
<summary>On the night before Akuru`s birthday, Yoshiko and Sayaka sneak into Akuru`s
room to search for a hint on what Akuru wants for a present. The disciplinary
committee president hears of their scheme and joins them, but their plans are
derailed, with Yoshiko and the disciplinary committee president going after a
sleeping Akuru!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>741349</identifier>
<identifier>aho-girl</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="188486" update="2017-10-06">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2017-07-18</airdate>
<rating votes="12">6.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">老後も安心! アホガール</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Security in Senior Citizenship! Aho Girl!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Aho Girl ! La retraite assurée !</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">노후도 안심! 바보 걸</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rougo mo Anshin! Aho Girl</title>
<summary>Sayaka visits the Hanabatake house! But awaiting her there was none other than
Yoshiko`s mother, Yoshie. Fearing that Akuru might be stolen away by Sayaka,
she does what she can to embarrass Sayaka. Yoshiko joins the mix, and what
does Sayaka do?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>741347</identifier>
<identifier>aho-girl</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="188487" update="2017-10-07">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2017-07-11</airdate>
<rating votes="12">5.95</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">増える! アホガール</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Aho Girl Multiplies!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Aho Girl ! Les idiots prolifèrent !</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">늘어난다! 바보 걸</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fueru! Aho Girl</title>
<summary>Yoshiko, self-proclaimed "master player," goes to the park. She immediately
starts playing with the kids, but the kids can`t help but show surprise and
confusion at the games her idiot whims bring her to play.  Kurosaki, a
delinquent, joins the mix, and the disciplinary committee president who can`t
keep her fantasies in check control appears. More idiots just keep coming!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>741345</identifier>
<identifier>aho-girl</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="188488" update="2017-07-23">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2017-07-04</airdate>
<rating votes="12">6.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">来たぞ! アホガール</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Here She Is! Aho Girl</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Aho Girl ! Voilà l’idiote !</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">왔다! 바보 걸</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kitazo! Aho Girl</title>
<summary>She loves bananas! The aho-girl, Hanabatake Yoshiko, who doesn’t care if she can’t do her studies at all, starts yet another day at school. Her carefree actions of idiocy seems to not only cause trouble for her childhood friend, A-kun, but her classmate, Sumino Sayaka, as well.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>741343</identifier>
<identifier>aho-girl</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="188783" update="2018-07-14">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2017-07-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="189188" update="2017-10-06">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2017-08-22</airdate>
<rating votes="11">5.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天使のような! アホガール</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Like an Angel! Aho Girl!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Aho Girl ! Comme un ange !</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">천사처럼! 바보 걸</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tenshi no Youna! Aho Girl</title>
<summary>Nozomi, Masaru, and Mamoru go to buy snacks for their field trip, with 300 yen
each as their budget, when Yoshiko tries to initiate them into the finer points
of buying field trip snacks. Masaru and Mamoru follow Yoshiko`s teachings as
they buy their snacks, but Nozomi buys a single expensive snack. Nozomi`s field
trip will end dark and gloomy... or so they thought!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>741357</identifier>
<identifier>aho-girl</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="189189" update="2017-10-06">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2017-08-15</airdate>
<rating votes="11">5.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ギャルが! アホガール</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Gal! Aho Girl!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Aho Girl ! Les pimbêches !</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">갸루가! 바보 걸</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gal ga! Aho Girl</title>
<summary>Emura Akane, Shiina Kuroko, and Hiiragi Himeko are hanging out in the classroom
after school when Yoshiko sets her sights on them. The girls, completely unable
to read Yoshiko`s behavior, get roped into playing with her. They agree to play
hide and seek in order to escape Yoshiko, but then...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>741355</identifier>
<identifier>aho-girl</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="189190" update="2017-10-06">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2017-08-08</airdate>
<rating votes="11">4.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">暑い夏だ! アホガール</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Hot Summer! Aho Girl</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Aho Girl ! Un été chaud bouillant !</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">더운 여름이다! 바보 걸</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Atsui Natsu Da! Aho Girl</title>
<summary>Yoshiko and friends arrive in Izu Atagawa, change into their swimsuits, and
head straight for the waves. The disciplinary committee president tries to
flaunt her precious rack, but fails and is buried in the sand as punishment by
Yoshiko. Yoshiko goes on rampage and buries Sayaka as well, and starts
sculpting some ------- and a ***** on them too!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>741353</identifier>
<identifier>aho-girl</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="189191" update="2017-10-06">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2017-08-01</airdate>
<rating votes="11">5.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夏だ! アホガール</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Summertime! Aho Girl!!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Aho Girl ! C’est l`été !</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">여름이다! 바보 걸</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Natsu Da! Aho Girl</title>
<summary>Yoshiko wins a vacation in the shopping district raffle and invites Akuru and
Sayaka to go with her, but the disciplinary committee president and Ryuuichi
catch wind of the trip and ask to go. The topic naturally changes to buying new
swimsuits, but then Akuru refuses to go. And a surprising someone swoops in to
convince him otherwise!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>741351</identifier>
<identifier>aho-girl</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="190042" update="2017-10-07">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2017-09-19</airdate>
<rating votes="12">7.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">出会い... そして! アホガール</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Meeting... and! Aho Girl</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Aho Girl ! Une rencontre... oui, mais pas que !</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">만남... 그리고! 바보 걸</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Deai... Soshite! Aho Girl</title>
<summary>Ten years ago, Yoshiko met Akuru. Childhood friends, the kid next door, the old
cliché story, shattered into a million pieces with the tragedy which unfolds.
Young Akuru seeks the power to defeat Yoshiko, surpassing his limits out of
fear. What is born in the young Akuru`s heart?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>741365</identifier>
<identifier>aho-girl</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="190043" update="2017-10-06">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2017-09-12</airdate>
<rating votes="11">5.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">決戦! 必殺! アホガール</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Final Battle! Decisive Blow! Aho Girl</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Aho Girl ! Le combat ! Mortel !</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">결전! 필살! 바보 걸</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kessen! Hissatsu! Aho Girl</title>
<summary>Yoshiko finds her soldier, Ryuuichi, in tatters. Yoshiko asks what happened,
and he responds that he was done in by guys who have wasted bananas.
Yoshiko stands silently, anger boiling up from within. They are
unforgiveable! I shall fight! Yes! For bananas everywhere! ...wait, bananas?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>741363</identifier>
<identifier>aho-girl</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="190044" update="2017-10-06">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2017-09-05</airdate>
<rating votes="11">6.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ドライブ! アホガール</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Drive! Aho Girl!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Aho Girl ! Un tour en voiture !</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">드라이브! 바보 걸</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Drive! Aho Girl</title>
<summary>Yoshiko goes out for a walk with her dog. But their walk is no simple walk.
Yoshiko rides on her dog`s back, and eventually they reach the mountains. A
race breaks out between Yoshiko and her dog traveling at unprecedented speed
and the legendary rider of the peak. Who will be the victor?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>741361</identifier>
<identifier>aho-girl</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="190045" update="2017-10-06">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2017-08-29</airdate>
<rating votes="11">5.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">フェスティバゥ! アホガール</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Festival! Aho Girl!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Aho Girl ! Festival !</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">페스티발! 바보 걸</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Festibau! Aho Girl</title>
<summary>In order to make the cultural festival that she looked forward to so much a
success, Emura volunteers to join the cultural festival committee. Progress on
the class attraction is slow, so she and her friends stay overnight at school
to get some work done, but then Yoshiko enters the scene. The three girls try
to get rid of her, but they get sucked into her game, and...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>741359</identifier>
<identifier>aho-girl</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="202823" update="2018-07-14">
<epno type="3">C11</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2017-09-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1k</title>
</episode>
<episode id="202824" update="2018-07-14">
<epno type="3">C10</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2017-09-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1j</title>
</episode>
<episode id="202825" update="2018-07-14">
<epno type="3">C9</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2017-08-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1i</title>
</episode>
<episode id="202826" update="2018-07-14">
<epno type="3">C8</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2017-08-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1h</title>
</episode>
<episode id="202827" update="2018-07-14">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2017-08-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1g</title>
</episode>
<episode id="202828" update="2018-07-14">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2017-08-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1f</title>
</episode>
<episode id="202829" update="2018-07-14">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2017-08-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1e</title>
</episode>
<episode id="202830" update="2018-07-14">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2017-07-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1d</title>
</episode>
<episode id="202831" update="2018-07-14">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2017-07-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1c</title>
</episode>
<episode id="202832" update="2018-07-14">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2017-07-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="212636" update="2019-02-17">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2017-07-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 1 Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="212637" update="2019-02-17">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2017-07-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 2 Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="212638" update="2019-02-17">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2017-07-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 3 Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="212639" update="2019-02-17">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2017-07-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 4 Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="212640" update="2019-02-17">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2017-08-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 5 Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="212641" update="2019-02-17">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2017-08-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 6 Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="212642" update="2019-02-17">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2017-08-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 7 Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="212643" update="2019-02-17">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2017-08-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 8 Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="212644" update="2019-02-17">
<epno type="2">S9</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2017-08-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 9 Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="212645" update="2019-02-17">
<epno type="2">S10</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2017-09-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 10 Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="212646" update="2019-02-17">
<epno type="2">S11</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-09-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 11 Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="212647" update="2019-02-17">
<epno type="2">S12</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2017-09-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 12 Ending</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
