<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="12834" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2017-07-01</startdate>
<enddate>2017-09-23</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Kakegurui</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Kakegurui - Compulsive Gambler</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">狂赌之渊</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">賭ケグルイ</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Kakegurui</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Безумный азарт</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">카케구루이</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="13718" type="Sequel">Kakegurui XX</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="5427" approval="10" total="22">Gyakkyou Burai Kaiji: Ultimate Survivor</anime>
<anime id="12888" approval="3" total="10">Killing Bites</anime>
<anime id="6139" approval="2" total="9">One Outs</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="160233">This a somewhat crazy mix about the sexual pleasure of beeing a gamble addict... but as a good addiction it hooks you into the plot and the twisted mind of these crazy players. Its fun to watch</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="317942">An academy filled with crazy characters who gamble their afternoons away (or something like that) Overall a fun watch with weird, yet enjoyable characters and interesting gambles.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://kakegurui-anime.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="2702" type="Series Composition">Kobayashi Yasuko</name>
<name id="34022" type="Original Work">Naomura Tooru</name>
<name id="48933" type="Original Work">Kawamoto Homura</name>
<name id="13349" type="Direction">Hayashi Yuuichirou</name>
<name id="15411" type="Character Design">Akita Manabu</name>
<name id="31375" type="Work">MAPPA</name>
<name id="9098" type="Music">Technoboys Pulcraft Green-Fund</name>
<name id="15411" type="Chief Animation Direction">Akita Manabu</name>
<name id="4538" type="Chief Animation Direction">Nishino Rie</name>
<name id="27012" type="Chief Animation Direction">Katou Yuuko</name>
<name id="18940" type="Chief Animation Direction">Nishimura Rie</name>
<name id="52488" type="Chief Animation Direction">Katou Yuuko</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a shounen manga series written by http://anidb.net/cr48933 [Kawamoto Homura] and illustrated by http://anidb.net/cr34022 [Naomura Tooru].
Hyakkaou Private Academy. An institution for the privileged with a very peculiar curriculum. You see, when you`re the sons and daughters of the wealthiest of the wealthy, it`s not athletic prowess or book smarts that keep you ahead. It`s reading your opponent, the art of the deal. What better way to hone those skills than with a rigorous curriculum of gambling?
At Hyakkaou Private Academy, the winners live like kings, and the losers are put through the wringer. But when http://anidb.net/ch88519 [Jabami Yumeko] enrolls, she`s gonna teach these kids what a high roller really looks like!
Source: Yen Press
Note: The first two episodes were shown at an advance screening event on June 23 that was held in Tokyo.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1968">5.50</permanent>
<temporary count="1971">6.83</temporary>
<review count="1">3.66</review>
</ratings>
<picture>202688.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19102</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>34933</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://kakegurui-anime.com/1st/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Kakegurui_-_Compulsive_Gambler</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>賭ケグルイ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4623</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>359728</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20394</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>kakegurui_anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="34">
<externalentity>
<url>https://www.netflix.com/title/80175351</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="55" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-11">
<name>awards</name>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3013" parentid="55" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-10">
<name>Newtype Anime Award</name>
<description>This anime has won 1 or more Newtype Anime Award(s)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3568" parentid="2607" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-02-07">
<name>gambling</name>
<description>Gambling is the wagering of money or something of value (referred to as "the stakes") on an event with an uncertain outcome with the primary intent of winning additional money and/or material goods. Gambling thus requires three elements be present: consideration, chance and prize. The outcome of the wager is often immediate, such as a single roll of dice or a spin of a roulette wheel, but longer time frames are also common, allowing wagers on the outcome of a future sports contest or even an entire sports season.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3887" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-09-30">
<name>cheating</name>
<description>Cheating is an act of lying, deception, fraud, trickery, imposture, or imposition. Cheating characteristically is employed to create an unfair advantage, usually in one`s own interest, and often at the expense of others. Cheating implies the breaking of rules.
Note: In the game of Mahjong you HAVE to cheat to win.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4224" parentid="7242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-03">
<name>adapted into JDrama</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into a JDrama.
A JDrama (Japanese drama), also called "terebi dorama" ("television drama") or "dorama" for short, is a Japanese live action television series.
Japan produces many drama series every year, from a huge variety of genres. Like anime, they generally air in three-month seasons or multiples thereof, with new shows airing every season. Some kinds of drama, especially the morning or afternoon ones, tend to be broadcast daily, while evening ones tend to be broadcast weekly, also like anime.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4314" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-04-11">
<name>psychological</name>
<description>Directed toward dealing with or affecting the mind, especially as a function of awareness, feeling, or motivation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5850" parentid="2869" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-13">
<name>absurdly powerful student council</name>
<description>A student council is a student-managed body inside a school which engages in administrative affairs, usually usually working in a partnership with management, staff and parents, for the benefit of the whole school environment. In real life, a student council holds no actual power; however, in many anime/manga, they have an insane amount of power, which usually allows them to overrule nearly everyone else (the school board, the mayor, the prime minster, you name it). In those cases, that device is explored as a major source of slapstick comedy.</description>
<picurl>70561.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7075" parentid="7242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-05-07">
<name>adapted into Japanese movie</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into a Japanese movie.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7242" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-03">
<name>adapted into other media</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into other media formats.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="88518" type="main character in" update="2017-04-29">
<rating votes="30">5.24</rating>
<name>Saotome Mary</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>201792.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38297" picture="150939.jpg">Tanaka Minami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88519" type="main character in" update="2019-02-03">
<rating votes="116">6.66</rating>
<name>Jabami Yumeko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67132.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="2296" picture="189623.jpg">Hayami Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="88520" type="main character in" update="2017-04-29">
<rating votes="19">1.65</rating>
<name>Suzui Ryouta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>201791.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="44389" picture="204677.jpg">Tokutake Tatsuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89077" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-05-31">
<rating votes="14">4.11</rating>
<name>Yumemite Yumemi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203249.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36230" picture="242785.jpg">Serizawa Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89078" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-05-31">
<rating votes="25">3.17</rating>
<name>Ikishima Midari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203245.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="101" picture="16709.jpg">Ise Mariya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89079" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-05-31">
<rating votes="15">3.75</rating>
<name>Sumeragi Itsuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203248.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34741" picture="222846.jpg">Wakai Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89080" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-05-31">
<rating votes="11">3.96</rating>
<name>Nishinotouin Yuriko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203247.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38905" picture="10121.jpeg">Nanami Karin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89081" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-05-31">
<rating votes="6">4.81</rating>
<name>Manyuuda Kaede</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203246.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45" picture="44970.jpg">Sugita Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89411" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-07-19">
<rating votes="10">2.65</rating>
<name>Igarashi Sayaka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>205292.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36617" picture="228872.jpg">Fukuhara Ayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89412" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-07-19">
<rating votes="54">5.21</rating>
<name>Momobami Kirari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>205293.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38" picture="171532.jpg">Sawashiro Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="89413" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-05-31">
<rating votes="16">5.46</rating>
<name>Yomotsuki Runa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>203250.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30257" picture="166714.jpg">Udono Mayu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91379" type="appears in" update="2017-09-13">
<rating votes="2">4.18</rating>
<name>Shagatake</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>207041.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38296" picture="228671.jpg">Aoyama Yoshino</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91380" type="appears in" update="2017-09-13">
<rating votes="2">4.18</rating>
<name>Tooame</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>207042.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38903" picture="239362.jpg">Uchimura Fumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99705" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-01-16">
<rating votes="9">4.28</rating>
<name>Momobami Ririka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>229179.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38" picture="171532.jpg">Sawashiro Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102316" type="appears in" update="2019-05-01">
<rating votes="2">3.82</rating>
<name>Saori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>233219.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2987" picture="23718.jpg">Shouji Umeka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102317" type="appears in" update="2019-05-01">
<name>Kumagusu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>233211.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40850" picture="188478.jpg">Shimizu Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102318" type="appears in" update="2019-05-01">
<name>Shinnouji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>233220.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="436" picture="90853.jpg">Kobushi Nobuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102531" type="appears in" update="2019-05-07">
<name>Kiwatari Jun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>233214.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1987" picture="225435.jpg">Egawa Hisao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102607" type="appears in" update="2019-04-30">
<name>Tsubomi Nanami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>233215.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="516" picture="34813.jpg">Iguchi Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="188438" update="2020-06-08">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-07-22</airdate>
<rating votes="12">7.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">家畜になった女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Woman Who Became a House Pet</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">가축이 된 여자</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Evcil Hayvan Olan Kız</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kachiku ni Natta Onna</title>
<summary>Yumeko and Mary square off against two others in a game of Indian poker after being given a chance to minimize their colossal gambling debts.
Source: Netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="188439" update="2020-06-08">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-07-15</airdate>
<rating votes="12">7.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">糸目の女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Slit-Eyed Woman</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">실눈의 여자</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Kısık Gözlü Kadın</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Itome no Onna</title>
<summary>To regain her status, Mary duels student board member Yuriko in a game of "life or death." With Mary`s crushing defeat, Yumeko offers to play next.
Source: Netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="188440" update="2020-06-08">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-07-08</airdate>
<rating votes="14">6.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">つまんない女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Boring Woman</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">시시한 여자</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Ezik Kız</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsumannai Onna</title>
<summary>Mary is relegated to the lowest levels of the gambling hierarchy after her loss. Student board member Itsuki challenges Yumeko to a game of pairs.
Source: Netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="188441" update="2020-06-08">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-07-01</airdate>
<rating votes="15">6.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">蛇喰夢子という女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Woman Called Yumeko Jabami</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">쟈바미 유메코라는 여자</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Yumeko Jabami Adında Bir Kız</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jabami Yumeko to Iu Onna</title>
<summary>Reigning class gambling champion Mary attempts to hustle unsuspecting transfer student Yumeko Jabami into a high-stakes game of rock-paper-scissors.
Source: Netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="189079" update="2020-06-08">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-08-26</airdate>
<rating votes="9">7.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛踊る女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Idol Woman</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">아이돌인 여자</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Aşkla Dans Eden Kız</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ai Odoru Onna</title>
<summary>In Kirari`s absence, pop idol sensation Yumemi offers to play against Yumeko, asking her to wager total control of her life.
Source: Netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="189080" update="2020-06-08">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-08-19</airdate>
<rating votes="10">7.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">拒絶する女たち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Refusing Women</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">거절하는 여자들</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Reddeden Kızlar</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyozetsu Suru Onna-tachi</title>
<summary>Deeply engaged in their deadly ESP card game, Midari tells Yumeko about her heated match against student board president, Kirari.
Source: Netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="189081" update="2020-06-08">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-08-12</airdate>
<rating votes="10">7.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">誘う女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Inviting Woman</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">유혹하는 여자</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Davet Eden Kız</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sasou Onna</title>
<summary>Yumeko must face Beautification Committee Chair Midari in an ESP card game involving Russian roulette before playing the student board president.
Source: Netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="189082" update="2020-06-08">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-07-29</airdate>
<rating votes="11">8.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">人間になった女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Woman Who Became a Human</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">인간이 된 여자</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">İnsan Olan Kız</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ningen ni Natta Onna</title>
<summary>Kiwatari continues to lose as Yumeko and Mary bluff their way through the game, but the final outcome all comes down to Tsubomi.
Source: Netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="189206" update="2019-08-06">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-07-01</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="189207" update="2019-08-06">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-07-01</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="190129" update="2020-06-08">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-09-23</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">賭ケグルイの女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Compulsive Gambling Woman</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">도박에 미친 여자</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Kumar Bağımlısı Kadın</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kakegurui no Onna</title>
<summary>Yumeko and student board president Kirari both wager self-expulsion from the academy as Ryota becomes the key to the final outcome of their game.
Source: Netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="190130" update="2020-06-08">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-09-16</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">人生を賭ける女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Woman Who Bets Her Life</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">인생을 건 여자</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Hayatını Ortaya Koyan Kız</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jinsei o Kakeru Onna</title>
<summary>Itsuki, no longer wanting to be under Manyuda`s control, offers to bankroll 100 chips after Yumeko goes all-in and loses on the previous hand.
Source: Netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="190131" update="2020-06-08">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-09-09</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">選択する女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Selecting Woman</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">선택하는 여자</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Seçim Yapan Kız</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sentaku Suru Onna</title>
<summary>Yumeko`s odds are stacked against her when she challenges the well-funded student board treasurer, Manyuda, in an original game of poker.
Source: Netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="190132" update="2020-06-08">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-09-02</airdate>
<rating votes="11">6.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夢見る女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dreaming Woman</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">꿈꾸는 여자</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Hayal Kuran Kız</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yumemiru Onna</title>
<summary>With her pop idol career on the line, an enraged Yumemi seeks to ruin Yumeko after a scandalous voice recording is used as a bargaining chip.
Source: Netflix</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="211693" update="2019-01-28">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-09-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 9 Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="212273" update="2019-01-27">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-10-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">メイド喫茶百花王</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Maid Cafe Hyakkaou</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maid Kissa Hyakkaou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="212274" update="2019-01-28">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2017-12-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ネコミミ学園百花王</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nekomimi Academy Hyakkaou</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nekomimi Gakuen Hyakkaou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="212275" update="2019-01-27">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2018-02-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">生徒会☆喫茶店計画</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Student Council Cafe Project</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seitokai Kissaten Keikaku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="233400" update="2020-12-16">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening Storyboard</title>
</episode>
<episode id="233401" update="2020-10-09">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending Storyboard</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
