<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="12906" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2018-01-11</startdate>
<enddate>2018-03-30</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Koi wa Ameagari no You ni</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Love is Like after the Rain</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Любовта е като изсипал се дъжд</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Koi wa Amaagari no You ni</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">koiame</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">恋は雨上がりのように</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">After the Rain</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Любовь, как ясный день после дождя</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">사랑은 비가 갠 뒤처럼</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">恋如雨止</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="9589" approval="12" total="14">Kotonoha no Niwa</anime>
<anime id="14512" approval="4" total="11">Araburu Kisetsu no Otome-domo yo.</anime>
<anime id="6466" approval="2" total="8">Kimi ni Todoke</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="21472">This is beautiful beyond words. 

It`s the kind of story that hits you right in the feels. Sweet, heartwarming but sometimes also sad and very melancholic. I`m sure everyone who watches it will be able to relate somehow with the story and the characters

Don`t watch this if you`re expecting a common romance focused on age difference taboos or something like that. Otherwise, a must see!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.koiame-anime.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="49114" type="Original Work">Mayuzuki Jun</name>
<name id="3755" type="Character Design">Shibata Yuka</name>
<name id="4556" type="Series Composition">Akao Deko</name>
<name id="762" type="Work">Aniplex</name>
<name id="51816" type="Work">DMM Pictures</name>
<name id="741" type="Work">Fuji TV</name>
<name id="805" type="Work">Dentsu</name>
<name id="13891" type="Music">Yoshimata Ryou</name>
<name id="34645" type="Animation Work">Wit Studio</name>
<name id="5317" type="Direction">Watanabe Ayumu</name>
<name id="3755" type="Chief Animation Direction">Shibata Yuka</name>
<name id="15726" type="Chief Animation Direction">Takada Akira</name>
<name id="7612" type="Chief Animation Direction">Oosugi Naohiro</name>
<name id="522" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kadowaki Satoshi</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on http://anidb.net/cr49114 [Mayuzuki Jun]`s seinen manga.
Tachibana Akira is a 17-year-old high school student who barely expresses herself. She harbors a secret crush on Kondou Masami, the 45-year-old manager of the family restaurant she works at part-time.
Source: ANN
Note: The first episode aired on Amazon Prime a day before the regular broadcast started.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1180">6.79</permanent>
<temporary count="1185">7.24</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>221973.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20226</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>34984</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.koiame-anime.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>After_the_Rain_(manga)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>恋は雨上がりのように</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4804</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>359903</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20795</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>koiame_anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B078X2N3YT</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="34">
<externalentity>
<url>https://www.primevideo.com/detail/0L47GCG67NWW8ALEGQN8QO38KY</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="235" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-05">
<name>waitress</name>
<description>A female attendant who serves customers in a restaurant, café, or similar.
Source: Wiktionary</description>
<picurl>163704.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2753" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>track and field</name>
<description>A collection of sports events that involve running, throwing, and jumping.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3146" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-04-29">
<name>divorce</name>
<description>The parents depicted in this anime have divorced, usually upsetting the life of their children.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3217" parentid="2864" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-17">
<name>working life</name>
<description>The life of someone actually working on a often less than glamorous job is depicted in this anime. The job is taxing and the pay is low, not really the dream job one would choose to work in.
Examples: Working as salesperson in a department store, or as a waitress in a family restaurant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3865" parentid="6153" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-08-07">
<name>noitaminA</name>
<description>noitaminA (ノイタミナ) – Animation written backwards – is a Fuji Television programming block, devoted to anime, broadcast each Thursday night from 00:45 to 1:15. It was launched with the intention of expanding the target audience beyond the typical young male demographic.
The timeslot was expanded from half an hour to a full hour in 2010, and now airs Thursday nights from 00:45 to 1:45.
noitaminA aired its first non-anime series in 2010, with the premiere of the live-action adaptation of Moyashimon. On April 15, 2010, Fuji TV and FUNimation announced an agreement that allows FUNimation to simulcast series from the noitaminA block in North America within an hour of their airing in Japan.</description>
<picurl>36897.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4669" parentid="6249" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-27">
<name>parenting</name>
<description>This anime is about parenting and its many challenges.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6073" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-11-23">
<name>age difference romance</name>
<description>A romance between individuals of significantly different ages is featured. Depending on how big the age gap is and on the society featured, that may be considered taboo.
While the terms "lolicon" and "shotacon", often used in relation to anime and its fandom, are limited to a physical or erotic attraction to sexually precocious girls or boys respectively, this tag expands into platonic romances and other age ranges.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7075" parentid="7242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-05-07">
<name>adapted into Japanese movie</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into a Japanese movie.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7242" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-03">
<name>adapted into other media</name>
<description>This anime is a http://anidb.net/t2797 [new original work], and it has been adapted into other media formats.
In exceedingly rare instances, a specific episode of a new original work anime can also be adapted.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="93196" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-05-04">
<rating votes="6">2.35</rating>
<name>Kase Ryousuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kase Ryousuke is a chef in the restaurant who had a sexual interest in http://anidb.net/ch93199 [Akira]. When he learned about Akira`s infatuation with http://anidb.net/ch93201 [Masami], he blackmailed with a date with him in order to keep her secret.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>211978.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="612" picture="79531.jpg">Maeno Tomoaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93197" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-05-04">
<rating votes="7">4.77</rating>
<name>Yoshizawa Takashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yoshizawa Takashi is http://anidb.net/ch93199 [Akira]`s classmate who had a crush on her. He works at the restaurant alongside Akira as a kitchen staff.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>211977.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="35756" picture="131623.jpg">Ikeda Jun`ya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93198" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-05-04">
<rating votes="13">8.03</rating>
<name>Kyan Haruka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kyan Haruka is http://anidb.net/ch93199 [Akira]`s former buddy in the track and field team, who remains steadfast in maintaining their friendship after Akira`s injury.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>211975.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42135" picture="211660.jpg">Miyajima Emi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93199" type="main character in" update="2018-05-04">
<rating votes="32">8.62</rating>
<name>Tachibana Akira</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tachibana Akira is a young high-school student, with a sharp, piercing expression, that make many people, slightly wary of her. She used to be part of the track and field team, before a leg injury forced her to give up running. Having fallen into a depression, she met http://anidb.net/ch93201 [Masami] who acted in a kind and friendly manner, offering her a free coffee when she took shelter at the restaurant in the rain. This act of kindness, began her infatuation with him. Despite her cold, and inapproachable demeanor, she is actually rather timid and shy, especially, when it comes to Masami.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>211973.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="47036" picture="211659.jpg">Watabe Sayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93200" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-05-04">
<rating votes="17">7.69</rating>
<name>Nishida Yui</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nishida Yui is http://anidb.net/ch93199 [Akira]`s fellow waitress who has a blonde hair and cheerful personality. She has a crush on http://anidb.net/ch93197 [Takashi].
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>211976.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3134" picture="211664.jpg">Fukuhara Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93201" type="main character in" update="2018-05-04">
<rating votes="16">7.96</rating>
<name>Kondou Masami</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kondou Masami is a 45-year-old manager of a http://anidb.net/ch95364 [family restaurant]. A kind, timid man, he is often criticized by his employees for being too weak. He is divorced and has a young son named http://anidb.net/ch95351 [Yuuto]. He is initially rather intimidated by http://anidb.net/ch93199 [Akira], whom he assumes actually hates him, while she, in fact, is merely staring at him in love.
He is a fan of "Pure Literature" and loves reading books. Prior to becoming a restaurant manager, he wrote novels alongside his former college buddy and now-renowned writer http://anidb.net/ch95360 [Kujou Chihiro].
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>211974.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="323" picture="211661.jpg">Hirata Hiroaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93370" type="appears in" update="2018-01-24">
<rating votes="1">7.62</rating>
<name>Yamamoto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212273.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="47945" picture="211756.jpg">Murai Yuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93371" type="appears in" update="2018-05-04">
<rating votes="3">3.06</rating>
<name>Ootsuka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>217161.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="340" picture="17176.jpg">Yabe Masahito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95339" type="appears in" update="2018-05-02">
<rating votes="2">7.85</rating>
<name>Kubo Kayoko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>217118.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="70" picture="249023.jpg">Kanai Mika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95349" type="appears in" update="2018-05-04">
<rating votes="1">5.66</rating>
<name>Morohoshi-sensei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>217153.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30740" picture="233850.jpg">Iwase Shuuhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95350" type="appears in" update="2018-05-03">
<rating votes="1">3.78</rating>
<name>Ishii</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>217138.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9511" picture="35179.jpg">Honda Mariko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95351" type="appears in" update="2018-05-03">
<rating votes="2">5.92</rating>
<name>Yuuto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>217139.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="302" picture="17134.jpg">Takeuchi Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95356" type="appears in" update="2018-05-04">
<rating votes="1">7.62</rating>
<name>Kyan Shouta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>217144.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38360" picture="239389.jpg">Sawashiro Chiharu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95357" type="appears in" update="2018-05-04">
<rating votes="1">5.66</rating>
<name>Okumura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>217145.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40893" picture="223270.jpg">Furukawa Yurina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95358" type="appears in" update="2018-05-04">
<rating votes="1">3.78</rating>
<name>Nakata</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>217146.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34976" picture="188448.jpg">Fujita Akane</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95359" type="appears in" update="2018-05-04">
<rating votes="1">3.78</rating>
<name>Akira Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>217149.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2089" picture="151696.jpg">Morota Kaoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95360" type="appears in" update="2018-05-04">
<rating votes="4">7.37</rating>
<name>Kujou Chihiro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>217150.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="398" picture="17243.jpg">Miyamoto Mitsuru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95361" type="appears in" update="2018-05-04">
<rating votes="1">5.66</rating>
<name>Kosho Tenshu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He is the owner of the secondhand bookstore http://anidb.net/ch93201 [Kondou Masami] used to visit a lot when he was a student.</description>
<picture>217152.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="289" picture="186204.jpg">Nishimura Tomomichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95362" type="appears in" update="2018-05-04">
<rating votes="1">3.78</rating>
<name>Nurse</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>217154.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40893" picture="223270.jpg">Furukawa Yurina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95364" type="appears in" update="2018-05-04">
<rating votes="1">7.62</rating>
<name>Garden</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>217163.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="194514" update="2017-12-29">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-02-02</airdate>
<rating votes="11">7.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">漫ろ雨[そぞろあめ]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gentle Rain</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Petite pluie fine</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">보슬비</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sozoro Ame</title>
</episode>
<episode id="194515" update="2017-12-29">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-01-26</airdate>
<rating votes="12">8.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">雨雫[あめしずく]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Raining Tears</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une pluie de larmes</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">비의 눈물</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ameshizuku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="194516" update="2017-12-29">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-01-19</airdate>
<rating votes="13">8.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">青葉雨[あおばあめ]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rain Drops on Green Leaves</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La pluie sur les feuilles</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">푸른 잎 비</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aobaame</title>
</episode>
<episode id="194517" update="2018-01-12">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-01-11</airdate>
<rating votes="15">8.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">雨音[あまおと]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Sound of Rain</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le bruit de la pluie</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">빗소리</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Amaoto</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195106" update="2018-01-12">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-01-11</airdate>
<rating votes="3">9.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195107" update="2018-01-12">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-01-11</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195432" update="2018-01-24">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-03-02</airdate>
<rating votes="12">8.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">静雨[せいう]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Quiet Rain</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Pluie silencieuse</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">조용한 비</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seiu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195433" update="2018-01-24">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-02-23</airdate>
<rating votes="12">9.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">迅雨[じんう]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Heavy Rain</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Grosse averse</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">소나기</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jin`u</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195434" update="2018-01-24">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-02-16</airdate>
<rating votes="12">8.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">沙雨[さう]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fine Rain</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ondée</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">모래비</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sau</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195435" update="2018-01-24">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-02-09</airdate>
<rating votes="12">8.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">香雨[こうう]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Scent of Rain</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L’odeur de la pluie</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">비의 향기</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kouu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="196578" update="2018-02-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-03-30</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">つゆのあとさき</title>
<title xml:lang="en">After the Rain</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Après la pluie</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">장마가 지나간 후</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsuyu no Atosaki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="196579" update="2018-02-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-03-23</airdate>
<rating votes="11">6.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">叢雨[そうう]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Passing Shower</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Pluie passagère</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">지나가는 비</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Souu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="196580" update="2018-02-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-03-16</airdate>
<rating votes="12">8.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">白雨[はくう]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sudden Shower</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Soudaine averse</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">소나기</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hakuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="196581" update="2018-02-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-03-09</airdate>
<rating votes="12">7.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">愁雨[しゅうう]</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rain of Sorrow</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Pluie de tristesse</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">슬픈 비</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shuuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="202629" update="2018-07-08">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2018-04-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">プレミア先行上映イベント映像</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Premiere Advance Screening Event</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Premiere Senkou Jouei Event Eizou</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
