<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="12959" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2017-10-06</startdate>
<enddate>2017-12-22</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Kino no Tabi: The Beautiful World - The Animated Series</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Kino`s Journey (2017)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Kino no Tabi (2017)</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">キノの旅 -the Beautiful World- the Animated Series</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Kino`s Journey: The Beautiful World - The Animated Series</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Kinos Reise: Die wunderschöne Welt - Die animierte Serie</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Kino`s Journey</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">키노의 여행: The Beautiful World - The Animated Series</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">奇诺之旅 -the Beautiful World- the Animated Series</title>
<title xml:lang="es-LA" type="official">Kino`s Journey -the Beautiful World- the Animated Series</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="575" type="Alternative Setting">Kino no Tabi: The Beautiful World</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="15202" approval="26" total="31">Majo no Tabitabi</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="2">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="143561">This new series of Kino is not as beautiful as the old one of 2003. I recommend to see first that, and the next two animated films.

In this new series, the mystery about Kino`s character is missing, and certain details about his life are missing as well. It is also more superficial, a bit too "moe". The old episodes that are re-proposed are mediocre, but there are some very interesting new ones.

However, I liked it enough to recommend it, and I hope that they will continue to develop the adventures of Kino, possibly in the old style.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="36359">This series is episodic, though a few thin threads do link some episodes. Contrary to the first season, Kino`s presence is prominent in roughly half of the episodes. The quality of the story is very irregular in this season. Another difference is the presence of ugly CGI, which fortunately isn`t widespread enough to spoil the fun.

Despite those minor defects, I really enjoyed this. The strong points of the first season are all there: psychology, meeting strange traditions, cruel fables. I thought 5 episodes out of 12 were superb. Two of these were new takes of the first season, but enough time had passed so I just remembered the story, I wasn`t comparing every scene. Other episodes sprung various levels of interest, and I thought 2 of them were failures, but that didn`t stain the whole. I long for a third season with 12 original episodes.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.kinonotabi-anime.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="14230" type="Chief Animation Direction">Tachikawa Seiji</name>
<name id="24350" type="Direction">Taguchi Tomohisa</name>
<name id="27220" type="Animation Work">Lerche</name>
<name id="14333" type="Character Design">Amisaki Ryouko</name>
<name id="33391" type="Series Composition">Sugawara Yukie</name>
<name id="5617" type="Original Work">Shigusawa Keiichi</name>
<name id="14333" type="Chief Animation Direction">Amisaki Ryouko</name>
<name id="8977" type="Music">Dewa Yoshiaki</name>
</creators>
<description>The story follows the travels of http://anidb.net/ch7856 [Kino], a young adventurer who rides a talking motorcycle named http://anidb.net/ch7857 [Hermes]. They explore the people and cultures of different places throughout their adventures, spending only three days at each location.
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="998">6.58</permanent>
<temporary count="1000">7.09</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>225886.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19997</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>38179</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>35079</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.kinonotabi-anime.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Kino's_Journey</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>キノの旅</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4694</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>360027</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20482</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>kinonotabianime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>kinos-journey-the-beautiful-world-the-animated-series</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B07JKR53MQ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="308" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>detective</name>
<description>A detective is an investigator, generally either a member of a law enforcement agency or as an individual working in the capacity of private investigators, tasked with solving crimes and other mysteries, such as disappearances, by examining and evaluating clues and records in order to solve the mystery; for a crime, this would mean uncovering the criminal`s identity and/or whereabouts. In some police systems, a detective position is achieved by passing a written test after a person completes the requirements for being a police officer; in others, detectives are college graduates who join directly from civilian life without first serving as uniformed officers.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210906.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2619" parentid="2841" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>gunfights</name>
<description>Fights where two or more parties are firing guns at one another.</description>
<picurl>211280.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2634" parentid="2613" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>countryside</name>
<description>The anime takes place far from the any densely populated areas like cities, i.e. out in the suburbs, in the countryside with many fields and forests.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2838" parentid="2628" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>parallel world</name>
<description>A parallel world, parallel universe, or alternative reality is a self-contained separate reality coexisting with our own. Because "alternative reality" sometimes implies that the reality is a variant of our own, like for example a mirror world, we use the term "parallel world/universe" which is more general, without any connotations implying a relationship (or lack thereof) with our own world/universe (meaning a fictional world can just as well have an alternative reality, it doesn`t need to be our reality). To put it more simply, this category is to show if more than 1 world/universe/reality is present in the anime.
Multiple timelines of the same world/universe/reality are NOT considered parallel worlds. For example, in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate] the cast travels through multiple "World Lines", which are defined as parallel timelines of the same universe had various events occurred with differing outcomes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2866" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>slavery</name>
<description>Someone is owned by somebody else. In anime this usually affects body (slaves in a fantasy setting) or mind (the evil villain brainwashes a sidekick, creates an obedient minion or places a spell on some poor bloke). Slavery is also a common element of hentai.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2882" parentid="2952" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-17">
<name>dystopia</name>
<description>A dystopia (from Ancient Greek: δυσ-, "bad, ill", and Ancient Greek: τόπος, "place, landscape"; alternatively cacotopia, or anti-utopia) is, in literature, an often futuristic society that has degraded into a repressive and controlled state, often under the guise of being utopian. Dystopian literature has underlying cautionary tones, warning society that if we continue to live how we do, this will be the consequence. A dystopia, thus, is regarded as a sort of negative utopia and is often characterized by an authoritarian or totalitarian form of government. Dystopias usually feature different kinds of repressive social control systems, a lack or total absence of individual freedoms and expressions and constant states of warfare or violence. Dystopias often explore the concept of humans abusing technology and how humans individually and collectively cope with technology that has evolved too quickly such as the car, the flamethrower or the microwave. A dystopian society is also often characterized by widespread poverty and brutal political controls such as a large military-like police.</description>
<picurl>69879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2952" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-06">
<name>rotten world</name>
<description>A rotten world is a setting or situation where the jaded notion that "anything that can go wrong will go horribly wrong" almost always applies. Oppression, perpetual warfare, lawlessness, despair or other forms of mental instability, and other highly undesirable factors tend to be rampant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3138" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-08">
<name>fictional language</name>
<description>Fictional languages are intended to be the languages of a fictional world and are often designed with the intent of giving more depth and an appearance of plausibility to the fictional worlds with which they are associated, and to have their characters communicate in a fashion which is both alien and dislocated.
Some of these languages, e.g. in worlds of fantasy fiction, alternative universes, Earth`s future, or alternate history, are presented as distorted versions or dialects of modern English or other natural language, while others are independently designed conlangs.
A fictional language often has the least amount of grammar and vocabulary possible, and rarely extends beyond the absolutely necessary. At the same time, some others have developed languages in detail for their own sake, such as J. R. R. Tolkien`s Quenya and Sindarin and Star Trek`s Klingon language which exist as functioning, usable languages. Here "fictional" can be a misnomer.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3150" parentid="4522" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>social class issues</name>
<description>A character`s standing in society is cause of many issues. More generally, the society`s class structure is the source of many problems in the anime.
A common example is class division; a strong and rigid class division between rich/elite and poor/commoners, with the elites having disproportionately more privilege than the common class.
This can be applied not only when royalty and nobility are present, but also dystopian societies display often these divisions.
Another example is a division between employees and management, with employees akin to the common class, and management akin to the elite class.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3227" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-06-24">
<name>introspection</name>
<description>The characters in this anime do not walk through life simply accepting how they are, but quite on the contrary constantly try to understand their own motives, feelings and reactions to the other protagonists. 
This self-searching included the questions: "Who am I?", "What makes me tick?", "What do I want?", "What do others expect of me?", etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3276" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-02">
<name>plot twists</name>
<description>The plot and story of this anime may seem to be going along a quite predictable path, when suddenly there is a jarring unexpected twist in the plot, taking the viewer by surprise.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3285" parentid="2850" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true">
<name>journey</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3805" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-13">
<name>European stylised</name>
<description>The anime`s setting is crafted in some classic European style. Imagine an architectural and cultural mix of London, Paris, Rome, Berlin, Prague, and other cities as they were at any point in the 19th century or earlier.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3929" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-09">
<name>sociocultural evolution</name>
<description>Describes how cultures and societies develop over time, based on both cultural evolution and social evolution.
A post-apocalyptic or a Utopian setting would show very interesting changes in human behaviour, mental state, or simply daily life.</description>
<picurl>191062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3953" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-10-04">
<name>in medias res</name>
<description>In medias res, also medias in res (Latin for "into the midst of affairs (lit. into mid-affairs)"), refers to a literary and artistic technique where the narrative starts in the middle of the story instead of from its beginning. It is generally a plot-driven concept rather than a character-driven one; though characters are commonly used to provide the backstory. The characters, setting, and conflict are often introduced through a series of http://anidb.net/t4299 [flashbacks] or through characters relating past events to each other.
Probably originating from an oral tradition, the technique is a convention of epic poetry, one of the earliest and most prominent examples in Western literature being Homer`s Odyssey and Iliad. Virgil`s Aeneid began the tradition in literature of imitating Homer, continued in Torquato Tasso`s Jerusalem Delivered, John Milton`s Paradise Lost and "Inferno" from Dante`s Divine Comedy. George Lucas`s Star Wars saga was told using in medias res.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4096" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>gore</name>
<description>A Splatter film or Gore film is a sub-genre of horror film that deliberately focuses on graphic portrayals of gore and graphic violence. These films, through the use of special effects and excessive blood and guts, tend to display an overt interest in the vulnerability of the human body and the theatricality of its mutilation. Due to their willingness to portray images society might consider shocking, splatter films share some ideological grounds with the transgressive art movement. The term "splatter cinema" was coined by George A. Romero to describe his film Dawn of the Dead, though Dawn of the Dead is generally considered by critics to have higher aspirations, such as social commentary, than to be simply exploitative for its own sake.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>32491.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4203" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>rebellion</name>
<description>Rebellion, uprising, or insurrection is a refusal of obedience or order. It may, therefore, be seen as encompassing a range of behaviors aimed at destroying or taking over the position of an established authority such as a government, governor, president, political leader, financial institution, or person in charge. On the one hand the forms of behaviour can include non-violent methods such as the (overlapping but not quite identical) phenomena of civil disobedience, civil resistance and nonviolent resistance. On the other hand it may encompass violent campaigns. Those who participate in rebellions, especially if they are armed rebellions, are known as "rebels".&#13;
&#13;
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>163803.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4227" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-03">
<name>detailed landscapes</name>
<description>An amazing view of nature, of artificially sculpted landscapes (i.e. gardens), or of a cityscape.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4257" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-08-07">
<name>survival</name>
<description>The theme/genre of survival typically depicts the act or process of continuing to live, generally in a hostile, possibly post-apocalyptic environment. Survival-centered media tends to be dark, set most commonly in a contemporary context, and generally leads either to small groups of people forming closely knit and functional units or to individuals turning against their fellows in a return to the survival of the fittest.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4281" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-04-11">
<name>mind games</name>
<description>An act or series of acts of calculated psychological manipulation, especially in order to confuse or intimidate.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4327" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-18">
<name>be careful what you wish for</name>
<description>Be careful what you wish for... your wish may actually come true. This is an age-old philosophical problem of what human beings think they want and what is actually good for them. The power to wish for anything can be very dangerous and usually — as a moral lesson — yields unexpected / unwanted results.
A contract with the devil is a specific case of this; receiving great power, especially from a devil, is usually a double edged sword.</description>
<picurl>230309.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4479" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-03">
<name>sense of foreboding</name>
<description>The anime starts off quietly, everything seems to be fine, but from episode to episode the signs that something ominous is about to happen increase. E.g. a typical mystery setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4521" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-28">
<name>lost technology</name>
<description>Any advanced technology or science-related knowledge that was lost for some reason fits the description. This could be technology from a time before a post-apocalyptic cataclysm, knowledge gained a long time ago but forgotten, or the relics of an old alien civilization only recently discovered.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4522" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>social commentary</name>
<description>Social commentary is the act of rebelling against an individual, or a group of people by rhetorical means. This is most often done with the idea of implementing or promoting change by informing the general populace about a given problem and appealing to people’s sense of justice. (Source: Wikipedia)&#13;
&#13;
Since this is anime, usually, the mores of Japan and the Japanese society are scrutinised, but not restricted to that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6019" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-01-20">
<name>brainwashing</name>
<description>Brainwashing, the application of coercive techniques to change the values and beliefs, perceptions and judgements, and subsequent mindsets and behaviours of one or more people, usually for political, financial, personal, or religious purposes. Often features in dark anime or pornography.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6972" parentid="2874" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-11-07">
<name>volcanic eruption</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="52973" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-04">
<rating votes="5">6.98</rating>
<name>Riku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Riku is a talking dog who travels with http://anidb.net/ch82564 [Shizu]. He is large, white, and his face seems to be always smiling.</description>
<picture>209248.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2488" picture="186147.jpg">Matsuda Ken`ichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90622" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-08-20">
<rating votes="4">9.24</rating>
<name>Ti</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>206467.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20762" picture="131325.jpg">Sakura Ayane</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90623" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-08-20">
<rating votes="8">7.60</rating>
<name>Shishou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>206465.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34901" picture="130616.jpg">Lynn</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90624" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-08-20">
<rating votes="2">7.85</rating>
<name>Aibou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>206466.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1692" picture="224934.jpg">Okitsu Kazuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91690" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-10-07">
<rating votes="2">9.38</rating>
<name>Sou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<picture>208014.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="187" picture="17002.jpg">Ogata Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91691" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-10-07">
<rating votes="4">5.58</rating>
<name>Photo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>208015.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21013" picture="201781.jpg">Minase Inori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91699" type="main character in" update="2017-10-07">
<rating votes="14">8.76</rating>
<name>Kino</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kino is sort of a valiant stoic cipher almost like a seinen hero. Kino comes off as androgynous and is considered male as often as female by the people she meets. Kino never talks much and never unnecessarily. She will lend a hand to someone in need and even risk her life for another but she does not purposely get involved in the affairs of others. Kino is often cynical and skeptical but you get the feeling deep down she still believes in people and the world. If Kino has one strong driving force and personality trait it seems to be curiosity. She will always investigate something if it seems intriguing and is sometimes the only reason she will interact with anyone.
Source: Reverse Thieves</description>
<picture>65434.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="1625" picture="226033.jpg">Yuuki Aoi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91700" type="main character in" update="2017-10-07">
<rating votes="4">9.45</rating>
<name>Hermes</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>Hermes is a talking Brough Superior motorcycle and is Kino`s loyal companion; although it can be reluctant sometimes, it faithfully accompanies Kino through all their travels. The relationship between Kino and Hermes is presented as symbiotic — as explained in the Land of Adults where Hermes provides speed, and Kino provides balance. In the first couple of episodes of the anime and almost all of the chapter in the novels, it has a tendency to mispronounce words and phrases. Its name is a reference to the Greek god Hermes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>208016.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36680" picture="153752.jpg">Saitou Souma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92499" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-26">
<rating votes="4">5.78</rating>
<name>Shizu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shizu is a young man with a great talent for swordsmanship. He travels in a dune buggy with http://anidb.net/ch52973 [Riku], his talking dog companion.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>209247.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39792" picture="176251.jpg">Umehara Yuuichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93651" type="appears in" update="2018-02-07">
<name>Zakkaya no Tenshu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212784.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32890" picture="89265.jpg">Nogawa Masashi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97533" type="appears in" update="2018-08-18">
<name>Regel</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>222477.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2271" picture="23219.jpg">Shibata Hidekatsu</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="190928" update="2017-10-27">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-10-27</airdate>
<rating votes="9">5.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">船の国</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Ship Country</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le pays-navire</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">배의 나라</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fune no Kuni</title>
<summary>Shizu and Riku arrive in a country known as the "Ship Country." It sails from continent to continent, trading goods and taking on travelers willing to work on the ship. The country`s leader gives Shizu the job of overseeing the common people, but he says he`d rather work alongside them. His wish is granted, and he`s given a girl called Ti to be his guide.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>749563</identifier>
<identifier>kinos-journey-the-beautiful-world-the-animated-series</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="190929" update="2017-10-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-10-20</airdate>
<rating votes="11">3.88</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">迷惑な国</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bothersome Country</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le pays problèmatique</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">피해를 주는 나라</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Meiwaku na Kuni</title>
<summary>Kino is napping in his hammock when the ground suddenly begins to shake. The shaking grows stronger, and a huge, ashen country wall appears. Kino and Hermes are shocked at the sight of the moving country. When Kino gives waving his hand a try, the moving country asks if he would like to enter. They welcome Kino in and he spends several days aboard the constantly moving country, until...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>749561</identifier>
<identifier>kinos-journey-the-beautiful-world-the-animated-series</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="190930" update="2017-10-13">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-10-13</airdate>
<rating votes="12">6.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">コロシアム</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Colosseum</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le Colisée</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">콜로세움</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Colosseum</title>
<summary>Kino arrives at a country he`s wanted to visit for a while. While he had high hopes for it after hearing it was a wonderful country, everything had changed with transition to a new king.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>749559</identifier>
<identifier>kinos-journey-the-beautiful-world-the-animated-series</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="190931" update="2017-10-06">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-10-06</airdate>
<rating votes="13">6.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">人を殺すことができる国</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Country Where People Can Kill Others</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le pays où l`on a le droit de tuer</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">사람을 죽여도 되는 나라</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hito o Korosu Koto ga Dekiru Kuni</title>
<summary>Kino and Hermes meet a young man on their travels. He planned to move to the country that lay up ahead, but according to him, murder isn`t prohibited by law there, and a vicious criminal has escaped to that land.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>749557</identifier>
<identifier>kinos-journey-the-beautiful-world-the-animated-series</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="191509" update="2017-10-14">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-10-06</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="191663" update="2017-10-14">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-10-13</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="191967" update="2017-11-24">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-11-24</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">電波の国</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Country of Radio Waves</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le pays des ondes</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">전파의 나라</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Denpa no Kuni</title>
<summary>Shizu begins his journey in search of a permanent residence along with Riku and Ti. After their group arrives at a country with stable order and a good economy, they take their time surveying the nation.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>749571</identifier>
<identifier>kinos-journey-the-beautiful-world-the-animated-series</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="191968" update="2017-11-27">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-11-17</airdate>
<rating votes="9">5.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">歴史のある国</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Historic Country</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`histoire d`un pays</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">역사가 있는 나라</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rekishi no Aru Kuni</title>
<summary>Kino tells Hermes a story.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>749569</identifier>
<identifier>kinos-journey-the-beautiful-world-the-animated-series</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="191969" update="2017-11-10">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-11-10</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">雲の中で</title>
<title xml:lang="en">In the Clouds</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Parmi les nuages</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">구름 속에서</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kumo no Naka de</title>
<summary>A group of travelers sets camp high up in a tall mountain range. The affluent group laughs together, wearing warm clothes, and prepares their dinner. Meanwhile, one girl works silently away.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>749567</identifier>
<identifier>kinos-journey-the-beautiful-world-the-animated-series</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="191970" update="2017-11-03">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-11-03</airdate>
<rating votes="9">5.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">嘘つき達の国</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Country of Liars</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le pays des menteurs</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">거짓말쟁이들의 나라</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Usotsuki-tachi no Kuni</title>
<summary>A cold wind blows with early winter. After receiving permission to stay in a country for three days, Kino and Hermes encounter a man who`s waiting for his lover`s return. After parting ways with him, Kino is welcomed by the residents in town.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>749565</identifier>
<identifier>kinos-journey-the-beautiful-world-the-animated-series</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="193055" update="2017-12-22">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-12-22</airdate>
<rating votes="9">2.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">羊たちの草原</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fields of Sheep</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La prairie des moutons</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">양들의 초원</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hitsuji-tachi no Sougen</title>
<summary>Framed by the warm sun, Kino passes through verdant, rocky plains. Beside the road, Kino spots some peaceful, napping sheep... who stand up and charge. A heated chase ensues until Kino is driven off a cliff by the herd of violent sheep.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>749579</identifier>
<identifier>kinos-journey-the-beautiful-world-the-animated-series</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="193056" update="2017-12-15">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-12-15</airdate>
<rating votes="11">7.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大人の国</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Country of Adults</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le pays des adultes</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">어른의 나라</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Otona no Kuni</title>
<summary>A girl going through her "Final Week" before becoming an adult meets a traveler named Kino. Kino travels a world unknown to the girl, the world outside her nation`s walls, living life freely.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>749577</identifier>
<identifier>kinos-journey-the-beautiful-world-the-animated-series</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="193057" update="2017-12-08">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-12-08</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">優しい国</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kind Country</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le pays accueillant</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">친절한 나라</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yasashii Kuni</title>
<summary>A small country lies surrounded by mountains. Blessed with beautiful forests, the country is still very poorly rated by travelers. The rumors were so bad they drew Kino`s interest, who decides to visit the country with Hermes.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>749575</identifier>
<identifier>kinos-journey-the-beautiful-world-the-animated-series</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="193058" update="2017-12-02">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-12-01</airdate>
<rating votes="8">3.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">いろいろな国</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Various Countries</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Toutes sortes de pays</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">이런저런 나라</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Iroiro na Kuni</title>
<summary>On top of a mountain, an old bandit stands on lookout with a teenage boy. Together, they carefully size up their prey: a dark-haired man in a buggy with a girl and a dog, a single rider on a motorrad, and... In addition, Kino drinks tea and makes a meal.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>749573</identifier>
<identifier>kinos-journey-the-beautiful-world-the-animated-series</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="198785" update="2018-05-07">
<epno type="2">S27</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">多数決ドラマ『キノの旅 the Beautiful World 「廃墟の国」-On Your Way- 』27</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 27</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198786" update="2018-05-07">
<epno type="2">S26</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">多数決ドラマ『キノの旅 the Beautiful World 「廃墟の国」-On Your Way- 』26</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 26</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198787" update="2018-05-07">
<epno type="2">S25</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">多数決ドラマ『キノの旅 the Beautiful World 「廃墟の国」-On Your Way- 』25</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 25</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198788" update="2018-05-07">
<epno type="2">S24</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">多数決ドラマ『キノの旅 the Beautiful World 「廃墟の国」-On Your Way- 』24</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 24</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198789" update="2018-05-07">
<epno type="2">S23</epno>
<length>8</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">多数決ドラマ『キノの旅 the Beautiful World 「廃墟の国」-On Your Way- 』23</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 23</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198790" update="2018-05-07">
<epno type="2">S22</epno>
<length>7</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">多数決ドラマ『キノの旅 the Beautiful World 「廃墟の国」-On Your Way- 』22</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 22</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198791" update="2018-05-07">
<epno type="2">S21</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">多数決ドラマ『キノの旅 the Beautiful World 「廃墟の国」-On Your Way- 』21</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 21</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198792" update="2018-05-07">
<epno type="2">S20</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">多数決ドラマ『キノの旅 the Beautiful World 「廃墟の国」-On Your Way- 』20</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 20</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198793" update="2018-05-07">
<epno type="2">S19</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">多数決ドラマ『キノの旅 the Beautiful World 「廃墟の国」-On Your Way- 』19</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 19</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198794" update="2018-05-07">
<epno type="2">S18</epno>
<length>8</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">多数決ドラマ『キノの旅 the Beautiful World 「廃墟の国」-On Your Way- 』18</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 18</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198795" update="2018-05-07">
<epno type="2">S17</epno>
<length>7</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">多数決ドラマ『キノの旅 the Beautiful World 「廃墟の国」-On Your Way- 』17</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 17</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198796" update="2018-05-07">
<epno type="2">S16</epno>
<length>11</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">多数決ドラマ『キノの旅 the Beautiful World 「廃墟の国」-On Your Way- 』16</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 16</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198797" update="2018-05-07">
<epno type="2">S15</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">多数決ドラマ『キノの旅 the Beautiful World 「廃墟の国」-On Your Way- 』15</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 15</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198798" update="2018-05-07">
<epno type="2">S14</epno>
<length>7</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">多数決ドラマ『キノの旅 the Beautiful World 「廃墟の国」-On Your Way- 』14</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 14</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198799" update="2018-05-07">
<epno type="2">S13</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">多数決ドラマ『キノの旅 the Beautiful World 「廃墟の国」-On Your Way- 』13</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 13</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198800" update="2018-05-07">
<epno type="2">S12</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">多数決ドラマ『キノの旅 the Beautiful World 「廃墟の国」-On Your Way- 』12</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 12</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198801" update="2018-05-07">
<epno type="2">S11</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">多数決ドラマ『キノの旅 the Beautiful World 「廃墟の国」-On Your Way- 』11</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 11</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198802" update="2018-05-07">
<epno type="2">S10</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">多数決ドラマ『キノの旅 the Beautiful World 「廃墟の国」-On Your Way- 』10</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 10</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198803" update="2018-05-07">
<epno type="2">S9</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">多数決ドラマ『キノの旅 the Beautiful World 「廃墟の国」-On Your Way- 』9</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 9</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198804" update="2018-05-07">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">多数決ドラマ『キノの旅 the Beautiful World 「廃墟の国」-On Your Way- 』8</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 8</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198805" update="2018-05-07">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">多数決ドラマ『キノの旅 the Beautiful World 「廃墟の国」-On Your Way- 』7</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198806" update="2018-05-07">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">多数決ドラマ『キノの旅 the Beautiful World 「廃墟の国」-On Your Way- 』6</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198807" update="2018-05-07">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>4</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">多数決ドラマ『キノの旅 the Beautiful World 「廃墟の国」-On Your Way- 』5</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198808" update="2018-05-07">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>6</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">多数決ドラマ『キノの旅 the Beautiful World 「廃墟の国」-On Your Way- 』4</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198809" update="2018-05-07">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>8</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">多数決ドラマ『キノの旅 the Beautiful World 「廃墟の国」-On Your Way- 』3</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198810" update="2018-05-07">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>7</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">多数決ドラマ『キノの旅 the Beautiful World 「廃墟の国」-On Your Way- 』2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198811" update="2019-07-06">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">多数決ドラマ『キノの旅 the Beautiful World 「廃墟の国」-On Your Way- 』1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Picture Drama 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198812" update="2018-05-07">
<epno type="4">T12</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview 12</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198813" update="2018-05-07">
<epno type="4">T11</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview 11</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198814" update="2018-05-07">
<epno type="4">T10</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview 10</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198815" update="2018-05-07">
<epno type="4">T9</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview 9</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198816" update="2018-05-07">
<epno type="4">T8</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview 8</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198817" update="2018-05-07">
<epno type="4">T7</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview 7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198818" update="2018-05-07">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198819" update="2018-05-07">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198820" update="2018-05-07">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198821" update="2018-05-07">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198822" update="2018-05-07">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198823" update="2018-05-07">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="218521" update="2019-07-06">
<epno type="2">S28</epno>
<length>7</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Kino`s Journey: An Interview with Keiichi Sigsawa</title>
<summary>An Interview conducted by Funimation, included with the U.S. release</summary>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
