<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="13257" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2017-12-29</startdate>
<enddate>2018-03-27</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Sora yori mo Tooi Basho</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">そらよりもとおいばしょ</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Дальше, чем космос</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Sora Yori mo Tooi Basho: A Story That Leads to the Antarctica</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Uchuu yori mo Tooi Basho</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="short">Yorimoi</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">宇宙よりも遠い場所</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">A Place Further Than the Universe</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">A Place Further Than The Universe</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Место за пределами вселенной</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">우주보다 먼 곳</title>
<title xml:lang="cs" type="official">Vzdálenější než vesmír</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">比宇宙更远的地方</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="7874" approval="7" total="11">Hanasaku Iroha</anime>
<anime id="6257" approval="4" total="14">K-On!</anime>
<anime id="6783" approval="3" total="10">Sora no Oto</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="3">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="498162">Very warm hearted and inspiring story.  Love the beginning and the end, when it talks about how each girls got to know each others, and why each joined this journey, also enjoy the end on how they became good friends and see how each of them has grown and learned how to face their issues.  I do find this anime falls short in the middle, especially whenever the story focus on individual character, the rest of the girls always have the same facial expression and reaction, this look and feel unreal.  Regardless, this is still a very positive and encouraging anime!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="396857">Good show. Everyone else already covered everything, so I`ll just add that while in the show they make a big deal out of how difficult it is for civilians, never mind highschoolers, to go to Antarctica, but in real life, that`s not actually the case. You can order cruises there online pretty easily. :-P And with the 1000000 yen, you could afford the ticket too, so yeah, that part is not actually accurate. But I guess it wouldn`t be as interesting or exciting if they made it that easy. Other than that, good drama (with a bit of comedy) anime I guess, though I don`t think it`s as sad or as good as other people here. I`ve seen many other anime series that affected me much more. But definitely worth watching.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://yorimoi.com</url>
<creators>
<name id="731" type="Animation Work">Madhouse</name>
<name id="3630" type="Character Design">Yoshimatsu Takahiro</name>
<name id="1775" type="Series Composition">Hanada Jukki</name>
<name id="6692" type="Direction">Ishizuka Atsuko</name>
<name id="3630" type="Chief Animation Direction">Yoshimatsu Takahiro</name>
<name id="31562" type="Music">Fujisawa Yoshiaki</name>
</creators>
<description>That is a place further than the universe...
http://anidb.net/ch92205 [Tamaki Mari], also called Kimari by her friends, is a second-year high school student who wants to make the most out of her school years but never really gets around to starting anything. When her schoolmate http://anidb.net/ch92204 [Kobuchizawa Shirase] tells her about her resolution to go to the South Pole, Kimari is moved by her tenacity and decides to go with her...
Source: Tokyo Otaku Mode
Note: The first two episodes received an early screening at a special event held at Cinema Sunshine Ikebukuro on 27.12.2017. Also the first episode received a special preliminary delivery on dAnime Store on 28.12.2017 (limited to 500 viewers), on NicoNico Live on 29.12.2017 and on AbemaTV on 30.12.2017. The regular TV broadcast started on 02.01.2018.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1683">8.42</permanent>
<temporary count="1692">8.04</temporary>
<review count="1">7.00</review>
</ratings>
<picture>221627.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19828</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>37123</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>35839</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://yorimoi.com</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>A_Place_Further_Than_The_Universe</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>宇宙よりも遠い場所</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4786</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>361123</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20768</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>yorimoi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="26">
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=kFByZt2YdYA</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>a-place-further-than-the-universe</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="55" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-11">
<name>awards</name>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2836" parentid="7082" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Australia</name>
<description>Australia, officially the Commonwealth of Australia, is a sovereign country comprising the mainland of the Australian continent, the island of Tasmania and numerous smaller islands. It is the largest country in Oceania and the world`s sixth-largest country by total area. The neighbouring countries are Papua New Guinea, Indonesia and East Timor to the north; the Solomon Islands and Vanuatu to the north-east; and New Zealand to the south-east. Australia`s capital is Canberra, and its largest city is Sydney.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192049.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3013" parentid="55" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-10">
<name>Newtype Anime Award</name>
<description>This anime has won 1 or more Newtype Anime Award(s)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3028" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-17">
<name>real-world location</name>
<description>Places seen in the show exist in reality.
Note: This could be sometime in the future, though names and certain places will still be recognizable.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3092" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-03-02">
<name>important haircut</name>
<description>When a character cuts off his or her hair, it often symbolizes a rite of passage or bout of character growth. A princess striking out on an adventure, or a new recruit at boot camp, for instance. Hair is something that takes time and effort to grow, so parting with it voluntarily can be a powerful act.
This is particularly a big deal when women get haircuts. Yet in fiction, even an accidental hair slicing can leave a character with a surprisingly even cut.
In many religions (Western Christianity, Ancient Egyptian religion, and others) priests and/or monks cut/shave their hair. Roman Catholic nuns also tend to cut and mantain their hair short under their veils when they enter the nunneries. The cutting of one`s own hair is also a part of Buddhist mythology, specifically something done by Siddhartha himself early on in his path to enlightenment, so anime examples might draw from this as an allusion. There are also some cultures, including Native American and many Asians, where a person would cut his or her hair as an act of grief, disgrace, or even rebellion. In the Confucian tradition, hair (like the rest of your body) is considered a gift from your parents and may not be damaged without a very good reason. Furthermore, prisoners and psychiatric patients commonly have their heads shaved, often to prevent the spread of lice, but sometimes also as a demeaning measure.
Source: TVTRope</description>
<picurl>169641.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3285" parentid="2850" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true">
<name>journey</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3394" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-25">
<name>environmentalism</name>
<description>Environmental protection is a practice of protecting the natural environment on individual, organizational or governmental levels, for the benefit of both the natural environment and humans. Due to the pressures of population and technology, the biophysical environment is being degraded, sometimes permanently. This has been recognized, and governments have begun placing restraints on activities that cause environmental degradation. Since the 1960s, activity of environmental movements has created awareness of the various environmental issues.
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3741" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-25">
<name>bullying</name>
<description>Bullying is the use of force, threat, or coercion to abuse, intimidate, or aggressively dominate others. One who engages in bullying is known as a bully.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4083" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-04">
<name>drastic change of life</name>
<description>One or more characters in this series go through an event that makes them change their way of life drastically and permanently. This change might be voluntary, or against the character`s will.
Some examples might be an accident, the gaining of superpowers, or simply graduating.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4251" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-20">
<name>ensemble cast</name>
<description>A show with an ensemble cast focuses on a larger group of main characters in a single plot narrative; anime containing several segmented plot narratives (such as episodic or arc-based plots) are excluded. As such, it doesn`t really have a "main" or "lead" character; instead, every member of the central main character group plays an important part in the show`s grander scheme; no single character is more important or prominent than the others (equality of importance). Further, subplots (if any) lead by each character in the ensemble have equal weighting in importance (or lack of weight).

* In a show where no single main character is more important or prominent than the others, 4+ main characters is almost always an ensemble cast.
* A show with 3 main characters of equal importance is likely also an ensemble cast; equality of importance must be considered carefully.
* A show with 2 main characters of equal importance is generally not an ensemble cast situation; however, on an exception basis where neither main character is considered an antagonist, a 2-main-character anime may be considered an ensemble (e.g. http://anidb.net/a11829 [Kimi no Na wa.]).

Pictured: http://anidb.net/a9043 [K (anime)]</description>
<picurl>94914.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4498" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-20">
<name>heart-warming</name>
<description>The story and its characters give off good vibes — includes elevated feelings of affection such as tenderness, sympathy and love, all in one package.
The kind of anime which leaves you with a warm feeling inside and you can not stop smiling while watching it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4874" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-05-14">
<name>overcoming adversity</name>
<description>Hang in there!
Overcoming problems of different variety.
Sometimes the journey is as important as the goal.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5151" parentid="3394" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-31">
<name>man vs nature</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5407" parentid="2630" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-30">
<name>Pacific Ocean</name>
<description>The Pacific Ocean is the largest of the Earth`s oceanic divisions. It extends from the Arctic in the north to the Southern Ocean (or, depending on definition, to Antarctica) in the south, bounded by Asia and Australia in the west, and the Americas in the east.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192046.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5604" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-04">
<name>following one`s dream</name>
<description>No matter what the hardships may be, at least one of the protagonists in this anime is following her/his dream.
Examples: To become a professional athlete, a musician, a painter or the ruler of this world!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5790" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-30">
<name>family without mother</name>
<description>For some reason, the protagonist`s mother is no longer among the living. The much-too-early death was due to sickness or accident.
This plot device adds a certain degree of tragedy to the anime, and usually has repercussions on the rest of the family. For example: the grief-stricken father and children barely function as humans; the oldest daughter has an extra burden of raising the other children, additional emphasis is given to the only female child in the family, i.e. with bishounen brother and dad in a shoujo setting.
In rare cases the mother may still be alive, just not living with the rest of the family presently, i.e. on some quest or job and gone for a long time.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5956" parentid="2862" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-13">
<name>broken friendship</name>
<description>For a broken friendship a group of three friends is a must, the break up can be caused by betrayal or death, a love triangle is also possible. The ghost of the old friendship will be the cause of many flashbacks and reminiscences. A dreaded face to face could be a major event or just used as plot device.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6191" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-05">
<name>card games</name>
<description>A card game is any game using playing cards as the primary device with which the game is played, be they traditional or game-specific. Countless card games exist, including families of related games (such as poker). A small number of card games played with traditional decks have formally standardized rules, but most are folk games whose rules vary by region, culture, and person.
Many games that are not generally placed in the family of card games do in fact use cards for some aspect of their gameplay. Similarly, some games that are placed in the card game genre involve a board. The distinction is that the gameplay of a card game primarily depends on the use of the cards by players (the board is simply a guide for scorekeeping or for card placement), while board games (the principal non-card game genre to use cards) generally focus on the players` positions on the board, and use the cards for some secondary purpose.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7082" parentid="2630" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-07">
<name>Oceania</name>
<description>Oceania is a geographic region comprising Melanesia, Micronesia, Polynesia and Australasia. Situated in the southeast of the Asia Pacific region, Oceania is the smallest continental grouping in land area and the second smallest in population after Antarctica.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214397.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7169" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-13">
<name>Antarctic</name>
<description>The Antarctic is a polar region around the http://anidb.net/t2630 [Earth`s] South Pole, including the continent of Antarctica and nearby islands.
In popular culture, the Antarctic is known not only as the land of snow and penguins, but also as a good place to find a secret http://anidb.net/t3342 [Nazi] base, frozen alien spacecraft, or ruins of old &amp; cryptic civilisation.</description>
<picurl>10572.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7496" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-02-01">
<name>preaired episodes</name>
<description>An anime has preaired episodes when one or more episodes, generally the first ones, were aired ahead of the usual schedule.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="62619" type="cameo appearance in" update="2014-03-10">
<rating votes="86">6.56</rating>
<name>Hatsuse Izuna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>151404.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="62620" type="cameo appearance in" update="2014-08-20">
<rating votes="180">7.47</rating>
<name>Shiro</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A truant, hikikomori, deadbeat game girl. The other-half member of http://anidb.net/ch67042 [『　　』], and http://anidb.net/ch62621 [Sora]`s little sister. She`s a beautiful girl with red eyes and pure white hair. She`s a genius who learned to speak in just one year after birth, mastered multiple languages and advanced mathematics by age 3, and is capable of calculating future events to a degree that`s almost clairvoyant.
Source: ANN</description>
<picture>147835.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="62621" type="cameo appearance in" update="2014-08-20">
<rating votes="118">8.38</rating>
<name>Sora</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A virgin, neet, deadbeat game boy. The one-half of http://anidb.net/ch67042 [『　　』] and http://anidb.net/ch62620 [Shiro]`s older brother. He excels at bargaining and has excellent skill in mind-reading. Since his gaming style invokes inspiration, conversion of ideas, and overturning premises, Sora excels at games which include lots of unidentified variables.
Source: ANN</description>
<picture>147834.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="92203" type="main character in" update="2018-04-07">
<rating votes="40">9.05</rating>
<name>Miyake Hinata</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Miyake Hinata is a girl brimming with curiosity and always looking for fun things to do. She is very friendly and can get along well with everyone. Since childhood, she has been a leader who has always willingly taken on roles of responsibility, such as class committee and club leader. However, she quit high school because of something that happened and is now working part-time at a convenience store.
Source: kadokawa</description>
<picture>209466.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="516" picture="34813.jpg">Iguchi Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92204" type="main character in" update="2018-04-07">
<rating votes="60">8.45</rating>
<name>Kobuchizawa Shirase</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kobuchizawa Shirase is a second-year high school student who attends the same school as Kimari. She is a black-haired beauty that turns heads, but she is shy and not good at conversation. When she actually does speak, she can`t help but say rather nasty things, which leads to misunderstandings. She has few friends and is treated as an oddball at school. At school, she is secretly called "Antarctica."
Source: kadokawa</description>
<picture>209465.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="176" picture="192484.jpg">Hanazawa Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92205" type="main character in" update="2018-04-07">
<rating votes="22">7.99</rating>
<name>Tamaki Mari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tamaki Mari is a second-year high school student a sunny disposition. Although she has a great attitude and is admired by her friends, she is not good at finding a place in their midst or being a leader. In spite of being filled with curiosity, she is also rather cowardly and timid. She is troubled by the dilemma that although part of her wants to do things, another part of her just ends up not doing them. Her nickname is "Kimari."
Source: kadokawa</description>
<picture>209463.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21013" picture="201781.jpg">Minase Inori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92206" type="main character in" update="2018-04-07">
<rating votes="37">8.45</rating>
<name>Shiraishi Yuzuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shiraishi Yuzuki is a girl who is one grade lower than Kimari and the others. She lives in Hokkaido. She has been an actress since childhood, and she now works as an entertainer while attending high school. She shows maturity and is a good speaker with has polite manners. She is concerned that because of always working, she is unable to make close friends.
Source: kadokawa</description>
<picture>209467.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2296" picture="189623.jpg">Hayami Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92755" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-12-13">
<rating votes="12">6.79</rating>
<name>Maekawa Kanae</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>210643.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1799" picture="156027.jpg">Hikasa Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92756" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-12-13">
<rating votes="8">5.02</rating>
<name>Tamaki Rin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>210646.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43552" picture="179144.jpg">Hondo Kaede</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92757" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-12-13">
<rating votes="7">3.38</rating>
<name>Shiraishi Tamiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>210647.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="74" picture="84835.jpg">Oohara Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92758" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-12-13">
<rating votes="20">6.98</rating>
<name>Toudou Gin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>210642.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92759" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-12-13">
<rating votes="15">5.09</rating>
<name>Takahashi Megumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>210645.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12266" picture="56026.jpg">Kanemoto Hisako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92760" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-12-13">
<rating votes="10">5.84</rating>
<name>Samejima Yumiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>210644.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34901" picture="130616.jpg">Lynn</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93205" type="appears in" update="2018-01-07">
<rating votes="1">8.07</rating>
<name>Kimari no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211693.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="442" picture="187043.jpg">Honda Takako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93551" type="appears in" update="2018-02-02">
<name>Sasaki Yume</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212578.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="424" picture="224027.jpg">Endou Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93552" type="appears in" update="2018-02-02">
<name>Yasumoto Honami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212579.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16085" picture="178446.jpg">Komatsu Mikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93553" type="appears in" update="2018-02-02">
<name>Himi Dai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212576.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4821" picture="186259.jpg">Fukushima Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93554" type="appears in" update="2018-02-02">
<name>Zaizen Toshio</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212575.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20249" picture="186289.jpg">Matsuoka Yoshitsugu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93555" type="appears in" update="2018-02-02">
<name>Todoroki Nobue</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212577.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="479" picture="222800.jpg">Asumi Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93556" type="appears in" update="2018-02-02">
<name>Mukai Chiaki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212574.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3185" picture="171529.jpg">Terasoma Masaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95052" type="appears in" update="2018-04-17">
<rating votes="1">6.09</rating>
<name>Kobuchizawa Takako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>216288.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20497" picture="252298.jpg">Kayano Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95584" type="appears in" update="2018-05-14">
<rating votes="1">3.78</rating>
<name>Tamaki Mari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>217623.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21013" picture="201781.jpg">Minase Inori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95585" type="appears in" update="2018-05-14">
<rating votes="1">7.62</rating>
<name>Takahashi Megumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>217624.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12266" picture="56026.jpg">Kanemoto Hisako</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="194113" update="2018-01-30">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-01-23</airdate>
<rating votes="20">6.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">四匹のイモムシ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Four Caterpillars</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les quatre chenilles</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">네 마리 유충</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yonhiki no Imomushi</title>
<summary>Kimari and the others finally have their tickets to Antarctica. However, they`ll need to go on a three-day summer training camp to learn the skills they`ll need. In the mountains, they experience everything from lectures to field work, and meet the team commander, who seems to have a history with Shirase.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>757775</identifier>
<identifier>a-place-further-than-the-universe</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="194114" update="2018-01-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-01-16</airdate>
<rating votes="19">8.11</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">フォローバックが止まらない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Follow Backs Don`t Stop!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Follow-back irrésistible</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">맞팔이 멈추지 않아</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Follow Back ga Tomaranai</title>
<summary>Kimari, Shirase, and Hinata need to figure out a way that high school girls might be allowed to go to Antarctica. Although dubious about their chances, they quickly find a report about a high school-aged actress named Shiraishi Yuzuki, who`s being allowed to come along. Shirase attempts to make contact with Yuzuki`s agency, but it just so happens that Yuzuki has come to them.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>757773</identifier>
<identifier>a-place-further-than-the-universe</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="194115" update="2018-01-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-01-09</airdate>
<rating votes="20">6.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">歌舞伎町フリーマントル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kabukicho Fremantle</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">De Kabukichô à Fremantle</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">가부키초 프리맨틀</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kabuki-chou Fremantle</title>
<summary>To get on a ship to Antarctica, Kimari and Shirase will first need the money to fly from Japan to Fremantle, Australia. To earn this money, Kimari gets a job at a convenience store, where she meets a girl named Miyake Hinata. Hinata decides to join them on the trip, and quickly gets swept up in Shirase`s next plan...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>757771</identifier>
<identifier>a-place-further-than-the-universe</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="194116" update="2018-01-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-12-29</airdate>
<rating votes="19">8.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">青春しゃくまんえん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">One Mwillion Yen for Youth</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une jeunesse à un million</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">청춘 백만 엔</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seishun Shaku Man`en</title>
<summary>Tamaki Mari, AKA Kimari, really wanted to have a great adventure in high school, but could never take the first step. Now in her second year, she meets Kobuchizawa Shirase, a girl who is determined to go to Antarctica despite being told it`s impossible. Kimari is so moved by Shirase`s indomitable spirit that she vows to go to Antarctica with her.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>757769</identifier>
<identifier>a-place-further-than-the-universe</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="194669" update="2018-01-02">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-12-29</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195013" update="2018-01-09">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-01-09</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195198" update="2018-03-13">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-02-20</airdate>
<rating votes="18">7.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">吠えて, 狂って, 絶叫して</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Howling, Maddening, Screaming</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Crie, perds la raison, hurle</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">으르렁대고, 미치고, 절규하고</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hoete, Kurutte, Zekkyou Shite</title>
<summary>The ship sets out from Fremantle, heading for Antarctica. The girls interview crew members, peel potatoes, and get training to improve their stamina. But as exhausted as they are already, an even greater disaster awaits them!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>757783</identifier>
<identifier>a-place-further-than-the-universe</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="195199" update="2018-03-13">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-02-13</airdate>
<rating votes="19">7.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">宇宙を見る船</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Ship That Sees the Universe</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le navire d’où observer le ciel</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">우주를 보는 배</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uchuu o Miru Fune</title>
<summary>After arriving in Fremantle, the girls get a tour of their icebreaker ship. When Gin mentions that their new room was where Shirase`s mother once stayed, the girls check to see if she might have left something behind there...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>757781</identifier>
<identifier>a-place-further-than-the-universe</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="195200" update="2018-03-13">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-02-06</airdate>
<rating votes="20">7.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ようこそドリアンショーへ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Welcome to the Durian Show</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Bienvenue au Durian Show</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">두리안 쇼에 오신 걸 환영합니다</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Youkoso Durian Show e</title>
<summary>The girls have a stopover in Singapore on their way from Japan to Fremantle. They decide to spend their time sightseeing, but Yuzuki notices Hinata acting strangely.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>757779</identifier>
<identifier>a-place-further-than-the-universe</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="195201" update="2018-01-30">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-01-30</airdate>
<rating votes="19">7.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Dear my friend</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dear My Friend</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Dear My Friend</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">Dear my friend</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dear My Friend</title>
<summary>It`s been several months since their training, and the girls` trip to Antarctica is drawing near. With Rin`s help, Kimari manages to sort out her luggage, and in doing so, finds a game she borrowed from Megumi a long time ago. When she visits her friend to return it and talk about old times, though, Megumi doesn`t seem to remember it at all...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>757777</identifier>
<identifier>a-place-further-than-the-universe</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="196085" update="2018-04-06">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-03-27</airdate>
<rating votes="16">9.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">きっとまた旅に出る</title>
<title xml:lang="en">We`ll Go On Another Journey Someday</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">On repartira sans doute à l’aventure</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">꼭 다시 여행을 떠날 거야</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kitto Mata Tabi ni Deru</title>
<summary>Kimari wakes up to the sound of her alarm and goes through her duties for the day. The girls have gotten used to their lives in Antarctica, but the summer team will have to leave in three days. Their journey of a lifetime is reaching its end.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>757793</identifier>
<identifier>a-place-further-than-the-universe</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="196086" update="2018-04-06">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-03-20</airdate>
<rating votes="21">9.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">宇宙よりも遠い場所</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Place Further Than the Universe</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un endroit plus loin que le ciel</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">우주보다 먼 곳</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sora yori mo Tooi Basho</title>
<summary>Ever since her mother was lost in Antarctica, Shirase has felt like she was lost in a terrible dream. Despite her fear of what will happen if nothing changes after she goes, she and her friends now set off on their final journey to the place where her mother was lost.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>757791</identifier>
<identifier>a-place-further-than-the-universe</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="196087" update="2018-03-13">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-03-13</airdate>
<rating votes="18">8.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ドラム缶でぶっ飛ばせ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bash That Drum Can!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Tout envoyer valser avec un bidon !</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">드럼통으로 날려버려!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Drum Kan de Buttobase!</title>
<summary>When the girls are testing a video connection to Japan for New Year`s, a few of Hinata`s "friends" come calling. Hinata begs off, but seems distracted for the rest of the day. Shirase decides to get to the bottom of things.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>757789</identifier>
<identifier>a-place-further-than-the-universe</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="196088" update="2018-03-13">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-03-06</airdate>
<rating votes="17">7.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">パーシャル友情</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Partial Friendship</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Amitié congelée</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">파셜 우정</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Partial Yuujou</title>
<summary>At last, the girls have arrived in Antarctica, and are awed by the scene before them. No one`s been at Syowa Station in three years, so there`s a lot to do to get it cleaned up. As the girls keep themselves busy, Yuzuki seems to make up her mind about something.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>757787</identifier>
<identifier>a-place-further-than-the-universe</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="196089" update="2018-03-13">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-02-27</airdate>
<rating votes="17">8.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">南極恋物語 (ブリザード編)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Antarctic Love Story (Blizzard Arc)</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Histoire d’amour en Antarctique (chapitre du blizzard)</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">남극 사랑 이야기(블리자드 편)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nankyoku Koimonogatari (Blizzard Hen)</title>
<summary>Expedition member Toshio confesses his love for Gin, and asks if Shirase knows anything that might help him get closer to her. Shirase tells him that Gin was just a friend of her mother`s, so the girls insist that Shirase go to talk to Gin herself.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>757785</identifier>
<identifier>a-place-further-than-the-universe</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="210371" update="2018-11-18">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>35</length>
<rating votes="1">9.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">「南極ハイスクール」前編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">South Pole High School (Part One)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Nankyoku High School" Zenpen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="210372" update="2018-11-18">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>35</length>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">「南極ハイスクール」後編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">South Pole High School (Part Two)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Nankyoku High School" Kouhen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="231950" update="2020-08-22">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2017-12-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">宇宙よりも遠い場所 予告 WEB限定</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview Episode 1</title>
<summary>Web-exclusive next episode previews for Sora yori mo Tooi Basho released on Kadokawa anime official YouTube channel.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="231951" update="2020-08-22">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2018-01-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview Episode 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="231952" update="2020-08-22">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2018-01-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview Episode 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="231953" update="2020-08-22">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2018-01-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview Episode 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="231954" update="2020-08-22">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2018-01-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview Episode 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="231955" update="2020-08-22">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2018-02-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview Episode 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="231956" update="2020-08-22">
<epno type="2">S9</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2018-02-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview Episode 7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="231957" update="2020-08-22">
<epno type="2">S10</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2018-02-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview Episode 8</title>
</episode>
<episode id="231958" update="2020-08-22">
<epno type="2">S11</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2018-02-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview Episode 9</title>
</episode>
<episode id="231959" update="2020-08-22">
<epno type="2">S12</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2018-03-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview Episode 10</title>
</episode>
<episode id="231960" update="2020-08-22">
<epno type="2">S13</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2018-03-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview Episode 11</title>
</episode>
<episode id="231961" update="2020-08-22">
<epno type="2">S14</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2018-03-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview Episode 12</title>
</episode>
<episode id="231962" update="2020-08-22">
<epno type="2">S15</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2018-03-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Web Preview Episode 13</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
