<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="13256" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2017-10-02</startdate>
<enddate>2017-12-22</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Shoujo Shuumatsu Ryokou</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Последнее путешествие</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="synonym">رحلة الفتاتان الأخيرة</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">少女終末旅行</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Girls` Last Tour</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Girls` Last Tour</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Girls` Last Tour</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">소녀 종말 여행</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="official">少女終末旅行</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">少女终末旅行</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="575" approval="38" total="46">Kino no Tabi: The Beautiful World</anime>
<anime id="424" approval="33" total="33">Yokohama Kaidashi Kikou</anime>
<anime id="6783" approval="11" total="17">Sora no Oto</anime>
<anime id="9482" approval="3" total="6">Kamisama no Inai Nichiyoubi</anime>
<anime id="14491" approval="2" total="17">Dr. Stone</anime>
<anime id="3302" approval="2" total="11">Ergo Proxy</anime>
<anime id="13165" approval="2" total="8">Houseki no Kuni (2017)</anime>
<anime id="12681" approval="2" total="8">Made in Abyss</anime>
<anime id="14785" approval="2" total="4">Somali to Mori no Kamisama</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="4">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="579554">This series is pretty difficult to review. I pretty much agree with the ratings. The story can`t be any simpler. Artworks are somewhat unstylish and at first glance only the soundtrack appears to be good. The thing is, if the viewer can immerse himself with this show it completly changes the experience of watching it. This end of the world sequel is presented from the perspective of two girls, who don`t know a lot about their world and treat their situation with little concern. All in all this creates a beautiful yet intimidating atmosphere, which i can`t compare to anything i`ve ever seen before. 

To me personally the best series in 2017 and everything else is far behind.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://girls-last-tour.com</url>
<creators>
<name id="1555" type="Animation Work">White Fox</name>
<name id="15501" type="Character Design">Toda Mai</name>
<name id="7582" type="Series Composition">Fudeyasu Kazuyuki</name>
<name id="15075" type="Direction">Ozaki Takaharu</name>
<name id="50742" type="Original Work">Tsukumizu</name>
<name id="15501" type="Chief Animation Direction">Toda Mai</name>
<name id="2435" type="Music">Suehiro Ken`ichirou</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on http://anidb.net/cr50742 [Tsukumizu]`s post-apocalyptic slice of life seinen manga.
Civilization is dead, but http://anidb.net/ch91276 [Chito] and http://anidb.net/ch91277 [Yuuri] are still alive. So they hop aboard their beloved http://anidb.net/ch98375 [Kettenkrad] motorbike and aimlessly wander the ruins of the world they once knew. Day after hopeless day, they look for their next meal and fuel for their ride. But as long as the two are together, even an existence as bleak as theirs has a ray or two of sunshine in it, whether they`re sucking down their fill of soup or hunting for machine parts to tinker with. For two girls in a world full of nothing, the experiences and feelings the two share give them something to live for...
Source: Yen Press
Note: The first episode was streamed online on Abema TV on 02.10.2017. The regular television broadcast started on 06.10.2017. The first episode also received an early screening at a special event held at Toho Cinemas Nihonbashi in Tokyo on 30.09.2017.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1511">8.14</permanent>
<temporary count="1516">7.86</temporary>
<review count="2">8.25</review>
</ratings>
<picture>225885.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19827</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>36468</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>35838</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://girls-last-tour.com</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Girls'_Last_Tour</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>少女終末旅行</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4689</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>361125</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>362311</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20524</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>girls_last_tour</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B0767MQKZD</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="33">
<externalentity>
<identifier>少女终末旅行/21514450</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="39">
<externalentity>
<identifier>27081136</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="55" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-11">
<name>awards</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2857" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-10-04">
<name>anthropomorphism</name>
<description>Anthropomorphism is the attribution of uniquely human characteristics to non-human beings, inanimate objects, or natural or supernatural phenomena. If it`s an animal or an object (AI excluded) and it speaks and/or does other human-like things (dresses up) then we`re dealing with anthropomorphism.
Anthropomorphism leans more on the animal-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t7 [juujin], which leans more on the human-looking side.
Usage the tag image for reference, when tagging characters:

* This is a juujin.
* This is split between juujin and anthropomorphism, to be decided on a case-by-case basis, but most likely leans on the human-looking juujin side in most cases.
* This is anthropomorphism; tag both anthropomorphism and the respective animal type.
* This is anthropomorphism; tag both anthropomorphism and the respective animal type.
* This is just a regular animal; do not tag juujin or anthropomorphism — only tag the actual animal type.
</description>
<picurl>252666.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2923" parentid="2874" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-06-25">
<name>post-apocalyptic</name>
<description>An anime that takes place on future Earth (or it could be an alternative universe) after a major cataclysm has occurred. World War III, an alien invasion, plague, global warming or some other general disaster are common themes to build a post-apocalyptic world upon, where the effects were severe enough that mankind barely survived.
The time frame may be immediately after the catastrophe, focusing on the travails or psychology of survivors, or considerably later, often including the theme that the existence of pre-catastrophe civilization has been forgotten (or mythologised). Post-apocalyptic stories often take place in an agrarian, non-technological future world, or a world where only scattered elements of technology remain. There is a considerable degree of blurring between post-apocalyptic fiction and that which deals with false utopias or dystopian societies.</description>
<picurl>42081.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2926" parentid="2874" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>post-war</name>
<description>An armed conflict has ended not too long ago, devastation of the world or society is still evident.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2962" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-03-14">
<name>neo-noir</name>
<description>Neo-noir is a style that prominently utilizes elements of the now declined film noir, but with updated themes, content, style, visual elements, or media that were absent in films noirs of the 1940s and 1950s.
Films noirs were typically crime dramas or psychological thrillers featuring a pessimistic worldview and starring conflicted antiheroes trapped in difficult situations and making choices out of desperation or nihilistic moral systems, with crime, especially murder, being featured on the majority of them. Some of the most obvious visual elements included low-key lighting, striking use of light and shadow, black-and-white filming, and unusual camera placement such as low-angle, wide-angle, and Dutch angle shots.
Film noir is often associated with urban settings, private detectives, femmes fatales, and bleak endings, but they are not necessary to the genre; a large number of these films, including some of the genre classics, take place in small towns, suburbia, rural areas, or on the open road, feature neither character type, and have clearly happy endings.
Film noir and the early neo-noir would come to influence the formation of tech noir, a crossover of neo-noir and science fiction, in the late 1970s; some the most influencial tech noir works are the American movies Alien (1979), Blade Runner (1982), and The Terminator (1984). Tech noir itself would also help form http://anidb.net/t2861 [cyberpunk] in the early 1980s.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3285" parentid="2850" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true">
<name>journey</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3305" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-05-14">
<name>light-hearted</name>
<description>Not being burdened by trouble, worry, or care; happy and carefree.
Just a casual and feel-good watch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3573" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-25">
<name>ominous future</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3738" parentid="2202" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-05">
<name>aliens living on Earth</name>
<description>There`s an alien or a hive of aliens blending into society near you!</description>
<picurl>70750.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3759" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-11">
<name>teamwork</name>
<description>A cooperative effort by the members of a group or team to achieve a common goal.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3792" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-06">
<name>iyashi-kei</name>
<description>A feel good, "no true conflict within story" type of plot, instead about the daily musings and activities of the characters with an overall tranquil mood. Similar to "Slice of Life", but much more relaxed, peaceful and "zen".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3813" parentid="6185" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-23">
<name>winter</name>
<description>Coldest season of the year with ice and snow, everything is covered in a blanket of white.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3869" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-12">
<name>mono no aware</name>
<description>Literally "the pathos of things", also translated as "an empathy toward things," or "a sensitivity of ephemera"; a Japanese term used to describe the awareness of the transience of things and a gentle sadness (or wistfulness) at their passing.
Also frequently been translated as "the `ahh-ness` of things".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4150" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-02-01">
<name>everybody is nice</name>
<description>All characters are nice in their own way; nobody has ill intentions to others. Even if a secondary character appears to be bad at the beginning, they will redeem themselves or become tamed/pacified/neutralized swiftly.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4257" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-08-07">
<name>survival</name>
<description>The theme/genre of survival typically depicts the act or process of continuing to live, generally in a hostile, possibly post-apocalyptic environment. Survival-centered media tends to be dark, set most commonly in a contemporary context, and generally leads either to small groups of people forming closely knit and functional units or to individuals turning against their fellows in a return to the survival of the fittest.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4498" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-20">
<name>heart-warming</name>
<description>The story and its characters give off good vibes — includes elevated feelings of affection such as tenderness, sympathy and love, all in one package.
The kind of anime which leaves you with a warm feeling inside and you can not stop smiling while watching it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4510" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-10-05">
<name>desolate ruins</name>
</tag>
<tag id="4663" parentid="2605" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-31">
<name>tone changes</name>
<description>The anime switches quickly, often rather drastically between different moods or tones, sometimes even on the same scene.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5561" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-08-16">
<name>lonely atmosphere</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6029" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-04-08">
<name>mundane made awesome</name>
<description>Sometimes normal just doesn`t cut it. Eating: you put food in your mouth and chew. Playing sports: you throw a ball around. You need to make it awesome, no matter how mundane it is.
Let`s throw in some gripping orchestral music, lighting changes, different camera angles, something! Don`t write like a man, write like an evil overlord! Exaggerate your expressions and gestures, speak with excessive intonation, and if all else fails, throw in some close-ups, slow motion, and ominous Latin chanting! With practice, even you can turn something like eating chips into an epic battle of light and dark, blinding the viewer with sheer awesomeness.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>149443.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6349" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-13">
<name>multi-segment episodes</name>
<description>Multi-segment episodes are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t5852 [short episodes], which are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length (up to and including 10 minutes).
Also not to be confused with an OVA or music video with multiple (otherwise unrelated) full-length http://anidb.net/t7241 [bundled episodes] consolidated into a single episode video track.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7131" parentid="55" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-05">
<name>Crunchyroll Anime Awards</name>
<description>Crunchyroll Anime Awards are annual awards given to recognize anime from the previous year. The awards were first held in January 2017. The judges create a short list in different categories and public votes for the winners are held online.</description>
<picurl>219996.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="91276" type="main character in" update="2018-08-10">
<rating votes="29">8.63</rating>
<name>Chito</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nicknamed "Chii-chan," she has dark hair and a wide knowledge of machines. She drives the Kettenkrad. She is literate, unlike Yuuri, and an avid reader. She is generally calm and composed, but can be riled by Yuuri on occasion.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>208297.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21013" picture="201781.jpg">Minase Inori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91277" type="main character in" update="2018-08-10">
<rating votes="28">7.44</rating>
<name>Yuuri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nicknamed "Yuu," she has blonde hair and is more easy-going than Chito, and she is also proficient with rifles. She rides in the back of the Kettenkrad. She is rather gluttonous, often wanting to eat more than they have.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>208298.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28392" picture="224735.jpg">Kubo Yurika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91876" type="appears in" update="2017-10-20">
<rating votes="5">6.98</rating>
<name>Kanazawa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kanazawa is a traveler http://anidb.net/ch91276 [Chito] and http://anidb.net/ch91277 [Yuuri] meet while trying to find a path to the upper stratum of the city. He is a cartographer who wants to map the entire city.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>208629.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92253" type="appears in" update="2017-11-10">
<rating votes="8">6.87</rating>
<name>Ishii</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ishii is a scientist who lives in an abandoned airbase. When http://anidb.net/ch91276 [Chito] and http://anidb.net/ch91277 [Yuuri] encounter her, she enlists their help to build an airplane based on old records so that she can fly to another city.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>209542.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="197" picture="58661.jpg">Mitsuishi Kotono</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92348" type="appears in" update="2017-11-18">
<rating votes="2">8.62</rating>
<name>Imo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>209762.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40438" picture="158268.jpg">Ogami Shinnosuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92414" type="appears in" update="2017-11-24">
<rating votes="2">3.94</rating>
<name>Sakana</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>209871.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29961" picture="79252.jpg">Tezuka Hiromichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92571" type="appears in" update="2017-12-02">
<rating votes="2">3.94</rating>
<name>Sakana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>210117.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42648" picture="207956.jpg">Yoshino Yuna</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92572" type="appears in" update="2017-12-02">
<rating votes="5">7.06</rating>
<name>Jiritsu Kikai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>210118.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1678" picture="68277.jpg">Kaji Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92578" type="appears in" update="2017-12-02">
<rating votes="2">5.84</rating>
<name>Sakana (Bone)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>210162.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29961" picture="79252.jpg">Tezuka Hiromichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92683" type="appears in" update="2017-12-30">
<rating votes="7">8.89</rating>
<name>Nuko</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nuko is a mysterious creature that http://anidb.net/ch91276 [Chito] and http://anidb.net/ch91277 [Yuuri] pick up on their journey. It can shape shift to activate mechanisms and communicate via radio signals, and has a habit of eating bullets.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>210494.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="176" picture="192484.jpg">Hanazawa Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93075" type="appears in" update="2017-12-30">
<rating votes="4">4.91</rating>
<name>Eryngii</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211421.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="508" picture="140061.jpg">Shimamoto Sumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95865" type="appears in" update="2019-05-25">
<rating votes="2">1.92</rating>
<name>Ojiisan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Grandpa was raising http://anidb.net/ch91276 [Chito] and http://anidb.net/ch91277 [Yuuri] until a battle occured in their place of living. He then gave them http://anidb.net/ch98375 [Kettenkrad] to escape to safety. After that his state and whereabouts are unknown. During his earlier years he travelled to multiple places and gathered books.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>218414.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="564" picture="146195.jpg">Kiyokawa Motomu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="98375" type="appears in" update="2018-10-22">
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<name>Kettenkrad</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>Kettenkrad is http://anidb.net/ch91276 [Chito]`s and http://anidb.net/ch91277 [Yuuri]`s tracked motorcycle. It was built using German WW2-era SdKfz 2 as a model.</description>
<picture>224865.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="190932" update="2017-11-05">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-10-27</airdate>
<rating votes="14">5.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">写真 / 寺院</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Photograph / Temple</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Foto / Tempel</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Photos / Temple</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">사진 / 사원</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shashin / Jiin</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans">照片 / 寺院</title>
<summary>Chito and Yuuri are fixated on using their photograph machine, but they can`t seem to get it to work. As they travel, they find a long forgotten temple.
Source: amazon</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="190933" update="2017-11-05">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-10-20</airdate>
<rating votes="14">5.61</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">遭遇 / 都市 / 街灯</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Encounter / City / Streetlights</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Strassenlaternen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Réverbères</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">조우 / 도시 / 가로등</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Souguu / Toshi / Gaitou</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans">遭遇 / 都市 / 街灯</title>
<summary>Yuuri and Chito meet another person after he almost accidentally kills them. Will they help him with his request?
Source: amazon</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="190934" update="2017-11-05">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-10-13</airdate>
<rating votes="14">5.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">風呂 / 日記 / 洗濯</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bath / Journal / Laundry</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Bad / Tagebuch / Waschtag</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Bain / Journal intime / Lessive</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">목욕 / 일기 / 세탁</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Furo / Nikki / Sentaku</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans">洗澡 / 日记 / 洗衣</title>
<summary>Yuuri and Chito make their way through snow packed plains and begin to freeze. Will they be offered a reprieve from the cold?
Source: amazon</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="190935" update="2017-10-07">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-10-02</airdate>
<rating votes="16">5.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">星空 / 戦争</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Starry Sky / War</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Sternenhimmel / Krieg</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ciel étoilé / Guerre</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">별하늘 / 전쟁</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hoshizora / Sensou</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans">星空 / 战争</title>
<summary>Yuuri and Chito make it out of the dark cavern on their Kettenkrad but what will they find on the outside?
Source: amazon</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="191646" update="2017-10-13">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-10-13</airdate>
<rating votes="5">8.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="191647" update="2017-10-13">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-10-13</airdate>
<rating votes="5">8.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="191963" update="2017-11-30">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-11-24</airdate>
<rating votes="16">7.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">記憶 / 螺旋 / 月光</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Memories / Spiral / Moonlight</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Erinnerungen / Spirale / Mondlicht</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Souvenirs / Spirale / Clair de lune</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">기억 / 나선 / 달빛</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kioku / Rasen / Gekkou</title>
<summary>The girls continue their journey as they venture into the unknown. With heartfelt conversations, they find out more than they bargained for.
Source: amazon</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="191964" update="2017-11-30">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-11-17</airdate>
<rating votes="13">5.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">迷路 / 調理</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Labyrinth / Cooking</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Labyrinth / Backen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Labyrinthe / Cuisine</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">미로 / 요리</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Meiro / Chouri</title>
<summary>Stuck in a labyrinth of pipes, the girls struggle to find their way out. Meanwhile, they look to make some food for themselves. What do they come up with?
Source: amazon</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="191965" update="2017-11-17">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-11-10</airdate>
<rating votes="14">7.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">故障 / 技術 / 離陸</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Accident / Technology / Takeoff</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Abflug</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Décollage</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">고장 / 기술 / 이륙</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koshou / Gijutsu / Ririku</title>
<summary>An odd person with some ambitious goals enters into Chito and Yuuri`s journey. She is willing to help them but only if they will help her in return.
Source: amazon</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="191966" update="2017-11-05">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-11-03</airdate>
<rating votes="15">5.40</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">住居 / 昼寝 / 雨音</title>
<title xml:lang="en">House / Nap / The Sound of Rain</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Wohnen / Mittagsschlaf / Regenmusik</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Domicile / Sieste / Bruit de pluie</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">집 / 낮잠 / 빗소리</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Juukyo / Hirune / Amaoto</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans">住所 / 午睡 / 雨声</title>
<summary>The girls continue to explore the ruins and they come across a house. Meanwhile, they take a nap which triggers some strange dreams.
Source: amazon</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="192191" update="2017-11-04">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-10-20</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">少女週末授業 3じかんめ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Girls` Weekend Class: 3rd Period</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shoujo Shuumatsu Jugyou: 3 Jikanme</title>
</episode>
<episode id="192192" update="2017-10-24">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-10-13</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">少女週末授業 2じかんめ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Girls` Weekend Class: 2nd Period</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shoujo Shuumatsu Jugyou: 2 Jikanme</title>
</episode>
<episode id="192193" update="2017-10-24">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-10-06</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">少女週末授業 1じかんめ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Girls` Weekend Class: 1st Period</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shoujo Shuumatsu Jugyou: 1 Jikanme</title>
</episode>
<episode id="192351" update="2017-11-04">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-10-27</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">少女週末授業 4じかんめ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Girls` Weekend Class: 4th Period</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shoujo Shuumatsu Jugyou: 4 Jikanme</title>
</episode>
<episode id="192546" update="2017-11-04">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-11-03</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">少女週末授業 5じかんめ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Girls` Weekend Class: 5th Period</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shoujo Shuumatsu Jugyou: 5 Jikanme</title>
</episode>
<episode id="192768" update="2017-11-10">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-11-10</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">少女週末授業 6じかんめ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Girls` Weekend Class: 6th Period</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shoujo Shuumatsu Jugyou: 6 Jikanme</title>
</episode>
<episode id="193059" update="2017-12-27">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-12-22</airdate>
<rating votes="12">7.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">接続 / 仲間</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Connection / Friends</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Freunde</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Connexion / Amis</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">접속 / 동료</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Setsuzoku / Nakama</title>
<summary>The girls discuss their realization of loneliness but still have dreams of getting to the next level with an aspiration of reaching the moon one day.
Source: amazon</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="193060" update="2019-11-02">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-12-15</airdate>
<rating votes="11">7.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">文化 / 破壊 / 過去</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Culture / Destruction / The Past</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Kultur / Zerstörung / Vergangenheit</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Culture / Destruction / Passé</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">문화 / 파괴 / 과거</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bunka / Hakai / Kako</title>
<summary>As they continue their exploration, the girls run into some interesting creatures, and are left wandering an old weapons facility.
Source: amazon</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="193061" update="2019-11-02">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-12-08</airdate>
<rating votes="12">5.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">電車 / 波長 / 捕獲</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Train / Wavelength / Capture</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Zug / Wellenlänge / Jagd</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Train / Longueur d`onde / Capture</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">전차 / 파장 / 포획</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Densha / Hachou / Hokaku</title>
<summary>Yuuri and Chito explore the ruins of an old town and are left puzzled with the little relics that are left behind.
Source: amazon</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="193062" update="2019-11-02">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2017-12-01</airdate>
<rating votes="20">8.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">技術 / 水槽 / 生命</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Technology / Aquarium / Life</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Leben</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Vivant</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">기술 / 수조 / 생명</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gijutsu / Suisou / Seimei</title>
<summary>The girls end up in a new facility where they meet a maintenance robot. With a fish and a lonely robot, they find the meaning of what it means for something to be alive.
Source: amazon</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="193174" update="2017-11-18">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-11-17</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">少女週末授業 7じかんめ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Girls` Weekend Class: 7th Period</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shoujo Shuumatsu Jugyou: 7 Jikanme</title>
</episode>
<episode id="193446" update="2017-11-24">
<epno type="2">S8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-11-24</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">少女週末授業 8じかんめ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Girls` Weekend Class: 8th Period</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shoujo Shuumatsu Jugyou: 8 Jikanme</title>
</episode>
<episode id="193551" update="2019-11-02">
<epno type="2">S9</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-12-01</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">少女週末授業 9じかんめ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Girls` Weekend Class: 9th Period</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shoujo Shuumatsu Jugyou: 9 Jikanme</title>
</episode>
<episode id="193699" update="2019-11-02">
<epno type="2">S10</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-12-08</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">少女週末授業 10じかんめ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Girls` Weekend Class: 10th Period</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shoujo Shuumatsu Jugyou: 10 Jikanme</title>
</episode>
<episode id="193870" update="2019-11-02">
<epno type="2">S11</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-12-15</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.78</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">少女週末授業 11じかんめ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Girls` Weekend Class: 11th Period</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shoujo Shuumatsu Jugyou: 11 Jikanme</title>
</episode>
<episode id="194274" update="2017-12-24">
<epno type="2">S12</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2017-12-22</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">少女週末授業 12じかんめ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Girls` Weekend Class: 12th Period</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shoujo Shuumatsu Jugyou: 12 Jikanme</title>
</episode>
<episode id="214598" update="2019-04-02">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">少女終末旅行 10月からTVアニメ放送開始!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 1 (0:30): Girls` Last Tour TV Anime Broadcasting Starts in October!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shoujo Shuumatsu Ryokou Juugatsu kara TV Anime Housou Kaishi!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="214599" update="2019-04-02">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">少女終末旅行 Blu-ray &amp; DVD シリーズ発売決定!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 2 (0:15): Girls` Last Tour Blu-ray &amp; DVD Series Announcement</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shoujo Shuumatsu Ryokou Blu-ray &amp; DVD Series Hatsubai Kettei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="214600" update="2019-04-02">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="ja">少女終末旅行 Blu-ray &amp; DVD シリーズ好評発売中!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 3 (0:15): Girls` Last Tour Blu-ray &amp; DVD Series Now On Sale!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shoujo Shuumatsu Ryokou Blu-ray &amp; DVD Series Kouhyou Hatsubai Chuu!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="214601" update="2019-04-02">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview 1 (1:20)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="214602" update="2019-04-02">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview 2 (1:40)</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
