<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="13259" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>24</episodecount>
<startdate>2018-01-13</startdate>
<enddate>2018-07-07</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Darling in the Franxx</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">情迷弗兰克斯</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="short">ダリフラ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">DitF</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">darlifra</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ダーリン・イン・ザ・フランキス</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Darling in the Franxx</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Любимый во Франксе</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">달링 인 더 프랑키스</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="7591" approval="19" total="23">Star Driver: Kagayaki no Takuto</anime>
<anime id="22" approval="14" total="38">Shinseiki Evangelion</anime>
<anime id="4575" approval="5" total="17">Tengen Toppa Gurren Lagann</anime>
<anime id="1104" approval="4" total="7">Shinkon Gattai Godannar!!</anime>
<anime id="1531" approval="3" total="3">Sousei Seiki Devadasy</anime>
<anime id="9002" approval="2" total="20">Shinsekai yori</anime>
<anime id="1544" approval="2" total="16">Elfen Lied</anime>
<anime id="10766" approval="2" total="11">Cross Ange: Tenshi to Ryuu no Rondo</anime>
<anime id="416" approval="2" total="4">Blue Gender</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="12">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="540059">Aesthetically phenomenal, so beautiful. Felt the story was absolute chaff, no traction for me. I felt Gurren Lagan was painful to watch, except visually it was a treat jaja. my 2c</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="278012">DO NOT WATCH THIS FOR THE MECHA.
This anime is decent but if you`re going to watch it don`t go into it for the giant robots, go into it for teenagers becoming adults drama with some dosses of cute stuff. Personally I got mad at the show because I went in expecting some nice mecha fights but they were always short and never that cool serving more as a vehicle for the drama. If you watch it don`t watch for the robots, go in watching for the teen drama and cute stuff and you will enjoy it much more.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="171248">This anime is the optimal mixture of Chrome Shelled Regios and Gunbuster (and I meant it in a good way), with an excellent addition of romance. I recommend it to those who watched the above 2 but left a "something is missing" feeling. This one won`t disappoint you, and those who`ve seen Gunbuster will appreciate the conclusion more than the naysayers around ;)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="833543">This anime brings nothing new to the table (mashup from plots and details of other older works), but current rate way to low.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="786076">For a show based on mechas, the fights were pretty simple, things blowing up left and right for no apparent reason other than assumed OP.
The romance aspect was pretty good in this series. 
It was a good watch, cringy at times, and the ending felt super rushed, but a good watch anyway.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="614830">brilliant dystopic mecha. The more Evangelion-like story I`ve seen since Evangelion.
I still have to see the final, but no final can be more confused and displacing the the Hideaki Anno`s one....</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="109723">Slow start for fans of romance, but definitely worth it. It very much gave me the same feelings at the end that Eureka Seven did. Although Eureka Seven did it better, this show definitely deserves a watch. Two protagonists are lovable, capable, and realistic. The show gets better with each episode if you can tolerate the very "meh" start.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="615767">This series has truly left me astounded.  With my general dislike of the Mecha genre, this was a hard anime to start; but once I got going, hoo boy.  Almost everything about this series was absolutely stunning, and it ended on a wonderfully sweet note.  Even if you`re not a huge proponent of the Mecha genre, you owe it to yourself to watch this series.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="772709">Another amazing series from Studio Trigger. There are a lot of parallels between this Gurren Lagann. But it was unique enough to set it apart in a good way. A great story about finding one`s path in life and our relationships to each other.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="727529">doesn`t matter how much you read about this one, words can`t describe it. just watch it already, it`s so much more than you expect.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.darli-fra.jp</url>
<creators>
<name id="2210" type="Character Design">Tanaka Masayoshi</name>
<name id="3078" type="Series Composition">Nishigori Atsushi</name>
<name id="3078" type="Direction">Nishigori Atsushi</name>
<name id="29313" type="Work">Trigger</name>
<name id="1303" type="Work">A-1 Pictures</name>
<name id="34205" type="Series Composition">Hayashi Naotaka</name>
<name id="34207" type="Music">Tachibana Asami</name>
<name id="29313" type="Animation Work">Trigger</name>
<name id="55442" type="Animation Work">A-1 Pictures Kouenji Studio</name>
<name id="2210" type="Chief Animation Direction">Tanaka Masayoshi</name>
<name id="54910" type="Animation Work">Clover Works</name>
</creators>
<description>They dream of one day flying into the endless sky, even though they are painfully aware of how far away the sky is beyond the glass that blocks their flight.
The distant future: Humanity established the mobile fort city, Plantation, upon the ruined wasteland and civilization flourished. Within the city were pilot quarters called Mistilteinn, otherwise known as the "Birdcage." That is where the children live... Not knowing anything of the outside world, and unaware of the vast sky. Their only mission in life was the fight.
Their enemies are the mysterious giant organisms known as Kyoryu. The children operate robots known as FRANXX in order to face these still unseen enemies because they believe that is their purpose in life. Among them was a boy who was once called a child prodigy: Code number 016, http://anidb.net/ch92216 [Hiro]. However, now he`s a failure and considered unneeded. Those who cannot pilot FRANXX basically do not exist.
One day, a mysterious girl called http://anidb.net/ch92214 [Zero Two] appears in front of Hiro. From her face grew two alluring horns.
"I`ve found you, my Darling."
Source: crunchyroll</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2458">5.03</permanent>
<temporary count="2490">6.64</temporary>
<review count="3">4.16</review>
</ratings>
<picture>221577.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>19850</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>35849</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.darli-fra.jp</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Darling_in_the_Franxx</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ダーリン・イン・ザ・フランキス</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4788</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>361126</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20772</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>DARLI_FRA</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>darling-in-the-franxx</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B07PFXXCYK</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="55" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-11">
<name>awards</name>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1157" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>horny nosebleed</name>
<description>In Japanese media, healthy young men who have no other sexual outlet will often suffer nosebleeds upon seeing the naked female body, or even just a pair of well-filled panties.
The nosebleed is, of course, a visual shorthand/euphemism for sexual arousal. It is commonly interpreted that way for males and females, with little trickles of blood indicating mild arousal, and gushing fountains of blood indicating erection/extreme arousal in both sexes. It can also be interpreted as shorthand strictly for erections in males. In that case, when blood shoots from the nose explosively, and in ridiculous quantity, the implication would be an ejaculation.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>233513.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2627" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
<picurl>242357.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2636" parentid="2846" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>human enhancement</name>
<description>Human enhancement can take various forms: It can be something comparatively non-intrusive as a power-up drug, a form of machine implantation or cyberization (http://anidb.net/a4414 [SAC Solid State Society]), or outright - possibly atrocious - genetic manipulation (http://anidb.net/a361 [Ao no 6 Gou]). Plot-wise enhanced protagonists in anime usually have to pay a price for their enhancements, be it physical or mental.</description>
<picurl>223945.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2640" parentid="2625" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-06-02">
<name>alternative past</name>
<description>An anime that takes place in an alternative past is an anime that clearly does not belong to the future or the present, and isn`t tied particularly closely to our history, or has ties to our history but only as a premise: there are too many things that don`t make sense for the time-period. In some cases there is futuristic technology present, but the overall setting still feels that of the past. However the setting must still take place on Earth, since we can not know if the history of a fantasy world is an alternate one or not.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2644" parentid="2274" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-14">
<name>transforming craft</name>
<description>A transforming craft is an object built by humans or other intelligent lifeforms, usually a robot but sometimes also a vehicle of some sort, that can rearrange its parts in order to switch between a minimum of two forms.</description>
<picurl>224142.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2645" parentid="2274" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>piloted robot</name>
<description>Piloted Robots are, as the name suggests, robots that cannot control themselves; they need to be steered from somewhere, this can be from a human sitting inside or a remote controlled option.</description>
<picurl>222199.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>sex</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%27Origine_du_monde).
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2764" parentid="2627" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>space colony</name>
<description>The human race (or possibly some alien race) has mastered space travel and founded at least one colony either in space, on a moon or another planet. This usually also includes colony-life episodes that not only show the technical staff of professionals (astronauts, scientists, etc.), but also their families (i.e. children).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2820" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>wardrobe malfunction</name>
<description>A euphemistic term for an embarrassing display of a body part when clothing droops, falls, or is torn. Wikipedia: "Super Bowl XXXVIII half-time show" for more details.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2821" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>sudden naked girl appearance</name>
<description>A character or group of characters are simply minding their own business, when suddenly, a naked girl appears. It does not matter how or why, but a naked someone is there. Sometimes the naked girl is not happy about this. 
Usually this is a fanservice element, but not always.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2871" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>anti-war</name>
<description>The anime portrays the insanity of war.</description>
<picurl>70855.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2876" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>religion</name>
<description>Religion is a collection of belief systems, cultural systems, and worldviews that relate humanity to spirituality and, sometimes, to moral values. Many religions have narratives, symbols, traditions and sacred histories that are intended to give meaning to life or to explain the origin of life or the universe. They tend to derive morality, ethics, religious laws or a preferred lifestyle from their ideas about the cosmos and human nature.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2878" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>conspiracy</name>
<description>The conspiracy thriller (or paranoid thriller) is a sub-genre of the thriller which flourished in the 1970s in the US (and was echoed in other parts of the world) in the wake of a number of high-profile scandals and controversies (most notably Vietnam, the assassination of President Kennedy, Chappaquiddick and Watergate), and which exposed what many people regarded as the clandestine machinations and conspiracies beneath the orderly fabric of political life.
The protagonists of conspiracy thrillers are often journalists or amateur investigators who find themselves (often inadvertently) pulling on a small thread which unravels a vast conspiracy that ultimately goes "all the way to the top".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2882" parentid="2952" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-17">
<name>dystopia</name>
<description>A dystopia (from Ancient Greek: δυσ-, "bad, ill", and Ancient Greek: τόπος, "place, landscape"; alternatively cacotopia, or anti-utopia) is, in literature, an often futuristic society that has degraded into a repressive and controlled state, often under the guise of being utopian. Dystopian literature has underlying cautionary tones, warning society that if we continue to live how we do, this will be the consequence. A dystopia, thus, is regarded as a sort of negative utopia and is often characterized by an authoritarian or totalitarian form of government. Dystopias usually feature different kinds of repressive social control systems, a lack or total absence of individual freedoms and expressions and constant states of warfare or violence. Dystopias often explore the concept of humans abusing technology and how humans individually and collectively cope with technology that has evolved too quickly such as the car, the flamethrower or the microwave. A dystopian society is also often characterized by widespread poverty and brutal political controls such as a large military-like police.</description>
<picurl>69879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2923" parentid="2874" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-06-25">
<name>post-apocalyptic</name>
<description>An anime that takes place on future Earth (or it could be an alternative universe) after a major cataclysm has occurred. World War III, an alien invasion, plague, global warming or some other general disaster are common themes to build a post-apocalyptic world upon, where the effects were severe enough that mankind barely survived.
The time frame may be immediately after the catastrophe, focusing on the travails or psychology of survivors, or considerably later, often including the theme that the existence of pre-catastrophe civilization has been forgotten (or mythologised). Post-apocalyptic stories often take place in an agrarian, non-technological future world, or a world where only scattered elements of technology remain. There is a considerable degree of blurring between post-apocalyptic fiction and that which deals with false utopias or dystopian societies.</description>
<picurl>42081.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2952" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-06">
<name>rotten world</name>
<description>A rotten world is a setting or situation where the jaded notion that "anything that can go wrong will go horribly wrong" almost always applies. Oppression, perpetual warfare, lawlessness, despair or other forms of mental instability, and other highly undesirable factors tend to be rampant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2968" parentid="4831" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-04-05">
<name>faceless alien invasion</name>
<description>Uncommunicative, faceless aliens suddenly invade Earth from outer space or a parallel world thus causing a war with humans.
If the humans are lucky, the invasion may go off without a war that would cause untold destruction and death.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3013" parentid="55" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-10">
<name>Newtype Anime Award</name>
<description>This anime has won 1 or more Newtype Anime Award(s)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3159" parentid="2623" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-11-27">
<name>emotions awaken superpowers</name>
<description>During an extreme emotional state — rage, love, hate, angst, sadness, compassion — something inside the character will "click" that will increase greatly his/her power or a new superpower awakes, that surpasses anything achieved by him/her until then.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3191" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-14">
<name>ohanami</name>
<description>Hanami (花見, lit. "flower viewing") is the Japanese traditional custom of enjoying the beauty of flowers, "flower" in this case almost always meaning cherry blossoms or ume blossoms. 
From the end of March to early May, sakura bloom all over Japan, and around the first of February on the island of Okinawa. The blossom forecast (桜前線 sakurazensen, literally cherry blossom front) is announced each year by the weather bureau, and is watched carefully by those planning hanami as the blossoms only last a week or two. 
In modern-day Japan, hanami mostly consists of having an outdoor party beneath the sakura during daytime or at night. Hanami at night is called yozakura (夜桜, literally night sakura). 
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
<picurl>160895.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3276" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-02">
<name>plot twists</name>
<description>The plot and story of this anime may seem to be going along a quite predictable path, when suddenly there is a jarring unexpected twist in the plot, taking the viewer by surprise.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3394" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-25">
<name>environmentalism</name>
<description>Environmental protection is a practice of protecting the natural environment on individual, organizational or governmental levels, for the benefit of both the natural environment and humans. Due to the pressures of population and technology, the biophysical environment is being degraded, sometimes permanently. This has been recognized, and governments have begun placing restraints on activities that cause environmental degradation. Since the 1960s, activity of environmental movements has created awareness of the various environmental issues.
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3436" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>human experimentation</name>
<description>Genetic, biological, chemical or psychological experimentation on human beings are portrayed or their aftermath is shown.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3805" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-13">
<name>European stylised</name>
<description>The anime`s setting is crafted in some classic European style. Imagine an architectural and cultural mix of London, Paris, Rome, Berlin, Prague, and other cities as they were at any point in the 19th century or earlier.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3842" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-31">
<name>TV censoring</name>
<description>The TV version is censored and later DVD/BD releases are uncensored, so the money-grubbing capitalists can make a couple more bucks at our expense.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3867" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>ED variety</name>
<description>Several ED sequences in this anime have either a different song or different animation, maybe even to the point of having a unique ED for each episode.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3929" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-09">
<name>sociocultural evolution</name>
<description>Describes how cultures and societies develop over time, based on both cultural evolution and social evolution.
A post-apocalyptic or a Utopian setting would show very interesting changes in human behaviour, mental state, or simply daily life.</description>
<picurl>191062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3953" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-10-04">
<name>in medias res</name>
<description>In medias res, also medias in res (Latin for "into the midst of affairs (lit. into mid-affairs)"), refers to a literary and artistic technique where the narrative starts in the middle of the story instead of from its beginning. It is generally a plot-driven concept rather than a character-driven one; though characters are commonly used to provide the backstory. The characters, setting, and conflict are often introduced through a series of http://anidb.net/t4299 [flashbacks] or through characters relating past events to each other.
Probably originating from an oral tradition, the technique is a convention of epic poetry, one of the earliest and most prominent examples in Western literature being Homer`s Odyssey and Iliad. Virgil`s Aeneid began the tradition in literature of imitating Homer, continued in Torquato Tasso`s Jerusalem Delivered, John Milton`s Paradise Lost and "Inferno" from Dante`s Divine Comedy. George Lucas`s Star Wars saga was told using in medias res.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3974" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>star-crossed lovers</name>
<description>Two lovers — usually teenagers — destined to be kept apart no matter how hard they struggle to be together. It may be fate or just feuding families, or even something as mundane as a few hundred miles, but something will always be in their way. Often, the two can only be together in death. The phrase is astrological in origin, stemming from the belief that the positions of the stars ruled over people`s fates. To describe a relationship as "star-crossed" is to say that it is "thwarted by a malign star", or that the stars are working against the relationship. Shakespeare`s Romeo and Juliet is the most famous example of this archetype but it dates back at least as far as the ancient Greeks.
"From forth the fatal loins of these two foes, / a pair of star-cross`d lovers, take their life."
- Romeo and Juliet, prologue</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4081" parentid="2841" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-27">
<name>space battles</name>
<description>There are space battles in this anime. Usually between Earth forces and some alien invader, but ship to ship skirmishes in deep space are just as common.</description>
<picurl>242377.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4096" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>gore</name>
<description>A Splatter film or Gore film is a sub-genre of horror film that deliberately focuses on graphic portrayals of gore and graphic violence. These films, through the use of special effects and excessive blood and guts, tend to display an overt interest in the vulnerability of the human body and the theatricality of its mutilation. Due to their willingness to portray images society might consider shocking, splatter films share some ideological grounds with the transgressive art movement. The term "splatter cinema" was coined by George A. Romero to describe his film Dawn of the Dead, though Dawn of the Dead is generally considered by critics to have higher aspirations, such as social commentary, than to be simply exploitative for its own sake.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>32491.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4128" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-07-29">
<name>zero to hero</name>
<description>With his first appearance, this character is getting his ass kicked by nearly everyone, but as the plot continues, through training (mental or physical) or instant power-up, he changes into a killing/fighting/winning machine.
The best example: Makunouchi Ippo from Hajime no Ippo series.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4178" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-06">
<name>manipulated memories</name>
<description>The protagonist finds out that his/her cherished memories are actually fake and have been implanted.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4257" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-08-07">
<name>survival</name>
<description>The theme/genre of survival typically depicts the act or process of continuing to live, generally in a hostile, possibly post-apocalyptic environment. Survival-centered media tends to be dark, set most commonly in a contemporary context, and generally leads either to small groups of people forming closely knit and functional units or to individuals turning against their fellows in a return to the survival of the fittest.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4271" parentid="2876" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-29">
<name>corrupt church</name>
<description>An official religion (not cult or sect) has become evil or was evil to begin with, and tends to be highly influential with political leaders, to strengthen / enforce the church`s power over the people.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4274" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-02-01">
<name>hidden agenda</name>
<description>Someone or some organization/government/etc. is misrepresenting themselves by doing/saying one thing while hoping/striving for something else.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4352" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-11">
<name>censored uncensored version</name>
<description>Even the DVD and Blu-ray releases do not let you see everything you were expecting to, and you will have to live with censorship in the show. That normally applies to fan service, but may also apply to gore and violence. A very common example is characters without nipples, as in http://anidb.net/a6083 [KissXSis]; in other cases, something such as steam or foam stays in the camera`s way, like in http://anidb.net/a6531 [Kanamemo]. In some shows, the censorship in the disk releases is even stronger than in the TV version, while others may use creative censorship as a replacement for the removed fan service or even as a joke.
This does not apply to censorship of what Japanese pornography laws still require to be censored.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4479" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-03">
<name>sense of foreboding</name>
<description>The anime starts off quietly, everything seems to be fine, but from episode to episode the signs that something ominous is about to happen increase. E.g. a typical mystery setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4480" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>happy ending</name>
<description>And they lived "happily ever after"... *sniff*.
All issues in the anime have been resolved, the love polygons sorted out, the conflicts resolved, the guy gets the girl (or the other way around), and everyone else lives on blissfully.
(Not very realistic, but then again this is anime.)</description>
<picurl>222185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4499" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-07-28">
<name>some weird shit goin` on</name>
<description>Scenes of this show point to insanely strange events which seem to be taking place; throughout its episodes, the show may or may not explain what is going on. Either way, many viewers will find that a succinct and accurate way to describe the show is "WTF?", and the show`s explanations (or lack thereof) to the events will often be subject of heated debate.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4537" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-15">
<name>time skip</name>
<description>The plot features at least one skip or jump in time.
Example: A skip from the present into the past, or time skips in increments, e.g. every hour there is a time skip by a day.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4614" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>narration</name>
<description>The most common example is that of a voice, either that of one of the characters or entirely unrelated, that appears at the beginning of an episode to offer a summary or introduction, and at the end of an episode for closure or for a preview to hint upon what to expect next.
Another use of narration comes in the form of a dominant voice belonging to one of the protagonists, intended only for the viewer and revealing the intimate thoughts to whom it belongs. This type of narration occurs frequently throughout the duration of the episode or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4831" parentid="2202" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-23">
<name>alien invasion</name>
<description>An alien invasion or space invasion is the invasion of the Earth by an extraterrestrial species, usually but not necessarily sentient and highly advanced technologically. The invasion typically happens for reasons such as to exterminate and supplant human life, to enslave the earthlings or harvest them for food, to steal the planet`s resources, or simply to destroy it altogether. It often happens during, causes, or is the result of a war between humans and aliens.</description>
<picurl>215284.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5530" parentid="2764" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-11-20">
<name>colony dome</name>
<description>A space colony with a dome to provide an atmospheric environment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5626" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>adults are useless</name>
<description>For when adults can`t do anything right.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5859" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-30">
<name>monster of the week</name>
<description>On a pretty much regular basis — weekly or episodic — the protagonists engage in some kind of conflict. This can be an actual showdown between mecha, or the all-out fight against an enemy, or a (car) race that needs to be won.
This can make the anime quite repetitive.</description>
<picurl>60013.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5862" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-08">
<name>melodrama</name>
<description>A melodrama is a dramatic work that exaggerates plot and characters in order to appeal to the emotions, often with strongly stereotyped characters. Language, behaviour, or events which resemble melodramas are also called melodramatic. In scholarly and historical musical contexts melodramas are dramas of the 18th and 19th centuries in which orchestral music or song was used to accompany the action.
Melodrama is a style of drama that has been applied on the stage, in movies and television, and radio formats, from the 18th century to the present. Because of the long timeframe in which the style has existed, it is difficult to derive a precise definition. The term melodrama is most often used pejoratively, to suggest that the work to which the term is applied lacks sophistication or subtlety.
The term originated from the early 19th-century French word mélodrame, which is derived from Greek melos, music, and French drame, drama (from Late Latin drāma, which in turn derives from Greek drān, to do, perform).
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6019" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-01-20">
<name>brainwashing</name>
<description>Brainwashing, the application of coercive techniques to change the values and beliefs, perceptions and judgements, and subsequent mindsets and behaviours of one or more people, usually for political, financial, personal, or religious purposes. Often features in dark anime or pornography.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6034" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>Engrish</name>
<description>Engrish is actually a mispronunciation of English, as can be the result of someone, who does not have English as their primary language of origin (such as Japanese or Chinese). Occasionally characters in the original Japanese dialogue version of an anime will speak in English... however; this often still requires the assistance of subtitles, for while the words are meant to be said in English, the sentence structure and letter pronunciation may still be strongly related to the person’s primary language.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6062" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-04-05">
<name>heroic sacrifice</name>
<description>"In order to save the many, the few will need to sacrifice their lives..." or so this character may think. 
In a seemingly hopeless situation, against impossible odds, the character does not choose the path of the coward and run, he or she chooses to bravely face the enemy, fully aware that this will mean death.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="92210" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-12-16">
<rating votes="28">5.55</rating>
<name>Ikuno</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>210777.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29972" picture="240161.jpg">Ishigami Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92211" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-01-23">
<rating votes="193">8.01</rating>
<name>Ichigo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ichigo is an honor student of the Mistilteinn academy seen as a natural-born leader. She is childhood friends with http://anidb.net/ch92216 [Hiro] and cares about his well being, despite her cool demeanor. Her Franxx partner is http://anidb.net/ch92213 [Gorou].
Source: Darling in the Franxx Wiki</description>
<picture>210778.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="52537" picture="225050.jpg">Ichinose Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92212" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-06-29">
<rating votes="49">5.60</rating>
<name>Kokoro</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kokoro is a student of the Mistilteinn academy. A very gentle soul with a kind personality to match. She doesn`t speak too often, but when she does her words are well thought-out and meaningful. Her Franxx partner is http://anidb.net/ch92217 [Futoshi].
Source: Darling in the Franxx Wiki</description>
<picture>210779.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2296" picture="189623.jpg">Hayami Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92213" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-01-23">
<rating votes="51">7.96</rating>
<name>Gorou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Gorou is a student of the Mistilteinn academy. He has an upbeat "class rep" personality. He`s a talented pilot and seen by many as one of the most well-valued parasites in Cerasus. He`s old friends with http://anidb.net/ch92216 [Hiro] and http://anidb.net/ch92211 [Ichigo]. His Franxx partner is Ichigo.
Source: Darling in the Franxx Wiki</description>
<picture>210782.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39583" picture="186257.jpg">Hamano Daiki</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="39792" picture="176251.jpg">Umehara Yuuichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92214" type="main character in" update="2020-09-13">
<rating votes="202">3.18</rating>
<name>Zero Two</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Zero Two is an elite pilot with the pseudonym "The Partner Killer", given the mysterious happening of her co-pilots dying after a short number of Franxx outings. Her Franxx partner is http://anidb.net/ch92216 [Hiro]. She is very fond of sweet taste and her personality is described as dangerous yet alluring.
Source: Darling in the Franxx Wiki</description>
<picture>210781.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5" picture="233827.jpg">Tomatsu Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92215" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-03-18">
<rating votes="16">2.52</rating>
<name>Zorome</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>210774.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3712" picture="240126.jpg">Tamura Mutsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92216" type="main character in" update="2018-01-23">
<rating votes="110">2.10</rating>
<name>Hiro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hiro is a former star student of the Mistilteinn academy, whose inability to pilot Franxx has left his hopes low, even to the point of choosing to leave Cerasus until his former partner http://anidb.net/ch93323 [Naomi] encourages him to stay. His emotions are strong, but his heart keeps him from giving up. His Franxx partner is http://anidb.net/ch92214 [Zero Two].
Source: Darling in the Franxx Wiki</description>
<picture>210776.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37466" picture="225911.jpg">Uemura Yuuto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92217" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-01-23">
<rating votes="13">2.85</rating>
<name>Futoshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Futoshi is a student of the Mistilteinn academy. Though he`s optimistic and does things at his own pace, he is also surprisingly sensible. He gets along with everyone and has a friendly personality. His Franxx partner is http://anidb.net/ch92212 [Kokoro].
Source: Darling in the Franxx Wiki</description>
<picture>210775.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23683" picture="65780.jpg">Gotou Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92218" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-12-16">
<rating votes="30">4.47</rating>
<name>Miku</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>210780.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38295" picture="222841.jpg">Yamashita Nanami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92219" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-05-02">
<rating votes="30">5.21</rating>
<name>Mitsuru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>210783.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="52057" picture="225903.jpg">Ichikawa Aoi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="92225" type="appears in" update="2017-11-08">
<rating votes="20">5.88</rating>
<name>Strelizia</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>209456.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="92226" type="appears in" update="2017-11-08">
<rating votes="4">7.56</rating>
<name>Delphinium</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>209457.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="92227" type="appears in" update="2017-11-08">
<rating votes="2">7.29</rating>
<name>Argentea</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>209459.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="92228" type="appears in" update="2017-11-08">
<rating votes="2">5.31</rating>
<name>Genista</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>209460.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="92229" type="appears in" update="2017-11-08">
<rating votes="2">8.19</rating>
<name>Chlorophytum</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>209461.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="93260" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-01-16">
<rating votes="20">6.35</rating>
<name>Nana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212003.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11" picture="32253.jpg">Inoue Marina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93261" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-01-16">
<rating votes="8">4.12</rating>
<name>Hachi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212004.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="179" picture="188456.jpg">Konishi Katsuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93262" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-01-16">
<rating votes="9">3.46</rating>
<name>Franxx-hakase</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212005.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2037" picture="244859.jpg">Horiuchi Ken`yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93322" type="appears in" update="2018-01-21">
<rating votes="2">2.48</rating>
<name>081</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212192.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="177" picture="170981.jpg">Hoshino Takanori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93323" type="appears in" update="2018-01-21">
<rating votes="9">6.64</rating>
<name>Naomi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212195.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="51" picture="39247.jpg">Koshimizu Ami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93324" type="appears in" update="2018-01-21">
<rating votes="3">4.51</rating>
<name>Shuseki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212196.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="343" picture="140430.jpg">Genda Tesshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93325" type="appears in" update="2018-06-29">
<rating votes="2">1.81</rating>
<name>Fukushuseki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>219698.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="190" picture="186145.jpg">Tobita Nobuo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93326" type="appears in" update="2018-01-21">
<rating votes="2">1.60</rating>
<name>Keibihei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>212194.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43111" picture="183457.jpg">Kobayashi Tatsuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93818" type="appears in" update="2018-06-29">
<rating votes="9">5.12</rating>
<name>Hiro (Youshouki)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>219680.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="51" picture="39247.jpg">Koshimizu Ami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93819" type="appears in" update="2018-06-29">
<rating votes="12">8.70</rating>
<name>Ichigo (Youshouki)</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>219699.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="52537" picture="225050.jpg">Ichinose Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93820" type="appears in" update="2018-02-17">
<rating votes="2">3.94</rating>
<name>090</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>213154.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34070" picture="130103.jpg">Furukawa Makoto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93821" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-02-24">
<rating votes="17">2.24</rating>
<name>9` Alpha</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>213535.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36680" picture="153752.jpg">Saitou Souma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94439" type="appears in" update="2018-03-10">
<rating votes="4">5.32</rating>
<name>Gorou (Youshouki)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>214635.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45121" picture="225365.jpg">Fujiwara Natsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94624" type="appears in" update="2018-03-18">
<rating votes="3">2.41</rating>
<name>Otona Josei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>215020.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="240" picture="17059.jpg">Inoue Kikuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94625" type="appears in" update="2018-03-18">
<rating votes="2">1.28</rating>
<name>13 Shichou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>215018.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38116" picture="223784.jpg">Kitada Masamichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94626" type="appears in" update="2018-03-18">
<rating votes="3">3.59</rating>
<name>Zorome (Youshouki)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>215019.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="95757" type="appears in" update="2018-06-10">
<rating votes="11">6.46</rating>
<name>001</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>218872.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3" picture="44969.jpg">Kugimiya Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95758" type="appears in" update="2018-06-29">
<rating votes="3">3.23</rating>
<name>9` Beta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>219693.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23805" picture="66166.jpg">Masuda Toshiki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95759" type="appears in" update="2018-06-29">
<rating votes="3">3.23</rating>
<name>9` Gamma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>219694.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2575" picture="139952.jpg">Eguchi Takuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95760" type="appears in" update="2018-06-29">
<rating votes="3">2.03</rating>
<name>9` Delta</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>219692.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20762" picture="131325.jpg">Sakura Ayane</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95761" type="appears in" update="2018-06-29">
<rating votes="3">2.03</rating>
<name>9` Epsilon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>219691.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="24946" picture="200733.jpg">Tamaru Atsushi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95762" type="appears in" update="2018-07-01">
<rating votes="3">4.39</rating>
<name>Mitsuru (Youshouki)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>219829.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="95763" type="appears in" update="2018-06-29">
<rating votes="3">2.76</rating>
<name>9` Zeta</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>219695.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="95764" type="appears in" update="2018-07-01">
<rating votes="2">2.48</rating>
<name>Shokuin B2 (Josei)</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>219828.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40151" picture="224296.jpg">Ooi Marie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95765" type="appears in" update="2018-06-28">
<rating votes="12">7.32</rating>
<name>Zero Two (Youshouki)</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>219637.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5" picture="233827.jpg">Tomatsu Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95766" type="appears in" update="2018-07-02">
<rating votes="2">5.31</rating>
<name>Ryousan-gata Franxx</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>Ryousan-gata Franxx is the mass-produced model of the FRANXX used by other Plantations.</description>
<picture>219827.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="95767" type="appears in" update="2018-07-02">
<rating votes="2">6.92</rating>
<name>Kyuushiki</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>Kyuushiki (The 9 Model) is a type of FRANXX built for the http://anidb.net/ch96339 [9`s].</description>
<picture>219825.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="95786" type="appears in" update="2018-06-26">
<rating votes="2">9.43</rating>
<name>Karina Milsa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>219565.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="160" picture="249021.jpg">Kaida Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95787" type="appears in" update="2018-06-26">
<rating votes="3">5.45</rating>
<name>Werner Frank</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>219566.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2037" picture="244859.jpg">Horiuchi Ken`yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96294" type="appears in" update="2018-06-27">
<rating votes="1">1.04</rating>
<name>APE</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The APE is group of scientists and politicians who govern all of known humanity. All civilian and military organizations report to them or someone under them, with the exception of the special forces pilots, also known as the "Nines," who report directly to APE. They worked with http://anidb.net/ch93262 [Dr. Franxx] in the creation of the FRANXX program.
APE is ruled by a http://anidb.net/ch93324 [Chairman], who is known as "Papa" by Children and adults alike and worshiped as a god. Members of APE wear elegant white robes and sport unique mechanical masks.</description>
<picture>219588.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="96295" type="appears in" update="2018-06-27">
<rating votes="1">1.04</rating>
<name>Shichi Kenjin</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The Seven Sages or Lamarck Club are the highest members of mankind`s governing institution, the http://anidb.net/ch96294 [APE].</description>
<picture>219589.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="96296" type="appears in" update="2018-06-28">
<rating votes="2">6.92</rating>
<name>Strelizia</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch92225 [Strelizia], in its Stampede mode.</description>
<picture>219629.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="96297" type="appears in" update="2018-06-27">
<rating votes="2">8.76</rating>
<name>Cerasus</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>Cerasus is the 13th Plantation and a home to http://anidb.net/ch92216 [Hiro] and his friends.
When it was attacked by a Mohorovic-class Klaxosaur, which was neutralized by http://anidb.net/ch92225 [Strelizia] shortly after, the damage resulted in the magma energy stockpile to plummet and thus the plantation was set to meet with http://anidb.net/ch96298 [26th Plantation] for an exchange.
Source: Darling in the Franxx Wiki</description>
<picture>219593.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="96298" type="appears in" update="2018-06-27">
<rating votes="1">3.78</rating>
<name>Chrysanthemum</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="4">Vessel</charactertype>
<description>Chrysanthemum is the 26th Plantation.
When the 13th Plantation, http://anidb.net/ch96297 [Cerasus], lost a significant amount of energy during the Mohorovic-class Klaxosaur`s attack, it was set to meet with nearby 36th Plantation to resupply its magma energy stockpile through a process known as "kissing". Like every other plantation, it houses a city inside.
After the first battle of Gran Crevasse, 26th Plantation was destroyed and all inhabitants died, including all Franxx pilots.
Source: Darling in the Franxx Wiki</description>
<picture>219591.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="96317" type="appears in" update="2018-06-28">
<rating votes="2">6.92</rating>
<name>Strelizia</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch92225 [Strelizia], while being piloted by http://anidb.net/ch95757 [001] and http://anidb.net/ch92216 [Hiro].</description>
<picture>219632.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="96319" type="appears in" update="2018-06-28">
<rating votes="1">5.66</rating>
<name>Strelizia Apath</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>219634.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="96320" type="appears in" update="2018-07-08">
<rating votes="2">5.92</rating>
<name>Strelizia Apath</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch96319 [Strelizia Apath], while she was still under http://anidb.net/ch95757 [001]`s control.</description>
<picture>219635.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="96321" type="appears in" update="2018-07-06">
<rating votes="2">4.88</rating>
<name>VIRM</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>VIRM are an alien hive mind species as well as invaders from outer space. Some time ago, they were once defeated and driven away by the Klaxo sapiens. Currently, the 3 known members of this race include http://anidb.net/ch93324 [Papa], http://anidb.net/ch93325 [Vice Chairman], and http://anidb.net/ch96326 [Tarsier] from http://anidb.net/ch96294 [APE].
Source: Darling in the Franxx Wiki</description>
<picture>219636.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="96322" type="appears in" update="2018-06-28">
<rating votes="2">1.60</rating>
<name>Gorilla</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>219638.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="96323" type="appears in" update="2018-06-28">
<rating votes="2">1.60</rating>
<name>Marmoset</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>219639.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="96324" type="appears in" update="2018-06-28">
<rating votes="2">1.60</rating>
<name>Lemur</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>219642.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="96325" type="appears in" update="2018-06-28">
<rating votes="2">1.60</rating>
<name>Baboon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>219643.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="96326" type="appears in" update="2018-06-28">
<rating votes="2">3.61</rating>
<name>Tarsier</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>219644.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="96336" type="appears in" update="2018-06-29">
<rating votes="3">3.59</rating>
<name>Hachi (Youshouki)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>219681.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="96337" type="appears in" update="2018-06-29">
<rating votes="3">4.72</rating>
<name>Nana (Youshouki)</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>219682.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="96338" type="appears in" update="2018-06-29">
<rating votes="2">4.85</rating>
<name>Shin Nana</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>219683.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="182" picture="226274.jpg">Itou Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96339" type="appears in" update="2018-06-29">
<rating votes="1">5.66</rating>
<name>9`s</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>The Nines are a special forces unit directly controlled by http://anidb.net/ch96294 [APE]. They also assume the role of "secret police", operating directly under http://anidb.net/ch93324 [Papa] and carrying out his commands, maintaining order within plantations. They are unbound by any restrictions, including the exempt on 13th Plantation, http://anidb.net/ch96297 [Cerasus].
In reality, they are clones created from http://anidb.net/ch92214 [Zero Two]`s cells, although they lack the Klaxosaur blood.
Source: Darling in the Franxx Wiki</description>
<picture>219690.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="96492" type="appears in" update="2018-07-05">
<rating votes="1">9.21</rating>
<name>Kyoryuu Dai Kantai</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>219982.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="96493" type="appears in" update="2018-07-05">
<rating votes="1">5.66</rating>
<name>VIRM Sekkou Kantai</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>219983.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="96592" type="appears in" update="2018-07-08">
<rating votes="5">6.51</rating>
<name>Hiro</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch92216 [Hiro], after he rejoined http://anidb.net/ch92214 [Zero Two] with piloting Strelizia True Apath.</description>
<picture>220132.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37466" picture="225911.jpg">Uemura Yuuto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96593" type="appears in" update="2018-07-08">
<rating votes="1">4.14</rating>
<name>Strelizia Shin Apath</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="2">Mecha</charactertype>
<picture>219984.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5" picture="233827.jpg">Tomatsu Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97344" type="appears in" update="2018-08-11">
<rating votes="3">7.48</rating>
<name>Futoshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>222130.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23683" picture="65780.jpg">Gotou Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97345" type="appears in" update="2018-08-11">
<rating votes="3">9.01</rating>
<name>Ikuno</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>222131.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29972" picture="240161.jpg">Ishigami Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97346" type="appears in" update="2018-08-11">
<rating votes="1">6.79</rating>
<name>Naomi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>222132.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="51" picture="39247.jpg">Koshimizu Ami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97347" type="appears in" update="2018-08-11">
<rating votes="8">8.61</rating>
<name>Ichigo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>222133.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="52537" picture="225050.jpg">Ichinose Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97348" type="appears in" update="2018-08-11">
<rating votes="3">7.93</rating>
<name>Miku</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>222134.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38295" picture="222841.jpg">Yamashita Nanami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97349" type="appears in" update="2018-08-11">
<rating votes="1">2.19</rating>
<name>Zorome</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>222135.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="194299" update="2018-02-04">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-02-03</airdate>
<rating votes="19">6.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">フラップ・フラップ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Flap Flap</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Flap Flap</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Flap Flap</title>
<summary>With the squad still feeling the aftershocks of the previous mission, things come to a head as the leaders run out of patience and decide to summon Strelizia back to the front lines.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>759581</identifier>
<identifier>darling-in-the-franxx</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="194300" update="2018-01-27">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-01-27</airdate>
<rating votes="17">5.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">戦う人形</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fighting Puppet</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Poupées de guerre</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tatakau Ningyou</title>
<summary>After their failure in the startup trial, things are awkward between Ichigo and Hiro, who decides to ask to ride with Zero Two again.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>759579</identifier>
<identifier>darling-in-the-franxx</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="194301" update="2018-01-28">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-01-20</airdate>
<rating votes="34">6.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">繋がるということ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">What It Means to Connect</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Être connectés</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsunagaru to Iu Koto</title>
<summary>The parasites struggle to come to terms with Hiro being the one who piloted Strelizia. Even Hiro can`t really believe it himself. Things come to a head when he`s ordered to participate in a mock battle.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>759577</identifier>
<identifier>darling-in-the-franxx</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="194302" update="2018-01-14">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-01-13</airdate>
<rating votes="37">6.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">独りとヒトリ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Alone and Lonesome</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Seule et solitaire</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hitori to Hitori</title>
<summary>The land has fallen into ruin, and children represent the last hope for humanity. One of them, Hiro, fails to live up to that purpose and decides to walk away from it all.... until he meets a girl with horns.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>759575</identifier>
<identifier>darling-in-the-franxx</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="194565" update="2018-09-02">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-01-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">事前特番</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jizen Tokuban</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195323" update="2018-05-28">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-01-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195324" update="2018-01-21">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-01-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195462" update="2018-03-04">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-03-03</airdate>
<rating votes="16">5.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">男の子x女の子</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Boys x Girls</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Garçons × Filles</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Otokonoko x Onnanoko</title>
<summary>The boys get caught in a compromising situation, causing a rift within Squad 13. Will they be able to bridge this divide? And how will Zero Two react to the most human of spats?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>759589</identifier>
<identifier>darling-in-the-franxx</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="195463" update="2018-05-06">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-02-24</airdate>
<rating votes="24">7.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">流星モラトリアム</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shooting Star Moratorium</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Trêve sous les étoiles filantes</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ryuusei Moratorium</title>
<summary>Squad 13 is given a much-needed break after defending the kissing plantations in a fierce battle. They head to an unexpected location and find something even more unexpected.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>759587</identifier>
<identifier>darling-in-the-franxx</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="195464" update="2018-05-06">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-02-17</airdate>
<rating votes="21">6.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ダーリン・イン・ザ・フランクス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Darling in the Franxx</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Darling in the FranXX</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Darling in the Franxx</title>
<summary>Ichigo, Goro, and the rest of Squad 13 engage in a battle far more dangerous than any they`ve fought before, all while having their mind preyed on by the fact that this will be Hiro`s third ride with Zero Two.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>759585</identifier>
<identifier>darling-in-the-franxx</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="195465" update="2018-02-10">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-02-10</airdate>
<rating votes="21">6.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">キミの棘, ボクのしるし</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Your Thorn, My Badge</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Tes épines, mon emblème</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kimi no Toge, Boku no Shirushi</title>
<summary>It`s time for Plantations 13 and 26 to start kissing, and the squad prepares for the huge battle this will cause. They also have to get used to Hiro being Zero Two`s partner, and so does he.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>759583</identifier>
<identifier>darling-in-the-franxx</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="196637" update="2018-03-31">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-03-31</airdate>
<rating votes="16">6.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ガーデン / 始まりの庭</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Garden Where It All Began</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le Jardin où tout a commencé</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Garden / Hajimari no Niwa</title>
<summary>Squad 13 heads back to the Garden for testing, with Zero Two`s emotional state worsening by the day. They run into Nine Alpha, who offers some insight about her, but the most revealing words come straight from the horse`s mouth...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>759597</identifier>
<identifier>darling-in-the-franxx</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="196638" update="2018-03-24">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-03-24</airdate>
<rating votes="14">5.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">パートナーシャッフル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Partner Shuffle</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Changement de partenaire</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Partner Shuffle</title>
<summary>Squad 13`s growth has been remarkable, but Chlorophytum`s score keeps going down. With this in mind, Nana and Hachi propose a partner shuffle, which finds an unexpected taker.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>759595</identifier>
<identifier>darling-in-the-franxx</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="196639" update="2018-03-17">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-03-17</airdate>
<rating votes="14">6.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">永遠の街</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The City of Eternity</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La Ville éternelle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Eien no Machi</title>
<summary>APE decide to give Squad 13 a reward in order to accelerate their development. The ceremony is held in a place Zorome has always dreamed of living in, and there he meets someone he has always wanted to meet.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>759593</identifier>
<identifier>darling-in-the-franxx</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="196640" update="2018-03-11">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-03-10</airdate>
<rating votes="28">7.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">トライアングル・ボム</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Triangle Bomb</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Bombe triangulaire</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Triangle Bomb</title>
<summary>Soon after Goro becomes keenly aware of his feelings, he is put in a perilous situation. How will he and Ichigo respond in this do-or-die scenario?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>759591</identifier>
<identifier>darling-in-the-franxx</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="196684" update="2018-05-28">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-02-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="196854" update="2018-05-28">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-03-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="197289" update="2018-05-05">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-05-05</airdate>
<rating votes="12">5.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ぼくたちの日々</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Days of Our Lives</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Notre quotidien</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bokutachi no Hibi</title>
<summary>The parasites` living situation has changed drastically after the battle for Gran Crevasse. Zero Two`s attitude toward them seems to have changed drastically, too.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>769603</identifier>
<identifier>darling-in-the-franxx</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="197290" update="2018-04-21">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-04-21</airdate>
<rating votes="24">6.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">比翼の鳥</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Jian</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Pihis</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hiyoku no Tori</title>
<summary>The fierce battle to take the Grand Crevasse begins, and Hiro is forced to watch from the sidelines. Zero Two may have left, but Squad 13 is still concerned about the way she fights.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>769599</identifier>
<identifier>darling-in-the-franxx</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="197291" update="2018-04-15">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-04-14</airdate>
<rating votes="21">7.07</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">罪と告白</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Punishment and Confession</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Péché et déclaration</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsumi to Kokuhaku</title>
<summary>The information regarding Hiro`s condition changes the entire dynamic of Squad 13, much to Zero Two`s chagrin. She only wants to speak to Hiro, but people stand in her way one after another.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>769597</identifier>
<identifier>darling-in-the-franxx</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="197292" update="2018-04-08">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-04-07</airdate>
<rating votes="31">7.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">まものと王子様</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Beast and the Prince</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La Bête et le prince</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mamono to Ouji-sama</title>
<summary>In the deepest, darkest parts of a forest lived a strong and beautiful beast princess. Beckoned by the moonlight, she wandered into a land of humans, and in the moonlit garden of a small castle, she fell in love with a prince.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>759599</identifier>
<identifier>darling-in-the-franxx</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="197898" update="2018-05-28">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-04-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198293" update="2018-06-09">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-06-09</airdate>
<rating votes="37">4.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">新しい世界</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A New World</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Nouveau monde</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Atarashii Sekai</title>
<summary>Humanity`s operation to wipe out the klaxosaurs once and for all begins, and APE sends Strelizia to take control of Star Entity, the enemy`s biggest weapon. However, the klaxosaur princess has other ideas.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>769613</identifier>
<identifier>darling-in-the-franxx</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="198294" update="2018-05-27">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-05-26</airdate>
<rating votes="15">5.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">人ならざるモノたち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Inhumanity</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Inhumanités</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hito Narazaru Monotachi</title>
<summary>Dr. Franxx confronts the APE brass about what they did to Kokoro and Mitsuru, and their attitude makes him reflect on his past, the choices he and humanity made, and the path they took.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>769609</identifier>
<identifier>darling-in-the-franxx</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="198295" update="2018-05-20">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-05-19</airdate>
<rating votes="18">6.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">桜の花が咲く頃に</title>
<title xml:lang="en">When the Sakura Blooms</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Quand fleurissent les cerisiers</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sakura no Hana ga Saku Koro ni</title>
<summary>Squad 13 is told they will be abandoning Mistilteinn soon, and they decide to go out with a bang by making one last memory of their lives there.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>769607</identifier>
<identifier>darling-in-the-franxx</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="198296" update="2018-05-12">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-05-12</airdate>
<rating votes="13">7.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">楽園</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Eden</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Paradis</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rakuen</title>
<summary>Having seized Gran Crevasse, emissaries are sent out to demand the surrender of the klaxosaurs` leader. Meanwhile, the Nines visit Squad 13, and there a shocking discovery is made.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>769605</identifier>
<identifier>darling-in-the-franxx</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="198438" update="2018-09-02">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-04-28</airdate>
<rating votes="4">5.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">プレイバック特番</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Playback Special</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Playback Tokuban</title>
<summary>The ten voice actors who play Squad 13`s parasites share their favorite moments from the show`s first fifteen episodes. There are also comments from series director Nishigori regarding the show`s upcoming second half.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="200304" update="2018-07-07">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-07-07</airdate>
<rating votes="23">7.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">わたしを離さないで</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Never Let Me Go</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ne me lâche pas</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Watashi o Hanasanaide</title>
<summary>While Hiro and Zero Two head to VIRM`s home planet to defeat them, the rest of Squad 13 do their best to get life on Earth back on track.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>769621</identifier>
<identifier>darling-in-the-franxx</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="200305" update="2018-07-01">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-06-30</airdate>
<rating votes="15">5.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ダーリン・イン・ザ・フランキス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Darling in the Franxx</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Darling in the FranXX</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Darling in the Franxx</title>
<summary>The gang heads off to space to fight in what they believe to be the final battle. Meanwhile, Kokoro and Mitsuru stay behind to fight a battle of their own.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>769619</identifier>
<identifier>darling-in-the-franxx</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="200306" update="2018-06-23">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-06-23</airdate>
<rating votes="18">5.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">スターゲイザー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Stargazers</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La tête dans les étoiles</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Stargazer</title>
<summary>Hiro is left shattered with an unresponsive Zero Two, and the children struggle to come to terms with the aftermath. Left all alone to battle for their survival, what path will they choose to take?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>769617</identifier>
<identifier>darling-in-the-franxx</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="200307" update="2018-06-16">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-06-16</airdate>
<rating votes="21">4.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大好きなあなたのために</title>
<title xml:lang="en">For You, My Love</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Pour toi que j`aime</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Daisuki na Anata no Tame ni</title>
<summary>There appears to be no escape from the impending destruction of Earth. But at the end of the world, Zero Two decides that she will keep her promise, no matter what.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>769615</identifier>
<identifier>darling-in-the-franxx</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="200344" update="2018-06-02">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-06-02</airdate>
<rating votes="2">4.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">プレイバック特番II</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Playback Special II</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Playback Tokuban II</title>
<summary>As voice recording for the series finishes, Zero Two and Hiro`s voice actors talk about their roles. There are additional comments from director Nishigori and the series` script writer, Hayashi.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="200493" update="2018-05-28">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-05-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="200494" update="2018-05-28">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-05-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1b</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
