<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="13270" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2018-01-08</startdate>
<enddate>2018-03-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Karakai Jouzu no Takagi-san</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Karakai Jozu no Takagi-san</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">からかい上手の高木さん</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Teasing Master Takagi-san</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">장난을 잘 치는 타카기양</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">擅长捉弄的高木同学</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="14591" type="Sequel">Karakai Jouzu no Takagi-san 2</anime>
<anime id="13991" type="Side Story">Karakai Jouzu no Takagi-san: Water Slider</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="9809" approval="28" total="37">Tonari no Seki-kun</anime>
<anime id="15382" approval="8" total="9">Uzaki-chan wa Asobitai!</anime>
<anime id="10352" approval="7" total="14">High Score Girl</anime>
<anime id="15421" approval="7" total="13">Tonikaku Kawaii</anime>
<anime id="14111" approval="4" total="10">Kaguya-sama wa Kokurasetai: Tensai-tachi no Ren`ai Zunousen</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="3">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="180235">little boy victim of jokes from his classmate, he always tries to retaliate but everything turns back to him because she is super smart, super clever and also stronger than him.
he is a kid that behave like a kid while she seems an aunt that have fun teasing her little nephew, so much is the difference between the two (of course it`s because she likes him... meh).

in any case, it can be enjoyable, it`s well done and it has his funny comedy moments.
i recommend it for fans of this kind of "cute" rom-com, or fans of OP female leads.
the others can be upset about how the story is driven, i was one of those, i felt unconfortable in several occasions (i like strong female leads, but i didn`t like it in such setting, put it this way).</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="419931">I seriously can`t understand negative votes on this series, it`s an amazing slice of life anime with great character development and great design.

If you don`t like this kind of anime just don`t watch it but don`t downgrade such an amazing work.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>https://takagi3.me/1st/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1284" type="Animation Work">Shin-Ei Animation</name>
<name id="20876" type="Music">Tsutsumi Hiroaki</name>
<name id="50830" type="Original Work">Yamamoto Souichirou</name>
<name id="22043" type="Character Design">Takano Aya</name>
<name id="3465" type="Series Composition">Yokote Michiko</name>
<name id="22733" type="Direction">Akagi Hiroaki</name>
<name id="15720" type="Chief Animation Direction">Mogi Takuji</name>
<name id="8408" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kondou Natsuko</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on http://anidb.net/cr50830 [Yamamoto Souichirou]`s slice of life comedy shounen manga.
"If you blush, you lose."
Living by this principle, the middle schooler http://anidb.net/ch91670 [Nishikata] gets constantly made fun of by his seat neighbor http://anidb.net/ch91671 [Takagi-san]. With his pride shattered to pieces, he vows to turn the tables and get back at her some day.
And so, he attempts to tease her day after day, only to find himself victim to Takagi-san`s ridicule again sooner than later. Will he be able to make Takagi-san blush from embarrassment even once in the end?
Source: M-U</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1373">6.55</permanent>
<temporary count="1375">7.21</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>210392.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20176</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>35860</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://takagi3.me/1st/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Karakai_Jōzu_no_Takagi-san</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>からかい上手の高木さん</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4781</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>361247</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20751</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>takagi3_anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>karakai-jozu-no-takagi-san</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B07ND57Y5V</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="34">
<externalentity>
<url>https://www.netflix.com/title/80228274</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1018" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-25">
<name>middle school</name>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2617" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-10-15">
<name>calling your attacks</name>
<description>"GIGAAAAAA DRIIIIIILLL BREAKEEEEEERRR"
If you can do something more impressive than just throw a punch, your attack(s) must have an equally impressive name. More than that, you have to call it out as you launch the attack. It doesn`t matter if it`s a martial arts move, a magical spell or your secret superweapon, if you can`t say its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective.
Having a special attack is always a must, but not impressive enough. Every special attack needs a name. A really awesome and outstanding name which is easy to remember and even easier and impressive to yell. Because it just is not enough to name your attack. No, to unleash the full power of your attack, you have to call its name in your most MANLY and LOUDEST voice.
It does not matter whether it is a martial arts move, a magical spell or flying drills from your mecha, if you can`t call its name, it just isn`t nearly as cool or effective. Not a requirement but wearing shades while calling your attack makes it at least twice as cool, moreover giving your mecha or magical companion shades too results in an immeasurable level of awesomeness, bringing down every enemy just through the POWER OF YOUR VOICE.
A standard feature of practically every mecha, mahou shoujo, high fantasy, or martial arts anime.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>144260.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2634" parentid="2613" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>countryside</name>
<description>The anime takes place far from the any densely populated areas like cities, i.e. out in the suburbs, in the countryside with many fields and forests.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2770" parentid="2653" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>violent retribution for accidental infringement</name>
<description>A comedy / slapstick element often found in Ecchi anime: The hilarity derives from spontaneous embarrassment, overreaction of the "victim" (girl), immediate retribution for a seemingly inappropriate act, and a sense of pity with the supposed "aggressor" (boy).
Typically a boy will - through no fault of his own - stumble into a girl, thus invading her personal space. In the process the boy may e.g. pull down her skirt, grab the girl`s breasts, or accidentally kiss her. Any level-headed girl would see the accident just for what it is. Not so the girl with an overly developed sense of modesty, and a thing for violence. She - often a tsundere - will clobber the boy with excessive brutality.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3185" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-27">
<name>wordplay</name>
<description>The characters play with words. 
E.g. purposely or accidentally use similar-sounding but wrongly applied words in the Japanese original, leading to supposedly funny misunderstandings and confusion.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3278" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false">
<name>deception</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3618" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-14">
<name>ocean</name>
<description>The large bodies of salt water surrounding the continents and islands are a (significant) setting of this anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3772" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-09-03">
<name>library</name>
<description>In a traditional sense, a library is a large collection of books, and can refer to the place in which the collection is housed.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3809" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-05-24">
<name>character driven</name>
<description>The main appeal of the show is the way the characters are portrayed and interact, focusing on dialogue, spending time together or getting to know each other. These anime are not "story-less" but story is secondary to character development and the characters themselves and what they experience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3867" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>ED variety</name>
<description>Several ED sequences in this anime have either a different song or different animation, maybe even to the point of having a unique ED for each episode.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3977" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-29">
<name>dialogue driven</name>
<description>A dialogue driven show has its story advanced by dialogue, with action being of much lower priority, and relies heavily on conversations between characters.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4131" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-05-11">
<name>cultural references</name>
<description>The plot of this anime shows signs of cultural references, these are often jokes that make reference to a certain custom, habit or history that is specifically attributed to that culture. Knowledge of the culture itself is needed in order to properly understand these jokes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4498" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-20">
<name>heart-warming</name>
<description>The story and its characters give off good vibes — includes elevated feelings of affection such as tenderness, sympathy and love, all in one package.
The kind of anime which leaves you with a warm feeling inside and you can not stop smiling while watching it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4560" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-02-23">
<name>psychological manipulation</name>
<description>Psychological manipulation is a type of social influence that aims to change the perception or behaviour of others through underhanded, deceptive, or even abusive tactics. By advancing the interests of the manipulator, often at the other`s expense, such methods could be considered exploitative, abusive, devious, and deceptive. 
Social influence is not necessarily negative. For example, doctors can try to persuade patients to change unhealthy habits. Social influence is generally perceived to be harmless when it respects the right of the influenced to accept or reject it, and is not unduly coercive. Depending on the context and motivations, social influence may constitute underhanded manipulation.
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4570" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-08-10">
<name>watercolour style</name>
<description>A watercolour or aquarelle is a painting method in which the paints are made of pigments suspended in a water-based solution. Some anime are created in the style of watercolour paintings, the watercolour style, usually with faded pastels that often give the show a warm and friendly visual presentation. In modern anime, this is generally achieved via computer effects that create an imitation of watercolour, rather than by creating real-life watercolour art. While the watercolour style is more commonly used for backgrounds, it is possible to create the entire anime in such a style.</description>
<picurl>251159.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4576" parentid="6185" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-03">
<name>summer</name>
<description>At least one of the episodes takes place in summer. Think oppressively warm weather, summer vacation, summer school, summer festival, or a visit to the beach.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4614" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>narration</name>
<description>The most common example is that of a voice, either that of one of the characters or entirely unrelated, that appears at the beginning of an episode to offer a summary or introduction, and at the end of an episode for closure or for a preview to hint upon what to expect next.
Another use of narration comes in the form of a dominant voice belonging to one of the protagonists, intended only for the viewer and revealing the intimate thoughts to whom it belongs. This type of narration occurs frequently throughout the duration of the episode or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4907" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-23">
<name>small town</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5276" parentid="2874" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-02-25">
<name>typhoon</name>
<description>A typhoon is a mature tropical cyclone that develops in the north-western part of the Pacific Ocean between 180° and 100°E. This region is referred to as the north-west Pacific basin. Identical phenomena in the eastern north Pacific are called hurricanes, with tropical cyclones moving into the western Pacific re-designated as typhoons.
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5518" parentid="7199" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-03">
<name>flat chest jokes</name>
<description>Jokes about the (supposedly or actually) flat chest of a character.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5705" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-08-18">
<name>butchered foreign languages</name>
<description>In this anime, some characters "speak" foreign languages, successfully making the audience`s ears bleed. That is especially true if the viewer is a native speaker of or otherwise proficient in the languages in question.
The foreigners in the show do not seem to take much notice of the fact that their supposed native languages are being massacred. In fact, oftentimes they also actively participate in the butchering of said languages. That happens, of course, because they, too, are voiced by Japanese people without knowledge of the language they`re supposed to speak, or to pretend to speak at any rate.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5834" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>show within a show</name>
<description>A fictional TV (or radio, or stage) show that takes place within an actual TV show; or, occasionally, a fictional instalment or incarnation of an actual show. Many comedies have short one-off gags where they parody existing shows.
Example: A large part of Martian Successor Nadesico is centred around the fictional popular anime Gekigangar III, which is being watched by several characters of the Nadesico crew.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6005" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-10-17">
<name>battle of wits</name>
<description>There is some intellectual battle between the characters. They each might attempt to discern what the other knows and/or could be planning. Then, rather than simply relying on the use of raw power, try to deduce an effective strategy to foil their opponent(s). The battle of wits can be in the center of the intrigue or just a side story.
Examples: Death Note, Code Geass</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6034" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>Engrish</name>
<description>Engrish is actually a mispronunciation of English, as can be the result of someone, who does not have English as their primary language of origin (such as Japanese or Chinese). Occasionally characters in the original Japanese dialogue version of an anime will speak in English... however; this often still requires the assistance of subtitles, for while the words are meant to be said in English, the sentence structure and letter pronunciation may still be strongly related to the person’s primary language.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6072" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-25">
<name>just as planned</name>
<description>A term usually used to describe a situation, where a seemingly smart and cunning villain sets up a plan that seems grand and impressive, but is actually long winding, ridiculous, and convoluted. And all of that just to trick his opponent(s), like the hero or anybody else, into doing things exactly as he planned. Suffice to say that the villain could have reached his goal by much shorter and easier means, it just wouldn`t seem as awesome anymore.
The phrase is also known as the original Japanese "keikaku doori" where keikaku stands translated for "plan" or "schedule", and doori for "in accordance with ..." or "following ...".
The phrase is a reference to http://anidb.net/ch301 [Yagami Light] from http://anidb.net/a4563 [Death Note], and his love for plans.</description>
<picurl>211219.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6349" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-13">
<name>multi-segment episodes</name>
<description>Multi-segment episodes are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t5852 [short episodes], which are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length (up to and including 10 minutes).
Also not to be confused with an OVA or music video with multiple (otherwise unrelated) full-length http://anidb.net/t7241 [bundled episodes] consolidated into a single episode video track.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6724" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-03-07">
<name>Anime no Me</name>
<description>Anime no Me was an anime brand and programming block by http://anidb.net/cr917 [TMS Entertainment], http://anidb.net/cr1284 [Shin-Ei Animation], East Japan Marketing &amp; Communications, Inc., Sumitomo Corporation, and http://anidb.net/cr36685 [Asmik-Ace]. It ran from July 2016 to March 2018. The "Me" in its name means "eye" and refers to the eye of a typhoon.</description>
<picurl>64114.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7199" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-12">
<name>sexual humour</name>
<description>Sexual humour is prevalent in this anime. It often involves cheeky or crude sexual language, with innuendos and jokes about the female or male genitalia. Often, such anime also have http://anidb.net/t2856 [ecchi] elements to them.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="91670" type="main character in" update="2020-02-12">
<rating votes="23">4.82</rating>
<name>Nishikata</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>222726.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1678" picture="68277.jpg">Kaji Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="91671" type="main character in" update="2018-08-25">
<rating votes="89">7.28</rating>
<name>Takagi-san</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>222727.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38380" picture="224406.jpg">Takahashi Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93161" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-01-09">
<rating votes="13">4.84</rating>
<name>Tsukimoto Sanae</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211787.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16794" picture="214757.jpg">Ogura Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93162" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-01-09">
<rating votes="29">5.05</rating>
<name>Hibino Mina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211785.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="48852" picture="225071.jpg">Kohara Konomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93163" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-01-09">
<rating votes="12">4.32</rating>
<name>Amakawa Yukari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211786.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36368" picture="224755.jpg">Mao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93164" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-01-09">
<rating votes="7">3.88</rating>
<name>Nakai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211788.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38579" picture="225249.jpg">Uchida Yuuma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93165" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-01-09">
<rating votes="7">1.95</rating>
<name>Kimura</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211791.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="44099" picture="225101.jpg">Ochiai Fukushi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93166" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-01-09">
<rating votes="4">3.25</rating>
<name>Tanabe-sensei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211792.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43359" picture="226056.jpg">Tadokoro Hinata</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93167" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-01-09">
<rating votes="20">3.58</rating>
<name>Mano</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211789.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32588" picture="87531.jpg">Koiwai Kotori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93168" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-01-09">
<rating votes="7">1.65</rating>
<name>Takao</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>211790.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="390" picture="33609.jpg">Okamoto Nobuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94867" type="appears in" update="2018-03-31">
<name>Kokugo no Sensei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>215670.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36770" picture="151722.jpg">Nose Ikuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94878" type="appears in" update="2018-04-02">
<name>Suugaku no Sensei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>215745.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12640" picture="226055.jpg">Souma Kouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94962" type="appears in" update="2018-04-08">
<name>Bijutsu no Sensei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>215994.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="539" picture="228668.jpg">Aizawa Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94963" type="appears in" update="2018-04-08">
<name>Bob Cut no Ko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>215995.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43914" picture="225361.jpg">Kondou Reina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94964" type="appears in" update="2018-04-08">
<name>Sakurai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>215996.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="52057" picture="225903.jpg">Ichikawa Aoi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94965" type="appears in" update="2018-04-08">
<name>Kyoutou Sensei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>216000.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32216" picture="223331.jpg">Sasa Kenta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94966" type="appears in" update="2020-04-18">
<rating votes="1">2.04</rating>
<name>Ponytail no Ko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>246361.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="44228" picture="222798.jpg">Asahina Madoka</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="194324" update="2018-01-29">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-01-29</airdate>
<rating votes="10">7.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">掃除当番 / 逆上がり / 風邪 / 尾行</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cleaning Duty / Kickover / Cold / Tailing</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Corvée de nettoyage / La barre fixe / Le rhume / La filature</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">청소당번 / 철봉오르기 / 감기 / 미행</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Soujitouban / Sakaagari / Kaze / Bikou</title>
<summary>Nishikata is put on cleaning duty as a punishment for interrupting class.
As he goes to the cleaning supply storage, Takagi-san is there! Was she put on cleaning duty too?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>759139</identifier>
<identifier>karakai-jozu-no-takagi-san</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="194325" update="2018-01-28">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-01-22</airdate>
<rating votes="11">6.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">コーヒー / 空き缶 / 炭酸 / 筋トレ / アフレコ / 傘</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Coffee / Empty Can / Soda / Muscle Training / Dubbing / Umbrella</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le café / Les canettes / Les boissons gazeuses / Musculation / Doublage de rue / Le parapluie</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">커피 / 빈 캔 / 탄산 / 근육운동 / 더빙 / 우산</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Coffee / Akikan / Tansan / Kin Tore / Afureko / Kasa</title>
<summary>Mina believes she’s mature enough to enjoy coffee, but Yukari and Sanae think otherwise.
On a rainy day, Takagi-san has forgotten her umbrella. Nishikata to the rescue...?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>759137</identifier>
<identifier>karakai-jozu-no-takagi-san</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="194326" update="2018-01-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-01-15</airdate>
<rating votes="11">5.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">習字 / 衣替え / 英訳 / プール</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Calligraphy / Seasonal Change of Clothing / English Translation / Pool</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Calligraphie / Traduction / La Piscine</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">습자 / 옷갈아입기 / 영어해석 / 수영시간</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shuuji / Koromogae / Eiyaku / Pool</title>
<summary>Nishikata doesn`t know what to write for his calligraphy class, so Takagi-san suggests they should both write what they want from each other.
Nishikata wants Takagi-san to stop teasing him, of course, but what does Takagi-san want from Nishikata?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>759135</identifier>
<identifier>karakai-jozu-no-takagi-san</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="194327" update="2018-01-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-01-08</airdate>
<rating votes="15">6.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">消しゴム / 日直 / 変顔 / 百円</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Eraser / Day Duty / Funny Face / One Hundred Yen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La gomme / Les corvées du matin / Les grimaces / La pièce</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">지우개 / 당번 / 웃긴표정 / 백엔</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Keshigomu / Nicchoku / Hengao / Hyaku En</title>
<summary>Takagi-san is an expert when it comes to teasing Nishikata.
Is there any way Nishikata can get back at her?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>759133</identifier>
<identifier>karakai-jozu-no-takagi-san</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="194999" update="2018-01-08">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-01-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195000" update="2018-01-08">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-01-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="195380" update="2018-03-13">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-02-26</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">台風 / マラソン / わき腹 / 未練</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Typhoon / Marathon / Ribs / Regret</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le typhon / La course à pied / Les chatouilles / Regrets</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">태풍 / 마라톤 / 옆구리 / 미련</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Taifuu / Marathon / Wakibara / Miren</title>
<summary>Nishikata has mastered tandem riding with Takagi-san, so why does he feel a bit melancholy?
On his way to school, Nishikata is psyched about the typhoon, but he runs into Takagi-san at the worst timing.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>759147</identifier>
<identifier>karakai-jozu-no-takagi-san</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="195381" update="2018-06-16">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-02-19</airdate>
<rating votes="7">8.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">買い物 / 水着 / 海 / 部屋</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shopping / Bathing Suit / Ocean / Room</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Shopping / Le maillot de bain / La mer / Ma chambre</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">쇼핑 / 수영복 / 바다 / 방</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaimono / Mizugi / Umi / Heya</title>
<summary>Nishikata is at the mall to buy the latest volume of "100% Unrequited Love" when he runs into Takagi-san. 
She wants Nishikata to help her pick out a bathing suit, but Nishikata is too embarrassed to be seen with her. 
Suddenly, Nishikata hears a familiar voice...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>759145</identifier>
<identifier>karakai-jozu-no-takagi-san</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="195382" update="2018-06-16">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-02-12</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.10</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">二人乗り / 夏休み初日 / 肝試し / 自由研究 / 水道</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tandem Riding / First Day of Summer Vacation / Test of Courage / Summer Science Project / Water Tap</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Rouler à deux / Premier jour des vacances / L`épreuve de courage / Journal d’observations / La fontaine</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">둘이 자전거 타기 / 방학 첫날 / 담력 훈련 / 자유 연구 / 수도</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Futarinori / Natsuyasumi Shonichi / Kimodameshi / Jiyuukenkyuu / Suidou</title>
<summary>Nishikata is so happy summer vacation is starting, but Takagi-san doesn`t seem that excited.
She suggests they should practice tandem riding during vacation. When Nishikata agrees, she finally seems enthusiastic about summer vacation.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>759143</identifier>
<identifier>karakai-jozu-no-takagi-san</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="195383" update="2018-06-16">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-02-05</airdate>
<rating votes="8">8.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">テスト勉強 / テスト / テスト返却 / 本屋 / 雨宿り</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Studying for the Test / Test / Test Results / Bookstore / Shelter from the Rain</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les révisions / Le contrôle / L`annonce des résultats / La librairie / Jour de pluie</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">시험공부 / 시험 / 채점확인 / 서점 / 비 피하기</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Test Benkyou / Test / Test Henkyaku / Hon`ya / Amayadori</title>
<summary>Nishikata is studying hard for the test for the sake of his video games when Takagi-san enters the library.
Takagi-san teaches him how to solve a math problem, but Nishikata can`t help but think she`s up to no good...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>759141</identifier>
<identifier>karakai-jozu-no-takagi-san</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="196463" update="2018-02-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-03-26</airdate>
<rating votes="8">8.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">手紙 / 入学式 / 席替え</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Letter / First Day of School / Seating Arrangement</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La lettre / La cérémonie de rentrée / Changement de places</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">편지 / 입학식 / 자리 변경</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tegami / Nyuugakushiki / Sekigae</title>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>759155</identifier>
<identifier>karakai-jozu-no-takagi-san</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="196464" update="2018-06-16">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-03-19</airdate>
<rating votes="10">9.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ネコ / 好み / 似顔絵 / 占い / クリティカル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cat / Taste / Portrait / Fortune Telling / Critical</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les chats / Les goûts et les couleurs / Portrait / Prédictions</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">고양이 / 취향 / 초상화 / 점 / 크리티컬</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Neko / Konomi / Nigaoe / Uranai / Critical</title>
<summary>Nishikata really likes cats but doesn`t want Takagi-san to know.
But when he sees a very friendly cat, he can`t help it.
What is a guy to do?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>759153</identifier>
<identifier>karakai-jozu-no-takagi-san</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="196465" update="2018-06-16">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-03-12</airdate>
<rating votes="7">8.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">背比べ / 寒がり / お誘い / 二択クイズ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Who`s Taller? / I Hate the Cold / Invitation / Two-Choice Question</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Qui est le plus grand ? / La frileuse / Les invitations / Choix à deux options</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">키 재기 / 추위 / 제안 / 선택 퀴즈</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sekurabe / Samugari / Osasoi / Nitaku Quiz</title>
<summary>Takagi-san and Nishikata compare heights to see if Nishikata did indeed grow. 
But as always, her method is unusual and Nishikata can`t help but wonder...
Meanwhile, Yukari is curious about the two because they`re always hanging out together.
Are Takagi-san and Nishikata going out?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>759151</identifier>
<identifier>karakai-jozu-no-takagi-san</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="196466" update="2018-06-16">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-03-05</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ケータイ / ホラー / 写真</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Cell Phone / Horror / Picture</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les portables / Histoires d`horreur / La photo</title>
<title xml:lang="ko">휴대폰 / 호러 / 사진</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Keitai / Horror / Shashin</title>
<summary>Nishikata receives his first cell phone and can`t wait to play tricks on Takagi-san.
He sends her a scary video to frighten her, but it doesn`t quite work. 
As usual, Takagi-san has the upper hand when it comes to teasing...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>759149</identifier>
<identifier>karakai-jozu-no-takagi-san</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="197890" update="2018-04-10">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-01-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="197892" update="2018-04-10">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-03-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="197893" update="2018-04-10">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-03-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.31</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="197894" update="2018-04-10">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-02-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="197895" update="2018-04-10">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-02-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="214718" update="2020-02-10">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-03-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 12 Ending</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
