<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="13434" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2018-04-06</startdate>
<enddate>2018-06-22</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Hinamatsuri (2018)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Hina Matsuri</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ヒナまつり (2018)</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Hinamatsuri</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Хинамацури</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">히나마츠리 (2018)</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="official">مهرجان هينا</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">黑社会的超能力女儿</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="12526" approval="24" total="47">Alice to Zouroku</anime>
<anime id="12091" approval="9" total="23">Kobayashi-san Chi no Maidragon</anime>
<anime id="4528" approval="2" total="11">Sumomo mo Momo mo: Chijou Saikyou no Yome</anime>
<anime id="13250" approval="1" total="9">Chio-chan no Tsuugakuro</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="11">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="26332">Not bad but somehow unfinished. There are a lot of unanswered questions left.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="808415">Somehow heart warming and the only one, of the last years, I`ve watched multiple times.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="118534">Short and sweet, and very enjoyable! You just need to adjust to its pacing because it is rather short with unfinished storytelling and overlooked sci-fi elements. The world building could use some work but the character building was superb for such a short series.

It`s quite funny, wholesome, and even heart-wrenching at times, which caught me off guard based on the overall tone. It did at times feel like two different anime’s playing out at once, or trying to juggle different genres. But I appreciate the satirical aspects as much as the humbling moments where they address real life issues or put things into perspective.  

I wish there was more, but this is easily recommended for what it is.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="531837">funny AF and can hit you in the feels too.
it`s a 20 out of 10.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="244610">One of the few things in the world that actually made me laugh out loud in places. Weird, whacky, quirky, etc. Stick with it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="41949">Enjoyable social satire which spotlights the weakest link in Japanese society -- effete, entitled [s]@#$%^&amp;!s[/s] kids, symbolized by [url=http://anidb.net/perl-bin/animedb.pl?show=character&amp;charid=93274]Hina[/url], who have too much pocket money but who could, if required, rise to any occasion. 

The delightful [url=https://anidb.net/perl-bin/animedb.pl?show=character&amp;charid=93272]Anzu[/url] and [url=https://anidb.net/perl-bin/animedb.pl?show=character&amp;charid=93276]Hitomi[/url] exemplify what the creators believe Japanese kids [i]could[/i] become, if they were allowed to (God forbid!) actually suffer and get their hands dirty.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://hina-matsuri.net/</url>
<creators>
<name id="51709" type="Original Work">Ootake Masao</name>
<name id="1006" type="Animation Work">Feel</name>
<name id="9387" type="Character Design">Kamimoto Kanetoshi</name>
<name id="16218" type="Chief Animation Direction">Araki Ryou</name>
<name id="6072" type="Chief Animation Direction">Takeuchi Tetsuya</name>
<name id="18608" type="Chief Animation Direction">Masuda Kuniaki</name>
<name id="19347" type="Series Composition">Oochi Keiichirou</name>
<name id="7821" type="Direction">Oikawa Kei</name>
<name id="7802" type="Music">Misawa Yasuhiro</name>
<name id="9387" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kamimoto Kanetoshi</name>
<name id="8546" type="Chief Animation Direction">Masuda Kuniaki</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a comedy seinen manga series written and illustrated by http://anidb.net/cr51709 [Ootake Masao].
One night, a strange object falls on the head of http://anidb.net/ch93277 [Nitta], a member of the yakuza. Inside the box is a strange young girl named http://anidb.net/ch93274 [Hina]. She has tremendous supernatural powers, and Nitta finds himself reluctantly taking her in. Her powers can come in handy for his yakuza business, but he also runs the risk of her using them on him! Not to mention, if she doesn`t use her powers, she will eventually go berserk and destroy everything around her. Nitta and Hina`s strange life together is just beginning...
Source: M-U</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1975">8.05</permanent>
<temporary count="1982">7.86</temporary>
<review count="1">8.00</review>
</ratings>
<picture>215332.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20335</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>36296</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://hina-matsuri.net/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Hinamatsuri_(manga)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ヒナまつり</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4853</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>361820</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21044</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>hinamatsuri4649</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>hinamatsuri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B07VNTPMY7</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1018" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-25">
<name>middle school</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2631" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-02-11">
<name>island</name>
<description>Part of this anime takes place on an island, a small landmass that is surrounded by the sea. Generally, an island setting involves interaction with "island" elements. Such elements could include (but is not limited towards): riding on a boat, fishing, foraging/hunting, beach scene, "peaceful island life", being "shipwrecked", island fever, lamenting isolation from the mainland, etc.
An island or isle is any piece of sub-continental land that is surrounded by water. Very small islands such as emergent land features on atolls can be called islets, cays or keys. An island in a river or lake may be called an eyot (also ait), or holm. A grouping of geographically or geologically related islands is called an archipelago.
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2634" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>countryside</name>
<description>The anime takes place far from the any densely populated areas like cities, i.e. out in the suburbs, in the countryside with many fields and forests.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2674" parentid="2834" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>China</name>
<description>China, officially the People`s Republic of China (PRC), is a unitary sovereign state in East Asia and the world`s most populous country. It is the third- or fourth-largest country by total area, depending on the source consulted. China also has the most neighbor countries in the world. Governed by the Communist Party of China, it exercises jurisdiction over 22 provinces, five autonomous regions, four direct-controlled municipalities (Beijing, Tianjin, Shanghai, and Chongqing), and the special administrative regions of Hong Kong and Macau.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214277.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2676" parentid="2672" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo</name>
<description>Tokyo, officially Tokyo Metropolis, is the capital city of Japan and one of its 47 prefectures. The Greater Tokyo Area is the most populous metropolitan area in the world. It is the seat of the Emperor of Japan and the Japanese government. Tokyo is in the Kantou region on the southeastern side of the main island Honshu and includes the Izu Islands and Ogasawara Islands.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214311.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2793" parentid="2883" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>performance</name>
<description>The song performance on stage or acting in a theatre is a central part of the character`s life in this anime type.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2821" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>sudden naked girl appearance</name>
<description>A character or group of characters are simply minding their own business, when suddenly, a naked girl appears. It does not matter how or why, but a naked someone is there. Sometimes the naked girl is not happy about this. 
Usually this is a fanservice element, but not always.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2840" parentid="2872" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>mafia</name>
<description>A mafia is a type of organized crime syndicate whose primary activities are protection racketeering, the arbitration of disputes between criminals, and the organizing and oversight of illegal agreements and transactions. Secondary activities may be practiced such as gambling, drug trafficking, loan sharking, and fraud. The term was originally applied to the Sicilian mafia, but has since expanded to encompass other organizations of similar methods and purpose, such as in "the Russian mafia" or "the Japanese mafia", and is applied informally by the press and public, but the criminal organizations themselves have their own terms; for example, the original Sicilian and Italian-American mafia call themselves "cosa nostra", while the Japanese mafia calls itself "yakuza".
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>211289.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2879" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>alcohol</name>
<description>Alcohol (or more scientifically, ethanol), is one of the world`s oldest psychoactive substances. It is traditionally found in the form of a beverage such as beer, wine, or liquor, although in some contexts it can be inhaled to produce similar or intoxication, and some people prefer another way of consuming beverage-form alcohol.
Alcoholic beverages are many and varied, due to production methods (fermentation or distillation), source materials (grains, fruits, vegetables, other plants), added substances such as flavorings, and many more ways of defining different forms of alcoholic beverages.
Alcoholic beverages are divided into three general classes: beers, wines, and spirits. They are legally consumed in most countries, and over 100 countries have laws regulating their production, sale, and consumption. In particular, such laws specify the minimum age at which a person may legally buy or drink them. This minimum age varies between 16 and 25 years, depending upon the country and the type of drink. Most nations set it at 18 years of age.</description>
<picurl>70749.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3028" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-17">
<name>real-world location</name>
<description>Places seen in the show exist in reality.
Note: This could be sometime in the future, though names and certain places will still be recognizable.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3037" parentid="2676" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Tokyo Skytree</name>
<description>Tokyo Skytree is a broadcasting, restaurant, and observation tower in Sumida, Tokyo, Japan. It became the tallest structure in Japan in 2010 and reached its full height of 634.0 metres in March 2011, making it the tallest tower in the world, displacing the Canton Tower, and the second tallest structure in the world after Burj Khalifa (829.8 m).
Source: Wikipedia
Note: Not to be confused with the very much older http://anidb.net/t3667 [Tokyo Tower].</description>
<picurl>161122.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3217" parentid="2864" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-17">
<name>working life</name>
<description>The life of someone actually working on a often less than glamorous job is depicted in this anime. The job is taxing and the pay is low, not really the dream job one would choose to work in.
Examples: Working as salesperson in a department store, or as a waitress in a family restaurant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3506" parentid="6397" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-23">
<name>Robinson Crusoe</name>
<description>Literary classic about a man marooned on a distant island.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3568" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-02-07">
<name>gambling</name>
<description>Gambling is the wagering of money or something of value (referred to as "the stakes") on an event with an uncertain outcome with the primary intent of winning additional money and/or material goods. Gambling thus requires three elements be present: consideration, chance and prize. The outcome of the wager is often immediate, such as a single roll of dice or a spin of a roulette wheel, but longer time frames are also common, allowing wagers on the outcome of a future sports contest or even an entire sports season.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3953" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-10-04">
<name>in medias res</name>
<description>In medias res, also medias in res (Latin for "into the midst of affairs (lit. into mid-affairs)"), refers to a literary and artistic technique where the narrative starts in the middle of the story instead of from its beginning. It is generally a plot-driven concept rather than a character-driven one; though characters are commonly used to provide the backstory. The characters, setting, and conflict are often introduced through a series of http://anidb.net/t4299 [flashbacks] or through characters relating past events to each other.
Probably originating from an oral tradition, the technique is a convention of epic poetry, one of the earliest and most prominent examples in Western literature being Homer`s Odyssey and Iliad. Virgil`s Aeneid began the tradition in literature of imitating Homer, continued in Torquato Tasso`s Jerusalem Delivered, John Milton`s Paradise Lost and "Inferno" from Dante`s Divine Comedy. George Lucas`s Star Wars saga was told using in medias res.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4055" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-10-12">
<name>facial distortion</name>
<description>The characters face are exaggerated into a misshape, deformed, and almost warped. Used as comedy element to express extreme mood swings.
Differing from "http://anidb.net/t2652 [super deformed]", here only the face changes to an extreme degree, not the whole body of the protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4083" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-04">
<name>drastic change of life</name>
<description>One or more characters in this series go through an event that makes them change their way of life drastically and permanently. This change might be voluntary, or against the character`s will.
Some examples might be an accident, the gaining of superpowers, or simply graduating.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4085" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-02-17">
<name>unlikely duo</name>
<description>Comedy element: There is usually not only a difference in gender but also in appearance, character, and background concerning the main characters of this anime. Making it very unlikely for them to appear in the same context. Non-the-less they share the same adventure, as in "opposites attract".
These differences are exploited to come up with all sorts of wacky situations.
Examples: A demon-killer or Hero and the daughter of the Demon King. A girl from a normal family and a very intelligent and attractive boy from a very rich background (Shoujo). A very energetic outgoing girl and her very calm almost introverted best friend.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4198" parentid="5604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-14">
<name>hard work and guts</name>
<description>One of the character`s motto in the anime. Because there is nothing that cannot be achieved by hard work and guts.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4257" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-08-07">
<name>survival</name>
<description>The theme/genre of survival typically depicts the act or process of continuing to live, generally in a hostile, possibly post-apocalyptic environment. Survival-centered media tends to be dark, set most commonly in a contemporary context, and generally leads either to small groups of people forming closely knit and functional units or to individuals turning against their fellows in a return to the survival of the fittest.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4498" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-20">
<name>heart-warming</name>
<description>The story and its characters give off good vibes — includes elevated feelings of affection such as tenderness, sympathy and love, all in one package.
The kind of anime which leaves you with a warm feeling inside and you can not stop smiling while watching it.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4522" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>social commentary</name>
<description>Social commentary is the act of rebelling against an individual, or a group of people by rhetorical means. This is most often done with the idea of implementing or promoting change by informing the general populace about a given problem and appealing to people’s sense of justice. (Source: Wikipedia)&#13;
&#13;
Since this is anime, usually, the mores of Japan and the Japanese society are scrutinised, but not restricted to that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4669" parentid="6249" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-27">
<name>parenting</name>
<description>This anime is about parenting and its many challenges.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4785" parentid="2794" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>rock music</name>
<description>Rock music is a genre of popular music that originated as "rock and roll" in the United States in the 1950s, and developed into a range of different styles in the 1960s and later, particularly in the United Kingdom and the United States. Musically, rock has centered on the electric guitar, usually as part of a rock group with electric bass guitar and drums. Typically, rock is song-based music usually with a 4/4 time signature using a verse-chorus form, but the genre has become extremely diverse. Like pop music, lyrics often stress romantic love but also address a wide variety of other themes that are frequently social or political in emphasis. The dominance of rock by white, male musicians has been seen as one of the key factors shaping the themes explored in rock music. Rock places a higher degree of emphasis on musicianship, live performance, and an ideology of authenticity than pop music.</description>
<picurl>10250.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5459" parentid="6243" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-10">
<name>poverty</name>
<description>It refers to the condition of not having the means to afford basic human needs.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5604" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-04">
<name>following one`s dream</name>
<description>No matter what the hardships may be, at least one of the protagonists in this anime is following her/his dream.
Examples: To become a professional athlete, a musician, a painter or the ruler of this world!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5773" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-14">
<name>secret organisation</name>
<description>A secret organisation or secret society is an organisation whose activities and inner functioning are concealed from non-members. The society may or may not attempt to conceal its existence itself. Examples of historical and existing secret societies include Freemasonry, the Knights Templar, the Rosicrucians, Skull and Bones, the Thule Society, and the Illuminati.</description>
<picurl>192876.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5935" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-07-06">
<name>ass-kicking girls</name>
<description>The female characters in the anime are very proficient in some form of martial arts, swordplay, or gunfights. They may also have super powers.</description>
<picurl>71307.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6243" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-29">
<name>money</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6397" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-02">
<name>tales</name>
<description>Tales are stories told time and again and passed down from generation to generation, and some of those show up in anime not just once or twice, but several times.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="93272" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-05-19">
<rating votes="64">8.22</rating>
<name>Anzu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Anzu is another superhuman with telekinetic powers like http://anidb.net/ch93274 [Hina]. She is initially sent to kill Hina, but loses to her in a contest of strength and abandons the mission. Unable to return to her masters because the device necessary to do so was inadvertently damaged, she joins a homeless camp in Tokyo, but is later taken in by a couple who run a Chinese restaurant and learns the secrets of making good ramen from them.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>211968.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32020" picture="127735.jpg">Murakawa Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93273" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-05-19">
<rating votes="7">4.56</rating>
<name>Sabu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sabu is http://anidb.net/ch93277 [Nitta]`s underling in his http://anidb.net/ch95617 [yakuza group]. He usually proves somewhat inept at whatever task he is assigned, such as debt collection, forcing Nitta to handle matters personally.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>211971.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23529" picture="178469.jpg">Kawanishi Kengo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93274" type="main character in" update="2018-05-19">
<rating votes="38">6.39</rating>
<name>Hina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hina is the titular heroine who has superhuman abilities, which include telekinesis and explosion. She may be from another world or timeline, and it is implied she was the subject of experiments or used as a weapon. She usually lazes around at http://anidb.net/ch93277 [Nitta]`s apartment and sleeps in school. She is very particular about food despite demonstrably lacking a refined palate, and her favorite food is salmon roe.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>211964.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="49207" picture="243216.jpg">Tanaka Takako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93275" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-06-23">
<rating votes="29">7.08</rating>
<name>Mao</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mao is another esper with telekinetic powers from the same organization as http://anidb.net/ch93274 [Hina] and http://anidb.net/ch93272 [Anzu]. After being sent to recover them both, she accidentally lands on a deserted island and is stuck there for months without human contact, creating wooden puppet versions of Hina and Anzu to keep from going insane.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>211969.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39007" picture="148258.jpg">Ozawa Ari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93276" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-05-19">
<rating votes="85">8.82</rating>
<name>Mishima Hitomi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mishima Hitomi is http://anidb.net/ch93274 [Hina]`s classmate in middle school, a pushover who has trouble saying no to helping people. Her demeanor indirectly leads her to usurp http://anidb.net/ch93279 [Utako]`s position as the bartender at her own bar. Then, through a series of coincidences, she is mistaken as an adult and later becomes an influential member of society with connections to businesspeople, politicians, and the yakuza.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>211966.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43552" picture="179144.jpg">Hondo Kaede</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93277" type="main character in" update="2018-05-19">
<rating votes="21">6.69</rating>
<name>Nitta Yoshifumi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nitta Yoshifumi is the main protagonist who takes http://anidb.net/ch93274 [Hina] into his home and somewhat resents her intrusion into his bachelor lifestyle. He is a yakuza of the http://anidb.net/ch95617 [Ashikawa group], where he quickly rises through the ranks thanks to Hina`s abilities and his own prowess at administration. He acquired cooking and housekeeping skills to take care of his mother and younger sister after his father died, and his hobby is collecting rare porcelain vases and urns (which Hina often destroys). His family and fellow yakuza members are convinced that Hina is his daughter from a past relationship.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>211965.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33069" picture="225127.jpg">Nakajima Yoshiki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93278" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-05-19">
<rating votes="7">2.22</rating>
<name>Baba Kiyoshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Baba Kiyoshi is the second-in-command of http://anidb.net/ch93277 [Nitta]`s http://anidb.net/ch95617 [yakuza group]. He views Nitta as a shameless brown-noser, but respects his recent accomplishments.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>211970.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="267" picture="250262.jpg">Koyama Tsuyoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93279" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-05-19">
<rating votes="19">4.87</rating>
<name>Utako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Utako is the owner and original bartender of the bar Little Song. She blackmails http://anidb.net/ch93276 [Hitomi] into working for her after Hitomi becomes highly skilled at bartending, but is soon made redundant in her own bar as her customers come to prefer Hitomi`s drinks. http://anidb.net/ch93277 [Nitta] was romantically interested in Utako, but she rejects him because she believes him to be a divorced single father, and Nitta later loses interest in her due to her self-centered personality.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>211967.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1799" picture="156027.jpg">Hikasa Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95216" type="appears in" update="2018-08-10">
<rating votes="1">5.66</rating>
<name>Ashikawa Yoshihiko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ashikawa Yoshihiko is the head of http://anidb.net/ch93277 [Nitta]`s http://anidb.net/ch95617 [yakuza group]. He eventually retires from his position due his advanced age and poor health, but maintains much of his influence. He dotes on http://anidb.net/ch93274 [Hina] in a grandfatherly way, even using yakuza resources to assist her in such situations as running for student council president, and encourages Nitta to take a more active interest in raising her.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picture>216732.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2271" picture="23219.jpg">Shibata Hidekatsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95217" type="appears in" update="2018-04-26">
<rating votes="2">6.80</rating>
<name>Matsutani-sensei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>216733.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="196" picture="17010.jpg">Nojima Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95218" type="appears in" update="2018-05-14">
<rating votes="3">8.12</rating>
<name>Yassan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>217617.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2021" picture="187129.jpg">Tsuji Shinpachi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95219" type="appears in" update="2018-04-26">
<rating votes="1">3.78</rating>
<name>Tanaka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>216735.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10906" picture="200861.jpg">Yanagita Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95480" type="appears in" update="2018-05-12">
<rating votes="1">5.66</rating>
<name>Shige-san</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>217469.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43013" picture="172173.jpg">Furukawa Tomomutsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95481" type="appears in" update="2018-06-23">
<rating votes="2">7.75</rating>
<name>Atsushi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>219461.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38431" picture="224824.jpg">Yashiro Taku</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95491" type="appears in" update="2018-05-13">
<rating votes="1">7.62</rating>
<name>Guitar</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>217488.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42006" picture="232274.jpg">Mizunaka Masaaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95493" type="appears in" update="2018-05-13">
<rating votes="1">3.78</rating>
<name>Central Park</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>217490.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="95494" type="appears in" update="2018-05-13">
<rating votes="1">3.78</rating>
<name>Bass</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>217491.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="95495" type="appears in" update="2018-05-13">
<rating votes="1">3.78</rating>
<name>Drummer</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>217492.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42617" picture="170041.jpg">Nakamura Kazumasa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95613" type="appears in" update="2018-05-19">
<rating votes="1">3.78</rating>
<name>Shimoda Takashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>217729.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10392" picture="38279.jpg">Chikaki Yuuya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95614" type="appears in" update="2018-05-19">
<rating votes="1">3.78</rating>
<name>Nakata Kengo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>217730.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42052" picture="225801.jpg">Ichikawa Taichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95615" type="appears in" update="2018-05-19">
<rating votes="6">4.80</rating>
<name>Aizawa Sayo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>217732.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16085" picture="178446.jpg">Komatsu Mikako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95616" type="appears in" update="2018-05-19">
<rating votes="1">5.66</rating>
<name>Yoshida</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>217733.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33784" picture="93013.jpg">Takeuchi Eiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95617" type="appears in" update="2018-05-19">
<rating votes="1">7.62</rating>
<name>Ashikawa-gumi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="95794" type="appears in" update="2018-05-29">
<rating votes="1">5.66</rating>
<name>Gotou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>218131.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="13954" picture="186143.jpg">Tokumoto Eiichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95795" type="appears in" update="2018-05-29">
<rating votes="1">5.66</rating>
<name>Nitta no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>218132.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33745" picture="92673.jpg">Nakamura Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95796" type="appears in" update="2018-05-29">
<rating votes="2">7.75</rating>
<name>Nitta Mika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>218133.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9511" picture="35179.jpg">Honda Mariko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95797" type="appears in" update="2018-08-10">
<rating votes="1">7.62</rating>
<name>Hayashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>222101.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2893" picture="240353.jpg">Yamaguchi Tarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95798" type="appears in" update="2018-05-29">
<rating votes="1">7.62</rating>
<name>Hayashi no Tsuma</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>218135.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40709" picture="159960.jpg">Makihara Chika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95799" type="appears in" update="2018-05-29">
<rating votes="1">7.62</rating>
<name>Ogura Gorou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>218136.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39260" picture="150015.jpg">Ishiya Haruki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95800" type="appears in" update="2018-05-29">
<rating votes="1">5.66</rating>
<name>Shinjou Mami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>218137.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37089" picture="228978.jpg">Suzuki Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="95801" type="appears in" update="2018-05-29">
<rating votes="1">3.78</rating>
<name>Watanabe Chuugakkou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
</character>
<character id="95979" type="appears in" update="2018-08-10">
<rating votes="1">7.62</rating>
<name>Mishima Minako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>222102.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1918" picture="225099.jpg">Sakurai Harumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96201" type="appears in" update="2018-06-17">
<rating votes="2">5.97</rating>
<name>Ikaruga Kei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ikaruga Kei is the chief of certain secret organization`s security, of which http://anidb.net/ch93274 [Hina], http://anidb.net/ch93272 [Anzu] and http://anidb.net/ch93275 [Mao] are members.</description>
<picture>219266.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23686" picture="224554.jpg">Uchiyama Yumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96202" type="appears in" update="2018-06-17">
<rating votes="1">3.78</rating>
<name>Mami no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>219269.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="50178" picture="202375.jpg">Imai Utako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96203" type="appears in" update="2018-06-17">
<rating votes="1">2.38</rating>
<name>Naitou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>219270.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1616" picture="23191.jpg">Inada Tetsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96240" type="appears in" update="2018-06-23">
<rating votes="3">8.14</rating>
<name>Mao</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Eventually, http://anidb.net/ch93275 [Mao] manages to build a raft and ends up in China, where she studies kung-fu while subtly using her powers to rise near the top of the school. There she meets http://anidb.net/ch95481 [Atsushi] 3 years later who tells her about http://anidb.net/ch93274 [Hina]`s whereabouts.</description>
<picture>219460.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39007" picture="148258.jpg">Ozawa Ari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96343" type="appears in" update="2018-06-29">
<rating votes="2">9.72</rating>
<name>Asagiri Shiho</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>219703.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36368" picture="224755.jpg">Mao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97332" type="appears in" update="2018-08-10">
<rating votes="1">2.38</rating>
<name>Seta Daisuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>222097.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9164" picture="69944.jpg">Matsumoto Shinobu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97333" type="appears in" update="2018-08-10">
<rating votes="1">3.78</rating>
<name>Kyokuchou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>222098.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40504" picture="158574.jpg">Watanuki Ryuunosuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="97334" type="appears in" update="2018-08-10">
<rating votes="1">5.66</rating>
<name>Shifu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>222099.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12640" picture="226055.jpg">Souma Kouichi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="197382" update="2018-05-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-04-27</airdate>
<rating votes="14">6.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">勘当ロックンロールフィーバー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Disownment Rock n` Roll Fever</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Rock’n’roll fever de l’expulsion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kandou Rock n` Roll Fever</title>
<summary>Furious about the destruction in his home, Nitta kicks Hina out of his home, and she’s left to fend for herself on the streets.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>769303</identifier>
<identifier>hinamatsuri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="197383" update="2018-05-14">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-04-20</airdate>
<rating votes="15">8.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ホームレス生活入門編</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Hobo Life 101</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Vie de SDF, initiation</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Homeless Seikatsu Nyuumon Hen</title>
<summary>Anzu is welcomed into the local homeless community, where she learns the ins and outs of society at the bottom. Hina, meanwhile, is concerned that Nitta might abandon her.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>769301</identifier>
<identifier>hinamatsuri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="197384" update="2018-04-16">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-04-13</airdate>
<rating votes="16">7.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">超能力勝負はこうやんだよ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">This Is How You Have a Superpower Battle!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les duels d’espers, ça se passe comme ça !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chounouryoku Shoubu wa Kou Yanda yo!</title>
<summary>Telekinetic Anzu is deployed on the streets. She will have to fend for herself as she searches for Hina, whom she is tasked with destroying.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>769299</identifier>
<identifier>hinamatsuri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="197385" update="2018-04-16">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-04-06</airdate>
<rating votes="18">6.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">超能力少女現る!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Arrival of the Psychokinetic Girl!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La fille esper entre en scène !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chounouryoku Shoujo Arawaru!</title>
<summary>Telekinetic girl Hina drops into the home of vase-collecting yakuza Nitta, who she then coerces into letting her stick around by threatening to destroy his entire collection.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>768969</identifier>
<identifier>hinamatsuri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="198177" update="2018-06-25">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-04-06</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.32</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198178" update="2018-06-23">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-04-13</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198280" update="2018-06-18">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-05-25</airdate>
<rating votes="12">9.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">そしてヒナはいつも通り</title>
<title xml:lang="en">And It`s the Same Old Hina</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Et Hina ne change pas d’un poil</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Soshite Hina wa Itumodoori</title>
<summary>Security chief Ikaruga Kei is called to check in on Hina, but what she discovers defies her expectations completely. Meanwhile, classmate and paranormal conspiracy theorist Mami spots Hina using her powers.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>769311</identifier>
<identifier>hinamatsuri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="198281" update="2018-06-18">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-05-18</airdate>
<rating votes="13">8.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">看板娘アンズ始めました</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Anzu Is a Greeter Now</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Anzu devient serveuse mascotte</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanbanmusume Anzu Hajimemashita</title>
<summary>Anzu is adjusting well to her new life at the Chinese restaurant, save for her ingrained hobo tendencies. Hina runs for school council president.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>769309</identifier>
<identifier>hinamatsuri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="198282" update="2018-05-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-05-11</airdate>
<rating votes="17">9.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">新田さんの父親はダンディ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nitta-san Has a Dandy Dad</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le père de Nitta est un dandy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nitta-san no Chichioya wa Dandy</title>
<summary>Nitta introduces Hina to his family, but being that he can’t tell them that she literally came out of nowhere and is telekinetic, he is forced to come up with an elaborate white lie.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>769307</identifier>
<identifier>hinamatsuri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="198283" update="2018-05-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-05-04</airdate>
<rating votes="17">5.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">三人集まれば文殊の知恵を打ち破れ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Three Heads Are Better Than One</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Mieux vaut réfléchir à trois que seul</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sannin Atsumareba Monju no Chie o Uchiyabure</title>
<summary>Hina and Anzu go scrap hunting together, but Hina doesn’t seem to miss the whole point.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>769305</identifier>
<identifier>hinamatsuri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="199024" update="2018-07-18">
<epno type="3">C8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-05-11</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="199625" update="2018-09-23">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-06-22</airdate>
<rating votes="13">8.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">雪まつり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yukimatsuri</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le festival de la neige</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yukimatsuri</title>
<summary>Hina and her friends from school get lost in a snowy mountain. It’s snow big deal for Hina, but the others are resistant to her help. Meanwhile, Mao runs into a man who might give her a chance to make it to Japan.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>769319</identifier>
<identifier>hinamatsuri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="199626" update="2018-07-24">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-06-15</airdate>
<rating votes="12">9.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">血と暴力と金に餓えた男</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Man Thirsty for Blood, Violence, and Money</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`homme assoiffé de sang, de violence et d`argent</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chi to Bouryoku to Kane ni Ueta Otoko</title>
<summary>A television station is producing a documentary on modern yakuza. They attempt to interview Nitta, but things don’t go quite as planned.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>769317</identifier>
<identifier>hinamatsuri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="199627" update="2018-07-24">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-06-08</airdate>
<rating votes="13">8.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">川の流れのように</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Like a River Stream</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Comme le courant d’une rivière</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kawa no Nagare no You ni</title>
<summary>Hitomi leaves home when her mother refuses to believe that she’s coming home late all the time because she’s working. Anzu wants to buy her foster parents a gift, but she doesn’t quite have enough.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>769315</identifier>
<identifier>hinamatsuri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="199628" update="2018-06-19">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-06-01</airdate>
<rating votes="13">7.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">人生はサバイバル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Life Is About Survival</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La vie est synonyme de survivalisme</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jinsei wa Survival</title>
<summary>Security chief Ikaruga summons Mao to Japan, who instead ends up stranded on a deserted island. Meanwhile, Nitta’s ailing president is searching for someone to replace him, and Nitta finds himself accidentally at the center of a high-stakes power struggle.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>769313</identifier>
<identifier>hinamatsuri</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="202048" update="2018-06-25">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-05-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="202049" update="2018-06-25">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-06-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1c</title>
</episode>
<episode id="202050" update="2018-06-25">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-06-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1d</title>
</episode>
<episode id="202051" update="2018-06-25">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-06-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1e</title>
</episode>
<episode id="202052" update="2018-06-25">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-06-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1f</title>
</episode>
<episode id="202053" update="2018-07-18">
<epno type="3">C9</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-05-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="202054" update="2018-07-18">
<epno type="3">C10</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-05-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1c</title>
</episode>
<episode id="202055" update="2018-07-18">
<epno type="3">C11</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-06-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1d</title>
</episode>
<episode id="202056" update="2018-07-18">
<epno type="3">C12</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-06-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1e</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
