<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="13625" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2018-04-13</startdate>
<enddate>2018-06-29</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Hisone to Masotan</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="synonym">Drachenflieger: Hisone und Masotan</title>
<title xml:lang="tr" type="synonym">Ejderha Pilotu: Hisone ve Masotan</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">hisomaso</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ひそねとまそたん</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Dragon Pilot: Hisone &amp; Masotan</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Drachenflieger</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">히소네와 마소땅</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">桧曾根与间租谭</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="8583" approval="1" total="4">Rinne no Lagrange: Flower Declaration of Your Heart</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="177640">This series is not remarkable in any way, it is a nonsensical comedy with a silly premise: dragons that are desguised as real aircraft and their "pilots". Yet it is amusing, Hisone and Masotan are funny characters that you can not dislike. Most of the supporting cast is also good. It is an enjoyable show if you keep your expectations down and just want spend time watching a light comedy. The voice actresses are very good, I liked specially Hisone and Ririko voices. However the thing that will remain in my memory is the ending sequence and the music "Le Temps de La Rentrée".</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://hisomaso.com</url>
<creators>
<name id="755" type="Animation Work">Bones</name>
<name id="7788" type="Character Design">Itou Yoshiyuki</name>
<name id="122" type="Series Composition">Okada Mari</name>
<name id="755" type="Original Work">Bones</name>
<name id="122" type="Original Work">Okada Mari</name>
<name id="511" type="Original Work">Higuchi Shinji</name>
<name id="25940" type="Direction">Kobayashi Hiroshi</name>
<name id="511" type="Chief Direction">Higuchi Shinji</name>
<name id="42807" type="Music">Iwasaki Taisei</name>
<name id="7788" type="Chief Animation Direction">Itou Yoshiyuki</name>
</creators>
<description>Straightforward and innocent http://anidb.net/ch93687 [Amakasu Hisone] is a rookie self-defense official. She was struggling with the fact that she sometimes hurts people unintentionally by her innocent words and decided to join in Air Self-Defence, hoping to maintain a certain distance from people. This decision led her to a fateful encounter which profoundly changes her life. It was the http://anidb.net/ch93691 [dragon] hidden in the base and it chose Hisone as his pilot. When it soared into the sky with Hisone, her fate as a dragon pilot was decided. It is said that dragons have a key to the future of the world...
Source: Official page</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="567">6.84</permanent>
<temporary count="567">7.14</temporary>
<review count="1">7.66</review>
</ratings>
<picture>224168.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20625</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>36884</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://hisomaso.com</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Dragon_Pilot:_Hisone_and_Masotan</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ひそねとまそたん</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4885</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>362976</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21120</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>hisomaso_anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="34">
<externalentity>
<url>https://www.netflix.com/title/80241960</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2355" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-28">
<name>dragon</name>
<description>Very intelligent mythical beings - a cross between a very large lizard and a dinosaur - that breath fire, and have a knack for kidnapping damsels, thus distressing them. In Fantasy anime this perceptive species often lives secluded from human civilisation, protectors of long lost knowledge. Dragons seem to be on the verge of extinction.</description>
<picurl>32579.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2876" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>religion</name>
<description>Religion is a collection of belief systems, cultural systems, and worldviews that relate humanity to spirituality and, sometimes, to moral values. Many religions have narratives, symbols, traditions and sacred histories that are intended to give meaning to life or to explain the origin of life or the universe. They tend to derive morality, ethics, religious laws or a preferred lifestyle from their ideas about the cosmos and human nature.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2878" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>conspiracy</name>
<description>The conspiracy thriller (or paranoid thriller) is a sub-genre of the thriller which flourished in the 1970s in the US (and was echoed in other parts of the world) in the wake of a number of high-profile scandals and controversies (most notably Vietnam, the assassination of President Kennedy, Chappaquiddick and Watergate), and which exposed what many people regarded as the clandestine machinations and conspiracies beneath the orderly fabric of political life.
The protagonists of conspiracy thrillers are often journalists or amateur investigators who find themselves (often inadvertently) pulling on a small thread which unravels a vast conspiracy that ultimately goes "all the way to the top".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3053" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-23">
<name>allergy to potential love interests</name>
<description>A character will be found responding to potential love interests, usually of the opposite gender, as if allergic to them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3103" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-07-11">
<name>first love</name>
<description>Ah… first love. The love that is remembered the most fondly by the participant, as this is commonly what people experience when they first have a first crush, but it is also the love before the Second Love, if that should ever happen, and for a guy, he usually holds her memory very close to him if he is a widower whereas for young girls, the memory of the First Love they ever had is a special memory to them, especially if he later becomes the boyfriend they`ve longed for.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>204995.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3123" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-06-27">
<name>symbiotic creatures</name>
<description>Some creatures form symbiotic relationships with humans in this anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3421" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-07-03">
<name>aviation</name>
<description>"These magnificant men in their flying machines"</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3572" parentid="2846" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>biopunk</name>
<description>Biopunk stories explore the struggles of individuals or groups, often the product of human experimentation, against a backdrop of totalitarian governments or mega-corporations which misuse biotech as means of social control or capitalist extortion. Unlike cyberpunk, biopunk does not centre on information technology but on synthetic biology.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3718" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true">
<name>love between enemies</name>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4128" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-07-29">
<name>zero to hero</name>
<description>With his first appearance, this character is getting his ass kicked by nearly everyone, but as the plot continues, through training (mental or physical) or instant power-up, he changes into a killing/fighting/winning machine.
The best example: Makunouchi Ippo from Hajime no Ippo series.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4251" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-20">
<name>ensemble cast</name>
<description>A show with an ensemble cast focuses on a larger group of main characters in a single plot narrative; anime containing several segmented plot narratives (such as episodic or arc-based plots) are excluded. As such, it doesn`t really have a "main" or "lead" character; instead, every member of the central main character group plays an important part in the show`s grander scheme; no single character is more important or prominent than the others (equality of importance). Further, subplots (if any) lead by each character in the ensemble have equal weighting in importance (or lack of weight).

* In a show where no single main character is more important or prominent than the others, 4+ main characters is almost always an ensemble cast.
* A show with 3 main characters of equal importance is likely also an ensemble cast; equality of importance must be considered carefully.
* A show with 2 main characters of equal importance is generally not an ensemble cast situation; however, on an exception basis where neither main character is considered an antagonist, a 2-main-character anime may be considered an ensemble (e.g. http://anidb.net/a11829 [Kimi no Na wa.]).

Pictured: http://anidb.net/a9043 [K (anime)]</description>
<picurl>94914.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4394" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-21">
<name>defeat means friendship</name>
<description>In a series based around an endless series of one-on-one fights, defeating a Worthy Opponent or The Rival will sometimes convert them to the hero`s side, if not always to his cause. 
Furthermore, no matter how many people the Worthy Opponent has killed, how much grief he has caused, even if he slaughtered helpless children or the hero`s own family, as soon as he shows a bit of remorse or goes out of his way to help the hero even once, he will be welcomed into the hero`s circle of True Companions with open arms.
(Source: TVTropes)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4860" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false">
<name>lost love</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5626" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>adults are useless</name>
<description>For when adults can`t do anything right.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5638" parentid="5626" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-25">
<name>military is useless</name>
<description>The regular military force per se or certain units thereof are way out of their league when trying to take on the usually vastly superior foes (e.g. powerful aliens). Thus the regular military is completely useless. 
Often, only children (of all people) with special abilities and/or powered suits can defend Earth.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5794" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-04-01">
<name>forbidden love</name>
<description>This anime contains characters pursuing a romantic interest that their parents, grandparents, the police, the fire department, the neighbourhood watch association and local politicians do not approve of.
Potential relationships defined as such may be ones that are incestuous, violations of caste systems, or socially unsanctioned.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5897" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2013-06-02">
<name>secret military unit</name>
<description>A military unit not publicly known or even unknown to the most parts of the military itself is involved. This includes also former members of those kind of special units that are now part of "normal" units or retired.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6028" parentid="2876" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-10-12">
<name>Shintoism</name>
<description>Shintoism presents a blessed being or creature that governs over areas of terrain, general space of existence, or an individual object (be it alive or inanimate). Everything has its own "spiritual essence".
Defined as the earliest Japanese thoughts of an unified religion, the word Shinto comes from the Chinese hanzi "神道", combining two kanji: "shin" (神), meaning gods or spirits; and "tō" (道), meaning a philosophical path or study.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6052" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-12-18">
<name>group love</name>
<description>Group love is a reciprocal love between three or more people. In group love, everyone loves everyone else; this is distinct from a harem, in which every member of the harem loves only one person, and also from a love polygon, in which each person loves someone else, who loves someone else in turn, and so on.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6062" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-04-05">
<name>heroic sacrifice</name>
<description>"In order to save the many, the few will need to sacrifice their lives..." or so this character may think. 
In a seemingly hopeless situation, against impossible odds, the character does not choose the path of the coward and run, he or she chooses to bravely face the enemy, fully aware that this will mean death.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6068" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-04-20">
<name>human sacrifice</name>
<description>Human sacrifice is the act of killing one or more human beings as part of a ritual. Throughout the majority of human history, primitive societies have engaged in human sacrifice, generally as a religious act, such as an offering to please or appease deities, spirits, or the deceased. Other uses that have been seen include magic rituals, usually related to black magic or the summoning of demons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6072" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-25">
<name>just as planned</name>
<description>A term usually used to describe a situation, where a seemingly smart and cunning villain sets up a plan that seems grand and impressive, but is actually long winding, ridiculous, and convoluted. And all of that just to trick his opponent(s), like the hero or anybody else, into doing things exactly as he planned. Suffice to say that the villain could have reached his goal by much shorter and easier means, it just wouldn`t seem as awesome anymore.
The phrase is also known as the original Japanese "keikaku doori" where keikaku stands translated for "plan" or "schedule", and doori for "in accordance with ..." or "following ...".
The phrase is a reference to http://anidb.net/ch301 [Yagami Light] from http://anidb.net/a4563 [Death Note], and his love for plans.</description>
<picurl>211219.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6086" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-17">
<name>the power of love</name>
<description>The power of love is not only the strongest power known to mankind, it is the strongest power in the universe. The power of love conquers all things. It makes people cry, it makes people laugh, it can make them sing and occasionally it even brings dead people back to life, just so.
More so than the power of friendship, the power of true love gives boundless strength and resolution; by the power of love every hardship can be overcome, every issue can be resolved and it does make people resistant to food poisoning (caused by the bad cooking of their loved ones). Even the big bad evil doesn`t stand a chance against the power of true love and often ends up redeemed.
Even when the power of love is not literally and directly responsible, the scene is often set so that the audience is left with the impression that it was "really responsible".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="93680" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-05-21">
<rating votes="3">6.37</rating>
<name>Okonogi Haruto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Haruto is a maintenance worker at Gifu Air Base. He is gentle and even, and his attitude is always uncertain. Though his boss tends to push extra work on him, Haruto actually is a person who has a fortitude and sticks to his conviction.
Source: Official page</description>
<picture>212853.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1678" picture="68277.jpg">Kaji Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93681" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-02-10">
<rating votes="1">6.79</rating>
<name>Ikushima Hiroki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hiroki is an engineer who develops pilots` suits. Pilots need to wear those to get inside dragons. To obtain necessary information and data, he spends most of his time at the base. In spite that many women get a crush on him, his interest is only pilots` suits development.
Source: Official page</description>
<picture>212844.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="200" picture="17015.jpg">Suwabe Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93682" type="main character in" update="2018-02-10">
<rating votes="3">6.34</rating>
<name>Hitomi Mayumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mayumi works at Iruma base in Saitama Prefecture as a dragon pilot. She is big, slow, powerful and always smiling calmly. When she was working at a zoo, an employee of Iruma base witnessed that all savage animals were attached to her and scouted her for a dragon pilot. Mayumi understands dragons and tells their feeling to other pilots. She pilots a dragon which mimics C-1, the transport aircraft.
Source: Official page</description>
<picture>212851.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="308" picture="44975.jpg">Nazuka Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93683" type="main character in" update="2018-02-10">
<rating votes="5">6.19</rating>
<name>Hoshino Eru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Eru works at Tsuiki base in Fukuoka Prefecture as a dragon pilot. She is cool and dignified, very good at both academics and sports. El believes that she should be the ace among other pilots. But in fact her depth of understanding of OTF(dragons) is very low and her co-workers find it difficult to deal with her. She pilots a dragon disguising F-2A fighter aircraft.
Source: Official page</description>
<picture>212849.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43438" picture="186227.jpg">Kawase Maki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93684" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-02-10">
<rating votes="3">9.05</rating>
<name>Sosoda Hiroshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hiroshi is a commander of Air Development and Test Wing and Major General. In spite of his tough-looking, he actually is very easy going, and loves animals including dragons. He holds a national secret and value Hisone who was chosen by Masotan.
Source: Official page</description>
<picture>212845.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="226" picture="17045.jpg">Nakata Jouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93685" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-02-10">
<rating votes="2">7.61</rating>
<name>Kakiyasu Remi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Remi is a Lieutenant Colonel and a flight branch leader at Gifu Base. She has a cool beauty looking and strong mind, but in fact is easy to scare and cry. Though she is bad at getting along with dragons, pilots` safety is her priority #1.
Source: Official page</description>
<picture>212843.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3" picture="44969.jpg">Kugimiya Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93686" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-02-10">
<rating votes="1">6.79</rating>
<name>Hinomoto Sada</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A mysterious old lady who comes in and out of the base to sell healthy drink. She always wandering around the base and gives Hisone significant advice. Although she seems to know very well about dragons, no one knows who she actually is.
Source: Official page</description>
<picture>212852.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="566" picture="25408.jpg">Paku Romi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93687" type="main character in" update="2018-02-10">
<rating votes="15">8.08</rating>
<name>Amakasu Hisone</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hisone is a rookie pilot at Gifu base of Japan Air Self-Defense Force (JASDF). She is a very honest person who can never lie, and this leads her to hurt people unconsciously. Early in her career she encountered a dragon, Masotan, and was swallowed by him. This is how he chose Hiosone as his pilot. She gradually gets a thrill to fly with Masotan, and decides to live her life with the legendary dragon.
Source: Official page</description>
<picture>212847.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20806" picture="182700.jpg">Kuno Misaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93688" type="main character in" update="2018-02-10">
<rating votes="7">8.22</rating>
<name>Kinutsugai Ririko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ririko is a cool and clever dragon pilot at Misawa base in Aomori Prefecture. She cannot help imagining worst-case scenario for everything, and always has negative thoughts. She fears catching others` eyes, always half crying and cannot live without handkerchiefs. Ririko is very competent and pilots a dragon which disguises E-2C, the Airborne Early Warning aircraft.
Source: Official page</description>
<picture>212850.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="600" picture="148972.jpg">Arai Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93689" type="main character in" update="2018-02-10">
<rating votes="8">5.80</rating>
<name>Kaizaki Nao</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nao is a candidate for dragon pilot at Gifu base, who has a strong fighting instinct and always provoke a fight to anyone around. Her mother was also a dragon pilot. Although Nao was the prime candidate for dragon pilot until Hisone showed up, dragons didn`t accept her. Being jealous of Hisone who was chosen by Masotan, Nao keeps teasing her. But she actually is such a hard worker.
Source: Official page</description>
<picture>212848.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16804" picture="224734.jpg">Kurosawa Tomoyo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93690" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-02-10">
<rating votes="1">2.16</rating>
<name>Zaitou Yutaka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A fighter pilot at Gifu base. Yutaka is Hisone`s supervisor and his directions during training are very exact. Despite his ability and broad experience, he looks like such a playboy. For Yutaka who tries to pick up all women regardless of age or looking, Hisone is the only woman who doesn`t interest him.
Source: Official page</description>
<picture>212842.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="298" picture="216156.jpg">Tokumoto Yukitoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93691" type="main character in" update="2018-05-21">
<rating votes="3">8.10</rating>
<name>Masotan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Disguising as F-15J Fighter aircraft. Huge wings and long tale. Honest and serious, but having a fear of strangers. Pilot: http://anidb.net/ch93687 [Amakasu Hisone].
Source: Official page</description>
<picture>212846.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="54140" picture="214596.jpg">Kanda Matsunojou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94427" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-05-21">
<rating votes="1">4.09</rating>
<name>F-2A</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Disguising as F-2A Fighter aircraft. Sharp body and long tale. Much pride and loner. Pilot: http://anidb.net/ch93683 [Hoshino Eru].
Source: Official page</description>
<picture>214597.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="94428" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-05-21">
<rating votes="1">4.09</rating>
<name>Futomomo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Disguising as C-1 Transport aircraft. Huge body, swallows everything. Easy going. Pilot: http://anidb.net/ch93682 [Hitomi Mayumi].
Source: Official page</description>
<picture>214598.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="94429" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-05-21">
<rating votes="1">4.09</rating>
<name>Akemi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Disguising as E-2C Airborne Early Warning aircraft. Disk-shaped head. Having a fear of others` eyes and always hiding one eye. Pilot: http://anidb.net/ch93688 [Kinutsugai Ririko].
Source: Official page</description>
<picture>214599.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="105471" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-09-18">
<rating votes="1">1.29</rating>
<name>Iboshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238495.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16987" picture="86303.jpg">Shimoyama Yoshimitsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="105473" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-09-18">
<rating votes="1">6.79</rating>
<name>Misumi Natsume</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>238497.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="54137" picture="214593.jpg">Fukumoto Riko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="197334" update="2018-05-10">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-05-04</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヤツらが岐阜にやって来た</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Those Guys Have Come Over to Gifu</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Gifu`ya Geliyorlar</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yatsura ga Gifu ni Yatte Kita</title>
<summary>Dragon pilots from Tsuiki, Misawa and Iruma base have gathered at Gifu base for joint training including mimic battle. As soon as arrived, Hoshino Eru from Tsuiki base suggested a night-time training to get to know each other. She doesn`t like treating her dragon like a pet and keeps it disguising in the battle plane F-2A. On the other hand, Hitomi Mayumi is very slow and Kinutsugai Ririko fears catching others` eyes. Can Hisone get along with these unique dragon pilots?
Source: Official page</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="197335" update="2018-05-10">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-04-27</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.45</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">責任とってくださいよ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Take Responsibility, Would You?</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Sorumluluk Alır Mısın?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sekinin Totte Kudasai yo</title>
<summary>Everyone in Gifu base is now focusing on rehearsal for the Aviation Festival. However Hisone`s inexperience in flight has disturbed the team. A few days ago she heard about Moriyama who used to be a dragon pilot until three years ago. The fact that Masotan react to Moriyama`s TAC name "Forest" made Hisone uneasy. Though she tries to figure out why Moriyama left the team, she has reached no success. And finally the Festival day has come.
Source: Official page</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="197336" update="2018-05-10">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-04-20</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ドラゴンの名前はまそたんにします</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Name the Dragon Masotan</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Ejderhanın Adını Masotan Koydum</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dragon no Namae wa Masotan ni Shimasu</title>
<summary>Hisone keeps flight training with the dragon. One day a long-haired Ikushima Hiroki appeared out of nowhere and touched all over Hisone`s body. He is a developer of pilot suits and got motivated to create a new suits for Hisone by witnessing she was swallowed by the dragon. On the other hand, Hisone`s rival Nao keeps teasing her out of spite not being chosen by the dragon, but she mistook that Nao likes her. While shortening the distance to the dragon, Hisone starts thinking it needs a name.
Source: Official page</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="197337" update="2018-05-10">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-04-13</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.52</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">正気の沙汰ではないんです</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It Is Insane</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Bu Çılgınlık</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shouki no Sata de wa Naindesu</title>
<summary>Amakasu  Hisone tends to hurt people unconsciously, as she is too honest. Suffering in a relationship, she joined Japan Air Self-Defense Force (JASDF) as a fixed term staff and was assigned to Gifu base. One day Hisone was sent to "the 8th hangar" and there bumped into a dragon. And what is more, she was swallowed by him! The dragon is called OTF (Organic Transformed Flyer), which has been managed by JASDF since ancient times. This is how Hisone`s new phase of life as a dragon pilot begins.
Source: Official page</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="198214" update="2019-02-16">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-04-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198215" update="2018-04-19">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-04-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198559" update="2018-05-24">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-06-01</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">期間限定! 激辛おばあさん味</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Limited Time Offer! Spicy Granny Flavor</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Kısa Süreli Bir Teklif! Büyükanne`nin Aroması</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kikan Gentei! Gekikara Obaasan Aji</title>
<summary>Finally dragon pilots were informed the whole picture of their mission for Ritual, for which not only Japan Air, Ground, Maritime Self-Defense Force but also the nation launch full-scare efforts. To take "Mitatsu", the giant OTF arising from sleep in every 74 years, to new "Fushido", the place to rest. It would take three whole days for dragon pilots and OTFs to lead way for Mitatsu as he can only move ate very low speed. In preparation for the day of Ritual, the training for dragon pilots shifts into high gear, and Iiboshi revealed Sada`s true identity.
Source: Official page</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="198560" update="2018-05-17">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-05-25</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">恋する王国</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kingdom of Love</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Aşk Krallığı</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koi Suru Oukoku</title>
<summary>After the 7 days training, Dragon Pilots finally started building a trusted relationship. And they were informed that their hard training was actually the preparation for a very important national project, "Ritual". In order to accomplish the Ritual, Ministry of Defense pursues an operation to control Dragon Pilots` feeling, as their romantic feeling has a big impact to their relationship with OTF. While MOD started collecting individual data of each Dragon Pilot, Hisone and Okonogi are to go out together.
Source: Official page</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="198561" update="2018-05-10">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-05-18</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">君の名前を叫ぶから</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Will Call Your Name</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Adını Söyleyeceğim</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kimi no Namae o Sakebu kara</title>
<summary>It is the fifth day of the training, and now they have only two days left. However, the four dragon pilots are not close enough yet. Eru in particular has been in an awkward position because of her harsh attitude toward F-2. She could no longer bear up under the stress and attempted an escape alone on a raft, but was caught in tidal waves. On the other hand, Hisone, Ririko and Mayumi found a secret of the island in the cave where they escaped from the storm.
Source: Official page</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="198562" update="2018-05-10">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-05-11</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">スキ好んで嫌われたい人なんていますか?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Who Likes to Be Disliked?</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Kim Sevilmemek İster ki?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suki Kononde Kirawaretai Hito Nante Imasuka?</title>
<summary>Each dragon pilots had different way to communicate with dragons, which caused tensions among them. But Hisone was troubled by the thought that she was the reason as she could never keep her honest feeling within herself. Chief Kakiyasu imposed dragon pilots on a training in an uninhabited island off the coast of Japan Sea. The purpose is to develop teamwork with limited supplies in a tough environment. How would they escape from the island and come back to the base with dragons?
Source: Official page</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="200262" update="2018-06-23">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-06-29</airdate>
<rating votes="6">8.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">無敵の私たち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Invincible Us</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Biz Yenilmeziz</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Muteki no Watashitachi</title>
<summary>The dragon pilots` mission to lead "Mitatsu" to the new place to rest has almost been completed. However, there is a great matter behind the thousands-year old ritual which has been strictly concealed. What actually is Kusabime, and what kind of life has Sada walked through? Now Ritual is ending. In middle of a critical situation of this country, how will Hisone and Masotan make their decision? And what kind of future will they select?
Source: Official page</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="200263" update="2018-06-14">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-06-22</airdate>
<rating votes="6">8.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">モンパルナスの空とクズ女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Montparnasse Sky and Scum Girl</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Montparnasse ve Pislik Kız</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Montparnasse no Sora to Kuzu Onna</title>
<summary>"Ritual" has now started. "Mizuchi Rock", the uninhabited island where dragon pilots did the training, turns out to be sleeping "Mitatsu". He arised from sleep and is now moving to the next place to rest with concealing himself in developed cumulonimbus clouds. Under the rough weather, four OTFs break their backs to lead him safely. "What is Hisone doing now?" She is not here, for the mission which affects the fate of this nation.
Source: Official page</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="200264" update="2018-06-07">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-06-15</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">好きになったらトロけちゃう</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Melty Love</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">Erimiş Aşk</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suki ni Nattara Toroke Chau</title>
<summary>Just as upper managements concerned, dragon pilots` romantic feeling created a gulf between OTF and themselves. "Anatomic" has prevented Hisone from riding Masotan, but she hasn`t realized her true feeling yet. Nao sees Hisone struggling and reconsiders what she can do. Eru cannot ride Noma anymore and started going after her original dream. Now "Ritual" is only days away. Everyone at Gifu Air Base is preparing for it in different ways with mixed feeling.
Source: Official page</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="200265" update="2018-06-07">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-06-08</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ギャーーー!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Eeeeeeeeeek!</title>
<title xml:lang="tr">İmdaaaaaaaaaat!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyaaaa!!</title>
<summary>After the three-days-training simulated Ritual, Priestesses arrive Gifu Air Base.
It was announced that Okonogi actually belongs to a ministry which conducts Ritual. A Priestess Natsume extends her favor to Okonogi and follows Hisone around for being close to him. While pilots of Air Development and Test Wing get excited over young priestess, Eru is having a change of heart. In the meantime, Sada and Iiboshi now worry about "Anastomotic".
Source: Official page</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="212624" update="2019-02-16">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-04-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="212625" update="2019-02-16">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-05-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="212626" update="2019-02-16">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-05-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="212627" update="2019-02-16">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-05-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="212628" update="2019-02-16">
<epno type="3">C8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-05-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="212629" update="2019-02-16">
<epno type="3">C9</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-06-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="212630" update="2019-02-16">
<epno type="3">C10</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-06-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 8</title>
</episode>
<episode id="212631" update="2019-02-16">
<epno type="3">C11</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-06-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 9</title>
</episode>
<episode id="212632" update="2019-02-16">
<epno type="3">C12</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-06-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 10</title>
</episode>
<episode id="212633" update="2019-02-16">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-06-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="216606" update="2019-05-07">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Bluray&amp;DVD CM</title>
</episode>
<episode id="216607" update="2019-05-07">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>0</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="216608" update="2019-05-09">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2018-11-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Flash Sketches 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="216609" update="2019-05-09">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2018-11-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Flash Sketches 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="216610" update="2019-05-09">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2018-12-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Flash Sketches 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="216611" update="2019-05-09">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>7</length>
<airdate>2018-12-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Flash Sketches 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="216612" update="2019-05-09">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>5</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Interview</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
