<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="13637" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>11</episodecount>
<startdate>2018-07-09</startdate>
<enddate>2018-09-17</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Jashin-chan Dropkick</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="synonym">Un calcio volante al mio demonio!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">jashin-chan</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">邪神ちゃんドロップキック</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Dropkick on My Devil!!</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">사신쨩 드롭킥</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">邪神与厨二病少女</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="14623" type="Sequel">Jashin-chan Dropkick Dash</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="12290" approval="18" total="25">Gabriel Dropout</anime>
<anime id="2820" approval="15" total="17">Bokusatsu Tenshi Dokuro-chan</anime>
<anime id="9479" approval="7" total="9">Namiuchigiwa no Muromi-san</anime>
<anime id="7275" approval="2" total="3">Yondemasu yo, Azazel-san.</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="419931">Great parody anime.
Silly funny, absolutely crazy and mindless. This is all you need to know to decide seeing it or not.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://jashinchan.com</url>
<creators>
<name id="54363" type="Work">Dangan</name>
<name id="1055" type="Animation Work">Nomad</name>
<name id="3644" type="Character Design">Koga Makoto</name>
<name id="7582" type="Series Composition">Fudeyasu Kazuyuki</name>
<name id="37906" type="Original Work">Yukiwo</name>
<name id="11190" type="Direction">Satou Hikaru</name>
<name id="3644" type="Chief Animation Direction">Koga Makoto</name>
<name id="54364" type="Music">Jinma Yuzuru</name>
<name id="54365" type="Music">Kurihara Yuuki</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on http://anidb.net/cr37906 [Yukiwo]`s slapstick comedy manga.
http://anidb.net/ch93664 [Yurine] is a delusional http://anidb.net/t1952 [gothic lolita] who summons a demon girl with the tail of a cobra, http://anidb.net/ch93665 [Jashin-chan]. They`ll have to live together - until Yurine finds a way to send Jashin-chan back to hell, or until Jashin-chan kills Yurine.
Source: M-U</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="508">4.08</permanent>
<temporary count="509">6.01</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>221092.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20484</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>36906</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>38383</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://jashinchan.com</url>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<url>https://comic-meteor.jp/jashin_anime/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Dropkick_on_My_Devil!</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>邪神ちゃんドロップキック</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4974</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>362720</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21238</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>jashinchan_PJ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B07FC7WLDL</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="34">
<externalentity>
<url>https://www.primevideo.com/detail/0SP0YIS05HRN7BOYGXAKF1MQB0</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2346" parentid="2849" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-09-14">
<name>angel</name>
<description>An angel is a supernatural being, said to be the messenger of God. They are often depicted as human beings with a pair of white feathered wings and sometimes with a halo.
In contrast, a fallen angel who has turned evil will be depicted with black wings.</description>
<picurl>35521.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2979" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-18">
<name>mutilation</name>
<description>Mutilation is an act of physical injury that degrades the appearance or function of any living body. Some ethnic groups practice ritual mutilation, e.g. scarification, burning, flagellation(whipping), tattooing, or wheeling, as part of a rite of passage. In some cases, the term may apply to treatment of dead bodies, such as soldiers mutilated after they have been killed by an enemy. Maiming, or mutilation which involves the loss of, or incapacity to use, a bodily member, is and has been practised by many societies with various cultural and religious significances, and is also a customary form of physical punishment, especially applied on the principle of "an eye for an eye".
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3953" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-10-04">
<name>in medias res</name>
<description>In medias res, also medias in res (Latin for "into the midst of affairs (lit. into mid-affairs)"), refers to a literary and artistic technique where the narrative starts in the middle of the story instead of from its beginning. It is generally a plot-driven concept rather than a character-driven one; though characters are commonly used to provide the backstory. The characters, setting, and conflict are often introduced through a series of http://anidb.net/t4299 [flashbacks] or through characters relating past events to each other.
Probably originating from an oral tradition, the technique is a convention of epic poetry, one of the earliest and most prominent examples in Western literature being Homer`s Odyssey and Iliad. Virgil`s Aeneid began the tradition in literature of imitating Homer, continued in Torquato Tasso`s Jerusalem Delivered, John Milton`s Paradise Lost and "Inferno" from Dante`s Divine Comedy. George Lucas`s Star Wars saga was told using in medias res.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4096" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>gore</name>
<description>A Splatter film or Gore film is a sub-genre of horror film that deliberately focuses on graphic portrayals of gore and graphic violence. These films, through the use of special effects and excessive blood and guts, tend to display an overt interest in the vulnerability of the human body and the theatricality of its mutilation. Due to their willingness to portray images society might consider shocking, splatter films share some ideological grounds with the transgressive art movement. The term "splatter cinema" was coined by George A. Romero to describe his film Dawn of the Dead, though Dawn of the Dead is generally considered by critics to have higher aspirations, such as social commentary, than to be simply exploitative for its own sake.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>32491.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6349" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-13">
<name>multi-segment episodes</name>
<description>Multi-segment episodes are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t5852 [short episodes], which are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length (up to and including 10 minutes).
Also not to be confused with an OVA or music video with multiple (otherwise unrelated) full-length http://anidb.net/t7241 [bundled episodes] consolidated into a single episode video track.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="93657" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-05-06">
<rating votes="17">6.39</rating>
<name>Pekora</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>217240.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="50502" picture="245789.jpg">Kozakai Yurie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93658" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-06-11">
<rating votes="5">3.66</rating>
<name>Poporon</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jashin-chan ate Poporon`s Halo; stripping Poporon of Heavenly powers.</description>
<picture>217242.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45198" picture="219576.jpg">Sasaki Riko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93659" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-06">
<rating votes="4">5.32</rating>
<name>Persephone II</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>245775.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="22171" picture="173757.jpg">Iida Riho</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93660" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-05-06">
<rating votes="12">7.70</rating>
<name>Minos</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>217241.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1679" picture="38587.jpg">Omigawa Chiaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93661" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-05-06">
<rating votes="11">6.56</rating>
<name>Medusa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>217239.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36583" picture="134947.jpg">Kubota Miyu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93662" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-06">
<rating votes="3">3.47</rating>
<name>Tachibana Mei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>245776.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43627" picture="176871.jpg">Hara Natsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93663" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-06">
<rating votes="3">4.58</rating>
<name>Koori-chan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>245778.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="53673" picture="212812.jpg">Terada Miko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93664" type="main character in" update="2018-08-09">
<rating votes="12">4.74</rating>
<name>Hanazono Yurine</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>217238.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39890" picture="161176.jpg">Oomori Nichika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93665" type="main character in" update="2018-05-06">
<rating votes="14">4.87</rating>
<name>Jashin-chan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>217237.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="41296" picture="177392.jpg">Suzuki Aina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93666" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-06">
<rating votes="3">5.44</rating>
<name>Yusa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>245777.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10080" picture="235712.jpg">Aranami Kazusa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96612" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-07-17">
<rating votes="2">2.08</rating>
<name>Beth</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>220213.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36368" picture="224755.jpg">Mao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109162" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-07">
<name>Akuma A</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>245780.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="370" picture="204461.jpg">Yusa Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="111253" type="appears in" update="2020-07-11">
<name>Gaikokujin</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>249754.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3186" picture="171957.jpg">Tone Kentarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="111254" type="appears in" update="2020-07-11">
<name>Zombie</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>249755.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="226" picture="17045.jpg">Nakata Jouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="112136" type="appears in" update="2020-08-13">
<name>Yoshihiko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>251302.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34504" picture="200900.jpg">Taichi You</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="201740" update="2020-06-24">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-07-30</airdate>
<rating votes="3">1.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 4</title>
<summary>Akihabara, the mecca of otaku, is also home to the Gachapon Hall. There, Mei Tachibana, the super cop of Banzaibashi Police, begs Yurine to give Jashin-chan to her and threatens to kill her if she doesn`t. Mei swings her sword at Jashin-chan. While completely flustered at the fatal attraction, Jashin-chan still manages to take despicable actions which triggers Medusa`s "passive-aggressive mode."
Source: Amazon</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="201741" update="2020-06-24">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-07-23</airdate>
<rating votes="6">3.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 3</title>
<summary>While the town dances with Christmas spirit, Pekola wanders the streets with a bag full of bread crusts and a carton of milk. Bad Santa Jashin-chan steals Pekola`s precious food and as punishment, Yurine turns her into a tree and Beth`s feast for the holy night. The surprise visitor turns out to be Kori-chan`s sister Yusa and Jashin-chan and Medusa`s relationship reveals itself to be questionable.
Source: Amazon</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="201742" update="2020-06-24">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-07-16</airdate>
<rating votes="7">3.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 2</title>
<summary>It`s summer. Beth sprawls in the shade and our devil Jashin-chan hogs the fan. Unable to deal with the heat, Jashin-chan summons and bullies Kori-chan the Ice Devil to cool things down...up to a point. Meanwhile, not one soul helps Pekola who`s about to faint, but an unexpected savior appears! Watch Pekola try Bondy`s curry for the first time and Jashin-chan and Medusa`s long history unfold.
Source: Amazon</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="201743" update="2020-06-24">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-07-09</airdate>
<rating votes="9">4.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">邪教徒の集い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yokoshima Kyouto no Tsudoi</title>
<summary>Tokyo, the big city. In the corner of this world, another day of bittersweet drama is about to unfold… According to Pekola the angel, Yurine the witch hosts a sabbath at a run-down apartment in Jinbocho. There, Jashin-chan the devil prepares a divine hot pot that captivates Yurine, Medusa, Minos and Pekola. But everything starts to fall apart when Jashin-chan brings drama to the dinner table.
Source: Amazon</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="202674" update="2018-10-01">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-07-09</airdate>
<rating votes="3">2.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="202675" update="2018-10-01">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2018-07-09</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="203280" update="2020-06-24">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-08-27</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 8</title>
<summary>Jashin-chan`s voice echoes throughout Jinbocho, "Lost again, damn it!" She lost the grocery money by playing the slots and is desperate to make Medusa lend her more. Infuriated, Yurine swings her morning star, "I`ve no choice but to kill you." Turns out Jashin-chan`s addicted to social-network games too. As Halo-less Poporon and the Ogre of Setsubun appears, Jashin-chan finds herself in a loop.
Source: Amazon</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="203281" update="2020-06-24">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-08-20</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 7</title>
<summary>One afternoon, Jashin-chan was on her way back from the grocery store for Yurine`s Polar Bear almond jelly when Poporon attacked her with the Light Sword. Mean, cowardice, lousy, and sly, Poporon`s much like Jashin-chan, even though she`s an angel. Jashin-chan repels vengeful Poporon by devouring her halo. Will she gain angel powers from it?
Source: Amazon</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="203282" update="2020-06-24">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-08-13</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 6</title>
<summary>Jashin-chan whips up pork cutlet curry for dinner one night, then hamburg steak curry the next, then croquette curry on the third night. Yurine calls her out but Jashin-chan`s not listening. Our Ice Devils Yusa and Koji are back in town while Pekola encounters her unexpected nemesis. Jashin-chan`s dropkick saves Pekola, making her feel overcome with gratitude for the devil.
Source: Amazon</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="203283" update="2020-06-24">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-08-06</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 5</title>
<summary>After a failed hunt for the second volume of a grimoire in Jinbocho`s bookstore district, Jashin-chan and Yurine enjoys lunch at Jiro. Yurine buys take-out for starving Pekola, who is hesitant to accept since she houses the devil. When Pekola finally decides to eat, Jashin-chan had devoured it all. Minos and Jashin-chan`s past and Pekola`s job is revealed as super cop Mei makes a comeback.
Source: Amazon</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="204214" update="2020-06-24">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-09-17</airdate>
<rating votes="2">1.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 11</title>
<summary>Jashin-chan`s killer dropkick hits Yurine, the finale is here! Turns out, Yurine`s down with a cold. Ecstatic, Jashin-chan fantasizes of returning to Hell, but ends up taking care of her with Minos and Medusa. Pekola, Poporon and Mei join them for a flower viewing. After a devilish relapse at the bakery, Persephone II finally finds Jashin-chan, only to bid farewell as she floats off into space!
Source: Amazon</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="204215" update="2020-06-24">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-09-10</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 10</title>
<summary>Charity workers ask for donations at the station as Pekola walks by with her well-earned pay. Tragedy strikes as her money vanishes into the donation box and her last 2,000 yen gets wasted for curry nanban eaten by Jashin-chan. Yusa and Koji reappear and Pekola works as Poporon`s bodyguard. Valentine`s Day stirs things up between Jashin-chan and Medusa and Jashin-chan`s sleaziness goes on parade!
Source: Amazon</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="204216" update="2020-06-24">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-09-03</airdate>
<rating votes="2">2.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 9</title>
<summary>After her 17,711th loss, Jashin-chan runs to the bank to withdraw Medusa`s cash to fund her gambling habit and "rewrite history." Instant karma leads them into a bank robbery and Jashin-chan just wants to save herself while Medusa stands against the robbers to save the people. Jashin-chan`s asshole-ness peaks as Minos is more popular with humans and Poporon disguises herself as Noel Amatsuka..
Source: Amazon</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="208186" update="2018-10-01">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-09-24</airdate>
<rating votes="1">1.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">邪神ちゃんねるV すぺしゃる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Jashin-Channel V Special</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jashin-chan Neru V Special</title>
</episode>
<episode id="208815" update="2020-06-24">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-10-01</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 12</title>
<summary>"It" was believed to be traveling in space, but, "I`m back, guys " Due to popular demand, we decided to bring Jashin-chan back for an extra episode! What will she face when she returns to Earth? Yurine, Medusa, Pekola, Minos, Yusa, Koji and Peru-chan are all in for the "swimsuit edition"! Then appears Kraken for what seemed like the last battle of the season, but the real battle continues...
Source: Amazon</summary>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
