<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="13698" restricted="false">
<type>Web</type>
<episodecount>6</episodecount>
<startdate>2018-07-14</startdate>
<enddate>2018-08-10</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Iya na Kao Sarenagara Opantsu Misete Moraitai</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">I Want You To Make a Disgusted Face and Show Me Your Underwear</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">iyapan</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">嫌な顔されながらおパンツ見せてもらいたい</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">싫은 얼굴을 하면서 팬티 보여줬으면 한다</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">摆出讨厌的表情露出内裤</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="14259" type="Sequel">Iya na Kao Sarenagara Opantsu Misete Moraitai 2</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="15659" approval="4" total="5">Dogeza de Tanondemita</anime>
</similaranime>
<url>http://iyapan-anime.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="53205" type="Original Work">Shimahara</name>
<name id="53661" type="Animation Work">Uwan Pictures</name>
<name id="46005" type="Direction">Fukase Saya</name>
<name id="56066" type="Character Design">Hakkaku</name>
<name id="56066" type="Chief Animation Direction">Hakkaku</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on http://anidb.net/cr53205 [Shimahara]`s adult doujin project.
Note: The episodes were released weekly online via Nico Nico Douga starting 14.07.2018. The Blu-ray Disc with all episodes was sold at Comiket 94 on 10.08.2018.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="347">2.56</permanent>
<temporary count="353">5.02</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>221602.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21119</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>37021</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://iyapan-anime.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>365436</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="627" parentid="2856" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-15">
<name>lingerie</name>
<description>Lingerie is a term for fashionable and alluring women`s undergarments.</description>
<picurl>238327.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3018" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>first person view</name>
<description>The events in this anime are shown from the perspective of one or several characters, as if you watch the scenes through their eyes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3977" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-29">
<name>dialogue driven</name>
<description>A dialogue driven show has its story advanced by dialogue, with action being of much lower priority, and relies heavily on conversations between characters.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4646" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-31">
<name>hospital</name>
<description>The place or building where sick people receive medical treatment in the hopes of curing their sickness. Also a dandy setting for creepy happenings in anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5852" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>short episodes</name>
<description>Short episodes are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length. This means up to and including 10 minutes; shows with episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length are http://anidb.net/t6494 [half-length episodes] instead.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6349 [multi-segment episodes], which are regular episodes that are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6184" parentid="6185" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-29">
<name>autumn</name>
<description>Autumn, interchangeably known as fall in the US and Canada, is one of the four temperate seasons. Autumn marks the transition from summer into winter, in September (Northern Hemisphere) or March (Southern Hemisphere), when the arrival of night becomes noticeably earlier and the temperature cools considerably. One of its main features is the shedding of leaves from deciduous trees.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>161967.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6399" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-25">
<name>episodic</name>
<description>An episodic anime consists of many successive short arcs that are generally 1-2 episodes in length, with strong plot continuity within each arc but generally little continuity from one arc to the next. For long shows (well upwards of 50 episodes), the episode count constraint is less tight; for example, a show with close to 250 episodes would also be considered episodic if it consisted of a majority of arcs of up to 3 or maybe 4 episodes and possibly also very few slightly longer arcs.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="93059" type="main character in" update="2018-07-28">
<rating votes="4">4.94</rating>
<name>Yuina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>220948.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="48909" picture="223240.jpg">Nagano Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93060" type="main character in" update="2018-07-28">
<rating votes="7">7.12</rating>
<name>Itou Chitose</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>220949.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29972" picture="240161.jpg">Ishigami Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93061" type="main character in" update="2018-07-28">
<rating votes="5">7.12</rating>
<name>Izumo Iori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>220944.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18198" picture="228672.jpg">Akasaki Chinatsu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93062" type="main character in" update="2018-07-28">
<rating votes="5">6.73</rating>
<name>Tanahashi Misuzu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>220947.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43430" picture="243752.jpg">Koga Aoi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93063" type="main character in" update="2018-07-28">
<rating votes="4">6.28</rating>
<name>Sega Airi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>220946.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38858" picture="225369.jpg">Yoshimura Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="93064" type="main character in" update="2018-07-28">
<rating votes="6">6.44</rating>
<name>Takayama Maria</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>220945.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32471" picture="173756.jpg">Hata Sawako</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="198575" update="2018-07-29">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2018-07-14</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="203589" update="2018-07-29">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2018-08-10</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="203590" update="2018-07-29">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2018-08-10</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="203591" update="2018-07-29">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2018-08-04</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="203592" update="2018-07-29">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2018-07-28</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="203593" update="2018-07-29">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>5</length>
<airdate>2018-07-21</airdate>
<rating votes="4">3.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="209535" update="2020-09-15">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2018-08-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="209536" update="2020-09-15">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2018-08-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="209537" update="2020-09-15">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2018-08-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="209538" update="2020-09-15">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2018-08-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="209539" update="2020-09-15">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2018-08-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="209540" update="2020-09-15">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2018-08-10</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode S6</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
