<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="13740" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>26</episodecount>
<startdate>2018-04-07</startdate>
<enddate>2018-09-29</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Nobunaga no Shinobi: Anegawa Ishiyama Hen</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Ninja Girl &amp; Samurai Master 3rd</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Ниндзя Нобунаги 3</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">信長の忍び~姉川・石山篇~</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Ninja Girl &amp; Samurai Master: Anegawa and Ishiyama Arc</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">노부나가의 시노비: 아네가와 이시야마편</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">信长的忍者 姊川·石山篇</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="12900" type="Prequel">Nobunaga no Shinobi: Ise Kanegasaki Hen</anime>
</relatedanime>
<url>https://nobunaga-no-shinobi.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="917" type="Animation Work">TMS Entertainment</name>
<name id="5795" type="Character Design">Yamanaka Junko</name>
<name id="45056" type="Original Work">Shigeno Naoki</name>
<name id="1423" type="Direction">Daichi Akitarou</name>
<name id="2341" type="Music">Masuda Toshio</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch81184 [Nobunaga]`s beloved sister http://anidb.net/ch81182 [Ichi] has married http://anidb.net/ch90416 [Azai Nagamasa]. But the impending battle between the Azai + Asakura forces and the Oda Army is unavoidable. Even a moment`s hesitation could cause either side to lose something important at the Battle of Anegawa. It is there that http://anidb.net/ch81186 [Chidori], who has been saving her tears, will awaken. In this battle to bring the whole country together, there are times where even brothers must fight!
Source: crunchyroll</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="119">6.16</permanent>
<temporary count="119">6.55</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>221800.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>20566</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>37126</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://nobunaga-no-shinobi.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Nobunaga_no_Shinobi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>信長の忍び</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4861</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>363095</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21080</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>shinobinobunaga</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ninja-girl-samurai-master</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1471" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-06-16">
<name>bad cooking</name>
<description>The character is hopelessly terrible at cooking, and any attempts he or she makes at making even the simplest dishes are spectacular failures.</description>
<picurl>248445.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2282" parentid="2841" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-18">
<name>martial arts</name>
<description>Various sports or skills, mainly of Japanese origin, that originated as forms of self-defense or attack, such as judo, karate, and kendo.</description>
<picurl>210947.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2572" parentid="2282" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-02-09">
<name>ninja</name>
<description>A ninja was a covert agent or mercenary of feudal Japan specializing in unorthodox arts of war.
The functions of the ninja included espionage, sabotage, infiltration, and assassination, as well as open combat in certain situations.
The ninja, using covert methods of waging war, were contrasted with the samurai, who had strict rules about honor and combat.</description>
<picurl>244347.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2618" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>collateral damage</name>
<description>The usually action orientated anime does not only show large amounts of combat and weapon use, but also the incidental massive destruction of property, often due to the inability of the protagonists to aim properly.
Example: Mecha duking it out in a densely populated urban area.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2634" parentid="2613" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>countryside</name>
<description>The anime takes place far from the any densely populated areas like cities, i.e. out in the suburbs, in the countryside with many fields and forests.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2641" parentid="2625" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>historical</name>
<description>Historical anime have clear ties to our history and usually occur in a particular epoch.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2679" parentid="2672" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Kyoto</name>
<description>Kyoto Prefecture is a prefecture of Japan in the Kansai region of the island of Honshu. The capital is the city of Kyoto.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214383.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2687" parentid="2641" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-02-05">
<name>Sengoku period</name>
<description>The Sengoku period (戦国時代, Sengoku jidai) or Warring States period in Japanese history was a time of social upheaval, political intrigue, and nearly constant military conflict that lasted roughly from the middle of the 15th century to the beginning of the 17th century. The name "Sengoku" was adopted by Japanese historians in reference to the Warring States period in Chinese history (Sengoku jidai (戦国時代) in Japanese) which preceded the unification of China. Likewise, the Sengoku period in Japan would eventually lead to the unification of political power under the Tokugawa shogunate.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2772" parentid="36" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>feudal warfare</name>
<description>Feudal Warfare is the warfare of the Middle Ages and therefore the setting must take place in a time line similar to that of Middle Ages or its Asian/American counterparts, or in a fantasy world. Generally it can be described the same way as the Military category, just that the weapons used are swords, spears, bows, catapults, cannons and other weapons used in the Middle Ages.
Note: Just because the anime contains a guy or a couple of guys with swords wondering about, doesn`t make it applicable for this category, unless there are larger military organizations/groups involved in armed conflict with each other, you might not want to add this genre.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2805" parentid="2798" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>4-koma manga</name>
<description>Yonkoma manga (4コマ漫画, four cell manga, or 4-koma for short), a comic-strip format, generally consists of gag comic strips within four panels of equal size ordered from top to bottom. (They also sometimes run right-to-left horizontally or use a hybrid 2x2 style, depending on the layout requirements of the publication in which they appear.) Though the word yonkoma comes from the Japanese, the style also exists outside of Japan in other Asian countries as well as in the English-speaking market.</description>
<picurl>70558.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2878" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>conspiracy</name>
<description>The conspiracy thriller (or paranoid thriller) is a sub-genre of the thriller which flourished in the 1970s in the US (and was echoed in other parts of the world) in the wake of a number of high-profile scandals and controversies (most notably Vietnam, the assassination of President Kennedy, Chappaquiddick and Watergate), and which exposed what many people regarded as the clandestine machinations and conspiracies beneath the orderly fabric of political life.
The protagonists of conspiracy thrillers are often journalists or amateur investigators who find themselves (often inadvertently) pulling on a small thread which unravels a vast conspiracy that ultimately goes "all the way to the top".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2964" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>OP variety</name>
<description>Several OP sequences in this anime have either a different song or different animation, maybe even to the point of having a unique OP for each episode.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2978" parentid="5604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-28">
<name>aim for the top</name>
<description>This can be a positive or negative plot device. A character may strive to become the best in an altruistic way (e.g. best healer, most widely learned master), or it can be quite banal and primitive (e.g. challenged delinquents wanting to be the strongest fighters).
Alas in fighting anime the latter usually prevails.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3245" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-02-05">
<name>strategy</name>
<description>Instead of blindly running into a battle or trap, at least one of the protagonists devises a clever strategy to significantly improve the odds of victory.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3581" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-23">
<name>tactics</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3941" parentid="2874" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-26">
<name>flood</name>
<description>A flood is an overflow of water that submerges land which is usually dry. The European Union (EU) Floods Directive defines a flood as a covering by water of land not normally covered by water. In the sense of "flowing water", the word may also be applied to the inflow of the tide. Flooding may occur as an overflow of water from water bodies, such as a river or lake, in which the water overtops or breaks levees, resulting in some of that water escaping its usual boundaries, or it may occur due to an accumulation of rainwater on saturated ground in an areal flood. While the size of a lake or other body of water will vary with seasonal changes in precipitation and snow melt, these changes in size are unlikely to be considered significant unless they flood property or drown domestic animals.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4096" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>gore</name>
<description>A Splatter film or Gore film is a sub-genre of horror film that deliberately focuses on graphic portrayals of gore and graphic violence. These films, through the use of special effects and excessive blood and guts, tend to display an overt interest in the vulnerability of the human body and the theatricality of its mutilation. Due to their willingness to portray images society might consider shocking, splatter films share some ideological grounds with the transgressive art movement. The term "splatter cinema" was coined by George A. Romero to describe his film Dawn of the Dead, though Dawn of the Dead is generally considered by critics to have higher aspirations, such as social commentary, than to be simply exploitative for its own sake.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>32491.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4316" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-11">
<name>murder</name>
<description>To murder means to bring about someone else`s death, by a voluntary act. Whether it comes from the killer`s own hand or by exposing the victim to life-threatening circumstances, the result is foreseeable and sought by the perpetrator. Someone who murders as their profession/job is an http://anidb.net/t2399 [assassin or hitman].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4520" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>betrayal</name>
<description>Friends become enemies.
Strong bonds of trust receive violations of confidence while friendships are faithlessly given up or revealed to have been false from the start.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4570" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-08-10">
<name>watercolour style</name>
<description>A watercolour or aquarelle is a painting method in which the paints are made of pigments suspended in a water-based solution. Some anime are created in the style of watercolour paintings, the watercolour style, usually with faded pastels that often give the show a warm and friendly visual presentation. In modern anime, this is generally achieved via computer effects that create an imitation of watercolour, rather than by creating real-life watercolour art. While the watercolour style is more commonly used for backgrounds, it is possible to create the entire anime in such a style.</description>
<picurl>251159.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4588" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-20">
<name>fast-paced</name>
<description>Hold onto your hats, this anime`s storyline is relentless.
The characters don`t get time to take a breath as events keep both them and the viewer on a roller coaster ride of revelation and excitement!
Hopefully it all makes sense...</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4614" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>narration</name>
<description>The most common example is that of a voice, either that of one of the characters or entirely unrelated, that appears at the beginning of an episode to offer a summary or introduction, and at the end of an episode for closure or for a preview to hint upon what to expect next.
Another use of narration comes in the form of a dominant voice belonging to one of the protagonists, intended only for the viewer and revealing the intimate thoughts to whom it belongs. This type of narration occurs frequently throughout the duration of the episode or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5515" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>faceless background characters</name>
<description>Unimportant random/extra characters that appear mostly as part of the background are often drawn without much facial details, normally to save money, effort and manpower for more important parts of the show. Sometimes, they have almost or no facial details, meaning their heads only have indications of the presence of parts such as hair or mouth, or not even that. This can go as far as only drawing an abstracted silhouette of the whole body.</description>
<picurl>233515.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5529" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-11-05">
<name>black and white</name>
<description>Some or all of this anime is in black and white, typical of older anime made before ~1960. Some modern anime may intentionally shift to black and white for certain scenes or episodes as an artistic effect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5604" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-04">
<name>following one`s dream</name>
<description>No matter what the hardships may be, at least one of the protagonists in this anime is following her/his dream.
Examples: To become a professional athlete, a musician, a painter or the ruler of this world!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5816" parentid="4316" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-10-03">
<name>massacre</name>
<description>Mass murder.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5826" parentid="2607" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-12">
<name>rivalry</name>
<description>Quite broadly used term describing a conflict, contest, struggle, or opposition of some sort.
Typical examples: The mostly comedic rivalry for the love of a protagonist in a harem anime (love polygon), the more "mindless" battles between wannabe delinquents in a school fighting anime, or the struggle between good &amp; evil in an epic conflict for world domination.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5852" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>short episodes</name>
<description>Short episodes are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length. This means up to and including 10 minutes; shows with episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length are http://anidb.net/t6494 [half-length episodes] instead.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t6349 [multi-segment episodes], which are regular episodes that are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5954" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-02-17">
<name>call my name</name>
<description>"TETSUOOOOOO!!" "KANEDAAAAAA!!"
"TAMAHOMEEEE!!" "MIAKAAAA!!"
Feelings of any kind towards other characters are best shown by calling each other`s name, loud, REALLY LOUD. For better effect at least twice or thrice. For lover`s couples and mortal enemies it is a requirement to run towards each other while calling each other`s name, unaware of the surroundings.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5965" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2015-02-10">
<name>incomplete story</name>
<description>The show does not cover all of the original work (if present) or was cancelled prematurely, leaving plot lines unresolved or aborting character development. Sometimes the show runs through all its initially slotted episodes and adapts all of the original work (if applicable) but fails to present a proper ending, leaving viewers wondering whether they`re missing the final episodes.
In some cases, this may overlap with the studio forging an anime-original ending. Such an ending normally manages to allow the show to "finish", but may still suffer from incomplete story issues.
An incomplete storyline is not to be confused with the sequel bait, which is when the story presented by the show is finished but leaves enough room for a sequel to be produced. Sometimes this goes as far as to present a new potential problem in the last few minutes; that is usual for after-credits footage in movies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6062" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-04-05">
<name>heroic sacrifice</name>
<description>"In order to save the many, the few will need to sacrifice their lives..." or so this character may think. 
In a seemingly hopeless situation, against impossible odds, the character does not choose the path of the coward and run, he or she chooses to bravely face the enemy, fully aware that this will mean death.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6075" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-12">
<name>educational</name>
<description>The entire series (at least a major part of it) is centred on a particular subject. Information is fed to the audience in a sublime manner. Most of the time an on-screen written comment by the narrator (or translator) can be seen, e.g. biological specimen, medicine, process, etc. Sometimes at the end of every episode’s closing song, a 20 seconds educational clip is presented.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="81182" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-14">
<name>Oichi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193775.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20025" picture="132938.jpg">Mimori Suzuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81184" type="main character in" update="2017-11-13">
<rating votes="1">4.32</rating>
<name>Oda Nobunaga</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193760.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29" picture="202917.jpg">Hatano Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81185" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-10-29">
<name>Sukezou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193761.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="30656" picture="153750.jpg">Murase Ayumu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81186" type="main character in" update="2016-10-29">
<name>Chidori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193759.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21013" picture="201781.jpg">Minase Inori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81187" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-10-29">
<name>Kichou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193763.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1665" picture="19756.jpg">Takahashi Chiaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="81188" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-12">
<name>Kinoshita Hideyoshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193762.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="254" picture="17073.jpg">Yamaguchi Kappei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="84200" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-10-29">
<name>Mori Yoshinari</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>193766.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="236" picture="132757.jpg">Seki Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90416" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-11-14">
<name>Azai Nagamasa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>205098.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10130" picture="151714.jpg">Takumi Yasuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="90420" type="secondary cast in" update="2017-07-13">
<name>Asakura Yoshikage</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>205102.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="63" picture="186695.jpg">Kishio Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="197413" update="2018-05-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-04-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">キケンな二人</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Dangerous Two</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Deux hommes dangereux</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kiken na Futari</title>
<summary>The Tokugawa army’s numbers start to fall below the Asakura army’s, and Honda Tadakatsu and Magara Naotaka face off. Nobunaga says what wins battles are strategy and direction, and Ieyasu starts to show his true strength.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>768751</identifier>
<identifier>ninja-girl-samurai-master</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="197414" update="2018-05-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-04-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">5.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">千鳥乱舞</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Chidori Dances</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La danse mortelle de Chidori</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chidori Ranbu</title>
<summary>Isono Kazumasa blasts through one camp of the Oda army after another. Isono only has one goal: to get Nobunaga’s head, and he awaits in the main camp. There, he encounters Maeda Toshiie and Chidori.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>768749</identifier>
<identifier>ninja-girl-samurai-master</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="197415" update="2018-04-19">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-04-14</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">磯野, 発進!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Isono Takes Off!</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Isono, en avant !</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Isono, Hasshin!</title>
<summary>Nobunaga plans to take over the Azai clan’s other castle, Yokoyama Castle. Ieyasu arrives to help Nobunaga with reinforcements, while the Azai and Asakura clans also join forces. Nagamasa finally leaves Odani Castle, and both armies get ready to clash at Anegawa.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>768747</identifier>
<identifier>ninja-girl-samurai-master</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="197416" update="2018-04-19">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-04-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">沈黙の小谷城</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Silent Odani Castle</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le silencieux château d`Odani</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chinmoku no Odani Jou</title>
<summary>The Nobunaga and Azai clans end up enemies after the clash at Kanegasaki. The Azai army only has 5,000 men, which isn’t much, but they’re safe in their mountain fortress of Odani Castle. Nobunaga comes up with a plan to get Azai out of the castle.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>768745</identifier>
<identifier>ninja-girl-samurai-master</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="197875" update="2018-04-09">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2018-04-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="198374" update="2018-07-02">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-05-26</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">それぞれの姉川</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Everyone`s Own Anegawa</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">À chacun sa propre Anegawa</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sorezore no Anegawa</title>
<summary>The Battle of Anegawa ended with the Azai and Asakura armies losing thousands of their troops. The Oda and Tokugawa allied forces celebrated a huge victory, and one of Azai’s castles, Yokoyama Castle, now belonged to the Oda clan. Yokoyama Castle was key to subduing the Azai clan, and our favorite monkey was left in charge of it.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>768759</identifier>
<identifier>ninja-girl-samurai-master</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="198375" update="2018-05-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-05-19</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">拙者の屍を越えてゆけ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Walk over My Corpse</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Piétinez mon cadavre et avancez</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sessha no Shikabane o Koete Yuke</title>
<summary>Endo manages to make it into the Nobunaga main camp himself. He manages to get right up to Nobunaga and his identity is revealed. Endo is immediately surrounded, but Chidori stops them, and asks Endo to surrender.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>768757</identifier>
<identifier>ninja-girl-samurai-master</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="198376" update="2018-05-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-05-12</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">特攻野郎遠藤さん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The One-on-One Bastard Endo-san</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Endô, le preneur d`assaut</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tokkou Yarou Endo-san</title>
<summary>The Azai army instantly falls in numbers because of the Tokugawa army. Nagamasa orders his men to retreat, but Endo Naotsune stays behind. Endo puts on an Oda army armor and rushes into the 20,000 soldiers of the Oda army.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>768755</identifier>
<identifier>ninja-girl-samurai-master</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="198377" update="2018-05-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-05-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">武士の本分</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Warrior`s Duty</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le devoir d`un guerrier</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bushi no Honbun</title>
<summary>An hour after the Battle of Anegawa started, the Tokugawa army defeats the Asakura army in the west, giving them a huge advantage in this battle. The Asakura army starts to flee, but Magara Naotaka is left behind the enemy camp, still facing off with Honda Tadakatsu.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>768753</identifier>
<identifier>ninja-girl-samurai-master</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="199646" update="2018-07-02">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-06-23</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">光の射す方へ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Towards the Light</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La voie qu`indique la lumière</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hikaru no Sasu Hou e</title>
<summary>Kennyo had agreed to various requests from Nobunaga in the past, but his most recent request to hand over Ishiyama Hongan-ji had irked him. Meanwhile, Chidori and Sukezo infiltrate Ishiyama Hongan-ji and Chidori seems to be affected by Kennyo’s charisma.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>768767</identifier>
<identifier>ninja-girl-samurai-master</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="199647" update="2018-07-02">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-06-16</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さわらぬ仏にたたり無し</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let Sleeping Buddhas Lie</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ne pas réveiller le chat qui dort</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sawaranu Hotoke ni Tatari Nashi</title>
<summary>Nobunaga starts gathering information on the leader of the Ikko religion, Hongan-ji Kennyo. Kennyo is known to financially assist daimyos in the area, and it would be bad if he turned against Nobunaga. Nobunaga sends Chidori to Hongan-ji to see what Kennyo was up to.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>768765</identifier>
<identifier>ninja-girl-samurai-master</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="199648" update="2018-07-02">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-06-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ちょっと森家まで</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Just a Little Trip to the Mori Clan</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Petit tour chez le clan Mori</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chotto Mori-ke made</title>
<summary>Nobunaga returns to Gifu Castle and plans his next attack, and the Miyoshi Three start to make a move in the west. Chidori and Sukezo head to Mori Yoshinari’s house on an errand. When they arrive, Mori’s older son challenges her to a duel.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>768763</identifier>
<identifier>ninja-girl-samurai-master</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="199649" update="2018-07-02">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-06-02</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">本当の覚悟</title>
<title xml:lang="en">True Resolve</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une vraie détermination</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hontou no Kakugo</title>
<summary>Nobunaga goes to visit the Shogun Yoshiaki in Kyoto to tell him that they had been victorious against the Azai clan. However, Yoshiaki seemed to be annoyed at Nobunaga. Meanwhile, Chidori recovers from Endo’s death.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>768761</identifier>
<identifier>ninja-girl-samurai-master</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="201637" update="2018-07-02">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-06-30</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">龍興は忘れた頃にやってくる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tatsuoki Always Appears Right Around the Time You Forget About Him</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Tatsuoki revient lorsqu`on l`a oublié</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tatsuoki wa Wasureta Koro ni Yatte Kuru</title>
<summary>Saito Tatsuoki joins forces with the Miyoshi Three and builds a fort near Ishiyama Hongan-ji to plan his next battle with Nobunaga. Shimotsuma arrives at the fort to complain on behalf of Ishiyama Hongan-ji, but Tatsuoki had a plan...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>768769</identifier>
<identifier>ninja-girl-samurai-master</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="202348" update="2018-07-30">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-07-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">きっかけは野田, 福島</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Opportunities Lie in Noda and Fukushima</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ôda et Fukushima au commencement</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kikkake wa Noda, Fukushima</title>
<summary>Nobunaga moves out to face the Miyoshi Three. Nobunaga’s army manages to gather around 40,000 men while the Miyoshi army only has about 12,000. So begins the Battle of Noda and Fukushima!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>774663</identifier>
<identifier>ninja-girl-samurai-master</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="202430" update="2018-07-30">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-07-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">信者の行進</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The March of the True Believers</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La marche de Nobunaga</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinja no Koushin</title>
<summary>Kennyo declares Nobunaga an enemy and asks that his followers take up arms, so hordes of his followers start to gather at Ishiyama Hongan-ji. Meanwhile, Nobunaga thinks he has the upper hand, but then the bell at Ishiyama Hongan-ji is rung.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>774665</identifier>
<identifier>ninja-girl-samurai-master</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="202431" update="2018-07-30">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-07-14</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">矢より鉄砲持って来い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bring Guns, Not Bows and Arrows</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Apportez-moi une arquebuse plutôt que des flèches</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ya yori Teppou Motte Koi</title>
<summary>The Nobunaga forces gather around the Miyoshi army’s fort and they begin a heavy attack with guns. Nobunaga’s forces have the upper hand and they head toward their next target of Ishiyama Hongan-ji, but...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>774664</identifier>
<identifier>ninja-girl-samurai-master</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="202806" update="2018-09-15">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-08-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">受け継ぐ者たち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Successors</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les héritiers</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uketsugu Mono-tachi</title>
<summary>As his men continue to fall left and right, Yoshinari continues to fight valiantly with his spear. Despite getting stabbed through the stomach with Yamazaki`s spear, he tells them about Nobunaga`s vision of a new world. Meanwhile, Chidori manages to return to Nobunaga`s main camp and hears that there is a message from Usayama Castle...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>774669</identifier>
<identifier>ninja-girl-samurai-master</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="202807" update="2018-09-15">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-08-11</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">覚悟完了</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Resolve Complete</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Détermination parfaite</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kakugo Kanryou</title>
<summary>The Azai and Asakura forces start their attack on Usayama Castle. Yoshinari sends Chidori away to deliver a message to Nobunaga in order to spare her life. He then goes to battle with his few men against the Azai Asakura forces of 30,000.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>774668</identifier>
<identifier>ninja-girl-samurai-master</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="202808" update="2018-08-14">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-08-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">絶対死守領域</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Territory Defended to the Last</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Défendez le domaine jusqu`à la mort</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zettai Shishu Ryouiki</title>
<summary>Mori Yoshinari only has a thousand troops at Usayama Castle to go up against the Azai and Asakura forces of 30,000. Despite having all the odds against them, Yoshinari decides to risk his life to protect Kyo for the sake of the Oda clan.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>774667</identifier>
<identifier>ninja-girl-samurai-master</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="202809" update="2018-07-30">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-07-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">逆襲の将</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Counterstrike General</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le général de la contre-attaque</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gyakushuu no Shou</title>
<summary>The Nobunaga forces are put at a disadvantage against the Saika and masses at Honga-ji. Matsunaga advises Nobunaga to try to make peace with Kennyo, but Kennyo declines. Nobunaga then realizes that Kennyo is after Kyoto.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>774666</identifier>
<identifier>ninja-girl-samurai-master</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="203878" update="2018-10-02">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-09-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">比叡山の屈辱</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Humiliation at Mount Hiei</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`humiliation du mont Hiei</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hieizan no Kutsujoku</title>
<summary>Nobunaga actually grovels before Asakura Yoshikage and Azai Nagamasa in order to declare a truce. Yoshikage is delighted by the sight, but Nagamasa really wonders if the truce was the right answer...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>774673</identifier>
<identifier>ninja-girl-samurai-master</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="203879" update="2018-10-02">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-09-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">悪夢の志賀の陣</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Nightmarish Shiga Encampment</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le cauchemard du siège de Shiga</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akumu no Shiga no Jin</title>
<summary>Enryaku-ji ignores Nobunaga’s requests and side with the Azai and Asakura forces. Meanwhile, Kennyo finds out that Nobunaga is at a stalemate and recruits even more troops nationwide.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>774672</identifier>
<identifier>ninja-girl-samurai-master</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="203880" update="2018-10-02">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-09-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">聖域無き戦国乱世</title>
<title xml:lang="en">There Are No Sanctuaries in These Troubled Times</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`ère Sengoku sans Terre sainte</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seiiki Naki Sengokuransei</title>
<summary>Hearing that Nobunaga was heading to Kyoto with 30,000 men, the Azai and Asakura forces seek sanctuary in Mt. Hiei. Nobunaga meets with a monk from Enryaku-ji, which is located on Mt. Hiei, asking them to side with him, but...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>774671</identifier>
<identifier>ninja-girl-samurai-master</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="203881" update="2018-10-02">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-08-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">天魔の御加護</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Blessing of the Demon</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La protection de Tenma</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tenma no Gokago</title>
<summary>Nobunaga hears about Yoshinari’s death as well as the fact that the Azai and Asakura forces are headed to Kyoto. He tries to make his way to Kyoto, but Kennyo attacks. Meanwhile, The Azai and Asakura forces try to take over Usayama Castle since Yoshinari no longer stands in their way but find that it more difficult than they had imagined.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>774670</identifier>
<identifier>ninja-girl-samurai-master</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="206487" update="2018-10-02">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-09-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">連鎖の終わり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The End of Misfortune</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La fin des enchaînements</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Rensa no Owari</title>
<summary>Because of the truce, Kennyo is also forced to stop attacking Nobunaga for the time being. However, Kennyo recruits the Saika to prepare for the next battle. Meanwhile, Nobunaga returns to Gifu.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>774674</identifier>
<identifier>ninja-girl-samurai-master</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="206488" update="2018-10-02">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2018-09-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">鉢巻きと再出発</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Headband and the Fresh Start</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Bandeau et nouveau départ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hachimaki to Saishuppatsu</title>
<summary>Nobunaga heads towards the Mori mansion. Despite Ranmaru’s warnings, Nagayoshi blames Nobunaga for their father’s death. Ei slaps Nagayoshi for his insolence, and then Nobunaga apologizes to Ei as soon as they were alone.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>774675</identifier>
<identifier>ninja-girl-samurai-master</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="208364" update="2018-09-22">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2018-07-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
