<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="14087" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2020-01-10</startdate>
<enddate>2020-03-27</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Oshi ga Budoukan Itte Kuretara Shinu</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">If the Fan Goes to Budoukan, She’ll Die</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Oshibudou</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">推しが武道館いってくれたら死ぬ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">If My Favorite Pop Idol Made It to the Budokan, I Would Die</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="official">神推偶像登上武道館我就死而無憾</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="kanareading">おしがぶどうかんいってくれたらしぬ</title>
</titles>
<url>https://oshibudo.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="11302" type="Chief Animation Direction">Fukunaga Tomoko</name>
<name id="55101" type="Original Work">Hirao Auri</name>
<name id="11379" type="Chief Animation Direction">Nishihata Ayumi</name>
<name id="13553" type="Chief Animation Direction">Nakano Keiya</name>
<name id="15726" type="Chief Animation Direction">Takada Akira</name>
<name id="21503" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kawatsuma Tomomi</name>
<name id="2932" type="Chief Animation Direction">Shitaya Tomoyuki</name>
<name id="19010" type="Chief Animation Direction">Morimoto Yuuki</name>
<name id="17952" type="Chief Animation Direction">Hayakawa Asami</name>
<name id="21883" type="Animation Work">8bit</name>
<name id="11706" type="Character Design">Yonezawa Masaru</name>
<name id="2932" type="Character Design">Shitaya Tomoyuki</name>
<name id="4556" type="Series Composition">Akao Deko</name>
<name id="6520" type="Direction">Yamamoto Yuusuke</name>
<name id="54197" type="Music">Hyuuga Moe</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on http://anidb.net/cr55101 [Hirao Auri]`s comedy yuri manga.
A girl called "Eripiyo" is an extreme idol fan. She is wildly enthusiastic about Maina, the shy and lowest-ranking member of the minor underground idol group Cham Jam that performs in Okayama Prefecture. She gets so wrapped up in her love for Maina during a particular performance, that she has a major nosebleed. Eri will continue to give her complete devotion to Maina until the day she can perform at Budoukan (a major performing venue in Tokyo).
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="173">5.77</permanent>
<temporary count="174">6.54</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>241580.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22307</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>37890</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://oshibudo.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>If_My_Favorite_Pop_Idol_Made_It_to_the_Budokan,_I_Would_Die</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>推しが武道館いってくれたら死ぬ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5552</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>364331</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22454</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>anime_oshibudo</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B084GD4NMB</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2438" parentid="2794" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-12-05">
<name>idol</name>
<description>In Japanese culture, idols (アイドル) are media personalities in their teens and early twenties who are considered particularly cute and cuddly and who will, for a period ranging from several months to a few years, regularly appear in the mass media, e.g. as singers for J-pop groups, bit-part actors, TV personalities, models in photo spreads published in magazines, advertisements, etc.
http://anidb.net/t860 [Virtual idols] are animated characters created as idols. They are often also http://anidb.net/t7774 [vTubers] and/or http://anidb.net/t7250 [vloggers].
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>63097.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3170" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-10">
<name>occupation and career</name>
<description>The kind of anime which shows the career of a character, usually from the beginning.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3971" parentid="3170" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-07-04">
<name>entertainment industry</name>
<description>The show depicts how the entertainment industry works and how the main protagonists strive to cope with the sudden change to fame. At times this can be a very ugly sight indeed.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6030" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-22">
<name>otaku culture</name>
<description>Otaku (おたく/オタク) is a Japanese term used to refer to people with obsessive interests, particularly anime, manga, and video games. A female otaku is occasionally referred to as a fujoshi. (Source: Wikipedia)
Here certain aspects of this "fandom" are presented in more detail, e.g. the creation of doujinshi (self-published amateur manga).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="104381" type="main character in" update="2019-10-28">
<rating votes="5">7.03</rating>
<name>Eripiyo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240479.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="57243" picture="229102.jpg">Fairouz Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106531" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-28">
<rating votes="1">7.45</rating>
<name>Kumasa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240480.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="612" picture="79531.jpg">Maeno Tomoaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106532" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-10-28">
<rating votes="1">1.13</rating>
<name>Motoi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240481.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36495" picture="176250.jpg">Yamaya Yoshitaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106533" type="main character in" update="2019-10-28">
<rating votes="4">6.95</rating>
<name>Ichii Maina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240482.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="58277" picture="242923.jpg">Tachibana Hina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107177" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-11-28">
<rating votes="4">6.28</rating>
<name>Igarashi Reo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>241594.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43552" picture="179144.jpg">Hondo Kaede</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107178" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-11-28">
<rating votes="2">4.29</rating>
<name>Hakata Maki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>241596.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39471" picture="242922.jpg">Enoyoshi Maya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107179" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-11-28">
<rating votes="4">5.10</rating>
<name>Teramoto Yuuka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>241598.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43435" picture="242925.jpg">Watada Misaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107180" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-11-28">
<rating votes="3">7.54</rating>
<name>Matsuyama Sorane</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>241595.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="53526" picture="242924.jpg">Hasegawa Ikumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107181" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-11-28">
<rating votes="4">7.45</rating>
<name>Yokota Aya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>241599.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43420" picture="175434.jpg">Itou Manami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107182" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-11-28">
<rating votes="2">4.29</rating>
<name>Mizumori Yumeri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>241597.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="16763" picture="45795.jpg">Ishihara Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107183" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-11-28">
<rating votes="2">6.61</rating>
<name>Rena</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>241600.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="52537" picture="225050.jpg">Ichinose Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="110260" type="appears in" update="2020-05-22">
<name>Fujikawa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>247677.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="336" picture="17172.jpg">Sakaguchi Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="110261" type="appears in" update="2020-05-22">
<name>Kosuge</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>247678.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="19" picture="50583.jpg">Imaruoka Atsushi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="110262" type="appears in" update="2020-05-22">
<rating votes="1">1.00</rating>
<name>Murota</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>247679.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="182" picture="226274.jpg">Itou Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="110263" type="appears in" update="2020-05-22">
<rating votes="1">4.93</rating>
<name>Misaki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>247681.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="162" picture="23208.jpg">Satou Satomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="110264" type="appears in" update="2020-05-22">
<rating votes="1">7.45</rating>
<name>ChamJam</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>247682.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="110267" type="appears in" update="2020-05-23">
<name>Yoshikawa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>247693.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="345" picture="84834.jpg">Nakamura Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="110268" type="appears in" update="2020-05-23">
<name>Ouna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>247694.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="41367" picture="164100.jpg">Wataya Miho</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="110269" type="appears in" update="2020-05-23">
<name>Okina</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>247695.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40456" picture="181638.jpg">Hayashi Daichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="110270" type="appears in" update="2020-05-23">
<name>Shop Ten`in</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>247696.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="55724" picture="253111.jpg">Yamane Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="110271" type="appears in" update="2020-05-23">
<name>Fumi-kun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>247697.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45" picture="44970.jpg">Sugita Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="110272" type="appears in" update="2020-05-23">
<name>Matsuo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>247698.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="60" picture="249027.jpg">Kawada Shinji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="110278" type="appears in" update="2020-05-23">
<name>Sakiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>247703.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="360" picture="171401.jpg">Hisakawa Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="110279" type="appears in" update="2020-05-23">
<name>Eripiyo no Itoko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>247704.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="54648" picture="216306.jpg">Mochida Himari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="110280" type="appears in" update="2020-05-23">
<name>Eripiyo no Oba</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>247705.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="253" picture="222833.jpg">Yuzuki Ryouka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="110281" type="appears in" update="2020-05-23">
<name>Eripiyo no Oba</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>247706.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="54918" picture="217157.jpg">Imaizumi Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="110297" type="appears in" update="2020-05-24">
<name>Yoshimune</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>247721.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2192" picture="248128.jpg">Kashii Shouto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="110298" type="appears in" update="2020-05-24">
<name>Miyu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>247722.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45121" picture="225365.jpg">Fujiwara Natsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="110299" type="appears in" update="2020-05-24">
<name>Mei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>247723.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28392" picture="224735.jpg">Kubo Yurika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="110300" type="appears in" update="2020-05-24">
<name>Fuyutarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>247724.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36680" picture="153752.jpg">Saitou Souma</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="110302" type="appears in" update="2020-05-24">
<name>Ruri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>247727.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="55724" picture="253111.jpg">Yamane Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="110303" type="appears in" update="2020-05-24">
<name>Hinaka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>247732.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="53351" picture="211867.jpg">Suyama Emiri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="110306" type="appears in" update="2020-05-24">
<name>Maple Doll</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>247731.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="110307" type="appears in" update="2020-05-24">
<name>Nagai</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>247734.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2796" picture="23212.jpg">Takemoto Eiji</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="225639" update="2019-12-27">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-01-10</airdate>
<rating votes="3">6.20</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">そんな舞菜を愛してる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">But I Love That Maina</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sonna Maina o Ai Shiteru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225640" update="2019-12-27">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-01-17</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">いちばん好きでいたい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Always Want to Love You the Most</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ichiban Suki de Itai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225641" update="2019-12-27">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-01-24</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">わたしのこと好きですか?</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Do You Like Me?</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Watashi no Koto Suki Desuka?</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225642" update="2019-12-27">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-01-31</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">絶対, 1位にするから</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Promise to Make You Number 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Zettai, Ichii ni Suru kara</title>
</episode>
<episode id="226301" update="2020-01-24">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-02-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">わたしは待つことしかできない</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Can Only Wait</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Watashi wa Matsu Koto shika Dekinai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="226302" update="2020-01-24">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-02-14</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ぼくの全てが君だった</title>
<title xml:lang="en">You Were My Everything</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Boku no Subete ga Kimi Datta</title>
</episode>
<episode id="226303" update="2020-01-24">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-02-21</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">舞菜のために走るんだ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Run for Maina`s Sake</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maina no Tame ni Hashirunda</title>
</episode>
<episode id="226304" update="2020-01-24">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-02-28</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">わたしの未来にいてほしい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Want You in My Future</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Watashi no Mirai ni Ite Hoshii</title>
</episode>
<episode id="227023" update="2020-02-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-03-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">オタクじゃなく一人の人間として</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Not as a Wota, but as a Person</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Otaku ja Naku Hitori no Ningen Toshite</title>
</episode>
<episode id="227024" update="2020-02-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-03-13</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">推しは友達じゃないから</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Your Fave Isn`t Your Friend</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oshi wa Tomodachi ja Nai kara</title>
</episode>
<episode id="227025" update="2020-02-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-03-20</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">いちばん, 身近にある奇跡</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Closest Miracle to Me</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ichiban, Mijika ni Aru Kiseki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="227026" update="2020-02-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-03-27</airdate>
<rating votes="1">3.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">推しが武道館いってくれたら</title>
<title xml:lang="en">If My Favorite Pop Idol Made It to the Budokan</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Oshi ga Budoukan Itte Kuretara</title>
</episode>
<episode id="228365" update="2020-05-26">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2020-01-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="228366" update="2020-05-26">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2020-01-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="229160" update="2020-05-25">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2020-04-15</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">『ずっと ChamJam』Special Music Video</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Zutto ChamJam Special Music Video</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">"Zutto ChamJam" Special Music Video</title>
</episode>
<episode id="229452" update="2020-05-25">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2020-03-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1b</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
