<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="14467" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2019-07-02</startdate>
<enddate>2019-09-17</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Tejina Senpai</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Фокусница-старшеклассница</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Tejina-senpai</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">手品先輩</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Magical Sempai</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">魔术学姐</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="12803" approval="1" total="6">Aho Girl</anime>
<anime id="10888" approval="1" total="6">Shimoneta to Iu Gainen ga Sonzai Shinai Taikutsu na Sekai</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="338163">Hilariously over the top. Can`t remember the last time I laughed at a show this much.

For fans of: Slapstick, magic, doves, and big titty senpai</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.tejina-senpai.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="56595" type="Original Work">Azu</name>
<name id="35233" type="Animation Work">Liden Films</name>
<name id="24222" type="Character Design">Itou Eriko</name>
<name id="46055" type="Series Composition">Ikeda Rintarou</name>
<name id="13080" type="Direction">Usui Fumiaki</name>
<name id="783" type="Work">NAS</name>
<name id="14021" type="Music">Hama Takeshi</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a comedy seinen manga series drawn by http://anidb.net/cr56595 [Azu].
The male protagonist finds out that his school requires him to join a club and during his reluctant search he stumbles upon Tejina Senpai attempting magic tricks in her clubroom. Tejina Senpai has massive stage fright however and so now that she has an audience her attempts are simply comedic.
Source: M-U</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="601">3.90</permanent>
<temporary count="603">6.10</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>231364.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>21549</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>38610</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tejina-senpai.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Magical_Sempai</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>手品先輩</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5355</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>366013</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22092</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>tejina_senpai</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>magical-sempai</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="308" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>detective</name>
<description>A detective is an investigator, generally either a member of a law enforcement agency or as an individual working in the capacity of private investigators, tasked with solving crimes and other mysteries, such as disappearances, by examining and evaluating clues and records in order to solve the mystery; for a crime, this would mean uncovering the criminal`s identity and/or whereabouts. In some police systems, a detective position is achieved by passing a written test after a person completes the requirements for being a police officer; in others, detectives are college graduates who join directly from civilian life without first serving as uniformed officers.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210906.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="627" parentid="2856" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-15">
<name>lingerie</name>
<description>Lingerie is a term for fashionable and alluring women`s undergarments.</description>
<picurl>238327.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2056" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-09-13">
<name>cosplaying</name>
<description>This character likes to cosplay.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2729" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-02">
<name>BDSM</name>
<description>A form of "kinky sex". The acronym BDSM derives from BD (bondage and discipline), DS (dominance and submission) and SM (sadism and masochism). BDSM usually characterizes with one side being superior (active) over the other (passive), with each side being one or more participants. Whips, chains, handcuffs, ropes, blindfolds are common elements of BDSM.</description>
<picurl>233865.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2746" parentid="2901" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-26">
<name>shibari</name>
<description>Not to be confused with Hojoujutsu (捕縄術) or Nawajutsu (縄術), which is the traditional Japanese martial art of restraining a person using cord or rope.
More commonly known as Kinbaku (緊縛) in Japan, Shibari is the word for "erotic bondage" or Kinbaku-bi which means "beautiful bondage". Kinbaku (also Sokubaku) is a Japanese style of sexual bondage or BDSM which involves tying up the bottom using simple yet visually intricate patterns, usually with several pieces of thin rope usually hemp or jute (generally 6 mm or 8 mm in diameter). The person`s body can also be hanging from the rope while tied to it.
The word Shibari came into common use in the West at some point in the 1990s to describe the bondage art Kinbaku. Shibari (縛り) is a Japanese word that literally means "to tie" or "to bind". It is used in Japan to describe the artful use of twine to tie objects or packages.
In anime/manga, Shibari or Kinbaku is often seen as a tool of rape or torture, rather than intended for a concept of bondage aesthetics.</description>
<picurl>161702.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2793" parentid="2883" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>performance</name>
<description>The song performance on stage or acting in a theatre is a central part of the character`s life in this anime type.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2820" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>wardrobe malfunction</name>
<description>A euphemistic term for an embarrassing display of a body part when clothing droops, falls, or is torn. Wikipedia: "Super Bowl XXXVIII half-time show" for more details.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2822" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-06">
<name>skirt flipping</name>
<description>Naughty characters — usually boys — flip the skirts of female protagonists to ascertain what panties they are wearing (also see Pantsu category).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2823" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>paper clothes</name>
<description>Worn clothing appears paper-thin and takes little abuse to be shredded or torn from the body. This is common in ecchi anime where the main storyline involves some type of fighting but consists primarily of dialogue and fanservice (Ikkitousen and Platonic Heart). Various girls’ clothing exploding as if made of rice paper is a very enticing prospect.</description>
<picurl>150776.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2901" parentid="2729" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-09">
<name>bondage</name>
<description>Bondage is the use of restraints for the sexual pleasure of the parties involved. It may be used in its own right, as in the case of rope bondage and breast bondage, or as part of sexual activity or BDSM activity. When a person is sexually aroused by bondage, it may be considered a paraphilia, known as vincilagnia (from Latin vincio, to bind or fetter with chains, and lagneia, lust).
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>42021.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3977" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-29">
<name>dialogue driven</name>
<description>A dialogue driven show has its story advanced by dialogue, with action being of much lower priority, and relies heavily on conversations between characters.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4440" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>boy meets girl</name>
<description>A classical type of plot in story writing, where the story begins with a boy meeting a girl leading to romantic development between the two. More often than not the boy loses the girl later on and has to find her again.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4576" parentid="6185" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-03">
<name>summer</name>
<description>At least one of the episodes takes place in summer. Think oppressively warm weather, summer vacation, summer school, summer festival, or a visit to the beach.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4588" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-20">
<name>fast-paced</name>
<description>Hold onto your hats, this anime`s storyline is relentless.
The characters don`t get time to take a breath as events keep both them and the viewer on a roller coaster ride of revelation and excitement!
Hopefully it all makes sense...</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5515" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>faceless background characters</name>
<description>Unimportant random/extra characters that appear mostly as part of the background are often drawn without much facial details, normally to save money, effort and manpower for more important parts of the show. Sometimes, they have almost or no facial details, meaning their heads only have indications of the presence of parts such as hair or mouth, or not even that. This can go as far as only drawing an abstracted silhouette of the whole body.</description>
<picurl>233515.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5695" parentid="2869" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>preschool</name>
<description>Preschool education (or infant education) is the provision of learning to children before the commencement of statutory and obligatory education, usually between the ages of zero and three or five, depending on the jurisdiction.
In Japan, development of social skills and a sense of group belonging are major goals for preschools. Class sizes tend to be large, up to 40 students per class, to decrease the role of the teacher`s personality and increase the likelihood of peer interactions. Because exclusion from the group is extremely undesirable, a wide range of behaviors is tolerated.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6075" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-12">
<name>educational</name>
<description>The entire series (at least a major part of it) is centred on a particular subject. Information is fed to the audience in a sublime manner. Most of the time an on-screen written comment by the narrator (or translator) can be seen, e.g. biological specimen, medicine, process, etc. Sometimes at the end of every episode’s closing song, a 20 seconds educational clip is presented.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6186" parentid="6185" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-29">
<name>spring</name>
<description>During spring, the axis of the Earth is increasing its tilt relative to the Sun, and the length of daylight rapidly increases for the relevant hemisphere. The hemisphere begins to warm significantly causing new plant growth to spring forth, giving the season its name. Snow, if a normal part of winter, begins to melt, and streams swell with runoff. Frosts, if a normal part of winter, become less severe. In climates that have no snow and rare frosts, the air and ground temperatures increase more rapidly. Many flowering plants bloom this time of year, in a long succession sometimes beginning when snow is still on the ground, continuing into early summer. In normally snowless areas spring may begin as early as February (Northern Hemisphere) heralded by the blooming of deciduous magnolias, cherries and quince, or August (Southern Hemisphere) in the same way. Many temperate areas have a dry spring, and wet autumn (fall), which brings about flowering in this season more consistent with the need for water as well as warmth. Subarctic areas may not experience spring at all until May or even June.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>161969.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6349" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-13">
<name>multi-segment episodes</name>
<description>Multi-segment episodes are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t5852 [short episodes], which are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length (up to and including 10 minutes).
Also not to be confused with an OVA or music video with multiple (otherwise unrelated) full-length http://anidb.net/t7241 [bundled episodes] consolidated into a single episode video track.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6494" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-19">
<name>half-length episodes</name>
<description>Half-length episodes are regular episodes that are somewhat shorter than the standard length. This includes episodes that are 11 to 20 minutes in length; shows with episodes up to and including 10 minutes are http://anidb.net/t5852 [short episodes] instead.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7199" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-12">
<name>sexual humour</name>
<description>Sexual humour is prevalent in this anime. It often involves cheeky or crude sexual language, with innuendos and jokes about the female or male genitalia. Often, such anime also have http://anidb.net/t2856 [ecchi] elements to them.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="103149" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-03-30">
<rating votes="7">4.20</rating>
<name>Onee-chan</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67656.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="38966" picture="147731.jpg">Akaneya Himika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103150" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-07-01">
<rating votes="4">2.13</rating>
<name>Masashi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67661.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="265" picture="25730.jpg">Namikawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103151" type="main character in" update="2019-07-04">
<rating votes="22">9.45</rating>
<name>Tejina Senpai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67657.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="43552" picture="179144.jpg">Hondo Kaede</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103152" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-07-01">
<rating votes="4">4.50</rating>
<name>Joshu</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67658.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="52057" picture="225903.jpg">Ichikawa Aoi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103153" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-03-30">
<rating votes="9">5.43</rating>
<name>Saki-chan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67659.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="401" picture="223216.jpg">Kitamura Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103154" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-07-01">
<rating votes="12">6.83</rating>
<name>Madara-san</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>67660.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="38380" picture="224406.jpg">Takahashi Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="218005" update="2019-07-22">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2019-07-02</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">未知の先輩 / 箱入り先輩 / 呼び出す先輩 / ハトと先輩</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Unknown Sempai / Sempai in a Box / Sempai Calls / Sempai and the Pigeon</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une étrange présidente</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Michi no Senpai / Hakoiri Senpai / Yobidasu Senpai / Hato to Senpai</title>
<summary>1, The Unknown Sempai: A cute but strange sempai appears!
2, Sempai in a Box: Sempai is cute but vulgar!
3, Sempai Calls: Keys, melon bread, and soaked sempai.
4, Sempai and the Pigeon: Sempai gives birth to a pigeon.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>786890</identifier>
<identifier>magical-sempai</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="218006" update="2019-07-22">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2019-07-09</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">曲げる先輩 / 非貫通先輩 / 責任転嫁先輩 / ヘタクソ手品おばさん / 本気先輩</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sempai Bends / Impenetrable Sempai / Sempai Shifts Responsibility / The Lady Who Stinks at Magic / Sempai Gets Serious</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La présidente est tordue</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mageru Senpai / Hi Kantsuu Senpai / Sekinintenka Senpai / Hetasou Tejina Obasan / Honki Senpai</title>
<summary>1, Sempai Bends: Sempai trains her fingertips.
2, Impenetrable Sempai: Sempai shows her butt.
3, Sempai Shifts Responsibility: A hairy animal crawls over Sempai.
4, The Lady Who Stinks at Magic: A quick-change outdoors.
5, Sempai Gets Serious: Assistant`s confinement is a se~cret
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>786891</identifier>
<identifier>magical-sempai</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="218007" update="2019-07-22">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2019-07-16</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">いやがる先輩 / 抜き打ち先輩 / 克服先輩 / 和装先輩 / 校外先輩</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sempai`s Discomfort / Pop Quiz Sempai / Conquering Sempai / Kimono Sempai / Sempai Off Campus</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La présidente n’a pas envie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Iyagaru Senpai / Nukiuchi Senpai / Kokufuku Senpai / Wasou Senpai / Kougai Senpai</title>
<summary>1, Sempai`s Discomfort: Sempai`s mortal enemy? Her big sister appears!
2, Pop Quiz Sempai: Sempai wears a flower print.
3, Conquering Sempai: Senpai really gives birth this time.
4, Kimono Sempai: Lots of wazuma.
5, Sempai Off Campus: An outdoor survival game?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>786892</identifier>
<identifier>magical-sempai</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="218008" update="2019-08-05">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2019-07-23</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">祝う先輩 / スカウト先輩 / ハトとハトと先輩 / 仕留める先輩 / 奇術部先輩</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Celebrating Sempai / Scouting Sempai / Pigeon, Pigeon, and Sempai / Sempai Finishes the Job / Magic Club Sempai</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La présidente fait la fête</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Iwau Senpai / Scout Senpai / Hato to Hato to Senpai / Shitomeru Senpai / Kijutsu Bu Senpai</title>
<summary>Celebrating Sempai: Together With Sempai, One Thousand Yen Per!&lt;3
Scouting Sempai: Sempai is lonely and loses her mind.
Pigeon, Pigeon, and Sempai: Sempai takes solace in pigeons.
Sempai Finishes the Job: Sempai is pierced, prodded, and exposed.
Magic Club Sempai: Sempai enjoys her time alone.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>786893</identifier>
<identifier>magical-sempai</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="218606" update="2019-07-10">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2019-07-02</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="218607" update="2019-07-10">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2019-07-02</airdate>
<rating votes="3">5.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="218800" update="2019-08-05">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2019-07-30</airdate>
<rating votes="5">5.51</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">見学者と先輩 / タマネギ先輩 / 化学先輩 / 想定外先輩 / 招く先輩</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Observers and Sempai / Onion Sempai / Chemistry Sempai / Unexpected Sempai / Inviting Sempai</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La présidente et les visiteurs</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kengakusha to Senpai / Tamanegi Senpai / Kagaku Senpai / Souteigai Senpai / Maneku Senpai</title>
<summary>Observers and Sempai: The terror of the school ghosts?!
Onion Sempai: Peel it and see!&lt;3
Chemistry Sempai: One-on-one experiments with Madara-san.&lt;3
Unexpected Sempai: Assistant loves her plush body?!
Inviting Sempai: Exciting times at Sempai`s house!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>786894</identifier>
<identifier>magical-sempai</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="218801" update="2019-08-19">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2019-08-06</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">知らない先輩 / ギャルパン先輩 / はかる先輩 / 胡散臭い先輩</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Sempai I Don`t Know / Gyaru-Pan Sempai / Measuring Sempai / Suspicious Sempai</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La Nouvelle Inconnue</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shiranai Senpai / Gyaru Pan Senpai / Hakaru Senpai / Usankusai Senpai</title>
<summary>Unknown Sempai: Street performance gyaru and fat dude attack!
Gyaru-Pan Sempai: Street performance is... awesome!!
Measuring Sempai: Sempai is over 2kg &lt;3
Suspicious Sempai: Sempai`s a master magician when hypnotized!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>786895</identifier>
<identifier>magical-sempai</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="218802" update="2019-08-19">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2019-08-13</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">作る先輩 / カンパ先輩 / プール先輩 / 乗り越える先輩</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Creative Sempai / Fund-Raising Sempai / Pool Sempai / Overcoming Sempai</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La présidente fait des gâteaux</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsukuru Senpai / Kanpa Senpai / Pool Senpai / Norikoeru Senpai</title>
<summary>Creative Sempai: Saki-chan`s aren`t that big.
Fund-Raising Sempai: Let those who cannot work leave the magic club!
Pool Sempai: Water escape in a school swimsuit!!
Overcoming Sempai: Sempai won`t get stage fright in front of "handsome" assistant.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>786896</identifier>
<identifier>magical-sempai</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="218803" update="2019-09-15">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2019-08-20</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">中華先輩 / メンタリスト先輩 / ミカン先輩 / ネット先輩 / デリバリー先輩</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Chinese Sempai / Mentalist Sempai / Mikan Sempai / Internet Sempai / Delivery Sempai</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La présidente et la magie chinoise</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chuuka Senpai / Mentalist Senpai / Mikan Senpai / Net Senpai / Delivery Senpai</title>
<summary>Chinese Sempai: Is Sempai more powerful than 4000 years of history?!
Mentalist Sempai: Sempai sees all!
Mikan Sempai: Sempai won`t make it alone.
Internet Sempai: The magic club website is 18+!
Delivery Sempai: Sempai entertains the good boys and girls.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>786897</identifier>
<identifier>magical-sempai</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="219313" update="2019-09-15">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2019-08-27</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">偏見先輩 / 追試先輩 / アイス先輩 / 水着先輩</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Biased Sempai / Make-Up Exam Sempai / Ice Cream Sempai / Swimsuit Sempai</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les préjugés de la présidente</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Henken Senpai / Tsuishi Senpai / Ice Senpai / Mizugi Senpai</title>
<summary>Biased Sempai: Time for se~crets &lt;3
Make-Up Exam Sempai: Scheming! Drowning in schemes!
Ice Cream Sempai: Ice cream later?
Swimsuit Sempai: Assistant and Ma-kun`s revealing swimsuit plan!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>786898</identifier>
<identifier>magical-sempai</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="219314" update="2019-09-15">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2019-09-03</airdate>
<rating votes="5">8.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">海と先輩 / カニ先輩 / スイカ先輩 / 花火先輩</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Beach Sempai / Crab Sempai / Watermelon Sempai / Fireworks Sempai</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La présidente à la mer</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Umi to Senpai / Kani Senpai / Suika Senpai / Hanabi Senpai</title>
<summary>Beach Sempai: Beach! Swimsuits! Training camp!
Crab Sempai: Lying on the beach with Madara-san&lt;3
Watermelon Sempai: Sempai is the watermelon-splitting champion.
Fireworks Sempai: Sempai is not allowed fire!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>786899</identifier>
<identifier>magical-sempai</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="219315" update="2019-10-05">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2019-09-10</airdate>
<rating votes="6">8.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">四つ玉先輩 / 腹話術先輩 / 尾行先輩</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Four Balls Sempai / Ventriloquism Sempai / Tailing Sempai</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La présidente et les quatre balles</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yottsu Tama Senpai / Fukuwajutsu Senpai / Bikou Senpai</title>
<summary>Four Balls Sempai: Thanks for the magic!
Ventriloquism Sempai: Try to say "Pushy" without moving your lips.
Tailing Sempai: Sempai has a boyfriend?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>786900</identifier>
<identifier>magical-sempai</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="219316" update="2019-10-05">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2019-09-17</airdate>
<rating votes="5">6.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">はやす先輩 / 失敗しない先輩 / 負けない先輩 / サイレント先輩 / バニー先輩</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Growing Sempai / Unfailing Sempai / Competitive Sempai / Silent Sempai / Bunny Sempai</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La présidente gonfle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hayasu Senpai / Shippai Shinai Senpai / Makenai Senpai / Silent Senpai / Bunny Senpai</title>
<summary>Growing Sempai: Sempai`s balloon art is a little bit lewd &lt;3
Unfailing Sempai: Sempai`s fist success!
Competitive Sempai: Sempai and Madara compete over Assistant!
Silent Sempai: Keep it quiet so Assistant doesn`t see!
Bunny Sempai: Magnificent misdirection!!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>786901</identifier>
<identifier>magical-sempai</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
