<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="14727" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>14</episodecount>
<startdate>2019-10-03</startdate>
<enddate>2019-12-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Honzuki no Gekokujou: Shisho ni Naru Tame ni wa Shudan o Erande Iraremasen</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Ascendance of a Bookworm: I`ll Do Anything to Become a Librarian!</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="short">Honzuki no Gekokujou</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Honzuki</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">本好きの下剋上 司書になるためには手段を選んでいられません</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Ascendance of a Bookworm</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Власть книжного червя</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">책벌레의 하극상: 사서가 되기 위해서라면 뭐든지 할 수 있어</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="official">هيمنة عثة كتب</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">书虫的下克上～为了成为图书管理员而不择手段～</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="15300" type="Sequel">Honzuki no Gekokujou: Shisho ni Naru Tame ni wa Shudan o Erande Iraremasen - Eustachius no Shitamachi Sennyuu Daisakusen / Corinna-sama no Otaku Houmon</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="5406" approval="18" total="28">Ookami to Koushinryou</anime>
<anime id="13871" approval="9" total="22">Tensei Shitara Slime Datta Ken</anime>
<anime id="14491" approval="5" total="19">Dr. Stone</anime>
<anime id="6187" approval="5" total="12">Kemono no Souja Erin</anime>
<anime id="9677" approval="3" total="14">Log Horizon</anime>
<anime id="9855" approval="3" total="13">Outbreak Company</anime>
<anime id="14750" approval="2" total="16">Choujin Koukousei-tachi wa Isekai demo Yoyuu de Ikinuku You Desu!</anime>
<anime id="10982" approval="2" total="14">Gate: Jieitai Kanochi nite, Kaku Tatakaeri</anime>
<anime id="12603" approval="2" total="6">Death March kara Hajimaru Isekai Kyousoukyoku</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="10">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="406148">Poor looking slow anime based on good manga. Watch it only if you can`t stand reading manga.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="37313">A successful improbable combination: Isekai meet World Masterpiece Theater. Recommended!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="567315">The very definition of a sleeper classic.

This show is good. Really good. If you need a show that is different from really anything else, has a wholesome vibe to it, and also educates you on development of literature and culture? This is the show for you.

There are a few other shows that try to do what it does, but this one does it the best, which is why it is a shame that it is not more recognized. Be ready for season 2.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="73747">The premise of being reincarnated in a different world has been done many times, but what sets this anime apart is the tone.  It was fun seeing normal day items being applied/created in a world that does not have those items. The supporting characters, pacing and enjoyment for this slice of life anime was nice.  If this series focused more on her ideas rather than her condition, I would`ve enjoyed this series more, but as it stands, this is a solid slice of life series.  I look forward to S2.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="470521">It is relaxing, it is something different and new. Try it out!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="668060">good story, characters. world is well fleshed out</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="625307">small scale, slow and heart warming.
superb worldbuilding on a very small scale. believable and engaging characters. and a smart and intriguing plot.
because Myne constantly tethers at the brink of death, the world gets expanded very slowly but thoroughly. comedic elements mostly stem from her obsession and the resulting bewilderment of the other characters. her sickly condition regularily pushes relationships with family and friends into the foreground. and despite all her struggles and setbacks she manages to cling onto hope. and thanks to her vast knowledge and ingenuity she slowly moves forward towards her dream.
mandatory for everyone who loves a good story. i hope this gets continued.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="325382">Loved it! This is an original take on the isekai genre in different ways. It also has a great story which progresses at a steady pace and manages to steer away from cliches.

A must see! Glad we don`t have to wait long for the sequal!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="431414">for me personally, best anime 2019</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://booklove-anime.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="4233" type="Chief Animation Direction">Yanagida Yoshiaki</name>
<name id="26189" type="Chief Animation Direction">Endou Emiko</name>
<name id="5808" type="Chief Animation Direction">Kaiya Toshihisa</name>
<name id="44779" type="Music">Michiru</name>
<name id="960" type="Animation Work">Ajia-dou</name>
<name id="5808" type="Character Design">Kaiya Toshihisa</name>
<name id="4233" type="Character Design">Yanagida Yoshiaki</name>
<name id="9774" type="Series Composition">Kunisawa Mariko</name>
<name id="49612" type="Original Work">Shiina Yuu</name>
<name id="1548" type="Direction">Hongou Mitsuru</name>
<name id="57580" type="Original Work">Kazuki Miya</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a fantasy light novel series written by http://anidb.net/cr57580 [Kazuki Miya] and illustrated by http://anidb.net/cr49612 [Shiina Yuu].
Motosu Urano, a book-loving college student and soon-to-be librarian, ends up crushed to death beneath a pile of books during an earthquake. With her dying breath, she wishes to be reincarnated in a world where she can read books forever. Fate, however, would have other plans, as she awakens in the body of a young girl named http://anidb.net/ch101309 [Myne] in a world of low literacy rate and where books are expensive, scarce, and only provided to nobility. Myne, retaining her memories from her previous life, decides to create and print her own books so that she can read them again.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="1040">8.33</permanent>
<temporary count="1046">8.04</temporary>
<review count="3">7.72</review>
</ratings>
<picture>235507.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22255</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>39468</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://booklove-anime.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Ascendance_of_a_Bookworm</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>本好きの下剋上</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5420</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>367462</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22245</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>anime_booklove</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="26">
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=xooRDoHcyIo</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=8AUVNYmxJ_c</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=KfPyxG-ZbFM</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ascendance-of-a-bookworm</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2876" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>religion</name>
<description>Religion is a collection of belief systems, cultural systems, and worldviews that relate humanity to spirituality and, sometimes, to moral values. Many religions have narratives, symbols, traditions and sacred histories that are intended to give meaning to life or to explain the origin of life or the universe. They tend to derive morality, ethics, religious laws or a preferred lifestyle from their ideas about the cosmos and human nature.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2926" parentid="2874" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>post-war</name>
<description>An armed conflict has ended not too long ago, devastation of the world or society is still evident.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3150" parentid="4522" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>social class issues</name>
<description>A character`s standing in society is cause of many issues. More generally, the society`s class structure is the source of many problems in the anime.
A common example is class division; a strong and rigid class division between rich/elite and poor/commoners, with the elites having disproportionately more privilege than the common class.
This can be applied not only when royalty and nobility are present, but also dystopian societies display often these divisions.
Another example is a division between employees and management, with employees akin to the common class, and management akin to the elite class.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3217" parentid="2864" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-17">
<name>working life</name>
<description>The life of someone actually working on a often less than glamorous job is depicted in this anime. The job is taxing and the pay is low, not really the dream job one would choose to work in.
Examples: Working as salesperson in a department store, or as a waitress in a family restaurant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3433" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false">
<name>power corrupts</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3528" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-05-13">
<name>reincarnation</name>
<description>One of the main characters was reborn in another body.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3663" parentid="6347" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-14">
<name>body takeover</name>
<description>A person`s body is taken over by some foreign intelligence. It`s not brainwashing, because they still have control of their own mind — but that`s all they have. Either they`ve been reduced to a spectator in their own body, or their soul has been booted out of their body entirely. Either way, the rest of the cast will soon find he`s not himself.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3797" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-01-13">
<name>trapped in the body of a child</name>
<description>For some reason, a character in this anime who is a late-teenager or an adult, has their mind trapped in the body of a child. E.g. a former late teenager or an adult is transformed into a child. This can be the result of magic, science, or otherwise.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3813" parentid="6185" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-06-23">
<name>winter</name>
<description>Coldest season of the year with ice and snow, everything is covered in a blanket of white.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4128" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-07-29">
<name>zero to hero</name>
<description>With his first appearance, this character is getting his ass kicked by nearly everyone, but as the plot continues, through training (mental or physical) or instant power-up, he changes into a killing/fighting/winning machine.
The best example: Makunouchi Ippo from Hajime no Ippo series.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4150" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-02-01">
<name>everybody is nice</name>
<description>All characters are nice in their own way; nobody has ill intentions to others. Even if a secondary character appears to be bad at the beginning, they will redeem themselves or become tamed/pacified/neutralized swiftly.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4271" parentid="2876" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-29">
<name>corrupt church</name>
<description>An official religion (not cult or sect) has become evil or was evil to begin with, and tends to be highly influential with political leaders, to strengthen / enforce the church`s power over the people.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4323" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-04">
<name>spacing out</name>
<description>A comedy element: The character starts to daydream or fantasize about some topic. The typical complete lack of reality makes the spacing out funny. Especially when the protagonist mumbles to himself / herself and friends hear this. Promptly teasing the possibly lovestruck and very embarrassed protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4522" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>social commentary</name>
<description>Social commentary is the act of rebelling against an individual, or a group of people by rhetorical means. This is most often done with the idea of implementing or promoting change by informing the general populace about a given problem and appealing to people’s sense of justice. (Source: Wikipedia)&#13;
&#13;
Since this is anime, usually, the mores of Japan and the Japanese society are scrutinised, but not restricted to that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4537" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-15">
<name>time skip</name>
<description>The plot features at least one skip or jump in time.
Example: A skip from the present into the past, or time skips in increments, e.g. every hour there is a time skip by a day.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4558" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-12">
<name>long time span</name>
<description>The anime spans a much longer than usual (for that genre) period of time, typically several years (possibly decades or even centuries).
Example: In a school setting this could mean the character development is followed from school through college right into working life and the founding of a family with children.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4577" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-19">
<name>family values</name>
<description>Family values are traditional or cultural values, generally conservative in nature, that pertain to the family`s structure, function, roles, beliefs, attitudes, and ideals. They encompass a set of beliefs, the most common of which is the classical "traditional family" involving a middle-class family with a breadwinner father and a homemaker mother, raising their biological children.
According to Merriam-Webster, family values are "values especially of a traditional or conservative kind which are held to promote the sound functioning of the family and to strengthen the fabric of society."
Source: English Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4642" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-03-08">
<name>economics</name>
<description>Economics is the social science that studies economic activity to gain an understanding of the processes that govern the production, distribution and consumption of goods and services in an economy.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>169811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4907" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-23">
<name>small town</name>
</tag>
<tag id="4951" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2018-03-22">
<name>age change</name>
<description>Because who wouldn`t like to be young/old again.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5335" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-04-10">
<name>dreams and reality</name>
<description>This genre of anime is typically set in both the world as we know it (reality) and a world of dreams, mythology or imagination.
Sometimes this dreamworld is actually real, sometimes it is not. Other times what we think is the real world is the dreamworld, and vice versa. They are not always easy to distinguish from each other, neither by the characters nor the viewer.
Whatever is real, and whatever is reality, both worlds are integral in shaping both the plot of this anime and the development of the characters.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5459" parentid="6243" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-10">
<name>poverty</name>
<description>It refers to the condition of not having the means to afford basic human needs.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5604" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-04">
<name>following one`s dream</name>
<description>No matter what the hardships may be, at least one of the protagonists in this anime is following her/his dream.
Examples: To become a professional athlete, a musician, a painter or the ruler of this world!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5768" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>intact family</name>
<description>The main character`s family is a so-called "nuclear family". Wherein both parents are alive and present in his or her life. This is actually relatively rare for anime, where "parental abandonment" is the norm.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5884" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-03-22">
<name>slow-paced</name>
<description>The story — including its characters and events — develop slowly.
May contain a weak continuity of plot and/or character development. 
Or may be a story telling device to increase the "sense of foreboding" in an anime with thriller or horror setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5948" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-18">
<name>visible aura</name>
<description>Characters are surrounded by a visible energy field usually representing inner strength, but not restricted to only that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6072" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-25">
<name>just as planned</name>
<description>A term usually used to describe a situation, where a seemingly smart and cunning villain sets up a plan that seems grand and impressive, but is actually long winding, ridiculous, and convoluted. And all of that just to trick his opponent(s), like the hero or anybody else, into doing things exactly as he planned. Suffice to say that the villain could have reached his goal by much shorter and easier means, it just wouldn`t seem as awesome anymore.
The phrase is also known as the original Japanese "keikaku doori" where keikaku stands translated for "plan" or "schedule", and doori for "in accordance with ..." or "following ...".
The phrase is a reference to http://anidb.net/ch301 [Yagami Light] from http://anidb.net/a4563 [Death Note], and his love for plans.</description>
<picurl>211219.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6075" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-12">
<name>educational</name>
<description>The entire series (at least a major part of it) is centred on a particular subject. Information is fed to the audience in a sublime manner. Most of the time an on-screen written comment by the narrator (or translator) can be seen, e.g. biological specimen, medicine, process, etc. Sometimes at the end of every episode’s closing song, a 20 seconds educational clip is presented.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6185" parentid="2612" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-11">
<name>season</name>
<description>A season is a division of the year, marked by changes in weather, ecology, and hours of daylight. Seasons result from the yearly orbit of the Earth around the Sun and the tilt of the Earth`s rotational axis relative to the plane of the orbit. In temperate and polar regions, the seasons are marked by changes in the intensity of sunlight that reaches the Earth`s surface, variations of which may cause animals to go into hibernation or to migrate, and plants to be dormant.
During May, June, and July, the northern hemisphere is exposed to more direct sunlight because the hemisphere faces the sun. The same is true of the southern hemisphere in November, December, and January. It is the tilt of the Earth that causes the Sun to be higher in the sky during the summer months which increases the solar flux. However, due to seasonal lag, June, July, and August are the hottest months in the northern hemisphere and December, January, and February are the hottest months in the southern hemisphere.
In temperate and subpolar regions, four calendar-based seasons (with their adjectives) are generally recognized: spring (vernal), summer (estival), autumn (autumnal), fall and winter (hibernal). Ecologists often use a six-season model for temperate climate regions that includes pre-spring (prevernal) and late summer (serotinal) as distinct seasons along with the traditional four.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162656.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6243" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-29">
<name>money</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6347" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-17">
<name>body and host</name>
<description>When a foreign entity like that of a symbiote, body snatcher, puppeteer parasite, or even a hacker (when regarding machines like robots and computers) enters/outright hijacks a body, the possessed subject becomes what is usually called: the host.
The basic purpose of the host varies on what the point was for it to have been hijacked in the first place. Sometimes it`s used as a disguise, other times it`s used as a decoy and destraction, even simply being used as a weapon and piece of armor that the possessor uses to cause sheer chaos and destruction, but sometimes... a host can be used for fetish fuel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6744" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-12-05">
<name>isekai</name>
<description>An isekai story is one in which the lead characters are transferred to and become stuck or trapped in another world, one completely different from the world they lived in up until the transfer. The new world is commonly a http://anidb.net/t2628 [fictional world], such as a http://anidb.net/t2838 [parallel world] or http://anidb.net/t2839 [virtual world]; other fictional world types can also apply. Once transferred, they must use the abilities and knowledge brought from their former world as well as any that may have been bestowed upon them by their brave new world. In some cases, they will seek and eventually find a way to return; in others, they will gleefully embrace their new life.
The misnomer "reverse isekai" is sometimes used to describe when characters from another world are sent to Earth, in an inaccurate usage likely born out of a mistaken notion that isekai is designed solely around transfers of earthlings. Rather, isekai is about the transfer itself; the identity of the origin and destination worlds, or the direction in which the transfer occurs, are not relevant. What defines isekai is that the characters are sent to another world, often but not always a parallel one, and that they generally cannot come back permanently without meeting a highly specific goal.
Broadly speaking, the following major characteristics, from most to least important, define the isekai theme:
1. The characters are trapped in a new world that is not the one they lived in up to then. This new world is usually unknown to them, at least in part, but that is not strictly mandatory. Generally speaking, while exceptions may apply, pure time travel does not qualify; there must be a change of location.
2. The trapping is, at least initially, permanent; there must be no quick and easy escape route back to their home world. A known way back may exist from the outset, but it requires effort, such as clearing the 100th floor of a difficult dungeon or defeating the demon lord; alternatively, it may be eventually found or developed.
3. The transfer to the isekai world was not intentional on the part of those being transferred. For example, it may have been orchestrated by a third party (malicious or otherwise), it may have been an accident, and the universe itself could be the actor responsible.</description>
<picurl>210952.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7674" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-06-27">
<name>reintroducing technology</name>
<description>Technology foreign to a world is (re)introduced by a third party.
This may happen because of time travel, spatial displacement, sleeping through armageddon and reawaking several hundred years in the future or other means.
Usually the technology itself is not actually developed by the person/machine/whatever introducing it, but they only have the knowledge by whatever means. "I read 500books about alchmey and now i know everyhting about oil and it`s applications."</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="101308" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-08-07">
<rating votes="10">7.09</rating>
<name>Ferdinand</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237056.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27" picture="26123.jpg">Hayami Shou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="101309" type="main character in" update="2019-12-29">
<rating votes="50">6.70</rating>
<name>Myne</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237046.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="516" picture="34813.jpg">Iguchi Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104911" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-08-07">
<rating votes="8">4.83</rating>
<name>Eva</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237048.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="157" picture="42784.jpg">Orikasa Fumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104912" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-08-07">
<rating votes="3">1.69</rating>
<name>Otto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237051.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="315" picture="70740.jpg">Hino Satoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104913" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-08-07">
<rating votes="8">3.39</rating>
<name>Gunter</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237049.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="267" picture="250262.jpg">Koyama Tsuyoshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104914" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-08-07">
<rating votes="4">3.38</rating>
<name>Gustav</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237054.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2340" picture="151335.jpg">Naka Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104915" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-11-03">
<rating votes="9">7.74</rating>
<name>Tuuli</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237047.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="423" picture="37799.jpg">Nakajima Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104916" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-08-07">
<rating votes="5">4.68</rating>
<name>Frida</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237055.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1614" picture="148394.jpg">Uchida Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104917" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-08-07">
<rating votes="8">5.43</rating>
<name>Benno</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237052.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104918" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-08-07">
<rating votes="6">3.00</rating>
<name>Marc</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237053.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="612" picture="79531.jpg">Maeno Tomoaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104919" type="main character in" update="2020-04-18">
<rating votes="6">5.35</rating>
<name>Lutz</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>237050.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3712" picture="240126.jpg">Tamura Mutsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106235" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-02-12">
<rating votes="3">1.62</rating>
<name>Ralph</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244417.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="55" picture="33603.jpg">Nabatame Hitomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106236" type="appears in" update="2020-02-12">
<rating votes="2">1.62</rating>
<name>Fey</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244418.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38634" picture="144425.jpg">Hanamori Yumiri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106527" type="appears in" update="2019-10-28">
<rating votes="1">1.15</rating>
<name>Fey no Tomodachi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240478.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32949" picture="243218.jpg">Hino Mari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106702" type="appears in" update="2019-11-03">
<rating votes="6">1.79</rating>
<name>Carla</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240719.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2355" picture="223496.jpg">Tachibana Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106703" type="appears in" update="2019-11-03">
<rating votes="1">1.15</rating>
<name>Gunter no Douryou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240724.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="46707" picture="190450.jpg">Okai Katsunori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106759" type="appears in" update="2019-11-07">
<rating votes="4">2.86</rating>
<name>Corinna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240836.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42697" picture="223257.jpg">Kinugawa Rika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106832" type="appears in" update="2019-11-11">
<rating votes="5">1.95</rating>
<name>Deed</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240979.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29684" picture="157183.jpg">Takeuchi Sou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107457" type="appears in" update="2019-12-14">
<rating votes="2">1.38</rating>
<name>Ilse</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>242074.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2069" picture="246996.jpg">Yamaguchi Mayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109094" type="appears in" update="2020-04-04">
<name>Uketsuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>245677.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="46707" picture="190450.jpg">Okai Katsunori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109095" type="appears in" update="2020-04-04">
<name>Monban</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>245678.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29684" picture="157183.jpg">Takeuchi Sou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109097" type="appears in" update="2020-04-04">
<rating votes="1">1.02</rating>
<name>Zasha</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>245684.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32949" picture="243218.jpg">Hino Mari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109098" type="appears in" update="2020-04-04">
<rating votes="1">1.02</rating>
<name>Sieg</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>245685.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39928" picture="181237.jpg">Yaehata Yukine</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109101" type="appears in" update="2020-04-04">
<name>Yutte</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>245689.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39928" picture="181237.jpg">Yaehata Yukine</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109102" type="appears in" update="2020-04-04">
<rating votes="2">1.38</rating>
<name>Jenny</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>245694.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="48909" picture="223240.jpg">Nagano Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109103" type="appears in" update="2020-04-04">
<rating votes="4">1.65</rating>
<name>Shindenchou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>245695.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2067" picture="186243.jpg">Hoshino Mitsuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="221299" update="2019-09-11">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-03-07</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">TVアニメ『本好きの下剋上 司書になるためには手段を選んでいられません』ティザーPV</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 01 (1:32)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">TV Anime "Honzuki no Gekokujou: Shisho ni Naru Tame ni wa Shudan o Erande Iraremasen" Teaser PV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="221300" update="2019-09-11">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2019-06-30</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">TVアニメ『本好きの下剋上 司書になるためには手段を選んでいられません』番宣CM</title>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 01 (0:15)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">TV Anime "Honzuki no Gekokujou: Shisho ni Naru Tame ni wa Shudan o Erande Iraremasen" Bansen CM</title>
</episode>
<episode id="221301" update="2019-09-11">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-09-09</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">TVアニメ『本好きの下剋上 司書になるためには手段を選んでいられません』本PV</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 02 (1:53)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">TV Anime "Honzuki no Gekokujou: Shisho ni Naru Tame ni wa Shudan o Erande Iraremasen" Hon PV</title>
</episode>
<episode id="221352" update="2020-01-11">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-10-03</airdate>
<rating votes="9">7.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">本のない世界</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A World Without Books</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un monde sans livres</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">عالم بلا كتب</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hon no Nai Sekai</title>
<summary>Motosu Urano, a college student and a bookworm of the highest order, loses her life in an avalanche of books and wakes up in another world as a sickly girl named Myne. Nevertheless confident that she can deal with any situation as long as she has books to read, she looks all over her new home for one, but doesn`t find any. To make matters worse, she couldn`t see any writing in town when out with her mother Eva. She realized that she found herself in a world with a low literacy rate, one where books were prohibitively expensive.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789360</identifier>
<identifier>ascendance-of-a-bookworm</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="221670" update="2020-01-11">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-10-10</airdate>
<rating votes="7">8.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">生活改善と石板</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Life Improvements and Slates</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Hausse du niveau de vie et ardoise</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">تحسينات نمط الحياة والألواح الأردوازية</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Seikatsu Kaizen to Sekiban</title>
<summary>Having learned how expensive books are in this world, Myne resolves to make books of her own. However, she soon finds out just how frail her new body is when she and her elder sister, Turi, decide to go to the gate to deliver something their father forgot—she can hardly take a few steps before running out of breath. But that`s when Lutz, a neighborhood kid the same age as Myne, offers his help. Myne is touched by this and soon makes it to the gate. There, Otto gives her his old slate, letting her experience the joy of writing once again.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789361</identifier>
<identifier>ascendance-of-a-bookworm</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="221671" update="2020-01-11">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-10-17</airdate>
<rating votes="8">9.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">冬のできごと</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Events of Winter</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Événements hivernaux</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">أحداث الشتاء</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fuyu no Dekigoto</title>
<summary>While everyone is snowed in by the harsh winter, Myne has a plan: a plan to craft pseudo-papyrus as the first step towards making a book. Meanwhile, Eva teaches Turi a bunch of skills in order to prepare her for her upcoming baptism in the summer. Myne is told to think about where she wants to apprentice, but as always, books are the only thing on her mind. As winter rolls on, however, the family bonds and grows closer together, and Myne hits upon the perfect gift to give Turi to wear on her baptism day.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789362</identifier>
<identifier>ascendance-of-a-bookworm</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="221672" update="2020-01-11">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-10-24</airdate>
<rating votes="7">9.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">初めての森と粘土板</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Forests and Clay Tablets</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Première excursion en forêt et tablettes d’argile</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">الغابات وألواح الصلصال</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajimete no Mori to Nendo Saka</title>
<summary>Spring has arrived, and Myne is raring to go make clay tablets in the forest. But first, she must convince her family that she can handle the journey.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789363</identifier>
<identifier>ascendance-of-a-bookworm</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="222499" update="2019-12-11">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-10-31</airdate>
<rating votes="7">8.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">洗礼式と不思議な熱</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Baptisms and Strange Fevers</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Baptême et fièvre mystérieuse</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">المعمودية والحمى الغريبة</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Senreishiki to Fushigi na Netsu</title>
<summary>Spring has arrived, and Main is raring to go make clay tablets in the forest. But first, she must convince her family that she can handle the journey.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789364</identifier>
<identifier>ascendance-of-a-bookworm</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="222500" update="2020-01-11">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-11-07</airdate>
<rating votes="6">9.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">会合</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Meeting</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L’entrevue</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">اجتماع</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kaigou</title>
<summary>Lutz and Myne prepare for the meeting with Otto. But Otto brings someone with him, turning a casual meeting into an interview that will decide both Lutz and Myne`s futures.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789365</identifier>
<identifier>ascendance-of-a-bookworm</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="222501" update="2020-01-11">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-11-14</airdate>
<rating votes="6">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">不信感の芽生え</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Seeds of Suspicion</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Éclosion de la suspicion</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">بذور الشك</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fushinkan no Mebae</title>
<summary>With the paper-making process about to begin, Myne can`t hide her excitement as she and Lutz go to meet Benno as per his invitation. He reveals that he is willing to arrange for all the equipment and materials they need to make the paper, but the ensuing conversation makes Lutz see Myne in a very different light.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789366</identifier>
<identifier>ascendance-of-a-bookworm</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="222502" update="2020-01-11">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-11-21</airdate>
<rating votes="7">9.53</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ルッツのマイン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Lutz`s Main</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La vraie Maïn de Lutz</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">ماين التي يعرفها لوتز</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Lutz no Myne</title>
<summary>As Myne and Lutz begin making their paper for real, Myne`s excitement gets the better of her, and Lutz`s suspicions come to a head. He resolves to talk about it after the paper is finished.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789367</identifier>
<identifier>ascendance-of-a-bookworm</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="223681" update="2019-10-31">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-10-03</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223682" update="2019-10-31">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-10-03</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="224313" update="2020-01-11">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-11-28</airdate>
<rating votes="7">8.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ギルド長の孫娘</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Guild Master`s Granddaughter</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La petite-fille du chef de la guilde</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">حفيدة رئيس النقابة</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Guild Chou no Magomusume</title>
<summary>Benno looks to have Myne and Lutz registered with the Merchant Guild, but the guild master proves to be an obstacle. This results in them making plans to meet Frieda, his granddaughter.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789368</identifier>
<identifier>ascendance-of-a-bookworm</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="224314" update="2020-01-11">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-12-05</airdate>
<rating votes="7">9.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">二度目の冬に向けて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">To the Second Winter</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Vers le deuxième hiver</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">إلى الشتاء الثاني</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nidome no Fuyu ni Mukete</title>
<summary>Myne learns from Frieda that the illness she has is called the Devouring, and that it will flare up if she ever feels anxiety or loses hope. Almost on cue, her fever starts acting up...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789369</identifier>
<identifier>ascendance-of-a-bookworm</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="224315" update="2020-01-11">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-12-12</airdate>
<rating votes="7">9.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">究極の選択と家族会議</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Life-or-Death Choices and Family Meetings</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Choix ultime et réunion de famille</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">حيارات الحياة أو الموت واجتماعات عائلية</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kyuukyoku no Sentaku to Kazoku Kaigi</title>
<summary>With Main collapses, everyone she knows comes together in a bid to save her life. But soon, she is faced with a life-or-death decision, one that she must discuss with her family.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789370</identifier>
<identifier>ascendance-of-a-bookworm</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="224316" update="2020-01-11">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-12-19</airdate>
<rating votes="6">9.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">洗礼式と神の楽園</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Baptisms and Divine Paradises</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Baptême et paradis des dieux</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">التعميد والجنان المقدسة</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Senreishiki to Kami no Rakuen</title>
<summary>The day of Main and Lutz`s baptism has arrived. Wearing a fancy dress and a new hair ornament, Main appears a clear standout from the rest of the kids, but soon she loses her way and finds herself in what she sees as heaven on earth.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789371</identifier>
<identifier>ascendance-of-a-bookworm</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="225167" update="2020-01-24">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-12-26</airdate>
<rating votes="6">8.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">巫女見習いという選択肢</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Choice to Be an Apprentice Priestess</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">J’ai décidé de devenir novice</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">خيار أن أكون كاهنة متدربة</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Miko Minarai to Iu Sentakushi</title>
<summary>When Main brings up wanting to become an apprentice priestess to her family, she learns the truth about the role and what it entails, and soon comes to realize that she is in for the fight of her life.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789372</identifier>
<identifier>ascendance-of-a-bookworm</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="225168" update="2020-01-24">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-12-26</airdate>
<rating votes="6">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">決着</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Conclusions</title>
<title xml:lang="ar">خاتمة</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kecchaku</title>
<summary>Main, Gunther, and Eva head to the cathedral for their fateful meeting, knowing that Main`s life is riding on a successful negotiation. But will things really go so smoothly for them?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>791469</identifier>
<identifier>ascendance-of-a-bookworm</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
