<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="14890" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2018-11-16</startdate>
<enddate>2018-11-16</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Nanatsu no Taizai: Imashime no Fukkatsu (2018)</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">七つの大罪 英雄たちは燥ぐ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">The Seven Deadly Sins: Revival of the Commandments (2018)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Nanatsu no Taizai: Eiyuu-tachi wa Hashagu</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">七つの大罪 戒めの復活 (2018)</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="11646" type="Parent Story">Nanatsu no Taizai: Imashime no Fukkatsu</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="241158">Fun series of mini stories much like the OVA of the first season.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<description>Note: Bundled with the 34th volume of the manga.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="75">5.22</permanent>
<temporary count="77">6.46</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>233294.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>38198</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>The_Seven_Deadly_Sins_(manga)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>七つの大罪_(漫画)</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="780" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-08-23">
<name>fairy</name>
<description>A fairy is a type of mythical being or legendary creature in European folklore, a form of spirit, often described as metaphysical, supernatural, or preternatural.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>206567.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1157" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>horny nosebleed</name>
<description>In Japanese media, healthy young men who have no other sexual outlet will often suffer nosebleeds upon seeing the naked female body, or even just a pair of well-filled panties.
The nosebleed is, of course, a visual shorthand/euphemism for sexual arousal. It is commonly interpreted that way for males and females, with little trickles of blood indicating mild arousal, and gushing fountains of blood indicating erection/extreme arousal in both sexes. It can also be interpreted as shorthand strictly for erections in males. In that case, when blood shoots from the nose explosively, and in ridiculous quantity, the implication would be an ejaculation.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>233513.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2774" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>spellcasting</name>
<description>The magic version of “call your attacks”. The protagonist will explicitly call out the magical incantation for the spells.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3635" parentid="2841" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-01-01">
<name>sea battles</name>
</tag>
<tag id="4052" parentid="2850" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-23">
<name>treasure hunting</name>
<description>A significant part of the anime centres on the protagonists` search for some obscure artefact or other treasure, an epic adventure and wild goose chase for something unusual and quite valuable.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4290" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>bath house visit</name>
<description>A sentou is a type of Japanese communal bath house where customers pay for entrance. Some Japanese find social importance in going to public baths, out of the theory that physical intimacy brings emotional intimacy, which is termed skinship in Japanese. Traditionally it is gender-segregated — men usually bathe only with men, and women with women. 
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in the nude and raise the DVD sales.
See also http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode], http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode], and http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].</description>
<picurl>160783.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4299" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-29">
<name>flashback</name>
<description>A flashback is a moment in which someone remembers events from their past. In fiction, flashbacks are used primarily to give insight into a character`s mind or to reveal information which had been previously kept from the audience. They normally consist essentially of new content; in some cases, they may also consist of short snippets of already displayed content, as in http://anidb.net/ch23266 [Okabe Rintarou]`s flashbacks in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate], but even in these cases the flashbacks are used to look into what the character is thinking. As such, they are different from and should not be confused with recaps, which are old content being shown again for no particular purpose other than padding or reminding the audience of the events up to that point. As a rule of thumb, to qualify as a flashback, the scene must advance the show`s content in some way or form; anything else is just a recap.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5846" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-26">
<name>beach visit</name>
<description>Every anime has to have them, episodes in which the characters for whatever reason end up going to the sea, ocean, random island or the local pond.
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in swimsuits and raise the DVD sales.
The cheap version is the http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].
Other marginally less used variants of this are the http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode] and the http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], used when it is too cold for a beach/pool episode.
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene].</description>
<picurl>160805.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6093" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-08">
<name>short story collection</name>
<description>An anthology is a collection of literary works chosen by the compiler. It may be a collection of poems, short stories, plays, songs, or excerpts by different authors.
An omnibus format release is not just one continuous story, but several short stories. They may feature a different cast between each story, and the authors may differ.
In genre fiction, anthology is used to categorize collections of shorter works such as short stories and short novels, by different authors, each featuring unrelated casts of characters and settings, and usually collected into a single volume for publication. The complete collections of works are often called complete works or Opera Omnia (Latin language equivalent).
Source: EN Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="67152" type="main character in" update="2018-01-07">
<rating votes="69">7.53</rating>
<name>Meliodas</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Meliodas is the captain of the http://anidb.net/ch70760 [Seven Deadly Sins] and the Dragon`s Sin of Wrath. He is the owner of the renowned tavern http://anidb.net/ch70764 [Boar Hat], and the main protagonist of the series. His Sacred Treasure is the Demon Sword Lostvayne and his inherent power is Full Counter. He is more than 3000 years old.
Source: Nanatsu no Taizai Wikia</description>
<picture>160542.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1678" picture="68277.jpg">Kaji Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67153" type="main character in" update="2018-03-03">
<rating votes="84">6.76</rating>
<name>Elizabeth Liones</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>214077.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34626" picture="144409.jpg">Amamiya Sora</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67154" type="main character in" update="2016-01-25">
<rating votes="147">6.98</rating>
<name>Hawk</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>160545.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20806" picture="182700.jpg">Kuno Misaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67155" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-03-03">
<rating votes="108">8.05</rating>
<name>Diane</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Diane is a member of the http://anidb.net/ch70760 [Seven Deadly Sins] and is known as the Serpent`s Sin of Envy. She is a member of the Giant Clan, and is thus much larger than ordinary people, including her fellow Deadly Sins. Her Sacred Treasure is the War Hammer Gideon, which she uses in conjunction with her inherent power, Creation. She is approximately 750 years old.
Source: Nanatsu no Taizai Wikia</description>
<picture>214078.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1625" picture="226033.jpg">Yuuki Aoi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67156" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-01-25">
<rating votes="94">8.05</rating>
<name>Ban</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>163863.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="644" picture="205640.jpg">Suzuki Tatsuhisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="67157" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-01-25">
<rating votes="25">4.60</rating>
<name>Gilthunder</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>162940.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="255" picture="40713.jpg">Miyano Mamoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="68859" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-11-22">
<rating votes="53">5.72</rating>
<name>King</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>King is a member of the http://anidb.net/ch70760 [Seven Deadly Sins] and is known as the Grizzly`s Sin of Sloth. His real name is Fairy King Harlequin for he protects the Fairy King`s Forest and the rest of the Fairy Realm. His Sacred Treasure is the Spirit Spear Chastiefol, which he uses in conjunction with his inherent power, Disaster. He is approximately 1300 years old.
Source: Nanatsu no Taizai Wikia</description>
<picture>68141.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="14" picture="75503.jpg">Fukuyama Jun</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70303" type="secondary cast in" update="2016-01-25">
<rating votes="28">5.55</rating>
<name>Guila</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>164198.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="101" picture="16709.jpg">Ise Mariya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70305" type="appears in" update="2016-01-25">
<rating votes="18">6.76</rating>
<name>Howzer</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>165232.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2225" picture="192115.jpg">Kimura Ryouhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70641" type="appears in" update="2015-04-01">
<name>Baltra Liones</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>171207.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="292" picture="68967.jpg">Nishi Rintarou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70752" type="main character in" update="2019-11-22">
<rating votes="83">8.33</rating>
<name>Merlin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>68140.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="227" picture="205854.jpg">Sakamoto Maaya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70753" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-03-03">
<rating votes="61">7.49</rating>
<name>Gowther</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>214080.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42704" picture="212008.jpg">Takagi Yuuhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70754" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-04-22">
<rating votes="66">8.58</rating>
<name>Escanor</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>216565.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45" picture="44970.jpg">Sugita Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70755" type="appears in" update="2015-02-25">
<name>Zaratras</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>162930.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="244" picture="23860.jpg">Koyama Rikiya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70756" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-02-25">
<rating votes="14">5.14</rating>
<name>Veronica Liones</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>165234.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12266" picture="56026.jpg">Kanemoto Hisako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70814" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-02-25">
<rating votes="6">6.07</rating>
<name>Griamore</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>165233.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="225" picture="17044.jpg">Sakurai Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="73423" type="appears in" update="2018-01-07">
<rating votes="4">2.33</rating>
<name>Helbram</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch70624 [Helbram] in his original Fairy form has a smaller body with a pair of wings. He has a youthful appearance with periorbital dark circles around his eyes. He wears a long sleeved shirt accessorized with a sunflower-like collar. He is approximately 1300 years old.
Source: Nanatsu no Taizai Wikia</description>
<picture>169096.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="224" picture="79056.jpg">Kamiya Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="94155" type="secondary cast in" update="2018-03-03">
<name>Poula</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>214015.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40047" picture="225902.jpg">Yano Shougo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="96390" type="appears in" update="2018-09-14">
<name>Griamore (Kodomo)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch70814 [Griamore`s] appearance after training in the Tower of Trials.</description>
<picture>219804.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39277" picture="150138.jpg">Hara Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102642" type="appears in" update="2019-05-05">
<name>Gilthunder (Kodomo)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>233295.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10380" picture="38227.jpg">Yamamoto Kazutomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="102643" type="appears in" update="2019-05-05">
<name>Howzer (Kodomo)</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>233296.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9365" picture="34581.jpg">Kokuryuu Sachi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="216552" update="2019-05-05">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2018-11-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">戦え!!残飯処理騎士団長 / ハダカのココロ / ハーレクインとヘルブラム / 大罪Vacation</title>
<title xml:lang="en">OAD</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tatakae!! Zanpan Shori Kishi Danchou / Hadaka no Kokoro / Harlequin to Helbram / Taizai Vacation</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
