<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="14968" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2019-10-06</startdate>
<enddate>2019-12-29</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Bokutachi wa Benkyou ga Dekinai!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">We Never Learn: Bokuben 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">bokuben2</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ぼくたちは勉強ができない!</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">We Never Learn!: Bokuben</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">우리는 공부를 못해!</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">我们真的学不来！</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="14289" type="Prequel">Bokutachi wa Benkyou ga Dekinai</anime>
</relatedanime>
<recommendations total="3">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="813396">Pretty good for a romcom, in this series they do an anime original ending which spoiled the "ending" of the manga before they decided they were going to do endings for all the main girls. Hopefully we can expect new seasons in the future that depict the endings of the other girls in the series; because there are easily better endings in planning...Hopefully...Maybe.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="748358">After I watched the first season of this anime, I praised it as an enjoyable, light-hearted series with nice, balanced and relatable characters, a decent pace and neat production values. With this second season, most of the good things stayed the same. The characters were still as good as ever, the plot continued to its conclusion with a good pace, and animation, voice acting and comedy remained strong. However, the series as a whole was also more balanced than the first season, implying less innovation, and focusing more on the harem aspect than on the ever-scarce romantic aspect, including less passionate moments and more light ecchi moments. Still, I liked, and felt it was a good combination. Its ending was nice and heartwarming, however strictly open harem, so there`s that.

A good anime to close 2019, in my opinion. Recommended for fans of the first season.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.boku-ben.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="10922" type="Music">Nakayama Masato</name>
<name id="56016" type="Animation Work">Arvo Animation</name>
<name id="821" type="Animation Work">Silver</name>
<name id="8038" type="Character Design">Sasaki Masakatsu</name>
<name id="8020" type="Series Composition">Zappa Gou</name>
<name id="43695" type="Original Work">Tsutsui Taishi</name>
<name id="1797" type="Direction">Iwasaki Yoshiaki</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch99452 [Yuiga Nariyuki] is in his last and most painful year of high school. In order to gain the "special VIP recommendation" which would grant him a full scholarship to college, he becomes a tutor for the three super-geniuses of the academy, http://anidb.net/ch99451 [Furuhashi Fumino], http://anidb.net/ch99454 [Ogata Rizu], and http://anidb.net/ch99453 [Takemoto Uruka]. Despite being completely clueless outside of their pet subjects, will they be able to pass the entrance exams to the school of their choice with Nariyuki`s guidance!? On top of that, he also has to deal with http://anidb.net/ch100011 [Kirisu Mafuyu], their seemingly cold-blooded but extremely klutzy teacher, and http://anidb.net/ch100010 [Kominami Asumi], an alum who works as a maid while trying to get into medical school.
Now, Nariyuki and his students are entering the final stretch of studying before the entrance exams! Meanwhile, could there be signs of love? The romantic comedy featuring our prodigies who never learn returns to the stage as they continue studying and, perhaps, they may even find love!
Source: Official website</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="421">5.71</permanent>
<temporary count="425">6.91</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>238054.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22278</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>40004</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.boku-ben.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>https://bokuben-anime.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>We_Never_Learn</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ぼくたちは勉強ができない</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5416</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>369009</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22306</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>bokuben_anime</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>we-never-learn-bokuben</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1157" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>horny nosebleed</name>
<description>In Japanese media, healthy young men who have no other sexual outlet will often suffer nosebleeds upon seeing the naked female body, or even just a pair of well-filled panties.
The nosebleed is, of course, a visual shorthand/euphemism for sexual arousal. It is commonly interpreted that way for males and females, with little trickles of blood indicating mild arousal, and gushing fountains of blood indicating erection/extreme arousal in both sexes. It can also be interpreted as shorthand strictly for erections in males. In that case, when blood shoots from the nose explosively, and in ridiculous quantity, the implication would be an ejaculation.
Source: TVTrope</description>
<picurl>233513.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1241" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-18">
<name>swimming</name>
<description>Swimming is an individual or team sport that involves using arms and legs to move the body through water. Typically, the sport takes place in pools or in open water. Competitive swimming is one of the most popular Olympic sports, with events in butterfly, backstroke, breaststroke, freestyle, and individual medley. In addition to these individual events, swimmers take part in relays.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>208479.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1471" parentid="2653" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-19">
<name>bad cooking</name>
<description>The character is hopelessly terrible at cooking, and any attempts he or she makes at making even the simplest dishes are spectacular failures.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2056" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-09-13">
<name>cosplaying</name>
<description>This character likes to cosplay.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2072" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>maid</name>
<description>A maid is a female employed in domestic service. They usually wear uniforms. Since their nature is to be obedient and serve their goshujin-sama (master), they are one of the most desired types of women in Japan, a dream of every Japanese man, particularly http://anidb.net/t1133 [otaku]. Often seen in so-called Maid Cafes in Akihabara, where male customers can for a little time enjoy the feeling of being served by a woman. The male gender opposite is the butler.</description>
<picurl>4954.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2652" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super deformed</name>
<description>A caricature style often seen in anime when the character shows extreme emotions, like fear, anger, happiness, surprise, or shame. Seen as cute, as part of humorous comedy. The character`s http://anidb.net/t4055 [face suddenly turns into a simplified version], the body will usually also deform into that of a small child (oversized head, short limbs, extra-large tears).</description>
<picurl>65692.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2816" parentid="2856" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>sexual fantasies</name>
<description>One or more characters in this anime let their imaginations run wild thinking about another character.
Yes, they are thinking about sex, and in an ecchi anime these thoughts are often perverted, leading to a nosebleed. But it may also be romanticising simply being husband and wife, and everything that implies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2820" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>wardrobe malfunction</name>
<description>A euphemistic term for an embarrassing display of a body part when clothing droops, falls, or is torn. Wikipedia: "Super Bowl XXXVIII half-time show" for more details.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2855" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-03">
<name>under one roof</name>
<description>For some reason or another, the main protagonist (e.g. male in harem / female in reverse-harem) is living together with many other characters of the opposite-gender, all under the same roof (in the same dwelling unit).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2859" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>harem</name>
<description>Harem is an entertainment-related trope which is characterized by three or more characters, normally female, who for some reason are in the presence and under the influence of one character, generally male, according to a few genre-defining guidelines; here it will be assumed, for simplicity of language, that the harem lead is a male character and the members are female characters. Though that is the rule, there are exceptions; a story in which there is one female character and several male characters is normally called a "http://anidb.net/t2792 [reverse harem]", or sometimes also "male harem". Aside from the swapping of the characters` genders, the trope`s details are mostly the same, with the majority of the changes relating to the differences in behavior between men and women of the characters` age range. It is also possible to create harems with homosexual relationships, again with very few changes to the main antics themselves. The harem may not have more than only one lead, as that would be a love polygon, or less than three members, as one would form a couple and two would make a love triangle.
As a defining rule of harem, the interactions between the lead and each of the individual members are filled with romantically or sexually loaded content, either implicitly, through innuendo or subtext, or explicitly, through text or actions, and those actions are a key plot element. Generally, the female characters` looks and personalities will vary a lot among the ones present in one single series, but quite rarely will they actually differ from the common stock archetypes, which are known, well-defined, and easy to copy; for this reason, the genre as a whole is often considered repetitive. Usually, the characters involved directly in this trope are in the late teenager to young adult age range, but that is not mandatory. Sexually charged behavior on the lead`s part pretty much can`t be avoided, and it`s typical to see him stamped as a pervert by some or all of the members, regardless of whether he is one; the sexual tones also applies to the depiction of the harem members, often leading the genre to labeled sexist. The lead will often suffer very violent retribution for his behavior, which has attracted criticism of gratuitous violence as well.
Most of the harem members will be romantically or sometimes sexually interested in the one male character, and in him alone; that, however, is not an absolute rule, and indeed sometimes none of the female characters are really interested at first, so the protagonist has to build relationships with them from scratch. That idea comes in large part from visual novels; it is quite common for visual novels to revolve around controlling the male lead and have him build relationships with either as many female characters as possible or with one of them, the latter being more common for visual novels with branched story paths; a large portion of those visual novels also feature erotic content, which may be hard to adapt to TV series. It may be also possible that the harem is only a support to the existing or predictable relationship between the lead and the most important member; additionally, the lead may end up in relationships with most or all of the harem members, with the agreement of all, in a setting normally called "harem ending".</description>
<picurl>94602.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2893" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>female teacher</name>
<description>Any kind of female teacher will do, even if she only does home visits. Female teachers imply mature women (even if they sometimes look like schoolgirls) dressed in what women would typically wear when doing official business (like a blouse, pinstripe dress with side front slit), but of course, not limited to that. Furthermore, school nurses also count as female teachers unless they`re actually wearing a nurse outfit, which they almost never are.
Almost completely exclusive to hentai animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2894" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-13">
<name>female student</name>
<description>Pretty much exclusive to hentai shows only unless an ecchi show has implied sex and/or a strong indicator of nudity. A character is considered a student if she goes to school, doesn`t matter if it`s high school, college or homeschooling, but she should be of appropriate age for a student; a housewife going to college should not get this category.</description>
<picurl>210611.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3092" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-03-02">
<name>important haircut</name>
<description>When a character cuts off his or her hair, it often symbolizes a rite of passage or bout of character growth. A princess striking out on an adventure, or a new recruit at boot camp, for instance. Hair is something that takes time and effort to grow, so parting with it voluntarily can be a powerful act.
This is particularly a big deal when women get haircuts. Yet in fiction, even an accidental hair slicing can leave a character with a surprisingly even cut.
In many religions (Western Christianity, Ancient Egyptian religion, and others) priests and/or monks cut/shave their hair. Roman Catholic nuns also tend to cut and mantain their hair short under their veils when they enter the nunneries. The cutting of one`s own hair is also a part of Buddhist mythology, specifically something done by Siddhartha himself early on in his path to enlightenment, so anime examples might draw from this as an allusion. There are also some cultures, including Native American and many Asians, where a person would cut his or her hair as an act of grief, disgrace, or even rebellion. In the Confucian tradition, hair (like the rest of your body) is considered a gift from your parents and may not be damaged without a very good reason. Furthermore, prisoners and psychiatric patients commonly have their heads shaved, often to prevent the spread of lice, but sometimes also as a demeaning measure.
Source: TVTRope</description>
<picurl>169641.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3119" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-24">
<name>restaurant</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3185" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-27">
<name>wordplay</name>
<description>The characters play with words. 
E.g. purposely or accidentally use similar-sounding but wrongly applied words in the Japanese original, leading to supposedly funny misunderstandings and confusion.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3606" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-11">
<name>family without father</name>
<description>For some reason the protagonists father is no longer among the living. The much too early death was due to sickness or accident.
This plot device adds a certain degree of tragedy to the anime and usually has repercussions on the rest of the family: Possibly the grieve-stricken mother and children barely function as humans. Or adding emphasis to the overall financial predicament of the family, should the father have been the money earner.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3694" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-23">
<name>dear mother in heaven</name>
<description>A form of veneration of ancestors, where people call upon their ancestors for help, advice and similar in their everyday life like in other cultures upon God, Jesus, the Virgin Mary or various saints. The veneration of the spirit`s of one`s ancestors is an integral part of Japanese culture.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3947" parentid="2869" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-04">
<name>cram school</name>
<description>Cram schools ("juku" in Japan) are specialized schools that train their students to meet particular goals, most commonly to pass the entrance examinations of high schools or universities. The English name is derived from the slang term "cramming", meaning to study hard or to study a large amount of material in a short period of time.
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3977" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-29">
<name>dialogue driven</name>
<description>A dialogue driven show has its story advanced by dialogue, with action being of much lower priority, and relies heavily on conversations between characters.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4030" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-04-13">
<name>mental cinema</name>
<description>The ability to imagine all kinds of things, as if they were real.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4055" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>facial distortion</name>
<description>The characters face are exaggerated into a misshape, deformed, and almost warped. Used as comedy element to express extreme mood swings.
Differing from "http://anidb.net/t2652 [Super Deformed]", here only the face changes to an extreme degree, not the whole body of the protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4455" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>dysfunctional family</name>
<description>When the nuclear family (Mother, Father and child(ren)) goes boom due to conflicts between family members, sometimes resulting in the breakup of the family or even violence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4669" parentid="6249" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-27">
<name>parenting</name>
<description>This anime is about parenting and its many challenges.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4729" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-07-06">
<name>colour coded</name>
<description>Every single character on the main cast has a unique hair colour to help less perceptive viewers distiguish between them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5420" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-03-24">
<name>it`s funny because they`re poor</name>
<description>A character`s relative lack of wealth is used as a source of humour.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5518" parentid="7199" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-03">
<name>flat chest jokes</name>
<description>Jokes about the (supposedly or actually) flat chest of a character.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5604" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-04">
<name>following one`s dream</name>
<description>No matter what the hardships may be, at least one of the protagonists in this anime is following her/his dream.
Examples: To become a professional athlete, a musician, a painter or the ruler of this world!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5790" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-30">
<name>family without mother</name>
<description>For some reason, the protagonist`s mother is no longer among the living. The much-too-early death was due to sickness or accident.
This plot device adds a certain degree of tragedy to the anime, and usually has repercussions on the rest of the family. For example: the grief-stricken father and children barely function as humans; the oldest daughter has an extra burden of raising the other children, additional emphasis is given to the only female child in the family, i.e. with bishounen brother and dad in a shoujo setting.
In rare cases the mother may still be alive, just not living with the rest of the family presently, i.e. on some quest or job and gone for a long time.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6034" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>Engrish</name>
<description>Engrish is actually a mispronunciation of English, as can be the result of someone, who does not have English as their primary language of origin (such as Japanese or Chinese). Occasionally characters in the original Japanese dialogue version of an anime will speak in English... however; this often still requires the assistance of subtitles, for while the words are meant to be said in English, the sentence structure and letter pronunciation may still be strongly related to the person’s primary language.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6097" parentid="4064" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>3D CG animation</name>
<description>Abbreviation for "three-dimensional computer generated animation" or "computer graphics" (CGI). The traditional 2D art is enhanced by 3D imagery developed through computer modeling software. Done in the right way, this union of 3D in a 2D animated world can be a very beautiful relationship.
The difference lies in what lacks the traditional 2D animation all together and may give term to something produced entirely with 3D graphics (such as the 2006 remake of "Appleseed" , 2007`s "Vexille", the 2008 addition to the "Biohazard" series and the more well known "Final Fantasy: The Spirits Within" and "Advent Children").</description>
<picurl>208569.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7199" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-12">
<name>sexual humour</name>
<description>Sexual humour is prevalent in this anime. It often involves cheeky or crude sexual language, with innuendos and jokes about the female or male genitalia. Often, such anime also have http://anidb.net/t2856 [ecchi] elements to them.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="99451" type="main character in" update="2018-12-29">
<rating votes="60">7.84</rating>
<name>Furuhashi Fumino</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>228281.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="33578" picture="225440.jpg">Shiraishi Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99452" type="main character in" update="2018-12-29">
<rating votes="11">7.54</rating>
<name>Yuiga Nariyuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>228284.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29979" picture="223317.jpg">Oosaka Ryouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99453" type="main character in" update="2018-12-29">
<rating votes="35">6.11</rating>
<name>Takemoto Uruka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>228283.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="55692" picture="224737.jpg">Suzushiro Sayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="99454" type="main character in" update="2019-06-02">
<rating votes="26">6.36</rating>
<name>Ogata Rizu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>228282.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43492" picture="232251.jpg">Tomita Miyu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100010" type="main character in" update="2020-05-03">
<rating votes="23">6.10</rating>
<name>Kominami Asumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>228279.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="44228" picture="222798.jpg">Asahina Madoka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="100011" type="main character in" update="2019-12-11">
<rating votes="41">6.75</rating>
<name>Kirisu Mafuyu</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>228280.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34901" picture="130616.jpg">Lynn</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103979" type="appears in" update="2020-02-02">
<rating votes="9">5.37</rating>
<name>Yuiga Mizuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244209.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="39199" picture="242466.jpg">Kouno Marika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103981" type="appears in" update="2019-06-28">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Gakuenchou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>235510.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2585" picture="22579.jpg">Tsuchida Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103982" type="appears in" update="2019-06-28">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Rizu no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>235511.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2192" picture="196332.jpg">Kashii Shouto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103988" type="appears in" update="2019-06-28">
<rating votes="2">6.70</rating>
<name>Umihara Chinami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>235512.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="479" picture="222800.jpg">Asumi Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103989" type="appears in" update="2020-01-22">
<rating votes="3">6.50</rating>
<name>Kawase Ayuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>243940.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34504" picture="200900.jpg">Taichi You</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103990" type="appears in" update="2019-06-28">
<rating votes="15">5.86</rating>
<name>Sekijou Sawako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>235517.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34449" picture="171791.jpg">Oonishi Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103991" type="appears in" update="2019-06-28">
<rating votes="3">5.35</rating>
<name>Oomori Kanade</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>235515.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="103992" type="appears in" update="2019-06-28">
<rating votes="3">5.35</rating>
<name>Kobayashi Haruma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>235516.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23529" picture="178469.jpg">Kawanishi Kengo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103994" type="appears in" update="2019-06-28">
<rating votes="2">5.71</rating>
<name>Chono</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>235519.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37089" picture="228978.jpg">Suzuki Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103995" type="appears in" update="2019-06-28">
<rating votes="1">7.63</rating>
<name>Kashima</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>235520.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38634" picture="144425.jpg">Hanamori Yumiri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103996" type="appears in" update="2019-06-28">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Inomori</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>235521.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="53513" picture="229081.jpg">Maeda Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103997" type="appears in" update="2019-06-28">
<rating votes="2">4.85</rating>
<name>Tenchou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>235522.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32751" picture="157891.jpg">Tanezaki Atsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103998" type="appears in" update="2019-06-28">
<rating votes="3">6.67</rating>
<name>Yuiga Hanae</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>235523.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12" picture="184301.jpg">Kawasumi Ayako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="103999" type="appears in" update="2019-06-28">
<rating votes="4">6.55</rating>
<name>Yuiga Hazuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>235524.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="57014" picture="239562.jpg">Mineda Mayu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104000" type="appears in" update="2019-06-28">
<rating votes="4">6.55</rating>
<name>Yuiga Kazuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>235525.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="45121" picture="225365.jpg">Fujiwara Natsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104002" type="appears in" update="2020-01-22">
<rating votes="4">6.39</rating>
<name>Machiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>243939.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="46676" picture="215636.jpg">Akao Hikaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104003" type="appears in" update="2020-02-02">
<rating votes="2">4.42</rating>
<name>Ikeda</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244210.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="47716" picture="194415.jpg">Ishibashi Momo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="104234" type="appears in" update="2020-01-26">
<rating votes="1">3.80</rating>
<name>Furuhashi Shizuru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244041.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="61" picture="58663.jpg">Horie Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107143" type="appears in" update="2019-11-25">
<name>Uruka no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>241514.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29972" picture="240161.jpg">Ishigami Shizuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108104" type="appears in" update="2020-01-22">
<name>Karasuma</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>243937.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="356" picture="224408.jpg">Toyoguchi Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108105" type="appears in" update="2020-01-22">
<name>Makikami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>243938.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32397" picture="151686.jpg">Nakazato Nozomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108106" type="appears in" update="2020-01-22">
<name>Himura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>243941.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38354" picture="150733.jpg">Kuwahara Yuuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108107" type="appears in" update="2020-01-22">
<name>Mikuni</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>243942.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43430" picture="243752.jpg">Koga Aoi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108108" type="appears in" update="2020-01-22">
<name>Takizawa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>243943.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23484" picture="151668.jpg">Keichou Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108150" type="appears in" update="2020-01-26">
<rating votes="2">1.59</rating>
<name>Furuhashi Reiji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244040.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="353" picture="17192.jpg">Midorikawa Hikaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108239" type="appears in" update="2020-02-02">
<name>Satou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244211.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="29961" picture="79252.jpg">Tezuka Hiromichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108240" type="appears in" update="2020-02-02">
<name>Suzuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244212.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10906" picture="200861.jpg">Yanagita Jun`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108241" type="appears in" update="2020-02-02">
<name>Full Pure</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244214.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="46283" picture="235990.jpg">Haruno Anzu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108242" type="appears in" update="2020-02-02">
<name>Kana no Ane</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244215.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="53526" picture="242924.jpg">Hasegawa Ikumi</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="221505" update="2019-10-06">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-10-06</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天才と彼はその[x]なる判定に銘々慮る</title>
<title xml:lang="en">He and a Genius Each Consider a Decision Pertaining to X</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tensai to Kare wa Sono [x] Naru Hantei ni Meimei Omonbakaru</title>
<summary>Even during summer vacation, Nariyuki and the girls have to study hard at cram school. One day, Rizu gets an abysmal “E” on one of her tests. Depressed, she shares her grade with the other girls, which causes an uproar. That`s because they mistakenly think she`s telling them her bra size.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789503</identifier>
<identifier>we-never-learn-bokuben</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="221506" update="2019-10-12">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-10-13</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">先人の誇りは時に[x]どもの事情と背反する</title>
<title xml:lang="en">At Times, an Elder`s Pride Is in Direct Opposition to X`s Circumstances</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Senjin no Hokori wa Toki ni [x] Domo no Jijou to Haihan Suru</title>
<summary>The maid café where Asumi works is starting a housekeeping service. Nariyuki and Asumi go together to their first clients, who turn out to be people they know, like Mafuyu and Uruka.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789504</identifier>
<identifier>we-never-learn-bokuben</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="221507" update="2019-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-10-20</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">天才は変遷する季節と[x]模様に憂う</title>
<title xml:lang="en">With the Changing Seasons, a Genius Experiences the Sorrow of X</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tensai wa Hensen Suru Kisetsu to [x] Moyou ni Ureu</title>
<summary>Thanks to her dad, Rizu accidentally cuts her bangs way too short. At first she doesn’t care, but gets more embarrassed until she hides her face from Nariyuki and dons a mask.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789505</identifier>
<identifier>we-never-learn-bokuben</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="221508" update="2019-10-27">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-10-27</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">時に天才は限定された[x]において奮闘する</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sometimes a Genius Struggles with a Limited X</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Toki ni Tensai wa Gentei Sareta [x] ni Oite Funtou Suru</title>
<summary>At the library, a beautiful girl Nariyuki has never seen before sits next to him when he`s studying. He`s nervous that he`s getting hit on, not realizing the girl is actually Rizu, who has changed her hairstyle at a salon.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789506</identifier>
<identifier>we-never-learn-bokuben</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="222780" update="2019-11-03">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-11-03</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">心尽くしの賜物は時に[x]の錯綜となる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Heartfelt Gift Sometimes Becomes a Complicated X</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kokorozukushi no Tamamono wa Toki ni [x] no Sakusou to Naru</title>
<summary>At Nariyuki`s house, Fumino is on her way out after a study session when he gives her a birthday present. However, when Fumino opens it, she`s startled to find a bra. What was Nariyuki thinking?!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>789507</identifier>
<identifier>we-never-learn-bokuben</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="222781" update="2019-11-10">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-11-10</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">彼らは安んぞ面する[x]の志を知らんや</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Wherefore Might They Fathom the Aspirations of the Immediate X</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Karera wa Yasunzo Mensuru [x] no Kokorozashi o Shiran ya</title>
<summary>When Mafuyu can`t use the bathtub in her apartment, she goes to a neighborhood bathhouse. On the way, she encounters Asumi and Nariyuki, and ends up in the sauna with Asumi. It`s so hot that the two get punchy.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>790340</identifier>
<identifier>we-never-learn-bokuben</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="222782" update="2019-11-17">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-11-17</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">人知れず天才は彼らの忖度に[x]する</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Genius Secretly Responds with X to Their Conjectures</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hitoshirezu Tensai wa Karera no Sontaku ni [x] Suru</title>
<summary>Nariyuki, Rizu, and Sawako go to an open campus event. Nariyuki and Sawako both want the other to become closer to Rizu, so they use every excuse in the book to get away so they can leave the other with Rizu.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>790341</identifier>
<identifier>we-never-learn-bokuben</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="222783" update="2020-01-12">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-11-24</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゆく[x]の流れは絶えずして...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Flow of X Never Ends...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuku [x] no Nagare wa Taezu Shite...</title>
<summary>Nariyuki is on the verge of failing Physical Education! Uruka tries teaching him how to swim, but she`s so bad at teaching that it doesn`t do any good.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>790342</identifier>
<identifier>we-never-learn-bokuben</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="222784" update="2019-10-19">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-10-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="222785" update="2019-10-19">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2019-10-06</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.30</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="224390" update="2020-01-12">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-12-01</airdate>
<rating votes="7">7.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">最愛の星に[x]の名を(前編)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Star of Ultimate Love and the Name of X, Part 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saiai no Hoshi ni [x] no Na o (Zenpen)</title>
<summary>Parent-teacher conferences are being held at Ichinose Academy. Nariyuki intends to decide his major based on what would be best for his family. Meanwhile, that math professor appears at the Academy.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>790343</identifier>
<identifier>we-never-learn-bokuben</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="224391" update="2020-01-12">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-12-08</airdate>
<rating votes="7">8.04</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">最愛の星に[x]の名を(後編)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Star of Ultimate Love and the Name of X, Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saiai no Hoshi ni [x] no Na o (Kouhen)</title>
<summary>Fumino continues to live with the Yuiga family. One day, his family needs to go out, leaving Nariyuki and Fumino alone. In gratitude for letting her stay over, Fumino attempts to cook and clean, but fails miserably at every turn!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>790344</identifier>
<identifier>we-never-learn-bokuben</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="224392" update="2020-01-12">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-12-15</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">祭のはじめは矢継ぎ早 彼らに[x]が降りかかる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">X Descends Like Wildfire at the Festival`s Beginning</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Matsuri no Hajime wa Yatsugibaya: Karera ni [x] ga Furikakaru</title>
<summary>While Fumino, Rizu, and Uruka all know what their major in college is going to be, Nariyuki still can`t decide what he wants to do. Meanwhile, everyone is busy getting ready for Ichinose Academy`s school festival.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>790345</identifier>
<identifier>we-never-learn-bokuben</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="224393" update="2020-01-12">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-12-22</airdate>
<rating votes="6">8.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">祭の騒ぎは留まらず[x]どもは茨の道を往く</title>
<title xml:lang="en">X Treads a Thorny Path as the Festivities Continue...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Matsuri no Sawagi wa Tomarazu [x] Domo wa Ibara no Michi o Iku</title>
<summary>The school festival is a roaring success! At the swim team`s live stage show, Umihara and Kawase perform with Mafuyu in a Full Pure costume for some reason.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>790346</identifier>
<identifier>we-never-learn-bokuben</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="224394" update="2020-01-12">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2019-12-29</airdate>
<rating votes="6">5.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">祭の終わりは寂しくも華やかに[x]どもを祝福する</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Post-Festival Celebration of X, Both Dazzling and Lonely</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Matsuri no Owari wa Sabishiku mo Hanayaka ni [x] Domo o Shukufuku Suru</title>
<summary>The animal-costumed Nariyuki’s intrusion onto the stage brings Fumino’s play to an ending that has the crowd on its feet. Meanwhile, business is booming at Rizu’s class’s udon shop.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>790347</identifier>
<identifier>we-never-learn-bokuben</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
