<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="14969" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2020-01-04</startdate>
<enddate>2020-03-28</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Ishuzoku Reviewers</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">異種族レビュアーズ</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Interspecies Reviewers</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Рецензенты других рас</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="11130" approval="10" total="20">Monster Musume no Iru Nichijou</anime>
<anime id="10982" approval="1" total="7">Gate: Jieitai Kanochi nite, Kaku Tatakaeri</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="6">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="813396">Easily was the meme of the year for 2020, it`ll be pretty hard for this to get topped, sadly the show gets a little stale after a couple episodes; but if you enjoy boobs and dick jokes then you can enjoy the show.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="21063">filth+comedy sums it up. I have zero interest in hentai or even ecchi shows and yet i enjoyed the adult humor. production quality is surprisingly good. I recommend at least the very first episode.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="784493">Better than it has any right to be</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="326899">This is Sword Art Online of brothel based animes to come ;)

I can’t recall any other Anime that nearly touched this topic
A bunch of typical isekai anime adventurers taking sweet break from questing to spend some quality time in a brothel.
Echii or rather censored “in your face” porn with every type of monster girl there is.
Great, very detailed world, characters, special abilities, magic and good deal of well-made puns and sex humor.
Even world politics was spot on. 

Must see for adults.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="231802">Sukebe ga daisuki

Field report of sorts. Came for the ecchi + hentai; got impressed by the creativity &amp; braveness of the studio for such a show, and got my laughs worth to climax.

With plenty of brothels to review, ensures a steady supply of fanservice+ecchi with girls of varying size, shapes and species. That and our brave heroes, cute waitress &amp; the bunch of cameo review followers gave alot of room for squirting creativity. From the highlights of the reviews, the fun times with the girls, &amp; char design ejeculated with fun personalities and back stories.

Hentai, ecchi, fan service (traps too), and jokes are cleverly mix and presented in a comical way. With the surprising high prod quality; you get hot curves, alluring girls &amp; scene that got me heart racing, me tool quivering &amp; me tummy aching from the good laughs

Glad to join this adventure even as an observer (like dragon dude), for the more mature crowd of coz tht appreciates sexual jokes and some ecchi time. 9/10 for me</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>https://isyuzoku.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="59334" type="Music">Naito Kotone</name>
<name id="14295" type="Chief Animation Direction">Izumo Takaaki</name>
<name id="44284" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ijuuin Izuro</name>
<name id="1641" type="Chief Animation Direction">Katou Hiroto</name>
<name id="59925" type="Chief Animation Direction">Hinata Haruka</name>
<name id="11842" type="Chief Animation Direction">Furukawa Hideki</name>
<name id="3333" type="Chief Animation Direction">Uno Makoto</name>
<name id="35245" type="Animation Work">Passione</name>
<name id="3333" type="Character Design">Uno Makoto</name>
<name id="7582" type="Series Composition">Fudeyasu Kazuyuki</name>
<name id="58131" type="Original Work">Amahara</name>
<name id="32756" type="Direction">Ogawa Yuuki</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on an adult comedy fantasy manga by writer http://anidb.net/cr58131 [Amahara] and artist http://anidb.net/cr58132 [masha].
Beauty truly is in the eye of the beholder! From elves to succubi to cyclopes and more, the Yoruno Gloss reviewers are here to rate the red-light delights of all manner of monster girls...The only thing is, they can never agree on which species are the hottest!
Source: Yen Press
Note: The first episode received an advance web delivery by d Anime Store and Niconico on January 4 and January 6, respectively. The regular TV broadcast started on January 11.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="525">6.34</permanent>
<temporary count="534">7.01</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>240604.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22612</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>40010</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://isyuzoku.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Interspecies_Reviewers</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>異種族レビュアーズ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5534</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>368982</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22439</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>isyuzoku</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B084753TWV</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="7" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-15">
<name>juujin</name>
<description>Kemono, "beast", is a genre of Japanese art and character design that prominently features anthropomorphic animal characters. It is used widely in visual arts, especially drawing and painting, and can be found in many manga, anime, and video game.
Anthropomorphic animal characters in the kemono genre are frequently called juujin, "therianthrope"; the kanji for juujin are also sometimes pronounced kemonobito, "beast-human". While their design differs from artist to artist, they generally employ animal traits considered cute and endearing; most kemono characters retain a fundamentally human personality, however, seldom behaving as the actual animals from which they have been anthropomorphized, and as such they are typically depicted living as humans do.
Juujin leans more on the human-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t2857 [anthropomorphism], which leans more on the animal-looking side.
Source: Manga Wikia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="235" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-05">
<name>waitress</name>
<description>A female attendant who serves customers in a restaurant, café, or similar.
Source: Wiktionary</description>
<picurl>163704.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="301" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-10">
<name>lactation</name>
<description>Capable of secreting breast milk, sometimes referred to as Mother`s milk.</description>
<picurl>176139.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="627" parentid="2856" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-15">
<name>lingerie</name>
<description>Lingerie is a term for fashionable and alluring women`s undergarments.</description>
<picurl>238327.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="780" parentid="2849" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-08-23">
<name>fairy</name>
<description>A fairy is a type of mythical being or legendary creature in European folklore, a form of spirit, often described as metaphysical, supernatural, or preternatural.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>206567.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1026" parentid="2712" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-02-19">
<name>sex doll</name>
<description>A sex doll is a type of sex toy in the size and shape of a human sexual partner for aid in masturbation. The sex doll may consist of an entire body with face, or just a head, pelvis or other partial body, with the accessories (vagina, anus, mouth, penis) for sexual stimulation. The parts are sometimes vibrating and may be removable or interchangeable, whereas the body may be inflatable, especially for cheaper models. A robotic sex doll, designed to be able to exhibit more complex interactions, is called a sex robot or sexbot. Sexbots may be considered subsets of sex dolls or different creations entirely. In Japan, the term Dutch wife is commonly used to refer to sex dolls, in particular the cheap, inflatable kind, whereas a high-end sex doll can be called a love doll.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1152" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-23">
<name>undead</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1155" parentid="2849" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-11-28">
<name>mermaid</name>
<description>A creature that is half-human (usually the upper body) and half-fish (usually the lower body). A male mermaid is called merman (but they can appear under many different names). Since mermaids are often confused with Sirens in media, they may posses special abilities akin to Sirens such as enchanting voice (on the other hand Sirens are often being portrayed as mermaids). Some mermaids might be able to transform their whole body into human (which is not surprising since mermaids are often associated with the "want to become human" theme) and that should not disqualify them from getting this tag.</description>
<picurl>209970.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1278" parentid="2274" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-16">
<name>android</name>
<description>An android is a robot or synthetic organism designed to look and act like a human.</description>
<picurl>223943.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1409" parentid="1152" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-03-20">
<name>vampire</name>
<description>A vampire is a mythological or folkloric nocturnal undead. Vampires use long fangs to penetrate the necks of people, usually young females, to drink their blood, both as a form of nourishment and to turn the targets into slaves.
In the classic vampire stories, they are thought to have no reflection in mirrors, are able to shapeshift into bats (sometimes also wolves or some form of fog), have unlimited lifespan and superhuman strength, reflexes and senses, and may only be killed by silver bullets, silver blades, a stake through the heart, fire, or exposure to sunlight; on the other hand, they cannot tolerate garlic, holy water, or Christian crosses (sometimes expanded to religious symbols in general).
In modern anime, these limitations are usually dropped, and they become far more powerful and fearsome opponents than usual. A human bitten, or sometimes even scratched, by a vampire typically becomes a slave, eventually dying as if poisoned, and becoming a vampire, ghoul, zombie, or other form of undead after death, often staying under the command of the vampire who originally bit them.</description>
<picurl>231496.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1609" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-03-01">
<name>elf</name>
<description>The origin of Elves (Norse; álfar(elves), álfr(elf)) can be found in ancient Norse mythology, in which, elves are described as divine, or near-divine, race of humanoids (Vættir), likened to the Æsir. In common description they are described as sage and immortal beings occupying the threshold between humans and the gods. In some cases humans that were beloved by the gods became elves within their lives. Ancient Elves are delineated into a pair of similar but distinct races; Light Elves (Ljósálfar) and Dark Elves (Svartálfar), each originating from separate homes within the nine worlds of Yggdrasil. Within the Poetic Edda the differences are commonly ascribed as:
"There is one place there that is called the Elf Home (Álfheimr which is the elven city). People live there that are named the light elves (Ljósálfar). But the dark elves (Dökkálfar) live below in earth, in caves and the dark forest and they are unlike them in appearance - and more unlike them in reality. The Light Elves are brighter than the sun in appearance, but the Dark Elves are blacker than pitch." (Snorri, Gylfaginning 17, Prose Edda)</description>
<picurl>63489.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1773" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-12">
<name>tentacle</name>
<description>A tentacle or bothrium (plural: bothria) is one of usually two or more elongated flexible organs present in animals, especially invertebrates. Usually, Tentacles are used for feeding, feeling and grasping.</description>
<picurl>236087.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1774" parentid="2891" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-06-05">
<name>gigantic breasts</name>
<description>Gigantic breasts are unnaturally large breasts, even by anime standards; they are true gargantuan monstrosities, either because of sheer size or through the combination of size and exceedingly unnatural shape. Essentially, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are gigantic; smaller breasts are the more common http://anidb.net/t2741 [large breasts], even if they`re as big as the character`s head.</description>
<picurl>160446.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2008" parentid="2891" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-05">
<name>small breasts</name>
<description>This character has a bust size that is considered small. 
The small size is usually a bust that would use a bra which is A or B. In anime, C may rarely enter this category.</description>
<picurl>162720.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2056" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-09-13">
<name>cosplaying</name>
<description>This character likes to cosplay.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2143" parentid="2646" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-28">
<name>succubus</name>
<description>A demon who takes the form of a woman to seduce men in dreams to have sexual intercourse. In modern times, a succubus is often depicted as highly attractive, while in the past succubi were depicted as frightening and demonic. Succubi draw energy from men to sustain themselves, often until the victim becomes exhausted or dies. The male counterpart is the incubus.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2257" parentid="1152" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-12">
<name>zombie</name>
<description>A zombie is asserted to be a reanimated corpse, or a human who is being controlled by someone else by use of magic with some media renditions using a pandemic illness to explain their existence.
Stories of zombies originated in the West African spiritual belief system of voodoo, which told of the people being controlled as laborers by a powerful wizard.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2274" parentid="2638" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-30">
<name>robot</name>
<description>A robot is an automatically guided machine, able to do tasks on its own. Another common characteristic is that by its appearance or movements, a robot often conveys a sense that it has intent or agency of its own.
Not to be confused with android (human-like robot).</description>
<picurl>215586.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2346" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-09-14">
<name>angel</name>
<description>An angel is a supernatural being, said to be the messenger of God. They are often depicted as human beings with a pair of white feathered wings and sometimes with a halo.
In contrast, a fallen angel who has turned evil will be depicted with black wings.</description>
<picurl>35521.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2355" parentid="2849" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-28">
<name>dragon</name>
<description>Very intelligent mythical beings - a cross between a very large lizard and a dinosaur - that breath fire, and have a knack for kidnapping damsels, thus distressing them. In Fantasy anime this perceptive species often lives secluded from human civilisation, protectors of long lost knowledge. Dragons seem to be on the verge of extinction.</description>
<picurl>32579.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2391" parentid="2608" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>bishoujo</name>
<description>In Japanese, a bishoujo is any pretty female from toddlerhood to late adolescence. In the West, the word specifically refers to attractive girls generally from late childhood or early adolescence, especially those that appeal to males, and particularly to fictional characters designed in a way traditionally associated to shoujo manga. Fictional bishoujo tend to be cute, pastel-coloured teenagers; they lack the sophistication of older women, instead having detailed eye and hair design, fluttery costumes often including ribbons, and all sorts of generally sparkly fluff.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2535" parentid="1152" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-01-18">
<name>ghost</name>
<description>In traditional belief, a ghost is the soul or spirit of a deceased person or animal that can appear, in visible form or other manifestation, to the living. Descriptions of the apparition of ghosts vary widely: The mode of manifestation can range from an invisible presence to translucent or wispy shapes, to realistic, life-like visions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2622" parentid="2841" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>swordplay</name>
<description>The act or art of using a sword or similar weapon skillfully.</description>
<picurl>211286.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2635" parentid="2613" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-06">
<name>jungle</name>
<description>This show features jungle(s) as one of its settings.
This can either involve jungle adventures or shady business revolving around deforesting of jungles or forests.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2638" parentid="2846" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>mecha</name>
<description>Mecha in Japanese basically means mechanical things; everything from an electric whisk or a car to a spaceship or a robot. Here however we limit it to the more exotic things usually referred to as mecha anime: robots, whether controlled by a human or not, and their ilk. See Androids, Piloted Robots, Power Suits, Robot Helpers, Transforming Robots for a more specific classification.</description>
<picurl>42077.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2646" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>demon</name>
<description>In Western lore, demons are often described as minions from Hell, generally known to attack humans and feast on their flesh or possess the bodies of those with weak souls. In Eastern lore, on the other hand, they are generally supernatural, often but not always malevolent beings who can be more mischievous than actually evil, or simply supernatural spirits of no specific alignment.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2697" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-05">
<name>voyeurism</name>
<description>Voyeurism is the sexual interest in or practice of spying on people engaged in intimate behaviors, such as undressing, sexual activity, or other actions usually considered to be of a private nature. The principal characteristic of voyeurism is that the voyeur does not normally interact directly with the subject of his/her interest, who is often unaware of being observed. The essence of voyeurism is the observing but may also involve the making of a secret photograph or video of the subject during an intimate activity. When the interest in a particular subject is obsessive, the behavior may be described as stalking.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>162189.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2706" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-13">
<name>masturbation</name>
<description>Manual erotic stimulation of the genitals or other erogenous regions, often to orgasm, either by oneself or a partner.</description>
<picurl>210612.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2712" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>sex toys</name>
<description>A sex toy is an object or device that is primarily used to facilitate human sexual pleasure, such as a dildo or vibrator.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2721" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-13">
<name>public sex</name>
<description>Public sex refers to sexual acts that take place in public or semi-public places.</description>
<picurl>175406.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2726" parentid="2848" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>prostitution</name>
<description>Prostitution is the practice or occupation of engaging in sexual activity with someone for payment.</description>
<picurl>222173.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2729" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-02">
<name>BDSM</name>
<description>A form of "kinky sex". The acronym BDSM derives from BD (bondage and discipline), DS (dominance and submission) and SM (sadism and masochism). BDSM usually characterizes with one side being superior (active) over the other (passive), with each side being one or more participants. Whips, chains, handcuffs, ropes, blindfolds are common elements of BDSM.</description>
<picurl>233865.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2730" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>exhibitionism</name>
<description>Exhibitionism is the act of exposing in a public or semi-public context the parts of one`s body that are not normally exposed. That may be done to prompt sexual arousal, but many forms of exhibitionism actually mean to create humour or disparagement through shock value or mockery. The idea of exhibitionism is closely tied to the notions of decency and modesty in dressing, and as such is highly dependent on one`s own cultural background. Certain forms of exhibitionism may be considered indecent exposure, and thus in many jurisdictions they may lead to civil or criminal charges. While both deal with the lack of clothing and may in certain cases overlap, exhibitionism is very different from and not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t2304 [nudism].</description>
<picurl>162657.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2741" parentid="2891" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-14">
<name>large breasts</name>
<description>Large breasts are breasts a fair notch larger than average, as found in some adolescent girls or fully grown women; however, as anime has no upper limit to breast size, the definition applies somewhat differently. To be considered large, breasts in anime must be bigger than real-life natural ones or natural-seeming fake ones, to the point they`d appear weirdly or even abnormally large in real-life females. On the high end of the spectrum, breasts that are as big as the character`s head or possibly a bit bigger are still considered large; however, breasts that take at least as much space as the rest of the chest or the abdomen, or that are almost as big but have an absurdly unnatural shape, are the less common http://anidb.net/t1774 [gigantic breasts] instead.</description>
<picurl>161014.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2746" parentid="2901" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-26">
<name>shibari</name>
<description>Not to be confused with Hojoujutsu (捕縄術) or Nawajutsu (縄術), which is the traditional Japanese martial art of restraining a person using cord or rope.
More commonly known as Kinbaku (緊縛) in Japan, Shibari is the word for "erotic bondage" or Kinbaku-bi which means "beautiful bondage". Kinbaku (also Sokubaku) is a Japanese style of sexual bondage or BDSM which involves tying up the bottom using simple yet visually intricate patterns, usually with several pieces of thin rope usually hemp or jute (generally 6 mm or 8 mm in diameter). The person`s body can also be hanging from the rope while tied to it.
The word Shibari came into common use in the West at some point in the 1990s to describe the bondage art Kinbaku. Shibari (縛り) is a Japanese word that literally means "to tie" or "to bind". It is used in Japan to describe the artful use of twine to tie objects or packages.
In anime/manga, Shibari or Kinbaku is often seen as a tool of rape or torture, rather than intended for a concept of bondage aesthetics.</description>
<picurl>161702.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2748" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>sex</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse, the ultimate bond of love and the "Origin of the World" (just think of Gustave Courbet`s painting: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%27Origine_du_monde).
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
<picurl>161190.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2770" parentid="2653" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>violent retribution for accidental infringement</name>
<description>A comedy / slapstick element often found in Ecchi anime: The hilarity derives from spontaneous embarrassment, overreaction of the "victim" (girl), immediate retribution for a seemingly inappropriate act, and a sense of pity with the supposed "aggressor" (boy).
Typically a boy will - through no fault of his own - stumble into a girl, thus invading her personal space. In the process the boy may e.g. pull down her skirt, grab the girl`s breasts, or accidentally kiss her. Any level-headed girl would see the accident just for what it is. Not so the girl with an overly developed sense of modesty, and a thing for violence. She - often a tsundere - will clobber the boy with excessive brutality.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2773" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-18">
<name>magic circles</name>
<description>A magic circle is circle or sphere of space marked out by practitioners of many branches of ritual magic. It may be marked physically, drawn in salt or chalk, for example, or merely visualised.
Traditionally, circles have been used by ritual magicians to form a protective barrier between themselves and what they summoned. Nowadays, circles often have the more benign function of containing and concentrating the energy raised during a ritual. Circles can also be used as barriers for non-magical work such as meditation.
Generally, as with most magical practices, an incantation is recited stating the purpose and nature of the circle, often repeating an assortment of divine and angelic names.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>32800.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2785" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>unrequited love</name>
<description>At least one character has a romantic interest in another one, but the feelings are not returned. 
This is the cornerstone of all love triangles or love polygons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2817" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>skimpy clothing</name>
<description>When a job needs to get done you need the appropriate clothing on the appropriate persons. That calls for preferably scantily clad young ladies. Spies will dress in sexy outfits, even when the mission explicitly calls for them to not to be noticed. Female warriors will charge into battle wearing armour that does not protect the vital organs. Bridge officers on a military starship will be issued go-go boots with their uniforms. Examples are the women in VanDread, AIKa or the most famous incarnation of that tag, the Strike Witches and their precursor the Sky Girls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2827" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-06">
<name>sudden naked guy appearance</name>
<description>A male specimen previously unknown to the viewer and not dressed in any clothes suddenly appears out of nowhere.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2828" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-26">
<name>borderline porn</name>
<description>Breaks the bounds of "excessive fanservice".
While the physical interactions and dialogue between characters may be extremely sexual, the most sexual situations do *not* have sex itself take place.
Specifically descriptive of containing all the plentiful features of (excessive) fanservice in addition to the interactions between characters being quite sexual — at most, sexual in NATURE only. This means physical touching such as groping, molesting, or bondage will focus primarily on the revealed (i.e. nude) upper portion of the body or through/over clothing on the lower half of the body. This is all WITHOUT actual sex acts (penetration, etc.) taking place.</description>
<picurl>214855.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2850" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>adventure</name>
<description>Adventures are exciting stories, with new experiences or exotic locales. Adventures are designed to provide an action-filled, energetic experience for the viewer. Rather than the predominant emphasis on violence and fighting that is found in pure action anime, however, the viewer of adventures can live vicariously through the travels, conquests, explorations, creation of empires, struggles and situations that confront the main characters, actual historical figures or protagonists. Under the category of adventures, we can include traditional swashbucklers, serialized films, and historical spectacles, searches or expeditions for lost continents, "jungle" and "desert" epics, treasure hunts and quests, disaster films, and heroic journeys or searches for the unknown. Adventure films are often, but not always, set in an historical period, and may include adapted stories of historical or literary adventure heroes, kings, battles, rebellion, or piracy.</description>
<picurl>178879.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2867" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>politics</name>
<description>From commies to fat capitalist pigs, all the stuff done by the "guys with the power", mainly evil tactics for gaining more power over the masses.
Watching this title may remind you why CNN is boring.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2879" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>alcohol</name>
<description>Alcohol (or more scientifically, ethanol), is one of the world`s oldest psychoactive substances. It is traditionally found in the form of a beverage such as beer, wine, or liquor, although in some contexts it can be inhaled to produce similar or intoxication, and some people prefer another way of consuming beverage-form alcohol.
Alcoholic beverages are many and varied, due to production methods (fermentation or distillation), source materials (grains, fruits, vegetables, other plants), added substances such as flavorings, and many more ways of defining different forms of alcoholic beverages.
Alcoholic beverages are divided into three general classes: beers, wines, and spirits. They are legally consumed in most countries, and over 100 countries have laws regulating their production, sale, and consumption. In particular, such laws specify the minimum age at which a person may legally buy or drink them. This minimum age varies between 16 and 25 years, depending upon the country and the type of drink. Most nations set it at 18 years of age.</description>
<picurl>70749.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2891" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-31">
<name>breasts</name>
<description>The female bust size matters! Or does it? The three subcategories spell out the sizes that relate to fetishes, be they gigantic, large or small. Normal sized breasts are not a fetish, it seems. The tag is not only used for ecchi anime, but also for hentai shows as well.</description>
<picurl>161015.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2895" parentid="2608" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>dark-skinned girl</name>
<description>The anime features a girl with dark skin. A fetish of sorts, since the other protagonists are usually as white-skinned as porcelain dolls.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2901" parentid="2729" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-09">
<name>bondage</name>
<description>Bondage is the use of restraints for the sexual pleasure of the parties involved. It may be used in its own right, as in the case of rope bondage and breast bondage, or as part of sexual activity or BDSM activity. When a person is sexually aroused by bondage, it may be considered a paraphilia, known as vincilagnia (from Latin vincio, to bind or fetter with chains, and lagneia, lust).
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>42021.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2979" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-18">
<name>mutilation</name>
<description>Mutilation is an act of physical injury that degrades the appearance or function of any living body. Some ethnic groups practice ritual mutilation, e.g. scarification, burning, flagellation(whipping), tattooing, or wheeling, as part of a rite of passage. In some cases, the term may apply to treatment of dead bodies, such as soldiers mutilated after they have been killed by an enemy. Maiming, or mutilation which involves the loss of, or incapacity to use, a bodily member, is and has been practised by many societies with various cultural and religious significances, and is also a customary form of physical punishment, especially applied on the principle of "an eye for an eye".
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3040" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>male protagonist</name>
<description>This anime has a male protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3170" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-10">
<name>occupation and career</name>
<description>The kind of anime which shows the career of a character, usually from the beginning.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3183" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-04">
<name>necrophilia</name>
<description>Sexual intercourse with or attraction toward corpses.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3185" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-27">
<name>wordplay</name>
<description>The characters play with words. 
E.g. purposely or accidentally use similar-sounding but wrongly applied words in the Japanese original, leading to supposedly funny misunderstandings and confusion.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3411" parentid="2841" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>fighting</name>
<description>For some reason or other one faction has to take it out on some opponent via fight or battle. Typical examples of this are all the anime with "endless pointless fighting" tag.</description>
<picurl>211266.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3443" parentid="2848" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-05">
<name>orgy</name>
<description>A wild gathering marked by promiscuous sexual activity.</description>
<picurl>190911.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3898" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-11-11">
<name>science and magic coexist</name>
<description>In this anime science and magic do not exclude each other. Magic here is actually very advanced, artefact- and/or ritual-based science.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3971" parentid="3170" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-07-04">
<name>entertainment industry</name>
<description>The show depicts how the entertainment industry works and how the main protagonists strive to cope with the sudden change to fame. At times this can be a very ugly sight indeed.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3977" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-29">
<name>dialogue driven</name>
<description>A dialogue driven show has its story advanced by dialogue, with action being of much lower priority, and relies heavily on conversations between characters.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4064" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>CGI</name>
<description>Computer-generated imagery (CGI) or computer animation is the art of creating moving images via the use of computers. It is a subfield of computer graphics and animation. Increasingly it is created by means of 3D computer graphics, though 2D computer graphics are still widely used for stylistic, low bandwidth, and faster real-time rendering needs. Sometimes the target of the animation is the computer itself, but sometimes the target is another medium, such as film.</description>
<picurl>222249.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4096" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>gore</name>
<description>A Splatter film or Gore film is a sub-genre of horror film that deliberately focuses on graphic portrayals of gore and graphic violence. These films, through the use of special effects and excessive blood and guts, tend to display an overt interest in the vulnerability of the human body and the theatricality of its mutilation. Due to their willingness to portray images society might consider shocking, splatter films share some ideological grounds with the transgressive art movement. The term "splatter cinema" was coined by George A. Romero to describe his film Dawn of the Dead, though Dawn of the Dead is generally considered by critics to have higher aspirations, such as social commentary, than to be simply exploitative for its own sake.
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>32491.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4131" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-05-11">
<name>cultural references</name>
<description>The plot of this anime shows signs of cultural references, these are often jokes that make reference to a certain custom, habit or history that is specifically attributed to that culture. Knowledge of the culture itself is needed in order to properly understand these jokes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4157" parentid="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-17">
<name>eyeball licking</name>
</tag>
<tag id="4223" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>running gag</name>
<description>(Bit) character(s) play out a short skit several times during the course of the anime. The skit may or may not be exactly the same but does tend to have the same theme throughout.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4352" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-11">
<name>censored uncensored version</name>
<description>Even the DVD and Blu-ray releases do not let you see everything you were expecting to, and you will have to live with censorship in the show. That normally applies to fan service, but may also apply to gore and violence. A very common example is characters without nipples, as in http://anidb.net/a6083 [KissXSis]; in other cases, something such as steam or foam stays in the camera`s way, like in http://anidb.net/a6531 [Kanamemo]. In some shows, the censorship in the disk releases is even stronger than in the TV version, while others may use creative censorship as a replacement for the removed fan service or even as a joke.
This does not apply to censorship of what Japanese pornography laws still require to be censored.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4614" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>narration</name>
<description>The most common example is that of a voice, either that of one of the characters or entirely unrelated, that appears at the beginning of an episode to offer a summary or introduction, and at the end of an episode for closure or for a preview to hint upon what to expect next.
Another use of narration comes in the form of a dominant voice belonging to one of the protagonists, intended only for the viewer and revealing the intimate thoughts to whom it belongs. This type of narration occurs frequently throughout the duration of the episode or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4642" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-03-08">
<name>economics</name>
<description>Economics is the social science that studies economic activity to gain an understanding of the processes that govern the production, distribution and consumption of goods and services in an economy.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>169811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5406" parentid="2729" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-03-02">
<name>submission</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5451" parentid="2726" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>soapland</name>
<description>A Soapland is a type of brothel in Japan where male clients can engage in sexual activity with female prostitutes, although officially the clubs do business as places where the client is bathed. There are also a few soaplands specifically for female clients.
There are various kinds of soaplands, and they are usually located in complexes with varying numbers of soaplands. Well-known complexes are located in Susukino in Sapporo, Yoshiwara and Kabukicho in Tokyo, Kawasaki, Kanazuen in Gifu, Ogoto in Shiga and Fukuhara in Kobe but there are many other areas, especially in onsen (hot springs) towns. Prices for a session at a soapland vary depending on factors such as location, time of day, and length of session.</description>
<picurl>222171.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5485" parentid="7199" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-28">
<name>penis jokes</name>
<description>A penis or other phallic object is used as a device to elicit laughter from the viewer. This also includes indirect references to such objects provided the intent is clearly the same.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5518" parentid="7199" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-03">
<name>flat chest jokes</name>
<description>Jokes about the (supposedly or actually) flat chest of a character.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5835" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-28">
<name>Gainax bounce</name>
<description>A term that has come to describe often exaggerated, very jiggly, fluid, and painstakingly detailed animation of female characters` bouncing breasts. 
The term has its roots in http://anidb.net/a185 [Top o Nerae!] — Gunbuster, Gainax`s first OVA (1988), in which the Gainax bounce is found unabated in the three female characters of Noriko, Kazumi, and Jung.</description>
<picurl>166074.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5993" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-28">
<name>black humour</name>
<description>Sure, it`s funny, but you really shouldn`t be laughing...
In other words, it`s a comedy that employs situations that nice people should not be laughing about.</description>
<picurl>222688.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6018" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-27">
<name>predominantly adult cast</name>
<description>This show features mostly adults. That means children and teenagers are relatively rare and unlikely to hold significance to the plot.
That is a rare trait in anime, as most shows spin around children or teenagers.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6021" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>gender bender</name>
<description>Term used to refer to a person who takes on the role of their opposite gender. This often only reaches to the extent of cross-dressing (involving physical appearance and clothing only), but in rarer cases, involves a total gender swap (which seems to be more common in anime) - where the willing or unwilling victim receives a body opposite of their original gender (either permanently or temporarily), with all natural parts per their new body fully (or just all-out amply) included.
Example of cross-dressing gender bender: "Maria+Holic"
Examples of body-swap gender bender: "Kashimashi: Girl meets Girl", "Birdy the Mighty Decode"</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6078" parentid="2850" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-23">
<name>gotta catch them all</name>
<description>A typical plot or sub-plot for many shows. Either the cast or somebody else, that being often the main antagonist, embarks on a quest to collect things, shiny things. Things that are said to grant simple wishes or even do miracles like bringing people back to life, destroying the whole world, galaxy, universe and in rare cases turning the hero into the greatest Pokemon Master. Those things can be weapons, lost technology, magical artefacts, pieces of a giant magical artefact and in some cases even people or little critters.
The point is, there`s stuff to collect!</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6349" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-13">
<name>multi-segment episodes</name>
<description>Multi-segment episodes are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t5852 [short episodes], which are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length (up to and including 10 minutes).
Also not to be confused with an OVA or music video with multiple (otherwise unrelated) full-length http://anidb.net/t7241 [bundled episodes] consolidated into a single episode video track.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6371" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-03-30">
<name>red-light district</name>
<description>A red-light district is a part of an urban area where there is a concentration of prostitution and sex-oriented businesses, such as sex shops, strip clubs, adult theaters, etc. The term originates from the red lights that were used as signs of brothels. There are areas in many big cities around the world which have acquired an international reputation as red-light districts.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6399" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-25">
<name>episodic</name>
<description>An episodic anime consists of many successive short arcs that are generally 1-2 episodes in length, with strong plot continuity within each arc but generally little continuity from one arc to the next. For long shows (well upwards of 50 episodes), the episode count constraint is less tight; for example, a show with close to 250 episodes would also be considered episodic if it consisted of a majority of arcs of up to 3 or maybe 4 episodes and possibly also very few slightly longer arcs.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6443" parentid="2729" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-09-02">
<name>wooden horse</name>
<description>A wooden horse is a device used in BDSM play, by having the victim straddle the wooden horse.</description>
<picurl>175282.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6537" parentid="2879" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-09">
<name>beer</name>
<description>A popular alcoholic drink with a relatively low alcohol content. It is traditionally made from malted cereal grains with hops.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7199" parentid="2611" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-12">
<name>sexual humour</name>
<description>Sexual humour is prevalent in this anime. It often involves cheeky or crude sexual language, with innuendos and jokes about the female or male genitalia. Often, such anime also have http://anidb.net/t2856 [ecchi] elements to them.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7229" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>fingering</name>
<description>Fingering is the manual stimulation of the vagina by another person`s hand and fingers. The male equivalent is a http://anidb.net/t2693 [handjob].</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7579" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2020-03-31">
<name>Judeo-Christian mythology</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="106610" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-01-26">
<rating votes="5">5.51</rating>
<name>Mii</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244033.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42353" picture="243221.jpg">Isobe Karin</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106611" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-01-19">
<rating votes="5">4.65</rating>
<name>Aloe</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>243874.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1799" picture="156027.jpg">Hikasa Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106612" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-01-26">
<rating votes="5">2.80</rating>
<name>Elza</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244036.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="44112" picture="225552.jpg">Koichi Makoto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106613" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-01-19">
<rating votes="7">4.12</rating>
<name>Eldley</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>243875.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18025" picture="183213.jpg">Matsuzaki Rei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106614" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-01-26">
<rating votes="6">4.87</rating>
<name>Elma</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244034.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="50015" picture="243217.jpg">Koyama Momoyo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106615" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-01-19">
<rating votes="4">4.43</rating>
<name>Okpa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>243878.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32949" picture="243218.jpg">Hino Mari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106616" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-11-01">
<rating votes="2">2.91</rating>
<name>Kanchal</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240608.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40415" picture="158225.jpg">Yuasa Kaede</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106617" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-01-19">
<rating votes="6">5.94</rating>
<name>Guinea</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>243876.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="47010" picture="223717.jpg">Nukui Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106618" type="main character in" update="2019-11-01">
<rating votes="12">4.37</rating>
<name>Crimvael</name>
<gender>intersexual</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240607.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43492" picture="232251.jpg">Tomita Miyu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106619" type="main character in" update="2019-11-01">
<rating votes="8">4.51</rating>
<name>Stunk</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240605.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="400" picture="171989.jpg">Majima Junji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106620" type="main character in" update="2019-11-01">
<rating votes="4">2.21</rating>
<name>Zel</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240606.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38670" picture="185856.jpg">Kobayashi Yuusuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106621" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-01-19">
<rating votes="4">4.36</rating>
<name>Tiaplate</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>243879.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23312" picture="205591.jpg">Takamori Natsumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106622" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-01-26">
<rating votes="4">3.53</rating>
<name>Piltia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244037.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10410" picture="223211.jpg">Izawa Shiori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106623" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-01-19">
<rating votes="3">1.71</rating>
<name>Mitsue</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>243880.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="34588" picture="243219.jpg">Yaoya Kyou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106624" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-01-19">
<rating votes="5">6.38</rating>
<name>Milky</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>243877.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="41719" picture="243220.jpg">Katou Yuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106625" type="secondary cast in" update="2019-11-01">
<rating votes="9">6.79</rating>
<name>Meidri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>240609.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="36368" picture="224755.jpg">Mao</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="106626" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-01-26">
<rating votes="6">3.53</rating>
<name>Lona</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244035.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="49207" picture="243216.jpg">Tanaka Takako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108135" type="appears in" update="2020-01-26">
<rating votes="1">1.56</rating>
<name>Brooz</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244027.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="373" picture="191382.jpg">Hamada Kenji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108136" type="appears in" update="2020-01-26">
<rating votes="1">1.56</rating>
<name>Narugami</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244028.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="23529" picture="178469.jpg">Kawanishi Kengo</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108137" type="appears in" update="2020-01-26">
<rating votes="1">1.56</rating>
<name>Bubulala</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244029.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32911" picture="230127.jpg">Furuki Nozomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108138" type="appears in" update="2020-01-26">
<rating votes="4">4.86</rating>
<name>Death Abyss</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244030.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5663" picture="228631.jpg">Igarashi Hiromi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108139" type="appears in" update="2020-01-26">
<rating votes="1">1.18</rating>
<name>Demon Two</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244031.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="19" picture="50583.jpg">Imaruoka Atsushi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108140" type="appears in" update="2020-01-26">
<rating votes="1">5.68</rating>
<name>Ookina-hakase</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244032.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="469" picture="17418.jpg">Umezu Hideyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108227" type="appears in" update="2020-02-02">
<rating votes="2">5.13</rating>
<name>Lymee</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244196.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="57157" picture="228652.jpg">Narumi Runa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108228" type="appears in" update="2020-02-02">
<rating votes="1">1.56</rating>
<name>Chalmi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244197.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="40415" picture="158225.jpg">Yuasa Kaede</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108229" type="appears in" update="2020-02-02">
<rating votes="1">5.68</rating>
<name>Zelzel</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244198.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12266" picture="56026.jpg">Kanemoto Hisako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108230" type="appears in" update="2020-02-02">
<rating votes="2">5.13</rating>
<name>Tiesu</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244199.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="53513" picture="229081.jpg">Maeda Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108231" type="appears in" update="2020-02-02">
<rating votes="2">4.13</rating>
<name>Mestunk</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244200.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18198" picture="228672.jpg">Akasaki Chinatsu</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="225430" update="2019-12-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-01-04</airdate>
<rating votes="12">4.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">エルフの熟女と人間の熟女についての議論が沸騰し, 天使はニャンニャン天国で昇天し, 有翼人は総排泄孔で感度も抜群!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Hot `n Heavy Debate About Elf and Human MILFS, an Angel Ascends at Meow Meow Paradise, Can`t Get Enough of That Sensitive Birdmaid Cloaca!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Elf no Shukujo to Ningen no Shukujo ni Tsuite no Giron ga Futtou shi, Tenshi wa Nyannyan Tengoku de Shouten shi, Yuuyokujin wa Sou Haisetsu Ana de Kando mo Batsugun!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225431" update="2019-12-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-01-18</airdate>
<rating votes="8">6.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">フェアリーは受け挿れられるサイズに制限があり, 悪魔族はあまり人気がなく, 乳牛系のミノタウロスはでかくて揺れてすごい出る!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fairies Have Limits on What They Can Take, Demons Aren`t Very Popular, Minotaur Girls Are Big, Bountiful, and Boobylicious!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fairy wa Ukeirerareru Size ni Seigen ga Ari, Akumazoku wa Amari Ninki ga Naku, Nyuugyuu Kei no Minotaur wa Dekakute Yurete Sugoi Deru!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225432" update="2019-12-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-01-25</airdate>
<rating votes="10">7.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">女体化してのプレイは選べる嬢が少ないし, 結構痛いが, 女の子の気持ちがわかるようになるから, 一度ぐらいは経験しておくのはいいかもしれないぞ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Gender-Swap Sex Means Less Succu-Girl Choices, and It Kinda Hurts, but You Learn Just What Girls Feel, So You Should Give It a Try!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Jotai Kashite no Play wa Eraberu Jou ga Sukunai shi, Kekkou Itai ga, Onnanoko no Kimochi ga Wakaru You ni Naru kara, Ichido Gurai wa Keiken Shite Oku no wa Ii Kamo Shirenaizo!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="225433" update="2019-12-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-02-01</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">低級淫魔は, もう出ないといっているのにもかかわらず, さらに搾り取ろうとしてきてもはや拷問の域. サラマンダーちゃんは身も心もサラもマンもダーも, とてもホットだがホットすぎてホットんど逝っちゃいそうになる!!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Salamander Girls Have Such Hot Bods, Hearts, Sals, and Manders, That You Can`t Help But Get Fired Up About `Em!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Teikyuu Inma wa, Mou Denai to Itte Iru no ni mo Kakawarazu, Sara ni Shiboritorou Toshite Kite Mohaya Goumon no Iki. Salamander-chan wa Mi mo Kokoro mo Sala mo Man mo Der mo, Totemo Hot Daga Hot Sugite Hottondo Icchaisou ni Naru!!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="226131" update="2020-01-19">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2020-01-04</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="226132" update="2020-01-19">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2020-01-04</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.15</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="226386" update="2020-01-26">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-02-08</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">単眼娘の輝く瞳に溺れたいけどハードル高すぎで, 同じくハードル高すぎるキノコ嬢選びはこの道数百年のプロに任せてヌルヌルねっとりふかふか!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Wanna Drown in a Cyclops Girl`s Pretty Eye, but It`s Pretty Hard? Speaking of Hard, Let the Pros Pick Out the Perfect Mushroom Girl for a Slimy, Sticky Good Time!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tangan Musume no Kagayaku Hitomi ni Oboretai kedo Hurdle Takasugide, Onajiku Hurdle Takasugiru Kinoko Jou Erabi wa Kono Michi Suuhyakunen no Pro ni Makasete Nurunuru Nettori Fukafuka!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="226387" update="2020-01-26">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-02-15</airdate>
<rating votes="6">7.39</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ゴーレムは, 理想の女の子さえ作れればすごく楽しめるけどセンスが問われるし, モデルにバレたら大変なことになるかもしれない. ウィルオーウィスプの店は幻想的な光のパレードがイク, まさに夢の園.</title>
<title xml:lang="en">You Can Build the Perfect Golem Girl, but Don`t Let the Girl You Base Her Off of Find Out. Cum to the Land of Dreams on the Light of the Will o` the Wisps.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Golem wa, Risou no Onnanoko Sae Tsukurereba Sugoku Tanoshimeru kedo Sense ga Towareru shi, Model ni Baretara Taihen na Koto ni Naru Kamoshirenai. Will-o`-wisp no Mise wa Gensouteki na Hikari no Parade ga Iku, Masa ni Yume no Sono.</title>
</episode>
<episode id="226388" update="2020-01-26">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-02-22</airdate>
<rating votes="7">4.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">産卵ショーでおっさんたちの目がらんらん! 出します見せますメイドリーちゃんのひみつ! そしてついに発表! サキュバス嬢人気投票!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Gang Gets Laid at the Egg-stravagant Egg-Laying Show, Miss Meidri`s Deep, Dark Secret Uncovered, and the Succu-Girl Popularity Ranking Is Unveiled!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sanran Show de Ossan-tachi no Me ga Ranran! Dasemasu Misemasu Meidri-chan no Himitsu! Soshite Tsui ni Happyou! Succubus Jou Ninkitouhyou!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="226389" update="2020-01-26">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-02-29</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">イメサキュのエロスの夢は夜開き, 天使のランスは聖槍ならぬ性槍で, サキュバスタワーは永遠にガチマヨ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Succu-girl Roleplay Will Get You Going All Night, the Angel`s Holy Lance Is Great at Lancing Holes, the Succubus Tower Lasts Forever, but You (and Your Mayo) Won`t!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ima-Succu no Eros no Yume wa Yoru Hiraki, Tenshi no Lance wa Seisou Naranu Seisou de, Succubus Tower wa Eien ni Gachi Mayo!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="227087" update="2020-02-23">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-03-07</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">肢体と死体の間には深くて暗いナニがあり, 若き天使はローション大爆発で, 野生で野性のレビュアーたちはエロのライバル!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Deep, Dark Something Lies Between the Living and the Dead, the Darling Angel`s Lotion Explosion, and the Uncouth, Unsanctioned Reviewer Rivals Are in Their Scene!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shitai to Shitai no Aida ni wa Fukakute Kurai Nani ga Ari, Wakaki Tenshi wa Lotion Dai Bakuhatsu de, Yasei de Yasei no Reviewer-tachi wa Ero no Rival!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="227088" update="2020-02-23">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-03-14</airdate>
<rating votes="5">8.26</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ついに明かされるオール40点満点の謎! 新妻で淫乱家庭教師で雌豚で恋人気分! 出ます出します引き取ります! 無限解放! 大満足の3日間! お汁もたっぷり! みんなお幸せになっちゃええええっ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let Your Eyes Behold the Glory and Mystery of the Brothel with a Perfect Score! Take a Newlywed of a Horny Tutor or a Little Piggie as Your Lover! They`ll Squeeze, Squeeze, Squeeze It Outta Ya! Infinite Pleasure over a Satisfying Three-Day Excursion! True Happiness Awaits!!!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsui ni Akasareru All 40 Ten Manten no Nazo! Niizuma de Inran Kateikyoushi de Mebuta de Koibitokibun! Demasu Dashimasu Hikitorimasu! Mugen Kaihou! Dai Manzoku no Mikkakan! Oshiru mo Tappuri! Minna Oshiawase ni Nacchaeeee!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="227089" update="2020-02-23">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-03-21</airdate>
<rating votes="6">4.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">片っ端から淫魔をイかせまくる恐るべき絶倫は博愛主義者で, あぶく銭が入った酔っ払いの末路はお察しの通りで, ミツエの部屋は本日完結!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Frighteningly Faultless Philanthropist Sexually Satisfies Several Succubi, Drunken Fools and Their Money Are, Of Course, Soon Parted, and Mitsue`s Room Comes to a Close!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Katappashi kara Inma o Ikase Makuru Osorubeki Zetsurin wa Hakuaishugisha de, Abukuzeni ga Haitta Yopparai no Matsuro wa Osasshi no Doori de, Mitsue no Heya wa Honjitsu Kanketsu!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="227090" update="2020-02-23">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-03-28</airdate>
<rating votes="5">7.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">レビュアーズを愛してくださったみなさん, さようなら....... サキュバス嬢が居る限り, レビュアーズも永遠に生き続けるでしょう. あなたがレビュアーズを想うとき, いつもこれだけは思い出すでしょう. ひとは他人をイカした時, 初めて自分もイケるということを.......</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Farewell, Beloved Fans of Our Beloved Reviewers... Worry Not; As Long As Succu-girls Keep Working Hard, So Too Will Our Reviewers. When You Think of Our Heroes, Remember This: When You Help Other (Get Their Fuck On), You`re Only Helping Yourself (Get Your Fuck On)...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Reviewers o Ai Shite Kudasatta Minasan, Sayounara....... Succubus-jou ga Iru Kagiri, Reviewers mo Eien ni Ikitsuzukeru Deshou. Anata ga Reviewers o Omou Toki, Itsumo Kore dake wa Omoidasu Deshou. Hito wa Tanin o Ikashita Toki, Hajimete Jibun mo Ikeru to Iu Koto o.......</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
