<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="14982" restricted="false">
<type>Web</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2020-03-27</startdate>
<enddate>2020-03-27</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Michiru Rescue!</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">みちるレスキュー!</title>
</titles>
<url>https://animetamago.jp/title.php?id=3</url>
<creators>
<name id="14960" type="Character Design">Maruyama Shuuji</name>
<name id="8937" type="Direction">Ochi Koujin</name>
<name id="52830" type="Animation Work">Yumeta Company</name>
</creators>
<description>When four glowing orbs of different colors (blue, yellow, silver, and purple) fly through space chasing after a red-black orb, they end up hitting each other, causing only the blue sphere to fall to the earth and reach the room where the main character, Michiru, sleeps. On the other hand, the red-black orb also appears on the earth turning itself into a boy, and start to raise Mejiro birds illegally.
One day, Michiru is at a flea market in a park, when a large flock of Mejiro birds appear over the sky and start attacking people. The yellow, silver, and purple orbs show up and try to calm down the flock of Mejiro, but their chirp is relentless. At that moment, a voice resounds inside Michiru`s head telling her to save the Mejiro...
Source: AnimeAnime.global</description>
<picture>242465.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>23159</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>40037</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>https://animetamago.jp/title.php?id=3</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>371193</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="4859" parentid="6153" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-06-09">
<name>Wakate Animator Ikusei Project</name>
<description>The Young Animator Training Project is an annual project launched in 2010 and funded by the Japanese government`s Agency for Cultural Affairs. The project, which culminates in a series of shorts produced by various animation studios each year, means to address the concern that more of the Japanese animation process is being outsourced overseas, thus leading to a decline in opportunities to teach animation techniques within Japan. As such, the animation production for each short is required to be based in Japan, and professionals must impart their know-how to the young animators through on-the-job training.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<episodes>
<episode id="227348" update="2020-03-28">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<airdate>2020-03-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Complete Movie</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
