<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="15072" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2020-04-05</startdate>
<enddate>2020-12-20</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Gal to Kyouryuu</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Gal and Dinosaur</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Gyaru to Kyouryuu</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ギャルと恐竜</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Gal &amp; Dino</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="official">辣妹與恐龍</title>
</titles>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="792517">Don`t write this off just because it`s subdivided into webisodes or contains live-action segments. It`s good for chuckle, it`s unexpectedly heartwarming, and it`s just plain cute.

The ending theme is a jam, too.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://galkyo.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="58622" type="Original Work">Mori Moriko</name>
<name id="44124" type="Animation Work">Kamikaze Douga</name>
<name id="22958" type="Series Composition">Aoki Jun</name>
<name id="22958" type="Direction">Aoki Jun</name>
<name id="58623" type="Original Work">Tomimura Cota</name>
<name id="43533" type="Music">Gin</name>
<name id="59683" type="Animation Work">Space Neko Company</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a comedy seinen manga written by http://anidb.net/cr58622 [Mori Moriko] and drawn by http://anidb.net/cr58623 [Tomimura Cota].
http://anidb.net/ch107840 [Kaede] is a fashion-conscious young woman who wakes up one morning to realize that, in her drunken stupor last night, she brought a http://anidb.net/ch109121 [dinosaur] home with her. The dinosaur can`t talk but does seem intelligent, can eat instant ramen, and is deathly afraid of cats even though they seem to love him. Will this be a permanent living arrangement?
Source: ANN
Note: On May 12, 2020, it was announced that airings of episode 8 and onward were delayed due to the effects of the ongoing COVID-19 pandemic. On July 19, 2020, it was announced that both the anime and live-action series will resume on October 2020.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="69">3.77</permanent>
<temporary count="69">5.24</temporary>
</ratings>
<picture>242810.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22492</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>40358</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://galkyo.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Gal_to_Kyōryū</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ギャルと恐竜</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>5633</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>369615</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>22673</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="23">
<externalentity>
<identifier>galkyo_info</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="26">
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=AUJwiICd9O4</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>watch?v=pGvBe-gRePQ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="34">
<externalentity>
<url>https://www.funimation.com/shows/gal-dino/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="566" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-10">
<name>dinosaur</name>
<description>Dinosaurs are vertebrate animals that dominated terrestrial ecosystems for over 160 million years, first appearing approximately 230 million years ago. At the end of the Cretaceous Period, 66 million years ago, non-avian dinosaurs suffered a catastrophic extinction, which ended their dominance on land. Taxonomists consider modern birds to be the direct descendants of theropod dinosaurs.
Since the first dinosaur was recognized in the 19th century, mounted, fossilized dinosaur skeletons have become major attractions at museums around the world. Dinosaurs have become a part of world culture and remain consistently popular, especially among children. They have been featured in best-selling books and films such as Jurassic Park, and new discoveries are regularly covered by the media.
Source: Dinopedia</description>
<picurl>191115.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2656" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>satire</name>
<description>In satire, vices, follies, abuses, and shortcomings are held up to ridicule, ideally with the intent of shaming individuals, and society itself, into improvement. Although satire is usually meant to be funny, its greater purpose is often constructive social criticism, using wit as a weapon. (Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2855" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-03">
<name>under one roof</name>
<description>For some reason or another, the main protagonist (e.g. male in harem / female in reverse-harem) is living together with many other characters of the opposite-gender, all under the same roof (in the same dwelling unit).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2857" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-10-04">
<name>anthropomorphism</name>
<description>Anthropomorphism is the attribution of uniquely human characteristics to non-human beings, inanimate objects, or natural or supernatural phenomena. If it`s an animal or an object (AI excluded) and it speaks and/or does other human-like things (dresses up) then we`re dealing with anthropomorphism.
Anthropomorphism leans more on the animal-looking side when compared to http://anidb.net/t7 [juujin], which leans more on the human-looking side.
Usage the tag image for reference, when tagging characters:

* This is a juujin.
* This is split between juujin and anthropomorphism, to be decided on a case-by-case basis, but most likely leans on the human-looking juujin side in most cases.
* This is anthropomorphism; tag both anthropomorphism and the respective animal type.
* This is anthropomorphism; tag both anthropomorphism and the respective animal type.
* This is just a regular animal; do not tag juujin or anthropomorphism — only tag the actual animal type.
</description>
<picurl>252666.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3185" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-27">
<name>wordplay</name>
<description>The characters play with words. 
E.g. purposely or accidentally use similar-sounding but wrongly applied words in the Japanese original, leading to supposedly funny misunderstandings and confusion.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3217" parentid="2864" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-17">
<name>working life</name>
<description>The life of someone actually working on a often less than glamorous job is depicted in this anime. The job is taxing and the pay is low, not really the dream job one would choose to work in.
Examples: Working as salesperson in a department store, or as a waitress in a family restaurant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3750" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-09-08">
<name>thick line animation</name>
<description>The characters are drawn with a thicker outline than is usually seen in anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3867" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-22">
<name>ED variety</name>
<description>Several ED sequences in this anime have either a different song or different animation, maybe even to the point of having a unique ED for each episode.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4131" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-05-11">
<name>cultural references</name>
<description>The plot of this anime shows signs of cultural references, these are often jokes that make reference to a certain custom, habit or history that is specifically attributed to that culture. Knowledge of the culture itself is needed in order to properly understand these jokes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4522" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>social commentary</name>
<description>Social commentary is the act of rebelling against an individual, or a group of people by rhetorical means. This is most often done with the idea of implementing or promoting change by informing the general populace about a given problem and appealing to people’s sense of justice. (Source: Wikipedia)&#13;
&#13;
Since this is anime, usually, the mores of Japan and the Japanese society are scrutinised, but not restricted to that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4572" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-09-22">
<name>human-animal relationship</name>
<description>The relationship between a human and an animal (or an animal-like creature like a dragon) plays an important role in the plot of this anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4614" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>narration</name>
<description>The most common example is that of a voice, either that of one of the characters or entirely unrelated, that appears at the beginning of an episode to offer a summary or introduction, and at the end of an episode for closure or for a preview to hint upon what to expect next.
Another use of narration comes in the form of a dominant voice belonging to one of the protagonists, intended only for the viewer and revealing the intimate thoughts to whom it belongs. This type of narration occurs frequently throughout the duration of the episode or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5227" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-04-26">
<name>alternating animation style</name>
<description>The animation style in this show may change between scenes, usually making the anime experimental in a way. This may be a form of artistic visualisation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5834" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>show within a show</name>
<description>A fictional TV (or radio, or stage) show that takes place within an actual TV show; or, occasionally, a fictional instalment or incarnation of an actual show. Many comedies have short one-off gags where they parody existing shows.
Example: A large part of Martian Successor Nadesico is centred around the fictional popular anime Gekigangar III, which is being watched by several characters of the Nadesico crew.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5980" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-24">
<name>live-action imagery</name>
<description>This anime incorporates still images and/or video footage of real-world objects and locations into the animation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6055" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-15">
<name>time loop</name>
<description>A time loop is a common plot device in science fiction (especially in universes where time travel is commonplace). Events in the story repeat themselves a number of times with or without some variation with each pass. Most characters either do not realise this is occurring or are attempting to break the cycle in some way. 
One well-known example of this is in the 1993 film Groundhog Day, in which the main character is the only one aware of the time loop, although time loops had appeared in many fictional works prior to that. Stories with time loops commonly center on correcting past mistakes or on getting a character to recognise some key truth; escape from the loop may then follow.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6349" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-13">
<name>multi-segment episodes</name>
<description>Multi-segment episodes are split into several short segments (parts), usually with separate titles and independent storylines.
Not to be confused with http://anidb.net/t5852 [short episodes], which are regular episodes that are much shorter than the standard length (up to and including 10 minutes).
Also not to be confused with an OVA or music video with multiple (otherwise unrelated) full-length http://anidb.net/t7241 [bundled episodes] consolidated into a single episode video track.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6399" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-25">
<name>episodic</name>
<description>An episodic anime consists of many successive short arcs that are generally 1-2 episodes in length, with strong plot continuity within each arc but generally little continuity from one arc to the next. For long shows (well upwards of 50 episodes), the episode count constraint is less tight; for example, a show with close to 250 episodes would also be considered episodic if it consisted of a majority of arcs of up to 3 or maybe 4 episodes and possibly also very few slightly longer arcs.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6840" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-07">
<name>social media</name>
<description>Social media are computer-mediated technologies that allow the creating and sharing of information, ideas, career interests and other forms of expression via virtual communities and networks.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="107838" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-12">
<name>Senpai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>246109.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="60178" picture="245717.jpg">Kudou Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107839" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-12">
<name>Yamada</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>246108.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="56190" picture="249034.jpg">Natsuyoshi Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107840" type="main character in" update="2020-04-12">
<name>Kaede</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>246106.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="53024" picture="232385.jpg">Shimabukuro Miyuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="107841" type="secondary cast in" update="2020-04-12">
<name>Shouta</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>246110.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="37882" picture="173035.jpg">Yamashita Seiichirou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="109121" type="main character in" update="2020-04-12">
<name>Kyouryuu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>246107.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="227705" update="2020-06-18">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-04-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">2.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">はじめまして! / 猫がいたよ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Nice to Meet You! / Look, Kitties!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hajimemashite! / Neko ga Ita yo</title>
<summary>Gal meets Dino. Dino meets ramen. Kitties meet Dino, much to Dino`s dismay. Later, Mieharu enjoys a wholesome Christmas with Dino.
Source: Funimation</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="227706" update="2020-06-18">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-04-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">友だちがやってきたよ / 元カレと会ったよ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My Friend`s Coming Over / I Ran Into Your Ex</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tomodachi ga Yatte Kita yo / Motokare to Deatta yo</title>
<summary>Yamada swings by to meet Dino and watch TV. Dino invites Kaede`s ex in for a game of cards. Later, Shouta Aoi tries to prevent a recurring disaster from happening.
Source: Funimation</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="227707" update="2020-06-18">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-04-19</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">お買い物だよ / 道を歩くよ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Goin` Shopping / Goin` Out and About</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Okaimono Da yo / Michi o Aruku yo</title>
<summary>Dino goes out on the town. Kaede asks her Senpai for help with Dino`s diet. Later, Kaede and Dino teleport to the park for an outdoor adventure.
Source: Funimation</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="227708" update="2020-06-18">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-04-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">しっぽはやめて / メリークリスマス!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Stop Messing with My Tail! / Merry Christmas!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shippo wa Yamete / Merry Christmas!</title>
<summary>Kaede gets creative with Dino`s problematic tail. Kaede gets a special Christmas visit at work. Later, Dino meets comedian Hollywood Zakoshisyoh.
Source: Funimation</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="228390" update="2020-06-18">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-05-03</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">良いお年を / 神様にごあいさつだよ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Happy New Year! / It`s Time to Pay Our Respects to the Gods</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yoi Otoshi o / Kamisama ni Goaisatsu Da yo</title>
<summary>Kaede and Dino celebrate the New Year. Dino visits its very first shrine. Later, Dino goes camping by itself.
Source: Funimation</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="228391" update="2020-06-18">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-05-10</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">何を借りようかな / みかんおいしいね</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Let`s Rent Something / Mikan Are So Yummy</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nani o Kariyou ka na / Mikan Oishii ne</title>
<summary>Kaede and Dino rent movies to watch. Kaede`s ex brings over mikan. Later, Dino and Kaede find ways to pass the time inside.
Source: Funimation</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="228392" update="2020-06-18">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-05-17</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">しんぱいだな / ないしょのお話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I`m Worried About You / Guy Talk</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinpai Da na / Naisho no Ohanashi</title>
<summary>When Kaede catches a cold, Dino tries to find a way to cheer her up. Kaede`s ex invites Dino out for some guy talk. Later, Dino brings over a gaggle of comedians to brighten up Kaede`s day.
Source: Funimation</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="228393" update="2020-12-02">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-11-22</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ラーメン以外も食べるよ / バースデーパーティーだよ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">It Eats More Than Just Ramen / Time for a Birthday Party!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ramen Igai mo Taberu yo / Birthday Party Da yo!</title>
<summary>Kaede`s coworker struggles to invite Kaede over for dinner. The gang throws Dino a birthday party. Later, Dino and guest stars solve an egg-citing mystery.
Source: Funimation</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="230129" update="2020-06-25">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2020-02-05</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">「ギャルと恐竜」実写版PV【毎週土曜25時〜放送中!】</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 1 (0:44): Live Action Preview</title>
</episode>
<episode id="230130" update="2020-06-25">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2020-03-04</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">「ギャルと恐竜」アニメ版PV【毎週土曜25時〜放送中!】</title>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 2 (1:00)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="234674" update="2020-12-02">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-11-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">ちょっとこわい / 二度寝するよ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">That Was Kinda Scary / It Loves Going Back to Sleep</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chotto Kowai / Nidone Suru yo!</title>
<summary>Kaede and Dino experience a terrifying blackout. Dino escapes to dreamland. Later, Dino makes Kaede`s dreams come true.
Source: Funimation</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="234675" update="2020-12-14">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-12-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">おともだちだよ / 字を書くよ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">We`re Friends / Calligraphy Time</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Otomodachi Da yo / Ji o Kaku yo</title>
<summary>Dino makes a feathered friend. Kaede and Yamada teach Dino about calligraphy. Later, Dino has a pawsitively purr-fect time with a lost cat.
Source: Funimation</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="234676" update="2020-12-14">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-12-13</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">もしもし~ / ラクだよ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Helloooo? / No Worries</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Moshimoshii / Raku Da yo</title>
<summary>Kaede loses her phone. Dino makes some hard-earned cash and learns about utility bills. Later, Kaede and Dino go to the amusement park.
Source: Funimation</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="234677" update="2020-11-22">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2020-12-20</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">お外でご飯 / 平和だな~</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Going Out to Eat / So Peaceful~</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Osoto de Gohan / Heiwa Da naa</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
