<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="199" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>26</episodecount>
<startdate>1998-10-02</startdate>
<enddate>1999-03-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Kareshi Kanojo no Jijou</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Tales at North Hills High</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">His &amp; Her Circumstances</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="synonym">Las circunstancias de él y ella</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">С его стороны - с её стороны</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="synonym">As Razões Dele, os Motivos Dela</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="synonym">Kare Kano</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Неговите и нейните обстоятелства</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Kareshi Kanojyo no Jijyo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">KareKano</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">他和她的故事</title>
<title xml:lang="fa" type="synonym">موقعیت این و آن</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">KKNJ</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Kare Kano</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">彼氏彼女の事情</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">His and Her Circumstances</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Kare Kano - Mein Geheimnis Dein Geheimnis</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Entre elle et lui</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Le situazioni di Lui &amp; Lei</title>
<title xml:lang="es" type="official">Kare Kano</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Его и Её обстоятельства</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="official">Jego i Jej Okoliczności</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="6466" approval="207" total="240">Kimi ni Todoke</anime>
<anime id="7008" approval="149" total="230">Kaichou wa Maid-sama!</anime>
<anime id="9235" approval="77" total="98">Tonari no Kaibutsu-kun</anime>
<anime id="5053" approval="43" total="62">Lovely Complex</anime>
<anime id="4441" approval="38" total="58">Bokura ga Ita</anime>
<anime id="5678" approval="10" total="20">Itazura na Kiss</anime>
<anime id="10385" approval="7" total="11">Ao Haru Ride</anime>
<anime id="9229" approval="6" total="9">Hori-san to Miyamura-kun</anime>
<anime id="34" approval="5" total="20">Fruits Basket</anime>
<anime id="5276" approval="5" total="19">KimiKiss Pure Rouge</anime>
<anime id="285" approval="5" total="13">Kodomo no Omocha (1996)</anime>
<anime id="11998" approval="4" total="15">Kuzu no Honkai</anime>
<anime id="9236" approval="4" total="11">Sukitte Ii na yo.</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="18">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="180200">One of the best love stories I`ve ever watched. The down side is that Gainax went bankrupt in midstride and didn`t finish it, so the last third is horrible quality and almost half the story one has to read on the manga</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="51579">Hum.... read the manga!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Well, this anime had it all to be a successful shoujo and it had a trump: a sensitive director capable of portraying depression and obsession in a very unique way.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Unfortunately, for reasons I`m not that sure, the director left his position in the middle of the show, leaving it to meet a terrible end.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A certain "I DON`T KNOW WHO"... someone very unrespectful and very discourteous &amp;gt;&amp;lt; insulted the author by presenting this shitty version that was aired. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Shame on the TV Team!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="134982">its so funny..</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="460400">very nice anime. good characters, nice story and along with drama and comedy well binded together to form a great slice of life</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="221885">It`s certainly a classic, and one of the best anime that are genuinely focused on the relationship &amp; its troubles. But its age does show a bit already, and the pacing can be a bit slow.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="84224">really good at everything but not the best at anything 
such a waste it is unfinished</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="194400">finaly, some action beyond getting together</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="84121">Simple but with various styles, creative and unpredictable presenting make this anime interesting.&lt;br /&gt;PS. SD characters are all cute and very funny.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="76759">It`s old, but it feels new. Really liked it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="238293">It`s a really great anime. Nice story and this old-school animation... you have to see it !</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="136401">Its one of the best of its gender, its one of those "love - love" high school golden years we all had (with more or less success :P)!! Lively recommended :D!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="17039">i`ve got to say that "elvenmon" is right. best love story ever. complex and beautiful. problem is, the dvd-release for the american market has some changes, for instance in ep 18 is a "love-scene" that has been removed. i have some old svhs-releases by a unknown fansub-crew that contain this scene. plus: after ep 18 they do loose the grip on the story somehow... lots of reviewing older scenes, lots of summarys. what a shame. Again: go for the manga, it even has a decent ending!</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.gainax.co.jp/anime/karekano/index.html</url>
<creators>
<name id="718" type="Animation Work">Gainax</name>
<name id="720" type="Animation Work">J.C.Staff</name>
<name id="3487" type="Original Work">Tsuda Masami</name>
<name id="1955" type="Music">Sagisu Shirou</name>
<name id="2186" type="Animation Character Design">Hiramatsu Tadashi</name>
<name id="57" type="Series Composition">Anno Hideaki</name>
<name id="10021" type="Direction">Satou Hiroki</name>
<name id="57" type="Direction">Anno Hideaki</name>
<name id="57410" type="Direction">Anno Hideaki</name>
<name id="57409" type="Direction">Anno Hideaki</name>
</creators>
<description>http://anidb.net/ch1965 [Miyazawa Yukino] has always been a show-off. She always wanted to be number one, to be the very best in everything, to be adored by all others. Then one day, she meets her match: http://anidb.net/ch1966 [Arima Souichirou], who seems about as perfect as she strives to be. But no one is quite what they seem... for whenever Yukino goes home, off comes the ojou-sama (princess) façade — and on go the headbands, reading glasses, and sweats. Miss Congeniality is in fact a conniving, petty con-artist with a streak of absolute nerdy bliss. Of course, Yukino is not the only one hiding a secret, since Arima himself is not quite what he seems to be either.
In her eagerness to become number one, she declares Arima as her arch-enemy, but then he declares his love for her...</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="4692">7.38</permanent>
<temporary count="4753">7.98</temporary>
<review count="10">8.03</review>
</ratings>
<picture>133471.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>392</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>145</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>225</identifier>
<identifier>aqinsu</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.gainax.co.jp/anime/karekano/index.html</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>http://his-and-her.rightstuf.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Kare_Kano</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>彼氏彼女の事情</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>446</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>88882</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1751</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/290</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1998/karekano</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1077" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shoujo</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shoujo, literally meaning "girl", refers to a female audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2345" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-04-26">
<name>zettai ryouiki</name>
<description>Zettai ryouiki, literally "absolute territory", is an area of exposed skin of a female in the gap between http://anidb.net/t2137 [thigh-high] or over-the-knee http://anidb.net/t6419 [hosiery] and a http://anidb.net/t2451 [miniskirt], http://anidb.net/t2222 [shorts], or on occasion a http://anidb.net/t1200 [minidress]. In addition to the area itself, the term can describe the clothing combination. Please note that zettai ryouiki requires all three components: over-the-knee or thigh-high hosiery, thigh skin, and one of skirt, shorts, or minidress.
The "golden ratio" for the length of the miniskirt, the exposed portion of thigh, and the over-knee part of the hosiery is 4:1:2.5, with a tolerance of 25%. Letter grades have also been assigned for the ratio variants, from E (too much leg is seen, the skirt is too long) to A (short skirt, high socks, short exposed area). A further grade S has been conceived, adding the criteria of a http://anidb.net/t2455 [tsundere] wearing http://anidb.net/t1923 [twintails] to grade A.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>165582.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2654" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-13">
<name>medium awareness</name>
<description>Medium awareness is the situational and generally temporary awareness characters in works of fiction have and display of the very fact that they are characters in works of fiction. For example, they may comment about the background music, quip about the script or narration, complain about the roles given to them by the writer or their lack of screen time, see the subtitles that appear on screen, inform the audience about the arrival of the commercial break, and even use medium effects as tools. The most common form of medium awareness is known as breaking the fourth wall, in which characters speak directly to the audience, either to it as a whole or to specific members of it. The "fourth wall" is the imaginary "wall" at the front of the stage of a proscenium theatre through which the audience sees the play; it is a metaphor for the boundary between what happens inside the work, to the characters, and outside it, to the audience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2778" parentid="2858" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-11-09">
<name>slow when it comes to love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3148" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>open-ended</name>
<description>The ending of this anime is left to the viewer`s imagination. There are no clear hints at a definite story outcome, several possibilities are presented without closure, or the story ends suddenly without explanation. There may also be room for a sequel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3227" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-06-24">
<name>introspection</name>
<description>The characters in this anime do not walk through life simply accepting how they are, but quite on the contrary constantly try to understand their own motives, feelings and reactions to the other protagonists. 
This self-searching included the questions: "Who am I?", "What makes me tick?", "What do I want?", "What do others expect of me?", etc.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3469" parentid="6232" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-04-26">
<name>popularity fetish</name>
<description>At least one character in this anime obsesses with being or becoming popular with the other characters.
E.g. a school girl may want to become as popular as an idol (which could turn out to be not what she hoped for). Good school grades may also improve popularity, at least in fiction.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3546" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-01-08">
<name>experimental animation</name>
<description>This anime uses distinct, alternative animation — much unlike other contemporary anime — either throughout or in individual episodes/sequences.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4199" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-02-20">
<name>live-action closing -- TO BE MOVED AND DELETED</name>
<description>This tag is set to be removed. For each tagged anime, please tag the corresponding ending/credits episodes with the http://anidb.net/t6679 [live-action episode] tag (adding them and their relation to the ending songs if necessary) and then remove this tag from it. Please do not apply this credit to the main episode that has the live-action ending, only to the corresponding credits episode. For example, if episode 22 has a live-action ending, and that ending is also credits episode C7, tag episode C7, not episode 22.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4304" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-04-26">
<name>anti-climactic end</name>
<description>The story in this anime and the character development were building up so some special point, and the viewer will probably have been looking forward to this resolution. But the ending was a let-down.
This may have several reasons, e.g. it may simply be "bad" story-telling, or the animation studio ran out of money and had to prematurely end the story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4314" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-04-11">
<name>psychological</name>
<description>Directed toward dealing with or affecting the mind, especially as a function of awareness, feeling, or motivation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4440" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>boy meets girl</name>
<description>A classical type of plot in story writing, where the story begins with a boy meeting a girl leading to romantic development between the two. More often than not the boy loses the girl later on and has to find her again.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5227" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-04-26">
<name>alternating animation style</name>
<description>The animation style in this show may change between scenes, usually making the anime experimental in a way. This may be a form of artistic visualisation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5768" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>intact family</name>
<description>The main character`s family is a so-called "nuclear family". Wherein both parents are alive and present in his or her life. This is actually relatively rare for anime, where "parental abandonment" is the norm.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5884" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-03-22">
<name>slow-paced</name>
<description>The story — including its characters and events — develop slowly.
May contain a weak continuity of plot and/or character development. 
Or may be a story telling device to increase the "sense of foreboding" in an anime with thriller or horror setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5965" parentid="6247" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2015-02-10">
<name>incomplete story</name>
<description>The show does not cover all of the original work (if present) or was cancelled prematurely, leaving plot lines unresolved or aborting character development. Sometimes the show runs through all its initially slotted episodes and adapts all of the original work (if applicable) but fails to present a proper ending, leaving viewers wondering whether they`re missing the final episodes.
In some cases, this may overlap with the studio forging an anime-original ending. Such an ending normally manages to allow the show to "finish", but may still suffer from incomplete story issues.
An incomplete storyline is not to be confused with the sequel bait, which is when the story presented by the show is finished but leaves enough room for a sequel to be produced. Sometimes this goes as far as to present a new potential problem in the last few minutes; that is usual for after-credits footage in movies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6232" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-10-21">
<name>character related tags which need deleting or merging</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6247" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2019-06-02">
<name>ending tags that need merging</name>
<description>See also: http://anidb.net/post426253 [http://anidb.net/post426253] and http://anidb.net/c6774745 [http://anidb.net/c6774745]</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="1965" type="main character in" update="2016-03-28">
<rating votes="45">8.83</rating>
<name>Miyazawa Yukino</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Smart, attractive, athletic and talented, Yukino Miyazawa had made herself to appear to be the model student. Both her male and female peers express their admiration for her, often asking her for help and commenting about her model features and characteristics. Her "perfect" exterior is a façade to hide the fact that everything she does is done solely to receive praise from others, and that she acts slovenly at home. She is a self-professed "queen of vanity", having been that way ever since childhood when her parents would praise her for the slightest actions. Yukino once practiced playing her recorder and almost vomiting blood from staying up all night practising. With so much praise, however, she never realized that she never had any real friends aside from her family, and was considered by her peers as a semi-approachable "guest". This all changes when Yukino meets Soichiro Arima, another model student who beats her high school entrance exam score, and is even more popular and athletic than Yukino.</description>
<picture>184337.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="348" picture="17186.jpg">Enomoto Atsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1966" type="main character in" update="2009-01-06">
<rating votes="14">7.45</rating>
<name>Arima Souichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Smart, attractive, athletic, and talented like Yukino, Soichiro Arima becomes Yukino`s rival at school. Very handsome and popular, Soichiro excels at kendo and becomes a national champion. He is at first smitten by Yukino, unaware that she secretly hated him and constantly tried to compete with him. After unwittingly discovering that Yukino is not the model student everyone thinks she is, Soichiro blackmails her into doing his school work so he can spend more time with her. After resolving the issue and becoming each other`s first true friend, they eventually fall in love.</description>
<picture>16736.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="444" picture="17329.jpg">Suzuki Chihiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1967" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-06">
<rating votes="6">6.96</rating>
<name>Izawa Maho</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An athletic, beautiful and intelligent student, Maho was the star of her middle school. But she falls out of the limelight when she arrives at Hokuei High School because of Yukino. Maho becomes jealous of Yukino, which mirrors Yukino`s jealousy of Soichiro. Maho also mentions that she had feelings of love for Yukino when she first saw her. That feeling changed when she found out that Yukino was not as perfect as she made everyone believe. Her jealousy becomes hatred and she turns the entire class against Yukino. However, it eventually backfires on her and the class turns on Maho. Yukino takes the high road and makes the first efforts to turn Maho into a friend. Maho soon becomes part of Yukino`s circle of friends, and although she maintains her aloof attitude, she also eventually learns to cherish the friendships.</description>
<picture>16737.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="140" picture="170306.jpg">Noda Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1968" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-06">
<rating votes="5">6.05</rating>
<name>Asaba Hideaki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yukino and Soichiro`s lazy and girl-crazy friend, very handsome and popular. Although bright enough to be accepted to the selective Hokuei High School, Hideaki is a terrible student, and spends most of his time surfing or chasing girls. Hideaki and Soichiro are considered the two most handsome boys in school, and while Soichiro is largely indifferent to the attention, Hideaki makes the most of it. During their school`s annual culture-fest, Hideaki`s class mounts a "Hideaki Asaba Dinner Show" which is a big hit with all the girls, but gives Yukino and Soichiro the creeps.</description>
<picture>16738.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="484" picture="17476.jpg">Kisaichi Atsushi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1969" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-06">
<rating votes="9">7.23</rating>
<name>Shibahime Tsubasa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A petite, beautiful girl who loved Soichiro since they attended middle school together. (She inherited her light hair, jade eyes, and cute looks from her father.) Although she studied hard so she could attend Hokuei High School with Soichiro, a bad skateboarding accident prevents her from starting school with everyone else. In the past, Tsubasa tried to confess her love to Soichiro several times, but Soichiro was comically oblivious. So she settled for being treated as Soichiro`s younger sister as long as he did not have his affections occupied by another girlfriend. But upon learning that Soichiro has a girlfriend, she becomes insanely jealous and increasingly resentful of Yukino. After fighting it out with Yukino, they become good friends. Among their group of friends, she is the baby of the group and Yukino cannot resist her cuteness, often wanting to dress her up like a doll.</description>
<picture>16739.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="485" picture="223410.jpg">Shintani Mayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1970" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-06">
<rating votes="4">6.09</rating>
<name>Miyazawa Hiroyuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yukino, Tsukino and Kano`s father. After meeting as children they married right after high school, a continuous source of consternation for Miyako`s father. When Hiroyuki asked to marry Miyako, her father beat him black-and-blue. Hiroyuki still bickers with his father-in-law, grumbling that the old fool could not let go of his daughter. His father-in-law was a policeman, and Hiroyuki encountered the old man under unfavourable conditions; he was caught while he and his friends were forcibly riding Miyako`s new bike.</description>
<picture>16740.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="198" picture="202893.jpg">Kusao Takeshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1971" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-06">
<rating votes="4">7.35</rating>
<name>Miyazawa Miyako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yukino, Tsukino and Kano`s mother. After meeting as children they married right after high school, a continuous source of consternation for Miyako`s father. When Hiroyuki asked to marry Miyako, her father beat him black-and-blue. Hiroyuki still bickers with his father-in-law, grumbling that the old fool could not let go of his daughter. His father-in-law was a policeman, and Hiroyuki encountered the old man under unfavourable conditions; he was caught while he and his friends were forcibly riding Miyako`s new bike.</description>
<picture>16741.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="486" picture="235171.jpg">Koyama Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1972" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-06">
<rating votes="5">6.23</rating>
<name>Miyazawa Tsukino</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The middle daughter of the Miyazawa family, Tsukino seems to be goofier and more laid back than her sisters. Tsukino tends to tease Kano, the youngest daughter.</description>
<picture>16743.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="487" picture="61736.jpg">Watanabe Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1973" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-01-06">
<rating votes="6">6.40</rating>
<name>Miyazawa Kano</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The youngest of the three Miyazawa daughters, Kano is known for her shoujo manga and novel obsessions. She uses the knowledge from her love stories to help out Yukino when she is in a psychological pinch.</description>
<picture>16742.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="86" picture="222842.jpg">Yamamoto Maria</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31986" type="appears in" update="2011-05-07">
<rating votes="1">9.80</rating>
<name>Ikeda Kazuma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kazuma Ikeda is the son of the woman who Tsubasa`s father is dating. He`s a member, along with the minor characters Martin, Joker, Ushio and Atsuya, of an indie-rock band (called "Yin &amp; Yang") Because of his bleached hair and skull jewelry, he is initially looked upon with suspicion by Tsubasa. Because he wants his mother to be happy and eager to have a little sister, he has no objections to their marriage. However, he makes the mistake of assuming that Tsubasa is an elementary school student due to her short stature, when in fact she is a month older than he is, causing Tsubasa to have a spectacular meltdown. Although their first meeting goes badly, Kazuma runs into Tsubasa a few days later. He saves her from a "dirty old man with money", but when the police arrive, they assume that he is the bad guy due to his appearance, so Tsubasa has to save him. After spending some time together they realize that they are similar in their loneliness, and immediately bond like a real brother and sister. After their parents marry and move in together, Tsubasa and Kazuma become inseparable. Seeing their close bond during their move-in day, Tsubasa`s father presciently wonders whether step-siblings can marry. His big-brother-like qualities are what naturally brings him and Arima together as friends, with the latter very much impressed with Kazuma`s musical talent. Arima and Kazuma easily relate to each other without any trace of friction, which elicits a bit of jealousy from Hideaki and Takefumi. Kazuma falls in love with Tsubasa but she feels he chose music over her. He leaves home, but writes many love songs about Tsubasa, which become huge hits for his band in their first label album, which they all agree to call `Tsubasa`. After working through whether he loves Tsubasa as a sister or as a woman, he eventually returns home, and immediately asks Tsubasa to marry him. They marry soon after Tsubasa`s high school graduation.</description>
<picture>71123.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="31990" type="appears in" update="2011-05-07">
<name>Shibahime Toshiharu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71127.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="31994" type="appears in" update="2011-05-07">
<rating votes="1">5.01</rating>
<name>Ikeda Izumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hiromi is Kazuma`s mother. She met Toshiharu while working as a nurse at the hospital in which Tsubasa was treated for her skateboarding accident.
She`s young, nice and well-mannered, but she sometimes snaps, comically showing her true nature, which is why Tsubasa once told her "you remind me of a friend of mine" (referring to Yukino).</description>
<picture>71131.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9002" picture="33493.jpg">Tamura Tagame</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32009" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-07">
<rating votes="3">4.16</rating>
<name>Sena Rika</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Rika Sena is a gifted seamstress and craftswoman. A self-effacing person, Rika considers her life as average, and the least distinguished among her friends, but she is happy to be behind the scenes. She works on costumes for school plays and events. She has been best friends with Aya since childhood, and she and Aya have a strange dynamic where Aya will do something selfish towards Rika, but Rika`s sheer goodness will shame Aya ... and the cycle continues. At some point before the cultural festival, Yukino asked Rika if she had a special someone in mind, and Rika responded to with a denial and blush. Yukino eventually realizes that Rika has a crush on Aya`s older brother Kyo when she again blushed while talking to him. However, Aya has been aware of her friend`s and brother`s mutual infatuation for some time, and after the cultural festival was over, she supposedly stayed behind to do some work so that Rika and her brother would have dinner without her. Though Rika sees herself as the most average and unimpressive member of the group, Tsubaki points out that Rika is actually the most popular with the "regular guys," i.e. the kind that would never tell a girl how they feel. The men in the classroom tense up, confirming Tsubaki`s theory. As such, the only one who sees Rika as unimpressive is Rika herself. With her sewing skills, Rika eventually becomes the designated seamstress of Tsubasa`s father, a famous fashion designer, who she is a big fan of.</description>
<picture>71135.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="80" picture="228656.jpg">Fukui Yukari</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32011" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-07">
<rating votes="1">6.08</rating>
<name>Sawada Aya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Aya Sawada is a published writer at a very young age, Aya is obsessive compulsive when it comes to her writing. She writes a play for the newly formed school drama club, and chases down Maho and Yukino to play lead parts. Although both Maho and Yukino run away at first, Yukino changes her mind after reading the play. Yukino`s sister Kano is a big fan of Aya`s books. Aya occasionally smokes despite her young age, which Rika and Yukino disapprove of. Later, Aya continues her career as a writer. But like in her younger days, she rushes like mad to meet publishing deadlines due to her forgetfulness. Her capable editor is Kano Miyazawa, Yukino`s younger sister.</description>
<picture>71140.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="43083" picture="172562.jpg">Motoya Yukiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32012" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-05-07">
<rating votes="2">6.68</rating>
<name>Tsubaki Sakura</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tsubaki Sakura is one of Yukino`s friends. A talented athlete, her tomboyish prankster attitude eventually catches up to her in the person of a person from her past, Tonami Takefumi. Initially, she could not recognise Takefumi, who underwent a complete transformation during the three years he was away. Takefumi uses this as leverage in his quest to get revenge on Tsubaki. As time goes by, Tsubaki`s never-say-die attitude and Takefumi`s realisation that he is in love with Tsubaki resolves the conflict between them. After graduating from high school, the two leave Japan to travel the world together. Tsubaki studies at an Egyptian university and eventually becomes a professor of archaeology at an American university. She uses her instincts and capabilities to discover many archaeological sites.</description>
<picture>71141.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="311" picture="44706.jpg">Chiba Saeko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32013" type="appears in" update="2011-05-07">
<name>Tounami Takefumi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Takefumi Tonami was a fat, sickly, and spoiled child who was constantly picked on in elementary school. He was somewhat protected by the tomboy Tsubaki, who, while protecting him from other bullies, would bully Takefumi herself. When he asked Tsubaki why she paid attention to him, she told him that a teacher had asked her to look after him. After hearing this, Takefumi is humiliated as he had never been in his life; he is humiliated because he had believed that he was somehow special to Tsubaki, but he realized that she did not care about him at all, and was just obeying a teacher`s request. He transferred to a school in another city, but returns years later to attend Hokuei High School with the other characters. When he returns to Tokyo, he had lost weight, become healthy, tall, handsome, and completely unrecognizable. He intends to take advantage of the fact that no one recognizes him to get revenge on Tsubaki. Although he butts heads with Yukino at first, she recognizes that his efforts to transform himself are similar to her own obsession with her image, and they share a mutual, albeit begrudging, admiration. He later realizes that his feelings for Tsubaki are actually love, and that the source of his seeming hatred for her was because he felt rejected by her. After he realizes this, he finds out that Tsubaki likes him, too, and they become a couple. However, he is conflicted by the fact that he loves her free nature but it is this that keeps her from being tied down in a relationship. In the end, the two are able to resolve the problem and stay together. Immediately after their high school graduation ceremony, they fly together to Egypt from Narita Airport. Later, he travels around the world with Tsubaki, investigating archaeological remains. Along the way, he learns eight languages. With his linguistic talent, he becomes an expert in deciphering ancient characters.</description>
<picture>71142.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="270" picture="25681.jpg">Sasaki Nozomu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32014" type="appears in" update="2011-05-07">
<name>Arima Eiko</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="21545" picture="55611.jpg">Yanaga Kazuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32015" type="appears in" update="2011-05-07">
<name>Arima no Oji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="3222" picture="24203.jpg">Fujishiro Yuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="32016" type="appears in" update="2011-05-07">
<name>Arima no Oba</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<seiyuu id="256" picture="188450.jpg">Satou Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="2434" update="2018-07-04">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-02-05</airdate>
<rating votes="15">1.96</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">14DAYS・1</title>
<title xml:lang="en">14 Days: 1</title>
<title xml:lang="de">14 Tage - Teil 1</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">14 jours - 1re partie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">14 Days - 1</title>
<summary>It`s the first day of planning for the Culture Fair. Yukino`s class tries to decide what they want to do while Asaba informs them of what his class is doing: a Asaba Hideki Dinner Show. A new transfer student arrives named Tonami Takefumi. When Rika hears the name she remembers a boy with the same name from 7th grade but figures it`s just a coincidence that they have the exact same name. Aya finally finishes whatever she was writing from the day before saying that it was a screenplay. She wrote it out hoping that Yukino, Maho, and Tsubasa would perform it since they have nothing to do during the Culture Fair.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="2435" update="2018-07-02">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-01-29</airdate>
<rating votes="12">7.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">シン・カ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Progress</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Wahre Liebe</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Évolution</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shin - Ka</title>
<summary>Arima has suffered grievously at the hands of his relatives over the disappearance of his father. Before he met Yukino, his foster parents were the only positive influence in his life. Now, however, he has come to depend on her greatly for emotional support. Now, however...
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="2436" update="2018-07-02">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-01-22</airdate>
<rating votes="11">7.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">彼の去来</title>
<title xml:lang="en">His Return</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Arimas Rückkehr</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Son retour à lui</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ka no Kyorai</title>
<summary>Yukino receives a letter from Arima, away at the Kendo tournament, that makes her think of him all the more. Then the moment she`s waited for comes: Arima returns to her, looking taller than before. This leads her to feel differently about him than she did before.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="2437" update="2018-07-02">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-01-15</airdate>
<rating votes="10">8.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">永遠の点綴</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Eternal Interspersions</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Band der Liebe</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une ligne tendue vers l`éternité</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Towa no Tentei</title>
<summary>The Miyazawa Family assembles for a trip to Grandfather`s house. There they find an old photograph of Yukino`s mother Miyaka, who looked just like Yukino at the same age. Yukino`s parents grew up together, and fell in love when Miyaka was a high-school freshman, the same age Yukino is now. Hiroyuki lived alone with his grandfather when he was little.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="2438" update="2018-07-02">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-01-08</airdate>
<rating votes="10">3.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">これまでのお話 (後編) / 声の向こうに見えるもの</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Story So Far (Part 3) / What Can Be Seen Beyond That Voice</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Was dahinter steckt</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`histoire jusqu`à aujourd`hui (2e partie)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kore made no Ohanashi (Kouhen) / Koe no Mukou ni Mieru Mono</title>
<summary>Arima and Yukino are separated from one another by training camp over Summer Vacation. An unexpected phone call from Arima makes Yukino`s heart beat faster. Asaba, meanwhile, bored because Arima isn`t around, shows up at Yukino`s house, where Tsukino and Kano make him welcome. Hiroyuki, their father, is not at all happy with this development, however.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="2439" recap="true" update="2018-07-02">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-12-30</airdate>
<rating votes="11">1.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">これまでのお話 (前編) / これまでのお話 (中編)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Story So Far (Part 1) / The Story So Far (Part 2)</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die ganze Geschichte</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`histoire jusqu`à aujourd`hui (1re partie)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kore made no Ohanashi (Zenpen) / Kore made no Ohanashi (Chuuhen)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="2440" update="2018-07-01">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-11-27</airdate>
<rating votes="13">6.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">モラトリアムの贖罪</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Atonement for Postponed Debt</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Konkurrenz</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Expiration du moratoire</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Moratorium no Shokuzai</title>
<summary>Yukino makes the decision to be her real self, but her classmates still treat her as a visitor from outside. The other girls mistrust her and spread rumors in the wake of her parents being called in on account of her falling grades, as well as her getting close not only with Arima, but also with Asaba. In the midst of all this, Isawa Maho, who had detected a change in Yukino some time back, takes advantage of the girls` antagonism toward Yukino to take control of them. And what will Yukino do when these moves finally lead to action?
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="2441" update="2018-07-01">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-12-25</airdate>
<rating votes="13">7.71</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">幸せの主観</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Subjectivity of Happiness</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ende gut, alles gut</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La découverte du bonheur</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shiawase no Shukan</title>
<summary>Tsubasa is opposed to her father`s remarriage, but realizing that her opinions carry no weight, she gives in and agrees to meet her stepbrother-to-be, who turns out to be a blond punk rocker named Kazuma. His remarks burn Tsubasa, and everything goes right to hell. Later, they meet by chance in the street, with very different results.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="2442" update="2018-07-01">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-11-20</airdate>
<rating votes="11">7.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">彼女の日常 / 桜の林の満開の下</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Her Day / In a Grove of Blossoming Cherry Trees</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Liebe unter Kirschblüten</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Son jour à elle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanojo no Nichijou / Sakura no Hayashi no Mankai no Shita</title>
<summary>One day not long before Summer Vacation, Yukino goes to play at Arima`s house. It`s the first time they`ve been alone there. As a test of the distance between them, they have their second kiss, and Yukino feels even more strongly for him than she did before.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="2443" update="2018-07-01">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-12-18</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">仕合わせの在処</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Location of Happiness</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ort des Glücks</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La famille du bonheur</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shiawase no Arika</title>
<summary>Tsubasa, opposed to her father`s remarriage, declares that she will stay at Yukino`s house instead of going home. Yukino is confused, but finally Tsubasa and Maho end up staying at the Miyazawa house. A phone call from Tsubaki brings Tsubasa`s father and his new fiancee.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="2444" update="2018-07-01">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-11-13</airdate>
<rating votes="14">8.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">二人の阻隔</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Their Estrangement</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Beziehung: Unerwünscht</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Leur dispute</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Futari no Sokaku</title>
<summary>The relationship between Yukino, Arima, and new friend Asaba gets deeper and deeper. Yukino and Arima don`t care in the slightest that their final exam results were not very good. The school authorities, however, present these scores to them as being a serious problem. In the face of this teacher response, Yukino persists in putting forth her intent to be her real self, but events progress to the point that their parents are called in.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="2445" update="2018-07-01">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-12-11</airdate>
<rating votes="12">7.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">1学期の終わりに / 夏の休みの始まりに</title>
<title xml:lang="en">At the End of the First Semester / At the Beginning of Summer Break</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der Ferienanfang</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">À la fin du 1er trimestre</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">1 Gakki no Owari ni / Natsu no Yasumi no Hajimari ni</title>
<summary>All sorts of things have happened in the currently ending school term. Arima tells Yukino that he won`t be able to see her for a while because he`ll be taking part in the upcoming Kendo tournament. Without Arima, Yukino finds herself spending Summer Vacation with female friends for the first time in her life. She puts a bold face on it, but Tsubasa acts very strangely.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="2446" update="2018-07-01">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-11-06</airdate>
<rating votes="14">8.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">僕を変える, 君の声</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Your Voice That Changes Me</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Sommergewitter</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ta voix qui me change</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Boku o Kaeru, Kimi no Koe</title>
<summary>With Summer Vacation close at hand, Arima and Yukino date one another constantly, to make up for all the time they`ve lost due to the troubles they`ve had. But the more he dates her, and learns what she is really like, the greater Arima`s complex about Yukino`s nature becomes. His worries build, until one evening, they meet under a blazing sunset.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="2447" update="2018-07-01">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-12-04</airdate>
<rating votes="14">8.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">すべてはこれから</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Everything Starts Now</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Blatt wendet sich</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Tout commence</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Subete wa Kore kara</title>
<summary>What with the girls in her class despising her, and yet another old friend of Arima`s, Shibahime Tsubasa, giving her the evil eye as well, Yukino is hemmed in on all sides. With no intention of giving into these assaults, however, she instead spends carefree days with Arima and Asaba. She even turns aside Shibahime`s escalating attacks as if they were mere jokes. Hearing all of this, Tsubaki, a friend of Shibahime`s, joins Aya and Rika in declaring their friendship for Yukino, thus abruptly drawing her into their group.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="2448" update="2018-07-04">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-03-26</airdate>
<rating votes="15">1.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">14DAYS・6</title>
<title xml:lang="en">14 Days: 6</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Die Liebe siegt</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">14 jours - 6e partie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">14 Days - 6</title>
<summary>Tonami shares a brief kiss with Tsubaki. Arima believes that Tonami is trying to take Yukino away. Yukino reassures Arima that she loves him and only him. Tonami is scared of his feelings toward Tsubaki so he runs and prays for the future.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="2449" update="2018-07-01">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-10-30</airdate>
<rating votes="13">6.86</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">日々の迷宮 / 彼の野望</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Days of Labyrinth / His Ambition</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ein neuer Freund</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les jours du Labyrinthe</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hibi no Meikyuu / Kare no Yabou</title>
<summary>Arima and Yukino finally become "boyfriend and girlfriend". But preparations are underway for the school Field Day. resulting in a state of controlled chaos. As both of them have the trust of students and faculty alike, they are given positions of leadership, which cause them to pass one another by in school for days on end. This situation causes them serious agitation. And when the Field Day is over, another boy starts to cramp Arima`s style in a big way: Asaba Hideaki, the handsome, popular young man from Class F.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="2450" update="2018-07-04">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-03-19</airdate>
<rating votes="13">3.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">これまでと違うお話し</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Different Story from Up to Now</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Der mysteriöse Unbekannte</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un épisode pas comme les autres (II)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kore made to Chigau Ohanashi</title>
<summary>Yukino`s youngest sister believes she is being stalked by a girl from her school. Kano confronts the girl and they both realize that it was a mere coincidence that they kept running into each other. They become friends and Kano`s older sister, Tsukino has an admirer in Kano`s friend who wants her (Tsukino) to her big sister.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="2451" update="2018-07-01">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-10-23</airdate>
<rating votes="17">9.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">彼女の難題</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Her Difficult Problem</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Liebe mit Hindernissen</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Son grand problème à elle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanojo no Nandai</title>
<summary>The more Yukino learns about Arima, the more attracted she is to him. When he comes on to her again, though, she suddenly becomes so tense that she cannot respond. Thus, they are once again more than friends, but less than lovers. Upset at her own failure, Yukino decides that she will make the next move herself. She creates a number of plots and schemes, and tries to make an opportunity to use them.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="2452" update="2018-07-04">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-03-12</airdate>
<rating votes="11">2.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">今までと違うお話し</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Different Story from So Far</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Eine Frage des Standpunktes</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un épisode pas comme les autres (I)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ima made to Chigau Ohanashi</title>
<summary>The first part of the episode has Arima and Yukino thinking about their insecurities. Arima still can`t move beyond his troubled past and Yukino feels gyped by her changed ways. Arima makes Asaba cry because he didn`t tell him that he and Yukino slept together. Part 2 of the episode is just a very brief recap of the series.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="2453" update="2018-06-30">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-10-16</airdate>
<rating votes="18">8.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">彼氏の事情</title>
<title xml:lang="en">His Circumstances</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Das Geständnis</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ses raisons à lui</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kareshi no Jijou</title>
<summary>Things have been good between Arima and Yukino for the past few weeks but lately Arima has been acting strange. He`s been very distant and it almost seems like he`s purposefully ignoring Yukino... what is it that`s changed so suddenly?
[I]Source: IMDB.com[/I]</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="2454" update="2018-07-04">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-03-05</airdate>
<rating votes="11">5.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">14DAYS・5</title>
<title xml:lang="en">14 Days: 5</title>
<title xml:lang="de">14 Tage - Teil 5</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">14 jours - 5e partie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">14 Days - 5</title>
<summary>The school festival is approaching, and Yukino is busy with both meetings and rehearsals for the play. Tonami, who has sworn revenge on Tsubaki, tells her that he hates her. Yukino and company get together on Sunday for a meeting, but before they know it, they get off on tangents. Maho, who cannot bear the sight of this, scolds them all.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="2455" update="2018-06-30">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-10-09</airdate>
<rating votes="18">8.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">二人の秘密</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Their Secret</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Sein Geheimnis</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un secret en commun</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Futari no Himitsu</title>
<summary>Due to her own serious foul-up, Yukino finds herself in a heap of trouble. She spends days terrified of Arima`s reaction. When days have passed as if nothing has happened, and Yukino lets down her guard, Arima`s unthinkable retaliation begins. In exchange for not revealing the truth about her, Yukino must help Arima with all the different committee work he gets, in effect reducing her to his slave. After-school sessions go on and on, with the two of them wading through a mountain of work.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="2456" update="2018-07-04">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-02-26</airdate>
<rating votes="11">6.16</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">14DAYS・4</title>
<title xml:lang="en">14 Days: 4</title>
<title xml:lang="de">14 Tage - Teil 4</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">14 jours - 4e partie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">14 Days - 4</title>
<summary>When Yukino says that they should do the play for the school festival, Maho, who really dislikes the idea, is reluctantly persuaded to go along. Yukino puts her negotiating skills to work to get the preparations made, including getting class director Kawashima to be their advisor. Arima, meanwhile, is...
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="2457" update="2018-06-30">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1998-10-02</airdate>
<rating votes="25">8.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">彼女の事情</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Her Circumstances</title>
<title xml:lang="de">Ihr Geheimnis</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Sa situation à elle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanojo no Jijou</title>
<summary>It is Spring, and Miyazawa Yukino has entered Hokuei Prefectural High School. With her looks, good grades, excellent athletic ability, and winning personality, she soon becomes the darling of her class. The truth, though, is that this is all a facade. Yukino is deathly concerned about how other people see her. Arima Souichiroo, a boy in her class, threatens her very existence as a result. A handsome boy who entered the school at the top of the entrance exams, he steals Yukino`s place as class representative, and steadily encroaches on her popularity in class. She feels an intense rivalry toward him.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="2458" update="2018-07-04">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-02-19</airdate>
<rating votes="11">6.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">14DAYS・3</title>
<title xml:lang="en">14 Days: 3</title>
<title xml:lang="de">14 Tage - Teil 3</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">14 jours - 3e partie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">14 Days - 3</title>
<summary>Tonami asks Yukino not to tell Tsubaki and company that he went to school with Tsubaki. Yukino and Maho turn up their noses at Aya`s suggestion that they do a play for the school festival, but read the script anyway. Yukino`s reaction is something else.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="2459" update="2018-07-04">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>1999-02-12</airdate>
<rating votes="11">6.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">14DAYS・2</title>
<title xml:lang="en">14 Days: 2</title>
<title xml:lang="de">14 Tage - Teil 2</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">14 jours - 2e partie</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">14 Days - 2</title>
<summary>Tonami is a transfer student who was teased by Tsubaki for being overweight all through grade school and intermediate school. Determined to change himself, he returns in a very handsome form, practically a different person. Aya, meanwhile, tells Yukino and company that she wants them to act out a play she`s written for the school festival.
Source: theTVDB.com</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="6409" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>15</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Interview of Kare Kano</title>
</episode>
<episode id="18947" update="2010-05-10">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>20</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Interview of Kare Kano</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35342" update="2005-04-02">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Kare Kano Special - Lets Dub</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35343" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>15</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Kare Kano Special - Interview with Kano &amp; Tsukino</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35344" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>15</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Kare Kano Special - Interview with Asapin &amp; Maho</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35345" update="2005-04-02">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>9</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Kare Kano Special - Interview with Souichirou &amp; Yukino</title>
</episode>
<episode id="35346" update="2010-05-10">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>20</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Kare Kano Special - Interview with Kare Kano</title>
</episode>
<episode id="119277" update="2010-06-25">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="119278" update="2010-06-25">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
