<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="4345" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>26</episodecount>
<startdate>2007-05-12</startdate>
<enddate>2007-12-01</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Dennou Coil</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Coil - A Circle of Children</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Cyber Coil</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Denno Coil</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Кибер-виток</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="synonym">Cyberkrąg</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Виртуален шум</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">电脑线圈</title>
<title xml:lang="fa" type="synonym">ذغال الکترونیکی</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">DenCo</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">電脳コイル</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Den-noh Coil</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Dennō Coil</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">전뇌 코일 Coil a Circle of Children</title>
<title xml:lang="fa" type="official">سایبر کویل</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="5132" approval="69" total="127">Eve no Jikan</anime>
<anime id="7873" approval="69" total="120">Fractale</anime>
<anime id="3512" approval="35" total="60">Noein: Mou Hitori no Kimi e</anime>
<anime id="99" approval="32" total="70">Serial Experiments Lain</anime>
<anime id="9128" approval="6" total="13">Robotics;Notes</anime>
<anime id="271" approval="5" total="18">Haibane Renmei</anime>
<anime id="9948" approval="1" total="4">Megane Bu!</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="66">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="547997">This will probably remain in my top 5 favourite anime list, for a very long time. 

Setting, characters, emotion, humor..Like most favourites, I had to watch this in one sitting.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="475247">It`s great series with lovely characters and interesting plot, but for me it was too long. I mean, it`s great that all characters was well presented in first 12 eps, but really interesting part should appeard earlier, not from 13 ep imho. Otherwise animation and desing was great, but music was a little bit disappointing (except OP/ED). Overall 8/10 from me.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="329405">Great series with a great story line one of my favorite animes of all time</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="243229">Truly a unique anime</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="321417">This Anime Doesn`t Have Anything that stands out and say "Look, I`m the Best Part" Everything in this Anime is Completely Synchronised at the Same Quality.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I Liked The Idea of being able to Hack into the Reality itself.&lt;br /&gt;I Liked the Idea of Virtual Reality Injecting Itself (Illegaly) into Reality itself.&lt;br /&gt;I Liked the idea of Young Children War Using Virtual Weapons.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="190271">I wasn`t sure if I was going to like this I am definitely starting to get into this series though. If your thinking about watching it I say do so.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="254383">Epic.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="66705">Loppu oli muistaakseni vähän pettymys ja päähenkilöt on kaikki lapsia, mutta hahmot on silti pidettäviä ja perusidea ihan älykäs.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="428986">I love it, but too much filler, and story too slow.
But overall a great anime for the story and ending :D</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="497799">Has an interesting setting with a very futuristic plot. Contains suspense from the beginning to the end. Exciting and unique story line. I love the beginning and end song. One of my favorits anime songs.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="236243">At first I thought this was a series about cute girls having fun with VR-goggles. It took me completely by surprise with its dark themes and suspense. I recommend watching it late at night for maximum fright-factor.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="381652">Set in a futuristic setting where glasses have replaced today`s smartphones, the story revolves around things that can be seen through them and a good portion of it`s run time is spent explaining the elements of it`s universe. While it involves children of a relatively young age their interactions often depict those of adults, proving that maturity doesn`t always come with age. It touches subjects such as the value of friendship, family bonds and the bonds that pet owners share with their pets. Approach this with an open mind and you will definitely enjoy it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="717410">Probably one of my favorite animes. The world and story are both very intriguing. Although it might not be for everyone, it is certainly worth trying.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="152042">Starts as light comedy but gets serious at the end. Good story with almost no fillers. Best cyberspace anime since Serial Experiments Lain.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="101560">Cyberspace and a story that evolves into something really fascinating. Must watch.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="268951">wonderfull!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="87703">It`s quite childish story brings one to memories and feelings of a youth, but creating a story which is interesting and understandable for an adult conscious. Among amazing things like glasses which are on the hand distance in real life it brings familiar things in metabugs, kirabugs and so on, leaving place for average knowledged person.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="273014">This is a really cool anime&lt;br /&gt;The first half is quite dragged out, but the second half is EPIC.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="13836">A story almost too funny sometimes :D&lt;br /&gt;As it introduces imaginable technologies of a possible future it tells a so far very interesting story in a very much so "gibli-style" which I like alot :P&lt;br /&gt;A true must-see for fans of fun&amp;tech&amp;story :D</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="65644">Although I admit it has a slow beginning, it has a really tremendous ending. I truly recommend it!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="138743">Cyberspace and Fairytales, this series will spark your adult interest with it`s technological setting and astonish the child in you with it`s marvelous plot.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="631252">The anime is presented lightly but it have great content. It is a must see.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="143965">A very great and unique anime. Simply a must see! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It has become a favourite of mine.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="110858">just great !</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="1294">Kids playing around in a cyber world. Uninspiring? No, by no means is it uninspiring, the animation, the directing and the carefully applied comedy and drama elements make it stand out.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="18351">Absolutely A MUST SEE.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It begins somehow slow, or that`s what people say `cause I never found it slow. But after 14th chapter, the show goes "in crescendo" until the end.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cute, pleasant and enjoyable in its whole length.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="527619">This anime is hands down the greatest I`ve seen in the last few years. It took elements from so many others I enjoyed, Ghost Hound and .hack//sign and Digimon for instance, and combined and improved on them in a way that was very compelling. 

I couldn`t stop watching this. If you`re at all interested in cyber-realm metaphysical themes this is an absolute must see. 30/10 would watch again.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="251338">This is noe of those series proving how lame most anime are. Quality over hype. Watch and gasp!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="120055">A unique artstyle, cute childish-seeming characters and overall friendly presentation belie a much deeper, more mature show than you`d be forgiven for mistaking this for at a glance. Dennou Coil strikes an impressive balance between depth and approachability making for a show that you`d be hard-pressed not to enjoy.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="4431">Gets more and more interresting as the seasons reich the end.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="276245">Wow, that was awesome. Excellent series.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="587468">This easily has one of the most detailed settings you`ll find in any sci-fi anime.  A lot of time is spent not building up the story as much as the world, but later on most of it comes back when the story gets into full swing.  This is the kind of mystery where there are so many things going on it seems impossible to resolve them in the short time the show has.  But they do.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.tokuma.jp/coil/</url>
<creators>
<name id="154" type="Direction">Iso Mitsuo</name>
<name id="3578" type="Animation Character Design">Honda Takeshi</name>
<name id="731" type="Animation Work">Madhouse</name>
<name id="154" type="Original Work">Iso Mitsuo</name>
<name id="3578" type="Character Design">Honda Takeshi</name>
<name id="3578" type="Chief Animation Direction">Honda Takeshi</name>
<name id="5734" type="Chief Animation Direction">Inoue Toshiyuki</name>
<name id="4364" type="Music">Saitou Tsuneyoshi</name>
</creators>
<description>In this future, a mobile phone like technology has people wear special visors to superimpose coordinated, instant virtual images over the top of their everyday real world. This cyberspace layer, space, interacts perfectly as you move about or touch things. It even allows children to have advanced Tamagotchi style cyberpets (very tidy!), or to make video calls using simple hand gestures alone.
However, something is happening in Daikoku which the adults have not yet noticed. Cyberpets go missing, dangerous spherical robots patrol the skies and a mysterious gigantic character named Satchii seems connected to it all.
When 6th grader Yasako moves to Daikoku to be with family, her beloved pet goes missing too, and she is drawn into the affairs of a Cyberpet Recovery Agency run by the local children.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="4973">8.37</permanent>
<temporary count="5034">8.32</temporary>
<review count="8">8.20</review>
</ratings>
<picture>222606.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>6278</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13955</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>2164</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3883</identifier>
<identifier>vicpjf</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.tokuma.jp/coil/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Dennō_Coil</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>電脳コイル</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1028</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>326980</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8953</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/1739</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2007/dennoucoil</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="308" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>detective</name>
<description>A detective is an investigator, generally either a member of a law enforcement agency or as an individual working in the capacity of private investigators, tasked with solving crimes and other mysteries, such as disappearances, by examining and evaluating clues and records in order to solve the mystery; for a crime, this would mean uncovering the criminal`s identity and/or whereabouts. In some police systems, a detective position is achieved by passing a written test after a person completes the requirements for being a police officer; in others, detectives are college graduates who join directly from civilian life without first serving as uniformed officers.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210906.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1004" parentid="2751" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-14">
<name>judo</name>
<description>Judo, or juudou in Japanese, is a modern martial art, combat and Olympic sport created in Japan in 1882. Its most prominent feature is its competitive element, where the objective is to either throw or takedown an opponent to the ground, immobilize or otherwise subdue an opponent with a pin, or force an opponent to submit with a joint lock or a choke. Strikes and thrusts by hands and feet as well as weapons defenses are a part of judo, but only in pre-arranged forms, and are not allowed in judo competition or free practice. A judo practitioner is called a judoka. The philosophy and subsequent pedagogy developed for judo became the model for other modern Japanese martial arts that developed from traditional schools. The worldwide spread of judo has led to the development of a number of offshoots.</description>
<picurl>157094.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1063" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-11">
<name>elementary school</name>
<description>The term elementary school is used in some countries for schools where children from the age of about five receive primary education.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1590" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-11">
<name>biker</name>
<description>A person who is skilled at riding a motorcycle/motorbike and does so on a regular basis.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2555" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-07-14">
<name>amnesia</name>
<description>The character suffers from some kind of amnesia (memory disturbance or loss). This may mean inability to memorize new information, or inability to recollect old memories. Since there are many types of memory, the person may e.g. forget who they are but still retain learned skills.
Amnesia is fairly common in fiction as a plot device. In fact, because it allows for major plot changes while requiring little creativity from the author, it may be subject to heavy overuse.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2628" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-31">
<name>fictional location</name>
<description>A fictional location is a place or world which is run by different set of rules than our common and ordinary world. This may include completely fictional worlds with no semblance of Earth, computer-generated worlds, fantasy worlds, magical worlds, parallel worlds accessible through portals, and so on. Or it may be fictional places like floating islands, dungeons or planets, which can co-exist with ordinary Earth, but are otherwise separate from it.
A world that generally shares the characteristics of, and/or is generally indistinguishable from the real world (bar research on a "more than cursory" level), would NOT be considered a fictional world. A good example is http://anidb.net/a4521 [Code Geass]. It contains several real world nationalities, such as http://anidb.net/a4521 [China], http://anidb.net/t2672 [Japan] (now Area 11), http://anidb.net/t5091 [India], etc, along with fictional nationalities such as http://anidb.net/t2361 [Britannia]. China, Japan, and India are easily identified with a cursory look. The location is unmistakably the planet Earth, even though national borders have been redrawn.
The fictional world should only be tagged if it plays a materially important role in the plot and setting; generally, an episodic occurrence of a fictional world should not be tagged.
A fantasy world is a type of fictional world, part of a fictional universe. Typical worlds involve, but are not limited to: magic or magical abilities, and/or a medieval theme. Some examples include: a parallel world tenuously connected to Earth via magical portals or items; a fictional Earth-like planet in the remote past or future; or an entirely independent world set in another universe. Many fantasy worlds draw heavily on real world history, geography, and sociology, and also on folklore.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2656" parentid="2853" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>satire</name>
<description>In satire, vices, follies, abuses, and shortcomings are held up to ridicule, ideally with the intent of shaming individuals, and society itself, into improvement. Although satire is usually meant to be funny, its greater purpose is often constructive social criticism, using wit as a weapon. (Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2751" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-27">
<name>combat</name>
<description>Combat involves a violent conflict with the goal to establish dominance over an opponent.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2786" parentid="2858" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>love polygon</name>
<description>A love polygon refers to a romantic relationship involving n people. Although a love triangle is not limited to just heterosexual relationships, in anime, it usually deals with two females liking one male and vice versa.</description>
<picurl>10989.gif</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2830" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>furo scene</name>
<description>Furo (polite: Ofuro) is Japanese for bath, specifically a type of bath which originated as a short, steep-sided wooden bathtub. Baths of this type are found all over Japan in houses, apartments and traditional Japanese inns (Ryokans).
Furo are part of the Japanese ritual of bathing, not used for washing but for relaxing and warming oneself. Washing is carried out separately outside the furo, and only when completely clean does the bather enter the water. Generally Japanese bathrooms are small, so the bathroom is set up much like a walk-in shower area but containing the ofuro.
The cheapest and shortest way to show naked skin on TV, at least as much as allowed. It usually only takes up few minutes at most and as such it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in the nude and raise the DVD sales while still maintaining a "non-filler" episode.
Compare to the big brothers http://anidb.net/t4290 [sentou episode] and http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode].
See also http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode], and http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].</description>
<picurl>160785.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2839" parentid="2628" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-05">
<name>virtual world</name>
<description>A virtual world is a place where the character interacts with a computer (or some other device)-simulated environment, be it real or imagined. The condition for a virtual reality to exist is the existence of an originating "real" (source/anchor) world for the character. In some cases, a virtual reality where characters can get harmed physically is depicted.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2842" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-19">
<name>incest</name>
<description>Incest is human sexual activity between family members or close relatives by consanguinity (blood relations) and sometimes by affinity (marriage or stepfamily), adoption, clan, or lineage. The incest taboo is among the most widespread cultural taboos in present and past societies. Most modern societies have laws regarding incest or social restrictions on closely consanguineous marriages, with first cousins being the closest kin that is often (but not always) considered legally acceptable.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210769.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2851" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>horror</name>
<description>The horror cinematic genre is characterized by the attempt to make the viewer experience dread, fear, terror, or horror. Often their plots involve the intrusion of an evil force, event or personage, sometimes of supernatural origin, on the mundane world and the consequences thereof.</description>
<picurl>214682.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2861" parentid="2846" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>cyberpunk</name>
<description>Cyberpunk focuses on computers or information technology, usually coupled with some degree of breakdown in social order. The plot often centres on a conflict among hackers, artificial intelligences, and mega corporations, tending to be set within a near-future dystopian Earth.</description>
<picurl>211264.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2862" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>friendship</name>
<description>The feeling of trust, kindness, and friendship between a group of high school students for example, is a central theme of this anime.</description>
<picurl>65691.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2867" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>politics</name>
<description>From commies to fat capitalist pigs, all the stuff done by the "guys with the power", mainly evil tactics for gaining more power over the masses.
Watching this title may remind you why CNN is boring.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2872" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-16">
<name>crime</name>
<description>The underworld we talk about here is not to be confused with the place where people are believed to go after they die, but the general term for organized crime. It is a shady world, unknown to most people, where illegal things like murder, smuggling, drug dealing and similar are happening daily. Groups known to be acting in this world are for example the mafia or the yakuza.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2877" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>revenge</name>
<description>A primary factor that drives the plot forward, is the almost obsessive desire of one of the characters to get back at someone else.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2878" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>conspiracy</name>
<description>The conspiracy thriller (or paranoid thriller) is a sub-genre of the thriller which flourished in the 1970s in the US (and was echoed in other parts of the world) in the wake of a number of high-profile scandals and controversies (most notably Vietnam, the assassination of President Kennedy, Chappaquiddick and Watergate), and which exposed what many people regarded as the clandestine machinations and conspiracies beneath the orderly fabric of political life.
The protagonists of conspiracy thrillers are often journalists or amateur investigators who find themselves (often inadvertently) pulling on a small thread which unravels a vast conspiracy that ultimately goes "all the way to the top".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2879" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-27">
<name>alcohol</name>
<description>Alcohol (or more scientifically, ethanol), is one of the world`s oldest psychoactive substances. It is traditionally found in the form of a beverage such as beer, wine, or liquor, although in some contexts it can be inhaled to produce similar or intoxication, and some people prefer another way of consuming beverage-form alcohol.
Alcoholic beverages are many and varied, due to production methods (fermentation or distillation), source materials (grains, fruits, vegetables, other plants), added substances such as flavorings, and many more ways of defining different forms of alcoholic beverages.
Alcoholic beverages are divided into three general classes: beers, wines, and spirits. They are legally consumed in most countries, and over 100 countries have laws regulating their production, sale, and consumption. In particular, such laws specify the minimum age at which a person may legally buy or drink them. This minimum age varies between 16 and 25 years, depending upon the country and the type of drink. Most nations set it at 18 years of age.</description>
<picurl>70749.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2952" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-06">
<name>rotten world</name>
<description>A rotten world is a setting or situation where the jaded notion that "anything that can go wrong will go horribly wrong" almost always applies. Oppression, perpetual warfare, lawlessness, despair or other forms of mental instability, and other highly undesirable factors tend to be rampant.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3023" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-19">
<name>funny expressions</name>
<description>The facial expressions of the characters may change so quickly or unexpectedly distort that hilarity will ensue.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3436" parentid="2846" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-03-23">
<name>human experimentation</name>
<description>Genetic, biological, chemical or psychological experimentation on human beings are portrayed or their aftermath is shown.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3741" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-25">
<name>bullying</name>
<description>Bullying is the use of force, threat, or coercion to abuse, intimidate, or aggressively dominate others. One who engages in bullying is known as a bully.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3795" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>remastered version available</name>
<description>This anime has been remastered in a higher quality format than the original release. The remaster may be a simple upscale, or it could be a full enhancement project from the original frames. This is irrespective of whether specific groups have released rips of such formats to the internet.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3915" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-04-10">
<name>child abuse</name>
<description>Story depicts child abuse, which is a very complex and dangerous set of problems that include child neglect and the physical, emotional, and sexual abuse of children.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3929" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-09">
<name>sociocultural evolution</name>
<description>Describes how cultures and societies develop over time, based on both cultural evolution and social evolution.
A post-apocalyptic or a Utopian setting would show very interesting changes in human behaviour, mental state, or simply daily life.</description>
<picurl>191062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3964" parentid="6254" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-07-26">
<name>cyberterrorism</name>
<description>With the development of computer and Internet technology a new form of terrorism has emerged, the cyberterrorism, which is the manipulation of a target`s computers and information, particularly via the Internet, to cause physical, real-world harm or severe disruption of infrastructure. It finds often use in science fiction stories.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3993" parentid="2872" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-28">
<name>kidnapping</name>
<description>In criminal law, kidnapping is the taking away or transportation of a person against that person`s will, usually to hold the person in false imprisonment, a confinement without legal authority. This may be done for ransom or in furtherance of another crime, or in connection with a child custody dispute.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>10583.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4217" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-02-11">
<name>nightmares</name>
<description>One or more characters in the anime are plagued by bad dreams.
Possible causes: A traumatic experience in the past or induced by an external "presence".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4277" parentid="2925" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-30">
<name>nuclear weapons</name>
<description>A nuclear weapon is an explosive device that derives its destructive force from nuclear reactions, which release vast quantities of energy from relatively small amounts of matter. Nuclear weapons are considered weapons of mass destruction, and their use and control have been a major focus of international relations policy since their debut.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4327" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-18">
<name>be careful what you wish for</name>
<description>Be careful what you wish for... your wish may actually come true. This is an age-old philosophical problem of what human beings think they want and what is actually good for them. The power to wish for anything can be very dangerous and usually — as a moral lesson — yields unexpected / unwanted results.
A contract with the devil is a specific case of this; receiving great power, especially from a devil, is usually a double edged sword.</description>
<picurl>230309.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4335" parentid="2867" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-09">
<name>governmental censorship</name>
<description>Censorship is the suppression of speech or deletion of communicative material which may be considered objectionable, harmful or sensitive, as determined by a censor. In fiction (particularly dystopian sci-fi works) often used by totalitarian regimes to control the people.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4516" parentid="2750" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-25">
<name>animal abuse</name>
<description>Violence against animals. The humane society will not like this.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4520" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-20">
<name>betrayal</name>
<description>Friends become enemies.
Strong bonds of trust receive violations of confidence while friendships are faithlessly given up or revealed to have been false from the start.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4537" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-15">
<name>time skip</name>
<description>The plot features at least one skip or jump in time.
Example: A skip from the present into the past, or time skips in increments, e.g. every hour there is a time skip by a day.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4566" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-05-08">
<name>transforming weapons</name>
<description>This anime features transforming weapons, this can either be cars or household appliances that transform into weapons, such as transformers or weapons that themselves transform into bigger badder shapes to deal more and more damage.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4570" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-01-07">
<name>watercolour style</name>
<description>A watercolour or aquarelle is a painting method in which the paints are made of pigments suspended in a water-based solution. Some anime are created in the style of watercolour paintings, the watercolour style, usually with faded pastels that often give the show a warm and friendly visual presentation. In modern anime, this is generally achieved via computer effects that create an imitation of watercolour, rather than by creating real-life watercolour art. While the watercolour style is more commonly used for backgrounds, it is possible to create the entire anime in such a style.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4663" parentid="2605" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-31">
<name>tone changes</name>
<description>The anime switches quickly, often rather drastically between different moods or tones, sometimes even on the same scene.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4716" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-25">
<name>experimental technology</name>
<description>In generic use, experimental technology has not yet been fully proven in operating. Often only a prototype exists that`s being tested.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4753" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-03-15">
<name>disturbing</name>
<description>Watching the show may cause the viewer to have unpleasant feelings.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5046" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-19">
<name>out-of-body experience</name>
<description>Out of Body Experience</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5466" parentid="2874" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-07-17">
<name>epidemic</name>
<description>A rapid spread or increase of something (e.g. a disease) affecting many persons.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5768" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>intact family</name>
<description>The main character`s family is a so-called "nuclear family". Wherein both parents are alive and present in his or her life. This is actually relatively rare for anime, where "parental abandonment" is the norm.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6004" parentid="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>development hell</name>
<description>Due to unforeseen circumstances, the production or release of this anime has been pushed back, stalled, or cancelled one or more times from when it was first announced.
While some of them have eventually been completed, others might have only had a trailer released or have been changed into another format (e.g. a TV series turned into an OVA).
Common reasons for a work to become stuck in development hell include creative differences, legal issues, financial problems, scheduling conflicts or the death of an involved creator.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6062" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-04-05">
<name>heroic sacrifice</name>
<description>"In order to save the many, the few will need to sacrifice their lives..." or so this character may think. 
In a seemingly hopeless situation, against impossible odds, the character does not choose the path of the coward and run, he or she chooses to bravely face the enemy, fully aware that this will mean death.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6070" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-15">
<name>mystery</name>
<description>The mystery film is a sub-genre of the more general category of crime film. It focuses on the efforts of the detective, private investigator or amateur sleuth to solve the mysterious circumstances of a crime by means of clues, investigation, and clever deduction. (Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6173" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-24">
<name>origin</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6254" parentid="2872" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-23">
<name>terrorism</name>
<description>Terrorism is, in the broadest sense, the use of intentionally indiscriminate violence as a means to create terror among masses of people; or fear to achieve a religious or political aim. It is used in this regard primarily to refer to violence during peacetime or in war against non-combatants (mostly civilians and neutral military personnel). Some definitions now include acts of unlawful violence and war.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>10657.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="1589" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-09-28">
<rating votes="21">7.50</rating>
<name>Hashimoto Fumie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>16127.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="643" picture="228609.jpg">Kojima Sachiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6470" type="main character in" update="2020-04-11">
<rating votes="43">8.74</rating>
<name>Amasawa Yuuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nicknamed Isako, which is another reading of 勇子 meaning "brave girl", Amasawa Yuuko is a powerful type of hacker known as an "encoder" (暗号屋) who is able to manipulate the electronic infrastructure through sophisticated chalk patterns. Rumored to have familial ties to an AR technology company, Isako uses a Brain-Computer Interface to interact with the virtual world — a function hidden inside the hardware of AR visors and eyeglasses. Isako is, on the surface, extremely arrogant and asocial, perceiving human relationships strictly as hierarchies of power and manipulation.
Isako relentlessly chases special illegals in order to collect kirabugs. She is secretly driven to this task in the hopes of finding her brother in "the other side".</description>
<picture>49578.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="166" picture="23196.jpg">Kuwashima Houko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6471" type="main character in" update="2020-04-11">
<rating votes="28">5.61</rating>
<name>Okonogi Yuuko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nicknamed Yasako, which is another reading of 優子 meaning "gentle girl". With her sister Kyouko and her two parents, Yasako moves to the city of Daikoku to live with her grandmother, Megabaa. Yasako is a sweet and passive girl who follows the lead of Fumie, who eventually initiates her into Megabaa`s Coil Cyber Detective Agency as its eighth member. Yasako has been to the city of Daikoku seven years ago for her grandfather`s funeral. A pair of dennou eyeglasses and the virtual pet Densuke were left to her as a memento.
During her time in Daikoku, she coincidentally wandered into the Coil Domain where she befriended a young boy with the codename 4423. After Yasako returns to live in Daikoku, her hazy memories of that enigmatic friendship gradually return to haunt her. Her father Ichirou works at a Dennou technology company, Megamass, which deploys Searchmaton in Daikoku.</description>
<picture>49579.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="157" picture="42784.jpg">Orikasa Fumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6472" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-09-25">
<rating votes="13">3.47</rating>
<name>Okonogi Kyouko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>She is the little sister of Yasako. She is young and childish and often gets in the way of danger. She shows a number of fixations; the most common one is the repeated use of the word "poop" when pointing at people and other items of interest.</description>
<picture>49581.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="237" picture="95027.jpg">Yajima Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6473" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-09-28">
<rating votes="24">8.63</rating>
<name>Densuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Densuke is Yasako`s dog, a memento of her deceased grandfather. There is a very strong bond between Densuke and Yasako and he protects her when she is in trouble.</description>
<picture>49580.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3064" picture="24692.jpg">Asou Tomohisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8488" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-09-28">
<rating votes="15">4.27</rating>
<name>Harakawa Ken`ichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>27641.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="566" picture="25408.jpg">Paku Romi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="8489" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-09-28">
<rating votes="12">5.72</rating>
<name>Sawaguchi Daichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>27642.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="627" picture="170955.jpg">Saitou Rie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="9470" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-09-28">
<rating votes="4">6.77</rating>
<name>Oyaji</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>From Denno Coil. Fumie`s servant, he does various tasks for her throughout the anime. She calls him Oyaji because it looks like an old man.</description>
<picture>49582.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="18895" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-16">
<rating votes="3">2.35</rating>
<name>Amasawa Nobuhiko</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>49787.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="63" picture="186695.jpg">Kishio Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18896" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-16">
<rating votes="6">6.52</rating>
<name>Denpa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>49788.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="19171" picture="50010.jpg">Umeda Kikumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18897" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-16">
<rating votes="3">2.75</rating>
<name>Gachagiri</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>49789.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2069" picture="246996.jpg">Yamaguchi Mayumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18898" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-16">
<rating votes="10">8.00</rating>
<name>Harakawa Tamako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tamako is Haraken`s aunt. As a consultant for Daikoku`s Cyberspace Administration, she holds authority over the programming of Searchmaton and is responsible for its highly aggressive behavior. She is especially intent on preventing Amasawa Yuuko from accomplishing her mission to summon a portal to Coil Domain. However Tamako herself is well-versed in hacking and the crafting of metatags, and she often oversteps her authority in investigating the protagonists` activities. Her fervent pursuit of making augmented reality a "safe place" stems from her re-opening the portal to the other side in her early days of hacking, thus initiating the constant battle between obsolete and new space.</description>
<picture>49790.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="140" picture="170306.jpg">Noda Junko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18899" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-16">
<rating votes="3">5.32</rating>
<name>Hashimoto Akira</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Akira is the youngest member of the Daikoku Hackers` Club. He agrees to spy on the Daikoku Hackers for his older sister, Fumie, by joining their ranks as a double agent. Akira makes use of his digital pet "Micet", which he illegally patched to unlock its video recording feature.</description>
<picture>49791.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="320" picture="66660.jpg">Kobayashi Yumiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18900" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-16">
<rating votes="3">5.41</rating>
<name>Kanna</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>49792.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="539" picture="228668.jpg">Aizawa Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18902" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-09-30">
<rating votes="3">4.97</rating>
<name>Maiko-sensei</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>49793.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="19170" picture="50009.jpg">Dounowaki Kyouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18903" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-16">
<rating votes="6">7.23</rating>
<name>Okonogi Sanae</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sanae Okonogi, or Megabaa is the owner of the Cyber Candy Shop Megasi-ya. Megasi-ya also sells software and metatags. Megabaa is the primary craftsman of metatags in Daikoku, and is an expert software programmer. She is also Yasako`s grandmother, and the head of the Coil Dennou Detective Agency. Her cunning frugality terrifies Yasako among other characters. Her deceased husband was a researcher in the early medical application of dennou technology. His secret legacy is slowly unveiled throughout the series.</description>
<picture>49794.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2040" picture="186173.jpg">Suzuki Reiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18904" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-16">
<rating votes="2">2.93</rating>
<name>Namecchi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>49795.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3702" picture="25829.jpg">Numata Yuusuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18905" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-16">
<rating votes="6">1.62</rating>
<name>Sousuke Nekome</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The antagonist of the series. He is a former acquaintance of Harakawa Tamako, and a collaborator in Isako`s quest to open the door to the "other side". His ultimate aim is to bring down the Megamass company.</description>
<picture>49796.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="370" picture="204461.jpg">Yusa Kouji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18906" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-06-16">
<rating votes="2">7.41</rating>
<name>Sousuke Takeru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The younger brother of Nekome. He is jealous of Isako and mercilessly bullies her, but takes a liking to Yasako and becomes split between his loyalty towards his brother and his desire to protect her. He has a modified pink midget named Momoko.</description>
<picture>49797.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2982" picture="23710.jpg">Hibi Aiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="70226" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-04-26">
<rating votes="2">4.41</rating>
<name>Mojo</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Mojos are Amasawa Yuuko`s cyber pets and servants. They are small, egg-sized, furry balls that share with each other a pair of tiny eyes, as well as a hair sized antennae on top of their head. They also have a pair of hair sized arms and legs that usually keep concealed within their fur, unless they require the use of them for carrying items and running.</description>
<picture>62198.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="81930" type="appears in" update="2016-04-30">
<name>Mayumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>186318.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11049" picture="247986.jpg">Ueda Seiko</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="72340" update="2007-05-01">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>6</length>
<rating votes="4">5.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72573" update="2007-05-20">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-12</airdate>
<rating votes="37">6.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">メガネの子供たち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Children of Glasses</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Megane no Kodomo-tachi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72574" update="2007-05-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-19</airdate>
<rating votes="19">7.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">コイル電脳探偵局</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Coil Cyber-Detective Agency</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Coil Dennou Tantei Kyoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="72575" update="2007-05-26">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-05-26</airdate>
<rating votes="17">7.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">優子と勇子</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yuuko and Yuuko</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuuko to Yuuko</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73697" update="2007-05-26">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-02</airdate>
<rating votes="18">8.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">大黒市 - 黒客クラブ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Daikoku City - Hacker Club</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Daikoku Shi - Hacker Club</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73710" update="2007-05-27">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-09</airdate>
<rating votes="16">7.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">メタバグ争奪バスツアー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Meta-bug Struggle Bus Tour</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Meta Bug Soudatsu Bus Tour</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73711" update="2007-05-27">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-16</airdate>
<rating votes="17">6.87</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">赤いオートマトン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Red Automaton</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Akai Automaton</title>
</episode>
<episode id="73712" update="2007-05-27">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-23</airdate>
<rating votes="17">7.65</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">出動! コイル探偵局</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mobilise! Coil Detective Agency</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shutsudou! Coil Tantei Kyoku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="75099" update="2007-06-11">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-06-30</airdate>
<rating votes="18">7.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夏祭りそして果たし合い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Summer Festival and the Duel</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Natsumatsuri Soshite Hatashiai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="75100" update="2007-06-11">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-07</airdate>
<rating votes="16">9.02</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あっちのミチコさん</title>
<title xml:lang="en">There`s Ms Michiko</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Acchi no Michiko-san</title>
</episode>
<episode id="79751" update="2007-07-08">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-04</airdate>
<rating votes="19">7.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">最後の首長竜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Last Plesiosaur</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saigo no Kubinagaryuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="79752" update="2007-07-08">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-28</airdate>
<rating votes="38">9.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ダイチ, 発毛す</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Daichi, Departing Hair</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Daichi, Hatsumousu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="79753" update="2007-07-08">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-21</airdate>
<rating votes="19">6.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">沈没! 大黒市</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Sinking! Daikoku City</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Chinbotsu! Daikoku Shi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="79754" update="2007-07-08">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-14</airdate>
<rating votes="16">8.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">カンナの日記</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kanna`s Diary</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanna no Nikki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="81073" recap="true" update="2009-05-04">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-01</airdate>
<rating votes="21">4.48</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">いきものの記録</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Record of Living Things</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ikimono no Kiroku</title>
</episode>
<episode id="82420" update="2007-09-04">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-29</airdate>
<rating votes="18">9.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">異界への扉</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Door to a Strange World</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ikai e no Tobira</title>
</episode>
<episode id="82421" update="2007-09-04">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-22</airdate>
<rating votes="18">9.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">最後の夏休み</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Last Summer Vacation</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saigo no Natsuyasumi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="82422" update="2007-09-23">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-15</airdate>
<rating votes="18">8.22</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">イサコの病室</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Isako`s Sickroom</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Isako no Byoushitsu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="82423" update="2007-09-23">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-08</airdate>
<rating votes="17">7.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">駅向こうの少年</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Boy on the Other Side of the Station</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Eki Mukou no Shounen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="82463" recap="true" update="2007-10-31">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-25</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">電脳コイル自由研究</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dennou Coil Free Research</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dennou Coil Jiyuukenkyuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="82803" update="2007-09-16">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-10-06</airdate>
<rating votes="20">9.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">黒い訪問者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Black Visitor</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kuroi Houmonsha</title>
</episode>
<episode id="82804" update="2007-09-16">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-10-13</airdate>
<rating votes="21">9.99</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">カンナとヤサコ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kanna and Yasako</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanna to Yasako</title>
</episode>
<episode id="84589" update="2007-10-22">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-10-20</airdate>
<rating votes="17">9.94</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">黒いオートマトン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Black Automaton</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kuroi Automaton</title>
</episode>
<episode id="84666" update="2007-10-24">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-10-27</airdate>
<rating votes="17">9.75</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">最後のコイル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Last Coil</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saigo no Coil</title>
</episode>
<episode id="84667" update="2007-10-31">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-11-10</airdate>
<rating votes="17">9.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">かなえられた願い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Granted Wish</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanaerareta Negai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="84711" update="2007-10-31">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-11-17</airdate>
<rating votes="17">8.97</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">メガネを捨てる子供たち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Kids who abandoned their Glasses</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Megane o Suteru Kodomo-tachi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="84712" recap="true" update="2007-10-31">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-11-03</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">電脳コイル総復習</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Dennou Coil Comprehensive Recap</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dennou Coil Soufukushuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="84819" update="2019-04-01">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-12-01</airdate>
<rating votes="19">9.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヤサコとイサコ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Yasako and Isako</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yasako to Isako</title>
</episode>
<episode id="84820" update="2018-09-24">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-11-24</airdate>
<rating votes="17">9.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">金沢市はざま交差点</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kanazawa City`s Loophole Nexus</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanazawa Shi Hazama Kousaten</title>
</episode>
<episode id="85712" update="2019-03-23">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-05-12</airdate>
<rating votes="3">9.43</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="85713" update="2019-03-23">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-05-12</airdate>
<rating votes="3">8.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="146463" update="2013-01-03">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">BD CM 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="146464" update="2013-01-03">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">BD CM 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="146465" update="2019-07-09">
<epno type="2">S6</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2007-12-01</airdate>
<rating votes="1">4.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 26 Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="148037" update="2019-07-09">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2007-11-24</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 25 Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="148038" update="2019-07-09">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>90</length>
<airdate>2011-11-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Total Summary Special</title>
</episode>
<episode id="148039" update="2019-07-09">
<epno type="2">S7</epno>
<length>6</length>
<airdate>2011-11-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Pilot</title>
</episode>
<episode id="218585" update="2019-07-09">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2007-12-01</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Episode 26 Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
