<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="5083" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2007-07-08</startdate>
<enddate>2007-09-23</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Sayonara Zetsubou-sensei</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Goodbye Teacher Despair</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Прощай, безрадостный сенсей</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Прощай, унылый учитель</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="synonym">Adeus, Professor Desespero</title>
<title xml:lang="bg" type="synonym">Сбогом, господин Отчаяние</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Прощавай, Відчай-сенсей</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Бувай, сумний учителю</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">再见! 绝望先生</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">szs</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">szs1</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">さよなら絶望先生</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="5576" type="Sequel">Zoku Sayonara Zetsubou-sensei</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="7238" approval="147" total="185">Arakawa Under the Bridge</anime>
<anime id="6327" approval="66" total="133">Bakemonogatari</anime>
<anime id="8899" approval="35" total="52">Joshiraku</anime>
<anime id="6087" approval="17" total="34">Maria Holic</anime>
<anime id="15267" approval="8" total="8">Kakushigoto</anime>
<anime id="7056" approval="4" total="16">Aoi Bungaku Series</anime>
<anime id="7569" approval="4" total="15">Soredemo Machi wa Mawatte Iru</anime>
<anime id="3298" approval="3" total="4">PaniPoni Dash!</anime>
<anime id="8889" approval="2" total="13">Sasami-san@Ganbaranai</anime>
<anime id="4777" approval="1" total="21">Lucky Star</anime>
<anime id="9955" approval="1" total="5">Hoozuki no Reitetsu</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="21">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="92088">Very crazy but really funny as well.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="424296">Interesting anime that constantly bitches about society. Very entertaining</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="488989">I didn`t find it funny (as I dont find Gintama to be funny) but, I loved the animation and the artwork, it was stunning!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="446157">i love this show....recommended</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="321417">Well , This is A Masterpiece but don`t try Reading All of The Blackboard Jokes even if your an old anime viewer then i`m sure there still are some jokes you too won`t get if you`re not familiar with japanese literature.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;WATCH IT , YOU`LL LOVE IT.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="374255">hilarious in a very dark way and yet insightful.  it works on many levels.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="624">Making fun of serious issues like suicide is always a win in my book! Now if they`d just lose the censoring, but can`t be helped I guess. All in all, this one will make anyone laugh out loud.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="333203">first season is the best enjoy</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="548153">1st season is great and extremely hilarious but when you see similar stuff in every season and watching episode after episode it gets repetitive and the show losing its attraction.
Nevertheless in every season you will see some worth to think about implied meanings not only silly once but some serious too..
Worth to see at least once for every1 a specially if you have seen a lot of anime already!!! :D</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.starchild.co.jp/special/zetsubou/</url>
<creators>
<name id="792" type="Animation Work">Shaft</name>
<name id="3019" type="Original Work">Kumeta Kouji</name>
<name id="3013" type="Character Design">Morioka Hideyuki</name>
<name id="2323" type="Series Composition">Kanemaki Ken`ichi</name>
<name id="59" type="Direction">Shinbou Akiyuki</name>
<name id="3013" type="Chief Animation Direction">Morioka Hideyuki</name>
<name id="3528" type="Chief Animation Direction">Yamamura Hiroki</name>
<name id="2832" type="Chief Animation Direction">Itou Yoshiaki</name>
<name id="4073" type="Music">Hasegawa Tomoki</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on a shounen manga by http://anidb.net/cr3019 [Kumeta Kouji], serialised in http://anidb.net/cr17160 [Weekly Shounen Magazine].
http://anidb.net/ch6443 [Itoshiki Nozomu] is the world`s most negative person. In his way of thinking, there is no hope or meaning in this existence. Even the three kanji of his name become the two-kanji word zetsubou, despair, when compressed. What an ironic twist of fate, then, that he becomes teacher to a class with a student his exact opposite in character, the invincibly positive-minded http://anidb.net/ch6444 [Fuura Kafuka].
Source: ANN
Note: The DVD content differs from the DTV content in terms of censoring. DTV content has black circles and images of http://anidb.net/cr23822 [Maeda]`s face (an assistant to Kumeta Kouji, the original manga creator) covering areas that could otherwise be revealing. The DVD version has these areas mostly revealed.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="5903">7.71</permanent>
<temporary count="5950">8.03</temporary>
<review count="3">7.66</review>
</ratings>
<picture>23828.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>7767</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>3674</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>2605</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4013</identifier>
<identifier>arpufh</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.starchild.co.jp/special/zetsubou/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Sayonara,_Zetsubou-Sensei</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>さよなら絶望先生_(アニメ)</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>さよなら絶望先生の登場人物</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1191</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>1298</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>327828</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9094</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="464" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-01-15">
<name>sarcastic</name>
<description>The character frequently uses sharp, bitter, or cutting expressions or remarks. (From Greek sarcasmos, "to tear flesh, gnash the teeth, speak bitterly".)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="922" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-04">
<name>shounen</name>
<description>In the context of manga and associated media, shounen, literally meaning "youth" and often also specifically "boy", refers to a male audience roughly between the ages of 10 and 18.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1283" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-06-24">
<name>tsukkomi</name>
<description>A tsukkomi is a comedy duo stock character in a traditional Japanese slapstick stand-up comedy style known as manzai. Tsukkomi characters are the smart, reasonable, and down-to-earth half of the unit; their simple-minded counterparts are the http://anidb.net/t1399 [boke] characters. As a result of their boke counterparts` simple mistakes and gross exaggerations, tsukkomi berate and abuse them both verbally and physically; a very common example of tsukkomi physical abuse is a paper fan slap, which is generally accompanied by a sound effect. Their approximate equivalent in Western culture is the comedy role of straight man.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2019" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-09-16">
<name>suicidal</name>
<description>The character has suicidal tendencies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2654" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-06-13">
<name>medium awareness</name>
<description>Medium awareness is the situational and generally temporary awareness characters in works of fiction have and display of the very fact that they are characters in works of fiction. For example, they may comment about the background music, quip about the script or narration, complain about the roles given to them by the writer or their lack of screen time, see the subtitles that appear on screen, inform the audience about the arrival of the commercial break, and even use medium effects as tools. The most common form of medium awareness is known as breaking the fourth wall, in which characters speak directly to the audience, either to it as a whole or to specific members of it. The "fourth wall" is the imaginary "wall" at the front of the stage of a proscenium theatre through which the audience sees the play; it is a metaphor for the boundary between what happens inside the work, to the characters, and outside it, to the audience.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2656" parentid="2853" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>satire</name>
<description>In satire, vices, follies, abuses, and shortcomings are held up to ridicule, ideally with the intent of shaming individuals, and society itself, into improvement. Although satire is usually meant to be funny, its greater purpose is often constructive social criticism, using wit as a weapon. (Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2798" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-02-14">
<name>manga</name>
<description>Manga is the lifeblood that drives the anime industry. Everything and its mother is based on manga. However! There are exceptions where the manga was not the basis for the anime.
It`s common practice to make manga adaptations of many popular anime, there`s a manga based on Evangelion, and two (one shounen and one shoujo) based on each of Escaflowne and Mahou Tsukai Tai. Also it`s quite common to release manga and anime versions of a story in parallel, for instance Nadesico and Shoujo Kakumei Utena. There are also cases where an anime continues in a manga, as in the case of Angel Beats! and Angel Beats: Heaven`s Door, or reverse.
See also http://anidb.net/t6493 [manhua] and http://anidb.net/t5010 [manhwa].</description>
<picurl>215593.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2826" parentid="2856" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>pantsu</name>
<description>"Panties" in Japanese. Upskirt views in various positions are typical, however all forms of partial or fully exposed panties are accepted. Exposure is usually accidental, but may also be deliberate. Pantsu views may be exclusive to the viewer without impacting any characters. Bikinis are not pantsu.</description>
<picurl>5721.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3185" parentid="2853" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-04-27">
<name>wordplay</name>
<description>The characters play with words. 
E.g. purposely or accidentally use similar-sounding but wrongly applied words in the Japanese original, leading to supposedly funny misunderstandings and confusion.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3316" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-08-10">
<name>despair</name>
<description>Involves characters that may be lost in negatively emotional atmospheres created through feelings of hopelessness and suffering.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3546" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-01-08">
<name>experimental animation</name>
<description>This anime uses distinct, alternative animation — much unlike other contemporary anime — either throughout or in individual episodes/sequences.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3842" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-31">
<name>TV censoring</name>
<description>The TV version is censored and later DVD/BD releases are uncensored, so the money-grubbing capitalists can make a couple more bucks at our expense.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4112" parentid="3842" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-07-14">
<name>excessive censoring</name>
<description>There are basically two cases to which this term can be applied to:
1) creative censorship
The TV station airing the anime does its best to remove most ecchi parts from the show, using various and original methods. Usually, an uncensored BD/DVD is released later. Apart from the publisher`s greed - sometimes the censorship is used intentionally to make a scene look more obscene than it actually is.
2) convenient censorship
Another case of it - more often known under the term of "convenient censoring/ship" - is a blatant substitute for mosaic/steam/etc. over nether regions. This applies both to normal shows with occasional nudity as a normal part of human life (or just occasional flash of fanservice), as well as to heavy ecchi / borderline hentai shows where /literally/ everything is a fair (and far more "obscene" no matter how to look at it) game, except that misinterpreted taboo nonsense coming from §175 of JPC.</description>
<picurl>169459.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4131" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-05-11">
<name>cultural references</name>
<description>The plot of this anime shows signs of cultural references, these are often jokes that make reference to a certain custom, habit or history that is specifically attributed to that culture. Knowledge of the culture itself is needed in order to properly understand these jokes.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4222" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>walls of text</name>
<description>Walls of text refers to Japanese text that appears in large quantities within the anime itself. This text is most likely vital to the storyline and may come in the form of charts and diagrams or pieces of paper, notes or even thoughts that are only partially or entirely unspoken.
May also be taken as a fair warning to viewers unable to translate Japanese text on their own, suggesting that thorough subtitle support may be required as well as making use of the pause button on their media players so that all text can be read.
Normally, tags don`t refer to physical translations of text, subtitle appearances and karaoke styling added by 3rd parties. But those who seek to describe an anime that is heavy on SPOKEN dialogue (which may tend to create a large quantity of natural subtitling to read for those not fluent in the language being used) could consider this tag but may make clearer reference with the dialogue driven tag.</description>
<picurl>32534.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4340" parentid="6242" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-09-26">
<name>suicide</name>
<description>One or several characters in this anime commit suicide.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4462" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-05-19">
<name>barefoot</name>
<description>This character never seems to wear any shoes — possibly a martial artist that prefers to stay in close contact with the ground, or a girl from the country now living in the city.
Alas, under more dire circumstances this can also be a sign of real poverty.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4474" parentid="2655" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-07-04">
<name>self-parody</name>
<description>The anime is a parody of itself. 
I.e. the authors make fun of the genre they are portraying, and take the actions of their characters and story lightly.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4522" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>social commentary</name>
<description>Social commentary is the act of rebelling against an individual, or a group of people by rhetorical means. This is most often done with the idea of implementing or promoting change by informing the general populace about a given problem and appealing to people’s sense of justice. (Source: Wikipedia)&#13;
&#13;
Since this is anime, usually, the mores of Japan and the Japanese society are scrutinised, but not restricted to that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5697" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-02">
<name>randomness</name>
<description>The anime does not follow a predictable storyline. New, strange, obscure, or otherwise unexpected story elements are introduced at a whim.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5769" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-02">
<name>panels that require pausing</name>
<description>Panels that require pausing are image or text panels that interrupt regular animation and flash by so quickly that the viewer cannot recognize the image or read the text fast enough while playing at regular speed; they require pausing the video, or at least viewing it at a lower speed. Given the short screen time these panels are given, they are usually not relevant to the plot.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6029" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-04-08">
<name>mundane made awesome</name>
<description>Sometimes normal just doesn`t cut it. Eating: you put food in your mouth and chew. Playing sports: you throw a ball around. You need to make it awesome, no matter how mundane it is.
Let`s throw in some gripping orchestral music, lighting changes, different camera angles, something! Don`t write like a man, write like an evil overlord! Exaggerate your expressions and gestures, speak with excessive intonation, and if all else fails, throw in some close-ups, slow motion, and ominous Latin chanting! With practice, even you can turn something like eating chips into an epic battle of light and dark, blinding the viewer with sheer awesomeness.
[Source: TV Tropes]</description>
<picurl>149443.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6242" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-07-24">
<name>death</name>
<description>Death is the state of no longer being alive or the process of ceasing to be alive.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="301" type="cameo appearance in" update="2019-04-01">
<rating votes="1761">8.42</rating>
<name>Yagami Light</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The main character of Death Note, Light is an extremely intelligent but bored 17-year old student. When he finds the Death Note, dropped in the human world by the shinigami Ryuk, he decides to use it to kill all criminals and earns the title Kira. His ultimate goal is to cleanse the world of evil to create a world without criminals and then reign over this new world as its "god."</description>
<picture>231916.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="6443" type="main character in" update="2010-01-02">
<rating votes="792">8.94</rating>
<name>Itoshiki Nozomu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>23897.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="224" picture="79056.jpg">Kamiya Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6444" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-25">
<rating votes="223">7.72</rating>
<name>Fuura Kafuka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>23898.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="347" picture="41555.jpg">Nonaka Ai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6445" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-25">
<rating votes="262">8.14</rating>
<name>Kitsu Chiri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>23910.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="11" picture="32253.jpg">Inoue Marina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6446" type="secondary cast in" update="2014-03-06">
<rating votes="286">8.79</rating>
<name>Komori Kiri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>23911.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3131" picture="234931.jpg">Tanii Asuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6447" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-25">
<rating votes="214">8.54</rating>
<name>Tsunetsuki Matoi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>23912.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="359" picture="65537.jpg">Sanada Asami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6448" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-25">
<rating votes="142">6.43</rating>
<name>Kimura Kaere</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>23913.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="79" picture="228519.jpg">Kobayashi Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6449" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-25">
<rating votes="121">5.95</rating>
<name>Sekiutsu Maria Tarou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>23914.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38" picture="171532.jpg">Sawashiro Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6450" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-25">
<rating votes="113">5.73</rating>
<name>Kobushi Abiru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>23915.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="248" picture="45126.jpg">Gotou Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6451" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-25">
<rating votes="113">7.27</rating>
<name>Hitou Nami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>23916.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="357" picture="32000.jpg">Shintani Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="6452" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-04-25">
<rating votes="138">6.39</rating>
<name>Fujiyoshi Harumi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>23917.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="203" picture="38566.jpg">Matsuki Miyu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="10400" type="cameo appearance in" update="2016-01-04">
<rating votes="372">9.15</rating>
<name>Black Jack</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Black Jack is a mysterious and charismatic young genius surgeon who travels the world performing amazing and impossible surgery. Because of his hatred of the hypocrisy and corruption of the medical establishment, Black Jack refuses to accept a medical license, and runs into frequent difficulties from the authorities, as well as from gangsters and criminals who approach him for illegal operations. Black Jack charges ludicrous fees for his services, and uses the proceeds for environmental projects and to aid the victims of criminals and corrupt capitalsts, but he rarely allows anyone to realize that he is a good person, preferring to be considered a heartless devil.</description>
<picture>3312.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="11266" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-08-18">
<rating votes="28">3.08</rating>
<name>Mihashi Ren</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mihashi, the main character of the series, is a nervous boy with no self confidence. He is shown to have always had this personality, (which seems to come in part from his father, who displays some of the same mannerisms) however, it became much more pronounced in middle school, where he was bullied by his teammates on the baseball team after gaining a place on the team apparently through favouritism, as his grandfather owned the school. The other members of the team were resentful of this and felt that their reserve pitcher, Kanou, was far more talented than Mihashi. However, Mihashi refused to give up the mound and pitched in every one of their games, even when his teammates stopped trying and the catcher wouldn`t give him signs to throw. Eventually, Mihashi decided to change schools for high school and succeeded in gaining a place in Nishiura. Although he felt guilty for ruining his junior high teams enjoyment of the game, and thus promised himself he wouldn`t play baseball in high school, Mihashi let slip that he was a pitcher, and is thus dragged into the baseball club, who had no other pitcher.</description>
<picture>33478.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="11267" type="cameo appearance in" update="2009-08-18">
<rating votes="40">8.25</rating>
<name>Abe Takaya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Abe is the teams catcher, and also one of their better batters. His skills as a catcher were developed during middle school, when he played in the Seniors league. Abe was paired with a talented pitcher named Haruna, whose pitches were so hard and lacking in control that he was constantly covered in bruises. However, he persevered, knowing that if he could catch Haruna`s pitches, he would gain a place as a regular. Although he succeeded, Abe soon began to resent Haruna, who strictly refused to throw more than 80 pitches per game, even if it meant walking off the field, and never followed Abe`s signs. Because of this, Abe initially values Mihashi for his obedience, desire to stay on the mound, and control. However, he comes to appreciate just how much work Mihashi puts in, and is determined to win games using Mihashi`s pitching and prove to him that he is a good pitcher.
Abe has a very short temper, particularly with Mihashi, and is noted to have a loud voice, even when laughing, which intimidates not only Mihashi but sometimes his other teammates too. However, when this is pointed out to him, he takes great pains to be more patient with Mihashi and speak more gently. He was charged by Momoe to look after Mihashi, and he takes this very seriously, constantly monitoring Mihashi`s practicing, what he is eating, and how much sleep he`s getting, causing Izumi to note that he`s very bossy. Abe is also a driving force on the field, generally shouting out instructions to his teammates during play, and closely analyzing the opposition. He uses this habit to his advantage as he is very good at predicting which of Mihashi`s pitches will cause a batter to strike out.</description>
<picture>33481.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="12049" type="appears in" update="2009-10-01">
<rating votes="108">8.35</rating>
<name>Itoshiki Rin</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>36492.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="237" picture="95027.jpg">Yajima Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13124" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-11-19">
<rating votes="92">7.68</rating>
<name>Arai Chie</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The student counsellor. If one supplies an alternate reading for the first kanji in her surname, her name is read "Niichie", a reference to Friedrich Nietzsche. She has an excellent figure and a large bust, which is admired by the local people during the swimming pool scene. A case of sexual fetishism features her as a sadist rebuking various masochistic males, often featured in the beginning of various episodes. Nozomu usually does anything she orders him to do (like getting Komori Kiri back to school) as he states her eyes are terrifying but he goes to her anytime he has one of his suicidal breakdowns brought on because of a random conspiracy theory.</description>
<picture>38986.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="237" picture="95027.jpg">Yajima Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13125" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-11-19">
<rating votes="107">3.95</rating>
<name>Otonashi Meru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A very shy girl who does not talk and only communicates via text messaging on her cell phone; she is notably and viciously abusive in her e-mails. Her family name, Otonashi, means "soundless", and her given name derives from the loan word "mail". Her e-mail address is "hazukashigariyasan", which means "full of shyness". She is called "MeruMeru" by her father. Aside from a few weak sounds and squeaks, she is essentially mute, and any attempt to speak will cause her to uncontrollably sputter in a horrific language. Her family also seems ridiculously rich, as her father is able to set up an audition for people to try and dub her voice in real time.
In the anime, her voice actress changes every episode and is chosen at random, and is credited with, at most, a short sequence of nonsense characters.</description>
<picture>38987.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="13126" type="appears in" update="2009-11-19">
<rating votes="38">4.63</rating>
<name>Kudou Jun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>38988.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="326" picture="17162.jpg">Mizushima Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13127" type="appears in" update="2009-11-19">
<rating votes="31">3.50</rating>
<name>Usui Kagerou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>38989.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17812" picture="65365.jpg">Ueda Youji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13128" type="appears in" update="2009-11-19">
<rating votes="4">5.04</rating>
<name>Jinroku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>School teacher, Nozomu`s colleague. He is generally gentle, but his back is covered with a large tattoo that suggests he has a past with the yakuza. He is a fan of Nightmare.</description>
<picture>38990.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17812" picture="65365.jpg">Ueda Youji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13129" type="appears in" update="2009-11-19">
<rating votes="10">2.86</rating>
<name>Takashi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>38991.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="326" picture="17162.jpg">Mizushima Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13130" type="appears in" update="2009-11-19">
<rating votes="5">2.23</rating>
<name>Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>38992.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="13131" type="appears in" update="2009-11-19">
<rating votes="4">1.97</rating>
<name>Cleaning-ya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>38993.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="13211" type="appears in" update="2009-11-22">
<rating votes="3">1.42</rating>
<name>Sekiutsu Tarou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The real Sekiutsu Tarou who sold his own family register to Sekiutsu Maria Tarou. The origin of the name is the same as Maria and refers to him. He sold his name as it was the only possession he had left to experience complete freedom. He is usually found in random places like Komori Kiri and is seen sitting in a cardboard box with a lamp shade over his head with holes for his eyes.</description>
<picture>39151.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="13212" type="appears in" update="2009-11-22">
<rating votes="3">1.42</rating>
<name>Mitsubishi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>39149.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="13213" type="appears in" update="2009-11-22">
<rating votes="2">1.50</rating>
<name>Matsushita</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>39150.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="13214" type="appears in" update="2009-11-22">
<rating votes="4">1.64</rating>
<name>Honda</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>39147.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="13215" type="appears in" update="2009-11-22">
<rating votes="12">4.20</rating>
<name>Abiru no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>39152.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="345" picture="84834.jpg">Nakamura Yuuichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13224" type="appears in" update="2014-04-21">
<rating votes="3">2.69</rating>
<name>Maeda-kun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Bald and wears glasses. The model of the character is Kumeta`s assistant, Maeda. Appears a lot of the time in the animated version in self-imposed restraint marks. He plays the voice of himself.</description>
<picture>154722.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="13225" type="appears in" update="2009-11-23">
<rating votes="17">6.92</rating>
<name>Itoshiki Mikoto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The third son of the Itoshiki family, with an uncanny resemblance to Nozomu. He is a doctor at the private "Itoshiki Clinic." When his name is written horizontally it resembles zetsumei (death), which explains why his hospital is rarely visited by the town`s residents; he has a tendency to lose control of himself whenever he is referred to as "Zetsumei-sensei" (Dr. Death).</description>
<picture>39190.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="224" picture="79056.jpg">Kamiya Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13226" type="appears in" update="2009-11-23">
<rating votes="10">3.60</rating>
<name>Tokita</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The Itoshiki family butler. He is called "Sebastian" by the students.</description>
<picture>39191.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="17812" picture="65365.jpg">Ueda Youji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13227" type="appears in" update="2009-11-23">
<rating votes="3">1.68</rating>
<name>Sakimoto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Thug hired by Tokita to make eye contact with Itoshiki Nozomu.</description>
<picture>39193.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="13228" type="appears in" update="2009-11-23">
<rating votes="5">1.47</rating>
<name>Ishikawaki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Thug hired by Tokita to make eye contact with Itoshiki Nozomu.</description>
<picture>39192.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="13240" type="appears in" update="2009-11-24">
<rating votes="20">3.23</rating>
<name>Kotonon</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A net idol. Her website of heavily photoshopped images is extremely popular; in reality she is overweight and unattractive, and wears gothic lolita-fashion. Her name is derived from voice actress Kotono Mitsuishi.</description>
<picture>39223.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="38" picture="171532.jpg">Sawashiro Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13673" type="appears in" update="2009-12-09">
<rating votes="18">4.09</rating>
<name>Mitama Mayo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An evil-looking girl who compulsively commits malicious acts. Not wanting to be accused of reacting to stereotypes, people simply assume she is a good girl who only looks evil and whatever she did was not her doing. Just as most girls in the class, she has developed a crush on Nozomu, but can only express her love through harming him. Maria made the comment of her being a tsundere. Her name derives from mita mama yo (見たままよ), which means "What she is is exactly what she looks."</description>
<picture>40022.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3131" picture="234931.jpg">Tanii Asuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13675" type="appears in" update="2009-12-09">
<rating votes="51">6.57</rating>
<name>Kaga Ai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A shy, insecure girl who constantly apologizes for trivial matters and things she didn`t even do. Her name in Eastern order sounds like kagai ("perpetrate"), and is most likely borrowed from former Morning Musume member Ai Kago.</description>
<picture>40028.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="355" picture="71573.jpg">Gotou Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13676" type="appears in" update="2009-12-09">
<rating votes="28">5.91</rating>
<name>Ookusa Manami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A married high-schooler who works multiple jobs to pay off her husband`s debts. Her name derives from okusama-nami ("a married person") It is revealed in episode 5 of Zan that her husband is unfaithful and she`s aware of it.</description>
<picture>40029.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="240" picture="17059.jpg">Inoue Kikuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="13843" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-12-31">
<rating votes="44">2.90</rating>
<name>Itoshiki Majiru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nozomu`s nephew, the son of Enishi. He was sent to live with Nozomu when his parents abandoned him. Although he is rather arrogant for his age, he is quite vulnerable to the psychological trauma caused by Nozomu`s students. His name becomes zekkou (絶交, "breach in a relationship") when compressed. It is hinted he has feelings for Nozomu`s student Kiri Komori but so seems to hide this and refer to her as big sister.</description>
<picture>40807.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="237" picture="95027.jpg">Yajima Akiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="28310" type="cameo appearance in" update="2011-07-05">
<rating votes="3">1.34</rating>
<name>Tsubouchi Chitan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The character with the least presence of the group. He tends to be the errand boy for everyone else at school, but at home he is constantly bragging - which can lead to some unfortunate events.</description>
<picture>69640.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="28799" type="cameo appearance in" update="2011-02-27">
<rating votes="19">8.22</rating>
<name>Tajima Yuuichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tajima Yuuichirou is the cleanup hitter of the team. He is an outgoing, confident, and friendly character, and very talented at baseball. However, because of his small build, he is unable to hit home runs, and relies on the team to complete runs. Tajima and Mihashi develop a friendship and is able to understand and elucidate Mihashi`s sometimes incomprehensible attempts at communication to others. Tajima enjoys catching fast balls and, as a result, becomes a back-up catcher in case of Abe`s absence and for training purposes.</description>
<picture>66632.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="28800" type="cameo appearance in" update="2011-02-27">
<rating votes="8">4.85</rating>
<name>Hanai Azusa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Hanai Azusa bats fifth for the team who batted cleanup in middle school. While originally presented as a hot-headed and rude character, he is later shown to be a relatively smart and observant person, and is unanimously voted to become team captain. He tries to surpass Tajima and compete with him, but decides that he must work for the good of the team, rather than taking risks to prove himself.</description>
<picture>66628.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="28805" type="cameo appearance in" update="2011-03-01">
<rating votes="6">1.81</rating>
<name>Izumi Kousuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Izumi Kousuke is one of the more experienced characters on the team, shown to be good at batting, catching, and to be a fast base runner. He is in the same class as Mihashi and Tajima and is revealed to share their lunchtime activities of talking, eating, and then falling asleep. Izumi attended the same elementary and junior high school as Hamada, although up until high school Hamada was a year above him. He appears to enjoy antagonizing Hamada and does not treat him with the respect due to a former senior schoolmate. Due to his more serious personality, Izumi tends to get annoyed quickly, especially at Abe`s constant bickering.</description>
<picture>66783.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="79740" update="2017-10-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-08</airdate>
<rating votes="29">7.06</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さよなら絶望先生</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Goodbye, Zetsubou-sensei</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sayonara Zetsubou-sensei</title>
</episode>
<episode id="79746" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-12</airdate>
<rating votes="15">6.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">見合う前に跳べ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Leap Before You Look</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Miau Mae ni Tobe</title>
</episode>
<episode id="79747" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-05</airdate>
<rating votes="22">7.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">身のたけくらべ / シミと毒だし</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Removing Toxins and Stains</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mi no Take Kurabe / Shimi to Doku Dashi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="79748" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-29</airdate>
<rating votes="25">8.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ヒジニモ負ケズ ヒザニモ負ケズ / アンテナ立ちぬ いざ生きめやも</title>
<title xml:lang="en">From Elbow to Knee</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hiji ni mo Makezu Hiza ni mo Makezu / Antenna Tachinu Iza Ikime ya mo</title>
</episode>
<episode id="79749" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-22</airdate>
<rating votes="25">7.12</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">その国を飛び越して来い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Go Fly Over That Country</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sono Kuni o Tobikoshite Koi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="79750" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-15</airdate>
<rating votes="27">8.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">トンネルを抜けると白かった</title>
<title xml:lang="en">When I Came Out of the Tunnel It Was White</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tunnel o Nukeru to Shirokatta</title>
</episode>
<episode id="80301" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-19</airdate>
<rating votes="15">6.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">仮名の告白 / ある朝 グレゴール・ザムザが目をさますと神輿を担いでいた</title>
<title xml:lang="en">As Gregor Samsa Awoke One Morning, He Found Himself on a Portable Shrine.</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kamei no Kokuhaku / Aru Asa Gregor Samsa ga Me o Samasu to Mikoshi o Katsuide ita</title>
</episode>
<episode id="80990" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-08-26</airdate>
<rating votes="12">6.84</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">私は宿命的に日陰者である</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Am Fated to Be an Outcast</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Watashi wa Shukumeiteki ni Hikagemono de Aru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="82015" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-09</airdate>
<rating votes="12">4.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">一人の文化人が羅生門の下で雨やどりしていた / 生八ツ橋を焼かねばならぬ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">You Mustn`t Burn the Raw Yatsuhashi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hitori no Bunkajin ga Rashoumon no Shita de Amayadori Shite Ita / Namayatsuhashi o Yakaneba Naranu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="82016" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-02</airdate>
<rating votes="14">5.01</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">富士に月見草は間違っている</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Evening Primrose on Fuji Is a Mistake</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Fuji ni Tsukimisou wa Machigatte Iru</title>
</episode>
<episode id="82744" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-16</airdate>
<rating votes="14">7.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">あれ不可よ 原作があるじゃないかね</title>
<title xml:lang="en">That`s Impossible Isn`t There an Original</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Are Ikenai yo Gensaku ga Aru ja Nai ka ne</title>
</episode>
<episode id="82745" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-09-23</airdate>
<rating votes="14">5.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">なんたる迷惑である事か!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">What an Incredible Bother!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nantaru Meiwaku de Aru Koto ka!</title>
</episode>
<episode id="85706" update="2019-10-30">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-07-08</airdate>
<rating votes="1">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="86626" recap="true" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>65</length>
<airdate>2008-01-01</airdate>
<rating votes="2">9.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さよなら絶望先生 序~絶望少女撰集</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Preface</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sayonara Zetsubou-sensei Jo: Zetsubou Shoujo Senshuu</title>
</episode>
<episode id="86945" update="2008-01-17">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="87911" recap="true" update="2017-10-21">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2008-01-04</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">絶望少女撰集 (BS11 Ver.)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Preface - BS11 Version</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112935" update="2019-10-30">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-07-08</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132165" update="2011-08-02">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Feedback Commentary</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223660" update="2019-10-30">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-09-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="223661" update="2019-10-30">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2007-07-29</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1b</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
