<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="6367" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>28</episodecount>
<startdate>2009-04-03</startdate>
<enddate>2009-10-09</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Suzumiya Haruhi no Yuuutsu (2009)</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Haruhi S2</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">The Melancholy of Haruhi Suzumiya 2</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="synonym">La mélancolie de Haruhi Suzumiya (2009)</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Меланхолия Харухи Судзумии (2009)</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="synonym">Melancholia Haruhi Suzumii (2009)</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="synonym">Melancholia Haruhi Suzumiyi (2009)</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="synonym">كآبة هاروهي سوزوميا 2</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="synonym">A Melancolia de Haruhi Suzumiya (2009)</title>
<title xml:lang="pt-BR" type="synonym">A Melancolia de Suzumiya Haruhi (2009)</title>
<title xml:lang="nl" type="synonym">De Melancholie van Haruhi Suzumiya</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Меланхолія Харухі Судзумії (2009)</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">haruhi2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">Haruhi 2009</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">涼宮ハルヒの憂鬱 (2009)</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">The Melancholy of Haruhi Suzumiya (2009)</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Die Melancholie der Haruhi Suzumiya (2009)</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">La malinconia di Haruhi Suzumiya (2009)</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="official">Меланхолия Харухи Судзумии. Второй сезон</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">스즈미야 하루히의 우울 (2009)</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-x-nan" type="official">涼宮春日的憂鬱 (2009)</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">凉宫春日的忧郁 (2009)</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="7221" type="Sequel">Suzumiya Haruhi no Shoushitsu</anime>
<anime id="3651" type="Summary">Suzumiya Haruhi no Yuuutsu</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="6564" approval="14" total="43">Angel Beats!</anime>
<anime id="6171" approval="1" total="11">Evangelion Shin Gekijouban: Ha</anime>
<anime id="2002" approval="0" total="9">Air</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="19">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="126257">I wanted to like this more, and i did kinda enjoy the first episode and the parts 3 to 5 of the sighs arc. Only for hardcore haruhi fans.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="480218">The Endless Eight arc has a pretty bad rep, and it really isn`t so bad.  I watched one DVD a day (meaning I had one-two days of just Endless Eight) and I honestly didn`t find it to be painful at all.  But yeah, if you aren`t familiar with the show beforehand, I recommend watching the first season before watching the second one or you can watch the second season as intended (as it includes all of the first season and the new episodes mixed in).</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="75679">There are only two types of people. Those who watched all eps of endless 8 arc, and others.
Good controversed show, watch it if you want to be surprised in many ways.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="326224">For me its as good as first season was. It fills empty spaces with additional info (Bamboo Leaf Rhapsody ), add movie-creation part (which was really good).

Most people say bad things about Endless 8 part, like its boring, useless, that it could be less eps or add something like Kyon doing something funny at end of each ep using the situation. But to be honest? I watched all 8 eps of this and i liked it. Now those who hated it and didn`t watch all 8 eps should think about how Yuki must feel `cuz she was there and remembers all 15530+ iterations. Compare 15530+ to you not even watch 8... it`s scary, and makes me feel pity for Yuki (especially `cuz for us 1 ep is 20 min, for her its 2 weeks).

I recommend it for general, for Haruhi fans (like me) its must see.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="109384">I believe the "summary" is better as a whole, but this season was very much a good one. Endless Eight has become a classic in my opinion, wich I believe you should not miss. I also disagree with most reccommendations here that it was horribly repetitive and boring. Of course you wanted to know what the reason was behind all of it, and you had to wait and wait and wait, but watching through all of them gave a unique perspective on how a story can be told and I found it very enjoyable to compare the episodes and see in what different ways you can bring the same and yet not the same. And if you are into fanservice, you will get to see a lot of different outfits for Haruhi! In the end you should watch this one instead of the summary, because it gives a unique experience, and give a great buildup to the movie, wich, by the way, you should also definitively watch!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="409371">Personally, I liked this new season. It added more character to everyone, especially Nagato (see the movie if you haven`t already), whom seem to develop a lot too.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="614621">I LOVE this series, including the "endless 8"...</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="367685">Clarification on the infamous Endless Eight story arc: This story line is about a time loop, where the characters live the same events over and over again. Therefore the 8 episodes are essentially the same, with minor changes. It can be tedious, so if you want to avoid it, you can just watch parts 1, 2 and 8 and still get the full story.

Don`t let the poor rating fool you. If you liked the first season of Haruhi, you`ll like this one too. The Endless Eight story arc is unnecessarily stretched out, but it didn`t ruin the anime for me, and shouldn`t for you either.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="445831">The producers surely had fun making Endless Eight and Someday in the Rain, less for the audience.

Apart from that it`s a good show, funny and interesting. But it`s not a masterpiece. Considering the hype, the show is a little bit overrated.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="487479">This anime is completely random, but at the same time really interesting. I thought it was amazing and maybe you will to, Haruhi is really a one of a kind character!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="120055">Imho, this series gets A LOT more hate than it deserves. Granted, it`s not quite the series 2 that everyone was hoping for but if you ignore the Endless Eight (which, protip: you can and should), you`ve got the original series which is absolutely great and worth watching 2nd/3rd/whatever-th time, with a handful of pretty great extra episodes giving you a more rounded and complete series.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="492628">The quality is top grade again, the episodes are fun as always and the animation brilliant.
Having that said, skip the never ending summer fiasco, see the first and the last episode of that part. It is the only downside but it is a big one.
Having 8 episodes repeating over and over was a trolling on epic proportions.
Everything else, top grade, and the sequel movie compensated the damage.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="495882">If you haven`t seen it yet. Get to it. It`s not the best anime in the world, but it is definitely one of the most unique anime. The characters are not "original," but all used in an original way.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="377550">I recommend it to all the true Haruhi fans out there! Don`t skip the Endless Eight!! ;D</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="727529">the summary had to be great back in the day, but right now it should be avoided at all costs. reason? Suzumiya Haruhi no Shoushitsu.

watch this series (all of it, including Endless Eight), then Suzumiya Haruhi no Shoushitsu and your jaw drop. everything here serves a purpose, even Endless Eight - and you`ll be amazed at how many levels Suzumiya Haruhi no Shoushitsu connects with it all.

on it`s own, it may seem just great - but don`t let it fool you. it`s an emotional build-up, designed to blow up in your face in Suzumiya Haruhi no Shoushitsu, making you admire the whole series way more than you`ve expected.

and after all that, with your heart shattered to pieces, you`ll enjoy Nagato Yuki-chan no Shoushitsu even more.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.haruhi.tv/</url>
<creators>
<name id="519" type="Direction">Ishihara Tatsuya</name>
<name id="523" type="Character Design">Ikeda Shouko</name>
<name id="536" type="Original Work">Tanigawa Nagaru</name>
<name id="736" type="Animation Work">Kyoto Animation</name>
<name id="530" type="Music">Kousaki Satoru</name>
<name id="523" type="Chief Animation Direction">Ikeda Shouko</name>
<name id="519" type="Brigade Leader`s Representative">Ishihara Tatsuya</name>
<name id="529" type="Chief Animation Direction">Nishiya Futoshi</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on http://anidb.net/cr536 [Tanigawa Nagaru]`s Suzumiya Haruhi series of novels and illustrated by http://anidb.net/cr518 [Itou Noizi].
http://anidb.net/ch271 [Suzumiya Haruhi] is a charismatic high school girl with a carefree personality and a very egocentric way of thinking, that she underlines upon enrolling at school by announcing: "I have no interest in ordinary humans. If there are any aliens, beings from the future, or espers, come see me. That is all!"
This makes quite a few heads turn, but Haruhi is dead serious, as she soon proves by establishing the SOS Dan.
As it turns out she has the unimaginable power to change the world, but is completely unaware of this power, and so she is also unaware of the effect her power has on the outside world. The cynical http://anidb.net/ch272 [Kyon] does not become Haruhi`s best friend and first member of the SOS Dan out of the kindness of his heart, but initially out of self preservation, since he quickly understands the possibly catastrophic implications of Haruhi`s powers. Luckily he seems to have the gift to keep her more outrageous schemes in check...
Note: This is a re-airing of the original http://anidb.net/a3651 [Suzumiya Haruhi no Yuuutsu] series, taken from the DVD release and aired in chronological order, adding 14 additional episodes with new content. These new episodes are the episodes 8 (Bamboo Leaf Rhapsody), 12-19 (Endless Eight), and 20-24 (The Sigh of Suzumiya Haruhi Parts 1-5).</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="6176">5.38</permanent>
<temporary count="6256">6.97</temporary>
<review count="6">5.85</review>
</ratings>
<picture>196098.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10924</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4382</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4141</identifier>
<identifier>hfjvcj</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.haruhi.tv/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Haruhi_Suzumiya</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>涼宮ハルヒシリーズ</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1639</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>334009</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11699</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/2401</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>368</identifier>
<identifier>v</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2009/haruhi</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="28" parentid="2881" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-11-16">
<name>baseball</name>
<description>Baseball is like a complicated version of Rounders. It involves hitting a ball with a stick, then running around several bases placed in the form of a diamond on a field. Big in the US, and also in Japan.</description>
<picurl>29801.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="464" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-01-15">
<name>sarcastic</name>
<description>The character frequently uses sharp, bitter, or cutting expressions or remarks. (From Greek sarcasmos, "to tear flesh, gnash the teeth, speak bitterly".)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="627" parentid="2856" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-15">
<name>lingerie</name>
<description>Lingerie is a term for fashionable and alluring women`s undergarments.</description>
<picurl>238327.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1136" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-18">
<name>transfer student</name>
<description>A transfer student is a student who changes from one institution or course to another at the same level. Their arrival, when not at the beginning of the school year, tends to cause a stir.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1241" parentid="2881" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-18">
<name>swimming</name>
<description>Swimming is an individual or team sport that involves using arms and legs to move the body through water. Typically, the sport takes place in pools or in open water. Competitive swimming is one of the most popular Olympic sports, with events in butterfly, backstroke, breaststroke, freestyle, and individual medley. In addition to these individual events, swimmers take part in relays.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>208479.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1446" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-15">
<name>energetic</name>
<description>An energetic character, often also called a genki character, shows great, often excessive levels of activity or vitality, and seems to always be doing everything extra fast. Genki characters are often slightly, or sometimes very, eccentric, and are filled with confidence and determination, regardless of whether they are competent or not; in fact, they often have little to no actual competence at whatever they generally do. Although genki characters are usually played exclusively for comedy effect, sometimes they may slow down for a serious or introspective moment. The most common genki character archetype is the genki schoolgirl, who will often be late to school and run with a toast in her mouth.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1783" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-27">
<name>immature</name>
<description>Marked by or indicating a lack of maturity</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1864" parentid="2623" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-12-14">
<name>extrasensory perception</name>
<description>Extrasensory perception (ESP), involves reception of information not gained through the recognized physical senses but sensed with the mind. The term was coined by Sir Richard Burton, and adopted by Duke University psychologist J. B. Rhine to denote psychic abilities such as telepathy and clairvoyance, and their trans-temporal operation as precognition or retrocognition. ESP is also sometimes casually referred to as a sixth sense, gut instinct or hunch, which are historical English idioms. The term implies acquisition of information by means external to the basic limiting assumptions of science, such as that organisms can only receive information from the past to the present.
In Japanese usage the term is often misappropriated to refer to any supernatural, non-magical, super power. Users of such powers are called `esper` in Japanese. The term `esper` is not normally in use outside of Japan but is slowly being introduced due to its usage in anime and manga.
In anime/manga the following powers, among others, are described as ESP:
- telepathy
- precognition
- clairvoyance
- retrocognition
- remote viewing
- aura reading
- out-of-body experiences (OBE)
- psychokinesis</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2043" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>high school</name>
<description>A secondary school that usually contains grades 10 through 12 in Japan, or 9 through 12 in America.</description>
<picurl>210064.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2056" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-09-13">
<name>cosplaying</name>
<description>This character likes to cosplay.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2396" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-02-08">
<name>swimsuit</name>
<description>A swimsuit is one of several kinds of garments designed to be worn by people engaging in water-based activities or sports or during certain activities under sunlight. Most kinds of swimsuit reveal a large portion of the body surface area, but exceptions exist. The more revealing kinds may also be worn as undergarment in sports that require wetsuits, or when there is a need to display the body, as in the case of beauty pageants or bodybuilding contests.
There is a very wide range of styles of modern swimsuits, which vary in relation to body coverage and materials. The choice of style of swimsuit is dependent on current fashions, community standards of modesty, and plain personal preference. Swimsuits for men usually expose the chest, while those for women do not usually do so; however, many women prefer to engage in water or sun activities with their torso uncovered, in a practice commonly described as toplessness or topfreedom. Since the early twentieth century a naturist movement has developed in western countries that seeks a return to non-sexual nakedness when swimming and during other appropriate activities; in some places around the world, nude beaches have been set aside for people who choose to engage in normal beach activities in the nude, and such beaches may or may not enforce nudity onto their goers.
In anime, it is common for at least one episode to feature the characters in swimsuits, usually as an excuse for gratuitous fanservice; when that happens, the episode is usually labeled a pool or beach episode, after the place the characters went to. Swimsuits, and in particular one-piece swimsuits, are a very common fetish in Japan; while the reason for that is uncertain, a common folk explanation is the fact that boys throughout their entire adolescence are commonly exposed to their female classmates wearing them, in what might be called an experiment in sexual discovery waiting to happen.</description>
<picurl>149786.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2637" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>time travel</name>
<description>In time travel anime characters are transported through time either figuratively or literally to find themselves either in the past or the future</description>
<picurl>210068.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2655" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-09">
<name>parody</name>
<description>Anime that imitate other stories (can be from TV, film, books, historical events, ...) for comic effect by exaggerating the style and changing the content of the original. Also known as spoofs. It can also refer to when whole elements of one work are lifted out of their context and reused.</description>
<picurl>150811.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2665" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-16">
<name>school sports festival</name>
<description>To show off the students in sports clothing — in ecchi anime the female students in particular — a sports festival (or athletic meet) is quite popular in your typical anime with school setting. Here the protagonists can show their skills in diverse athletic competitions.
Note: This festival may also, though very rarely, take place at a kindergarten or preschool.</description>
<picurl>161025.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2669" parentid="2869" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school clubs</name>
<description>Even though school clubs in Japan are not mandatory, there is some pressure from the social grid (e.g. fellow students, teachers) to participate in some kind of after-school activity, be it in sports or arts. Colleges also have clubs.
As a comedy element in anime, some students have joined too many clubs, and are thus constantly stressed out. There is also the element of social commentary, making it clear that you have to join a club, if you want to be part of the class. Since self-founded clubs need at least 3 members, the desperate search and advertising for new members can be cause for hilarity in anime.</description>
<picurl>210065.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2775" parentid="2202" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-03-15">
<name>humanoid alien</name>
<description>Humanoids are aliens, intelligent beings who do not originate from Earth, but have a striking similarity to humans or at least show the basic body layout, i.e. two arms and legs, head with two eyes and ears, one nose and mouth. Though the latter - head-related features - may vary. As "DearS" shows some aliens actually exhibit super-human beauty, or as in the case of "Onegai Teacher" they are genetically compatible to humans for some strange reason.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2799" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-08-13">
<name>novel</name>
<description>A novel is a relatively long work of narrative fiction, normally written in prose form, and which is typically published as a book. Manga, comics, or visual novels do not fit this description and are not considered novels; including a small number of illustrations, however, is still permissible, which means that light novels are considered novels.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2865" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-16">
<name>summer festival</name>
<description>The summer festival is used to show off the female protagonists in traditional Japanese clothing — the yukata — a casual form of kimono.
The festivities include food stalls (cotton candy, candy apples, choco bananas, taiyaki), various games (scoop goldfishes), and a fireworks display.</description>
<picurl>161023.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2909" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-14">
<name>karaoke</name>
<description>Obligatory national pastime for students in any anime with school setting. Amateur singing to subtitled music videos.
The word itself is a compound of the Japanese words for "empty orchestra".</description>
<picurl>160894.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3007" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-07-16">
<name>monologues</name>
<description>This show features a noticeable amount of screen time during which characters talk to themselves. That is usually a way to display to the viewers what the characters are thinking. When used in excess, it may be a sign of poor storytelling, but when done skillfully, it may be excellent comedy fuel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3028" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-17">
<name>real-world location</name>
<description>Places seen in the show exist in reality.
Note: This could be sometime in the future, though names and certain places will still be recognizable.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3237" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-02-16">
<name>test of courage</name>
<description>As part of a summer excursion or festival, an anime with school setting may also have a test of courage (or kimodameshi in Japanese), where the male and female students are paired up (by lottery) to retrieve a "charm" by passing though a "haunted house" or a scary forest at night.
The teachers usually disguise themselves as monsters or ghosts, scaring the students out of their socks.
This seems to be some sort of Japanese "coming of age" ritual, providing a certain level of excitement under controlled and safe circumstances.
Frequently seen in the Festival Episode.</description>
<picurl>38866.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3683" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>storytelling</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3758" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-28">
<name>concert</name>
<description>The main characters play one or more live music performances during the show. This mostly happens for anime with the main focus on music.</description>
<picurl>169133.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3806" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-13">
<name>tanabata</name>
<description>Tanabata (七夕, meaning "Evening of the seventh") is a Japanese star festival, originating from the Chinese Qixi Festival.
It celebrates the meeting of the deities Orihime and Hikoboshi (represented by the stars Vega and Altair respectively). According to legend, the Milky Way separates these lovers, and they are allowed to meet only once a year on the seventh day of the seventh lunar month of the lunisolar calendar. The date of Tanabata varies by region of the country, but the first festivities begin on July 7 of the Gregorian calendar. The celebration is held at various days between July and August.
(Source: Wikipedia)</description>
<picurl>160813.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3822" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-15">
<name>strong male lead</name>
<description>The lead male protagonist in this anime shows backbone, is competent, and does not shy away from seemingly insurmountable objectives.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3908" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-02">
<name>lap pillow</name>
<description>As a sign of closeness the usually male character is encouraged to rest his weary head on the female’s lap.</description>
<picurl>167007.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3946" parentid="2883" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-04-16">
<name>filmmaking</name>
<description>Filmmaking is the process of making a film. This may be tied to studios with very large budgets or to inexpensive independent products alike, and even to amateur films; modern technology allows people to film events of significance in their lives, such as their marriages. Anime in school settings may have a film club, which sometimes produce their own films for e.g. the school culture festival.</description>
<picurl>68842.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4051" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-04-25">
<name>indifferent</name>
<description>Indifference or apathy is a lack of or a suppression of interest, concern, excitement, motivation, and/or passion. This may range from not caring enough to seek to get involved on matters that don`t directly concern the indifferent individuals to not caring about life itself, be it other individuals` lives or even their own.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4417" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-02">
<name>existentialism</name>
<description>Most commonly defines the rejection of a god and any transcendent will that dictates how humans should live. It rejects any "created" meaning of life and the world, stating a leap of faith is required to live an authentic life. In this existentialism, belief in a god is often considered a form of Bad Faith.
In length, the Absurd contains ideas that there is no meaning in the world beyond what meaning it`s given. Meaninglessness also encompasses amorality or "unfairness" of the world. This contrasts with "karmic" ways of thinking in which "bad things don`t happen to good people"; there is no such thing as a good person or a bad thing; what happens happens, and it may just as well happen to a good person as to a bad person. This contrasts daily experience where most things appear meaningful, and where good people receive a "reward" for goodness.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4440" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>boy meets girl</name>
<description>A classical type of plot in story writing, where the story begins with a boy meeting a girl leading to romantic development between the two. More often than not the boy loses the girl later on and has to find her again.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4517" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-13">
<name>inter-dimensional schoolgirl</name>
<description>One, or more, schoolgirls cross through time, space or some dimension using a space-warp-magic-portal-wormhole-singularity-thing to save one, or more, worlds, or planets.
A major twist could be that the schoolgirl might originate from that very magic-futuristic world, bearing one great secret legendary power to defeat one big bad legendary foe. The return back home is the leitmotiv of the whole series.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4614" parentid="3683" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>narration</name>
<description>The most common example is that of a voice, either that of one of the characters or entirely unrelated, that appears at the beginning of an episode to offer a summary or introduction, and at the end of an episode for closure or for a preview to hint upon what to expect next.
Another use of narration comes in the form of a dominant voice belonging to one of the protagonists, intended only for the viewer and revealing the intimate thoughts to whom it belongs. This type of narration occurs frequently throughout the duration of the episode or movie.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5789" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-05-02">
<name>back to square one</name>
<description>The story returns to its starting point (or another situation) once or even multiple times. Possible causes for this might be amnesia or time travel.
This sometimes leads to the repetition of certain events (like in the "Endless Eight" episodes in Suzumiya Haruhi no Yuutsu (2009)).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5807" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2007-08-08">
<name>cosmic reset</name>
<description>All events that occurred up to a certain point are mysteriously undone, as if the Universe pressed a rewind button. This usually means some characters are being given another chance to unknowingly play out events differently, perhaps to prevent certain consequences from the previous time line`s actions. Occasionally they become doomed to repeat portions of their life over and over again until an individual event or series of events are performed correctly in just the right way, as seemingly to gain the Universe`s approval.</description>
<picurl>36685.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5824" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-23">
<name>god is a girl</name>
<description>In storylines where many or all gods are portrayed as goddesses (female gods), "The God of all Gods", or the Number-One-God so to speak, is also female.
In other instances, such may just refer to a girl with god-like powers.</description>
<picurl>215285.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5846" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-12-26">
<name>beach visit</name>
<description>Every anime has to have them, episodes in which the characters for whatever reason end up going to the sea, ocean, random island or the local pond.
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in swimsuits and raise the DVD sales.
The cheap version is the http://anidb.net/t6046 [pool episode].
Other marginally less used variants of this are the http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode] and the http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], used when it is too cold for a beach/pool episode.
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene].</description>
<picurl>160805.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6023" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-06-01">
<name>cosplay restaurant</name>
<description>Cosplay restaurants are theme restaurants and pubs that originated in Akihabara, Tokyo, Japan around the year 1999. They include maid cafés and butler cafés, where the service staff dress as elegant maids, or as butlers. Such restaurants and cafés have quickly become a staple of Japanese otaku culture. Compared with service at normal cafés, the service at cosplay cafés involves the creation of a rather different atmosphere. The staff treat the customers as masters and mistresses in a private home rather than merely as café customers.
The popularity of the cosplay restaurants and maid cafés has spread to other regions in Japan, such as Osaka`s Den Den Town as well as other countries, such as Hong Kong, Taiwan, Singapore, Mexico, and Canada.
Often such cafés or a more simple kissaten, small Japanese-style coffee shops, are part of school festivals where the protagonists` class runs one.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6046" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-15">
<name>pool episode</name>
<description>An episode playing at the pool, mostly in school, sometimes outside of it when the cast does not have a chance for a beach episode.
Usually used for fanservice purpose as it gives the staff the opportunity to draw the characters in swimsuits and raise the DVD sales.
The cheap version of the http://anidb.net/t5846 [beach episode].
Other variants are the http://anidb.net/t3444 [onsen episode] and the http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene], used when it is too cold for a beach/pool episode.
See also http://anidb.net/t2830 [furo scene].</description>
<picurl>160904.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6055" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-15">
<name>time loop</name>
<description>A time loop is a common plot device in science fiction (especially in universes where time travel is commonplace). Events in the story repeat themselves a number of times with or without some variation with each pass. Most characters either do not realise this is occurring or are attempting to break the cycle in some way. 
One well-known example of this is in the 1993 film Groundhog Day, in which the main character is the only one aware of the time loop, although time loops had appeared in many fictional works prior to that. Stories with time loops commonly center on correcting past mistakes or on getting a character to recognise some key truth; escape from the loop may then follow.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6086" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-17">
<name>the power of love</name>
<description>The power of love is not only the strongest power known to mankind, it is the strongest power in the universe. The power of love conquers all things. It makes people cry, it makes people laugh, it can make them sing and occasionally it even brings dead people back to life, just so.
More so than the power of friendship, the power of true love gives boundless strength and resolution; by the power of love every hardship can be overcome, every issue can be resolved and it does make people resistant to food poisoning (caused by the bad cooking of their loved ones). Even the big bad evil doesn`t stand a chance against the power of true love and often ends up redeemed.
Even when the power of love is not literally and directly responsible, the scene is often set so that the audience is left with the impression that it was "really responsible".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="271" type="main character in" update="2015-03-25">
<rating votes="1798">7.02</rating>
<name>Suzumiya Haruhi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>In the beginning of the story, she is initially shown as anti-social and displayed various personality quirks, but as the series progressed, she became more open with her emotions, whilst still remaining highly active. She became the founder of, and recruiter for, the SOS Brigade, forcibly enlisting Kyon, Yuki Nagato (the only member of the Literature Club), Mikuru Asahina, and Itsuki Koizumi. She is responsible for organizing most of their activities as a group.
Unknown to her, she has the power to change, destroy, or create a new reality based on her inner desires and feelings. She is described in various ways; Yuki states that she has `the potential for auto-evolution`, Mikuru believes that she is the originator of a large time-quake and finally Itsuki declares her to be `God`. Due to this, she is the main focus of the Integrated Data Entity, the Organization, and an organization of future humans.</description>
<picture>10490.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="4" picture="177060.jpg">Hirano Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="272" type="main character in" update="2015-03-25">
<rating votes="1318">8.81</rating>
<name>Kyon</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kyon is one of Haruhi`s companions, and the second founding member of the SOS Brigade. Upon his entry into high school, he resigns himself to a lifestyle where his adolescent fantasies such as aliens, time travelers, and espers have no place. After one small conversation with him, Haruhi unexpectedly opened up to him and dragged him into her new club. His reputation and fate have since become entangled with Haruhi`s.</description>
<picture>60733.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="45" picture="44970.jpg">Sugita Tomokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="274" type="main character in" update="2015-03-25">
<rating votes="1367">8.80</rating>
<name>Nagato Yuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yuki is initially portrayed as an introverted, taciturn bibliophile. She is actually an artificial human created by the Integrated Data Entity, and possesses supernatural powers as a result. She joins Haruhi Suzumiya`s SOS Brigade in order to observe her on the behalf of the Integrated Data Entity. In addition, she is present to ensure that Haruhi does not use her godlike powers, and aids the other Brigade members in stopping forces that wish her to do so.</description>
<picture>31404.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="245" picture="46862.jpg">Chihara Minori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="278" type="main character in" update="2015-03-25">
<rating votes="498">6.09</rating>
<name>Asahina Mikuru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mikuru is the only character other than Kyon to be brought into the SOS Brigade against her will. She is defined by Kyon to be extremely cute, and is often sexually harassed by Haruhi Suzumiya. She is in fact a time traveler from the future with the purpose of observing Haruhi Suzumiya during the course of the story line.</description>
<picture>168976.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="248" picture="45126.jpg">Gotou Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="280" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-03-25">
<rating votes="379">7.92</rating>
<name>Tsuruya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Tsuruya is the hyperactive friend of Mikuru (from the current time plane) notable for her loud voice, knee-length hair, and prominent tooth. She possesses a cheerful and friendly disposition. She is also prone to long fits of unrestrained and intense laughter at things she considers even the slightest bit humorous.</description>
<picture>54844.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="392" picture="17237.jpg">Matsuoka Yuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="349" type="main character in" update="2015-03-25">
<rating votes="341">4.89</rating>
<name>Koizumi Itsuki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Itsuki is the last member to have joined the SOS Brigade, having been recruited by Haruhi as a "mysterious transfer student". Itsuki was sent to observe and keep Haruhi emotionally stable, in order to protect the rest of humanity. Although he is an esper, which is exactly one of the sorts of people Haruhi desires to meet, Itsuki never reveals himself as such, at least, not to her.</description>
<picture>10347.gif</picture>
<seiyuu id="250" picture="157976.jpg">Ono Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="361" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-09-11">
<rating votes="252">6.18</rating>
<name>Asakura Ryouko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ryouko appears to be a compassionate and hard-working high school girl. One of Kyon`s friends, Taniguchi, places her in the top three first-year girls in the school with a grade of A++: indicative of her pleasant personality, beauty, and athleticism. Her enormous popularity made her the unanimous choice for class president of Kyon`s homeroom class. She also showed particular concern about how Haruhi had distanced herself from the rest of the class.</description>
<picture>54846.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="328" picture="17164.jpg">Kuwatani Natsuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="372" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-03-25">
<rating votes="64">3.75</rating>
<name>Kunikida</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kunikida plays a minor role and does not contribute much dialogue. However since he and Kyon went to the same junior high school, he might know more about Kyon since he once stated that "Kyon likes weird girls," as evidence to support the idea that Kyon is romantically interested in Haruhi. His character is also shown to be smarter than his friends Taniguchi and Kyon, at one time explaining a difficult concept to Taniguchi. Kunikida is also included in certain SOS Brigade activities when there is a shortage of people.</description>
<picture>14656.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="435" picture="188447.jpg">Matsumoto Megumi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="378" type="secondary cast in" update="2015-03-25">
<rating votes="113">4.46</rating>
<name>Taniguchi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Taniguchi is comically lascivious; he gave a `score` of attractiveness to each first-year girl based upon his tastes and preferences. He remembers the full names of everyone receiving an `A` rank, with Ryouko receiving an AA+ and Nagato receiving an A-. As for Mikuru, her mere presence elicits an altered state of adoration for Taniguchi and Kunikida, especially when she was in her soba-serving costume. He also knew Haruhi from back in junior high, and was Kyon`s original source of information on Haruhi before he started conversing with her. It is hinted that he may have been the person that dated Haruhi for the shortest amount of time.</description>
<picture>14661.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="434" picture="41082.jpg">Shiraishi Minoru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="420" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-09-11">
<rating votes="35">4.60</rating>
<name>Kimidori Emiri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54845.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="437" picture="173174.jpg">Shiratori Yuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="422" type="appears in" update="2017-11-22">
<rating votes="134">6.81</rating>
<name>Kyon no Imouto</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Not much is revealed about Kyon`s fifth-grade sister; not even her real name is given. Other characters simply refer to the ten-year-old as Kyon`s (Younger) Sister or Little Sis.
She is carefree, happy and playful and is also the force behind the use of the nickname "Kyon"; after she heard their aunt call her older brother such, she started using the nickname as well in front of his school friends. From there, the name spread and eventually stuck. She seems to get along well with all of the SOS Brigade, especially with Mikuru and Tsuruya, sharing a sister-like relationship with them.</description>
<picture>209815.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="410" picture="228116.jpg">Aoki Sayaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="424" type="appears in" update="2008-12-10">
<rating votes="38">3.48</rating>
<name>Compiken Buchou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>He is the President of the Computer Research Society (or Computer Society), which shares a room adjacent to the SOS Brigade. The President is never given a name other than "Computer Society President" or variations upon that term (all that is known of his name is the first syllable: "ya"). He and his club have had the misfortune of being targeted by Haruhi`s blackmail, being forced to give away their best computer and wire the Brigade`s clubroom for an internet connection. He hasn`t yet forgiven this, and checks the SOS Brigade website to see if they are putting the computer to use (which they haven`t), making him the primary cause of their hit counter`s steady rise.</description>
<picture>14720.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="42817" picture="90853.jpg">Kobushi Nobuyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="896" type="appears in" update="2008-12-14">
<rating votes="20">4.63</rating>
<name>Enomoto Miyuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Miyuki is the singer in the all girl student band called ENOZ.</description>
<picture>15235.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="228" picture="17047.jpg">Kadowaki Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="902" type="appears in" update="2008-12-14">
<rating votes="22">4.65</rating>
<name>Nakanishi Takako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Takako is the guitar player in the all girl student band called ENOZ.</description>
<picture>15242.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="433" picture="17312.jpg">Nagata Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="904" type="appears in" update="2008-12-14">
<rating votes="22">5.48</rating>
<name>Okajima Mizuki</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mizuki is the drums player in the all girl student band called ENOZ.</description>
<picture>15245.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="432" picture="17311.jpg">Hiroe Mina</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="905" type="appears in" update="2008-12-14">
<rating votes="12">4.50</rating>
<name>Zaizen Mai</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Mai is the bass player in the all girl student band called ENOZ.</description>
<picture>15246.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="915" type="appears in" update="2013-06-22">
<rating votes="21">4.40</rating>
<name>Okabe</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The homeroom teacher of Kyon and Haruhi`s class. In charge of the handball club at the school. First name remains unknown.</description>
<picture>60589.png</picture>
<seiyuu id="438" picture="25479.jpg">Yanagisawa Eiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="916" type="appears in" update="2017-12-08">
<rating votes="60">5.51</rating>
<name>Shamisen</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A stray cat selected by Haruhi to play the role of Yuki`s familiar for their film The Adventures of Mikuru Asahina, Shamisen is unusual in the sense that he is a male calico cat. During the filming of the movie, Haruhi`s reality-altering powers temporarily give Shamisen the ability to speak. He is adopted by Kyon after the completion of the movie, and is given the nickname "Shami" by his sister.</description>
<picture>210388.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="604" picture="154161.jpg">Ogata Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1114" type="appears in" update="2008-12-15">
<rating votes="12">3.13</rating>
<name>Tamaru Keiichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Supposedly a distant relative of Koizumi`s. Actually a member of the Agency. His normal appearance is of a wealthy middle-aged man who has a private villa on a small isolated isle. Played a part in the murder mysteries, as well as the other three agency members, that were meant to alleviate Haruhi`s boredom.</description>
<picture>15468.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="189" picture="203306.jpg">Inoue Kazuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1115" type="appears in" update="2008-12-15">
<rating votes="12">2.93</rating>
<name>Tamaru Yutaka</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Yutaka is Keiichi`s younger brother. Also a member of the Agency.</description>
<picture>15470.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="341" picture="52370.jpg">Morikawa Toshiyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1135" type="appears in" update="2008-12-15">
<rating votes="30">4.19</rating>
<name>Mori Sonou</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sonou is a member of the Agency. She is the one who leads negotiations with Mikuru Asahina`s captors in the seventh novel, suggesting that she has a higher ranking position within the Agency. Her normal appearance is that of a maid.</description>
<picture>15495.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1879" picture="20977.jpg">Oomae Akane</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="1137" type="appears in" update="2008-12-15">
<rating votes="26">3.20</rating>
<name>Arakawa</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A member of the Agency. First name remains unknown. His normal appearance is that of a multi-talented butler.</description>
<picture>15497.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="286" picture="17117.jpg">Ootsuka Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7166" type="appears in" update="2018-11-05">
<rating votes="10">4.18</rating>
<name>Morimura Kiyosumi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>25489.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="438" picture="25479.jpg">Yanagisawa Eiji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7167" type="appears in" update="2018-11-05">
<rating votes="9">3.76</rating>
<name>Suzuki Yuusuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>25490.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2503" picture="186211.jpg">Mochizuki Ken`ichi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7185" type="appears in" update="2009-05-24">
<rating votes="8">3.34</rating>
<name>Oomori Eijirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Sponsor of "Adventures of Asahina Mikuru" film.</description>
<picture>25544.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1613" picture="158486.jpg">Hiramatsu Hirokazu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7186" type="appears in" update="2009-05-25">
<rating votes="38">7.59</rating>
<name>SOS-Dan</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>2876.png</picture>
</character>
<character id="8633" type="appears in" update="2009-06-06">
<rating votes="105">6.61</rating>
<name>Asahina Mikuru</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>An older, adult Mikuru from farther into the future traveled back in time to give Kyon some critical information regarding future events relative to his time span.
However, like her younger time-variant, she was still unable to go into much detail and was only able to provide short, rather vague pieces of information. Also, she was strictly prohibited from letting her younger self become aware of her presence in the same time and had to plan accordingly.</description>
<picture>27900.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="248" picture="45126.jpg">Gotou Yuuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="82293" type="appears in" update="2016-09-04">
<rating votes="5">4.69</rating>
<name>ENOZ</name>
<gender>none/does not apply</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<description>An all girl student band called ENOZ. ENOZ is an acronym of the founding members` family names:
* Enomoto Miyuki (vocalist/guitarist)

* Nakanishi Takako (guitarist)

* Okajima Mizuki (drummer)

* Zaizen Mai (bassist)

In the episode http://anidb.net/e105140 [Live Alive], the band almost could not play at the Culture Festival, as Miyuki (vocalist/guitarist) had tonsillitis and Takako (guitarist) had a sprained wrist, forcing them to sit out. Suzumiya Haruhi and Nagato Yuki subbed in as temporary vocalist/guitarist and temporary guitarist respectively, allowing the band to perform at the Festival.
At the Culture Festival, Haruhi and Yuki performed http://anidb.net/s906 [God Knows...] and http://anidb.net/s907 [Lost my Music] with the band.</description>
<picture>187290.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="102626" update="2019-02-01">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-05-22</airdate>
<rating votes="34">7.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">笹の葉ラプソディ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bamboo Leaf Rhapsody</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Rapsodie en feuilles de bambou</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sasa no Ha Rhapsody</title>
<summary>On Tanabata, July 7, Kyon and Mikuru travel back in time on a mission to the Tanabata of three years before. The future Mikuru puts her younger self to sleep and tells Kyon to help a certain person. Carrying the sleeping Mikuru, Kyon finds a young Haruhi sneaking into East Junior High and assists her using the alias "John Smith". After helping her draw strange symbols on the school athletics grounds, Haruhi questions him on the existence of strange beings; Kyon suggests that they might exist because he knows someone like her at his school (referring to her future self). After Haruhi leaves, Kyon wakes up Mikuru and finds that she does not have her time traveling device, or TPDD. They go to see Yuki, who helps them return to their proper time. Kyon wonders if he was the one who inspired Haruhi to attend North High and start searching for strange beings.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="102627" update="2019-02-01">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-05-15</airdate>
<rating votes="15">7.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">涼宮ハルヒの退屈</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Boredom of Haruhi Suzumiya</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">L`Ennui de Suzumiya Haruhi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suzumiya Haruhi no Taikutsu</title>
<summary>Haruhi has once again become bored. In an effort to alleviate some of this stagnation, Haruhi enters the SOS Brigade into a baseball tournament. Due to a lack of players, Tsuruya, Taniguchi, Kunikida, and Kyon`s sister are recruited into the team. However, the team is hopelessly inept, and if they lose, Haruhi might destroy the world. To remedy the situation, Yuki uses her powers to alter the course of the game.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="102628" update="2019-02-01">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-05-08</airdate>
<rating votes="19">9.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">涼宮ハルヒの憂鬱VI</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Melancholy of Haruhi Suzumiya VI</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La Mélancolie de Suzumiya Haruhi 6</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suzumiya Haruhi no Yuuutsu VI</title>
<summary>Haruhi becomes frustrated and jealous of Mikuru`s friendly relationship with Kyon. One night, Haruhi`s power is activated without her knowing, and both she and Kyon become trapped in a sealed reality at their school. Before long, a blue giant appears and begins to destroy the school and the surrounding area. As more appear, Kyon and Haruhi evacuate the school. Kyon uses hints, provided by Yuki and Mikuru beforehand, to defuse the situation and escape. In the end, he expresses his desire to return to the old world and kisses Haruhi, which brings the two back to the "old world". It remains unknown if the world that Kyon returns to is really the previous world, or if it is the new world that Haruhi created during their time inside closed space, though Yuki, Mikuru, and Itsuki are all glad to see Kyon again.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="102629" update="2019-02-01">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-05-01</airdate>
<rating votes="15">8.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">涼宮ハルヒの憂鬱V</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Melancholy of Haruhi Suzumiya V</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La Mélancolie de Suzumiya Haruhi 5</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suzumiya Haruhi no Yuuutsu V</title>
<summary>Haruhi enlists the help of Kyon to attempt to investigate what happened to Ryōko, as Haruhi believes it strange that she would transfer without notice. After a fruitless search, Haruhi tells Kyon about her earlier years, and how she changed from an ordinary girl into her present state. Later that day, Itsuki tells Kyon his organization`s theories about Haruhi, and shows him some of his powers within a sealed reality.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="102630" update="2019-02-01">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-04-24</airdate>
<rating votes="15">9.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">涼宮ハルヒの憂鬱IV</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Melancholy of Haruhi Suzumiya IV</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La Mélancolie de Suzumiya Haruhi 4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suzumiya Haruhi no Yuuutsu IV</title>
<summary>Haruhi is visibly bored and is not her usual energetic self. Ryōko Asakura, the class president, is concerned and asks Kyon to help her. Kyon later finds a mysterious letter in his locker, which directs to come to a classroom, where Ryōko confronts him. Revealed to also be an alien, Ryōko attempts to kill Kyon in order to provoke a reaction from Haruhi, but is stopped by Yuki. Later, Kyon meets Mikuru`s older self that had traveled from the future, who reveals a clue essential to his future: Snow White.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="102631" update="2019-02-01">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-04-17</airdate>
<rating votes="15">8.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">涼宮ハルヒの憂鬱III</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Melancholy of Haruhi Suzumiya III</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La Mélancolie de Suzumiya Haruhi 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suzumiya Haruhi no Yuuutsu III</title>
<summary>Yuki completes her explanation of the Integrated Data Entity and how it relates to herself and to Haruhi. Furthermore, she discusses Haruhi`s powers, and how she could destroy and recreate the world on a whim. Kyon, while simply trying to understand all of what Yuki had told him, is initially skeptical of her story. The SOS Brigade gets a new member — a mysterious transfer student by the name of Itsuki Koizumi. On a day off from school, the SOS Brigade searches the city in groups to try to investigate mysteries, during which Mikuru reveals to Kyon the existence of time-travelers. Kyon later confronts Itsuki, revealed to be an esper, and learns of the Agency.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="102632" update="2019-02-01">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-04-10</airdate>
<rating votes="17">8.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">涼宮ハルヒの憂鬱II</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Melancholy of Haruhi Suzumiya II</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La Mélancolie de Suzumiya Haruhi 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suzumiya Haruhi no Yuuutsu II</title>
<summary>Haruhi starts the SOS Brigade with four members: Kyon, Yuki Nagato, Mikuru Asahina, and herself. Haruhi begins to improve the club room`s appearance, but still feels that it is missing something—a computer. Going next door to the Computer Society`s clubroom, Haruhi manages to obtain a computer through forcing the leader to grab Mikuru`s breast and takes pictures saying if they do not give her a computer she will tell everyone they sexually harassed her friend. She enlists the help of Mikuru to help promote the SOS Brigade by dressing up as a bunny girl and handing out fliers. Later, Yuki invites Kyon to her apartment, where she begins to unveil a secret about Haruhi and herself.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="102633" update="2019-02-01">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-04-03</airdate>
<rating votes="17">9.63</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">涼宮ハルヒの憂鬱I</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Melancholy of Haruhi Suzumiya I</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La Mélancolie de Suzumiya Haruhi 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suzumiya Haruhi no Yuuutsu I</title>
<summary>Kyon enters high school as a first year student and meets a strange girl by the name of Haruhi Suzumiya. During her class introduction, she states that she has no time for normal humans and asks that any time-travelers, aliens, or espers come out and join her. Interested in her, Kyon becomes the first person to solicit a normal conversation from Haruhi. This leads Haruhi to form the SOS Brigade.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="102662" update="2019-02-01">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-05-29</airdate>
<rating votes="15">6.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ミステリックサイン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mysterique Sign</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Mysteric sign</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mysterique Sign</title>
<summary>The SOS Brigade`s website has been created, but it is composed of little more than the club logo. Coincidentally, the SOS Brigade gets their first case after the website goes up — they are to find the missing Computer Research Society President. Upon going to his apartment, they find that he is not there, and nothing seems too out of the ordinary on the surface. After the Brigade leaves, the members, excluding Haruhi, return to the apartment where they find that Haruhi`s SOS Brigade logo and a Data Entity are behind the disappearance.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="102663" update="2012-12-30">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2009-04-03</airdate>
<rating votes="2">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="102664" update="2010-09-11">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-04-03</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.72</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="102665" update="2010-04-12">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2009-05-22</airdate>
<rating votes="1">8.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="103077" update="2019-02-01">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-06-05</airdate>
<rating votes="15">7.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">孤島症候群(前編)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Remote Island Syndrome Part 1</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Syndrome d`île solitaire (1re partie)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kotou Shoukougun (Zenpen)</title>
<summary>A "distant relative" of Itsuki`s allows the SOS Brigade, along with Kyon`s sister, to stay at his newly built island villa. On their first day there, they enjoy the island`s facilities, but are soon drawn inside by the arrival of a storm. While waiting for the storm to pass, Haruhi and her friends play games in doors and have fun together. Later, the owner of the villa disappears, and everyone starts searching for him. Ultimately, the SOS Brigade members find him dead in his room.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="103078" update="2019-02-01">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-06-12</airdate>
<rating votes="14">6.89</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">孤島症候群(後編)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Remote Island Syndrome Part 2</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Syndrome d`île solitaire (2e partie)</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kotou Shoukougun (Kouhen)</title>
<summary>Haruhi and the SOS Brigade attempt to find clues to the villa owner`s murder. Yutaka, the owner`s younger brother, is initially suspect due to having been seen leaving the island the previous day before the storm hit. Haruhi and Kyon head outside during the storm, but find nothing. While drying off inside a cave, Haruhi comes to a startling conclusion about the murder. They return to the villa and set to devising a plan to solve the mystery. In the end, there never was a murder, for all was just a set-up.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="103079" update="2019-02-01">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-06-19</airdate>
<rating votes="36">5.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">エンドレスエイト</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Endless Eight I</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Endless Eight</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Endless Eight</title>
<summary>Kyon`s relaxing summer vacation is interrupted by a sudden phone call. It appears that Haruhi wants the SOS Brigade to join her in summer activities and unfortunately for Kyon, Haruhi has a long list of activities she wants to try out. As such, the group is taken on a whirlwind tour of summer activities, from swimming pools to summer festivals, part-time jobs, and bug hunting. Finally, having gone through Haruhi`s entire list, the last day of August arrives. Though Kyon tries to make up for his lost time by doing his neglected summer homework, he eventually gives in to distraction and goes to bed without finishing it.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="103080" update="2019-02-01">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-06-26</airdate>
<rating votes="33">5.77</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">エンドレスエイト</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Endless Eight II</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Endless Eight</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Endless Eight</title>
<summary>Like the previous episode, Kyon`s easy going summer vacation is interrupted as the group is taken on a whirlwind tour of summer activities. However, Kyon is wracked by a sense of déjà vu. Itsuki is likewise troubled, while Yuki seems even more detached than usual. They finally figure out that Haruhi has put the last two weeks of August into an infinite loop because she refuses to let summer end. They find out that the loop has repeated 15,498 times, but none of them can devise anything to stop the cycle from repeating. Though the repeating cycle changed during the 2391 and 11054th times when the SOS Brigade did not attend the Bon Odori festival, 437 times when they did not go goldfish catching and 9025 times when they did various part time jobs, which is divided into six different jobs. Upon their last meeting in a restaurant on August 30, Kyon calls out after Haruhi in a last-ditch attempt to stop her from leaving, but fails to think of anything he can do, and she leaves. As the last day of vacation arrives, Kyon, resigned to the loop repeating itself, goes to bed without finishing his summer homework.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="103888" update="2019-02-01">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-07-03</airdate>
<rating votes="41">1.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">エンドレスエイト</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Endless Eight III</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Endless Eight</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Endless Eight</title>
<summary>The same exact events in the previous episode once again unfold with slight variations and the gang wearing different clothes. Once again the Brigade, with the exception of Haruhi, finds out that they are trapped in an infinite loop. In this 15,499th loop, Kyon and the others once again are unable to discover how to escape the endless summer. In the same scene in the restaurant, Kyon is unable to stop Haruhi from leaving, hence dooming the world to another summer loop. Kyon again goes to sleep without finishing his homework on the last day of summer.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="103889" update="2019-02-01">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-07-17</airdate>
<rating votes="38">1.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">エンドレスエイト</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Endless Eight V</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Endless Eight</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Endless Eight</title>
<summary>The previous time loop continues for the 15,521st time. The scene prior to Haruhi`s dismissal of group activities is repeated, showing the same event happening in this loop, and the next two loops. As the last day of vacation arrives, Kyon once again goes to bed without finishing his summer homework.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="104930" update="2019-02-01">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-08-07</airdate>
<rating votes="29">3.19</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">エンドレスエイト</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Endless Eight VIII</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Endless Eight</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Endless Eight</title>
<summary>The loop continues for the 15,532nd time, but as Haruhi leaves on August 30, Kyon beckons the SOS Brigade to finish their summer homework together, thus breaking the endless loop of summer. Irritated, Haruhi berates him, but decides to come anyway even though she has already finished her homework. Kyon wakes up on September 1 to embrace a new school term.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="104931" update="2019-02-01">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-07-31</airdate>
<rating votes="31">1.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">エンドレスエイト</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Endless Eight VII</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Endless Eight</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Endless Eight</title>
<summary>The loop continues for the 15,527th time. The scene where Kyon answers Haruhi`s call loops twice, the scene in which Kyon notices Yuki at the pool loops twice, and the scene where Haruhi says she left the last day of summer open just in case also loops twice. Kyon once again goes to bed without finishing his summer homework.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="104932" update="2019-02-01">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-07-24</airdate>
<rating votes="34">1.44</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">エンドレスエイト</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Endless Eight VI</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Endless Eight</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Endless Eight</title>
<summary>The previous time loop continues for the 15,524th time. Kyon rides his bike and approaches Yuki. In that moment, he speculates his reason for doing so and simply lets her leave without conversation. Kyon goes to bed without finishing his summer homework once again.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="104933" update="2019-02-01">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-07-10</airdate>
<rating votes="41">1.59</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">エンドレスエイト</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Endless Eight IV</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Endless Eight</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Endless Eight</title>
<summary>The previous time loop continues for the 15,513th time. This time, Kyon mentally senses an even greater familiarity with events and places from previous cycles. Once again, none of the Brigade members can devise anything to stop the cycle from repeating. On their final meeting in the restaurant, Kyon tries to call out after Haruhi but fails to do anything as visions of the loop`s events flash in his mind. As Kyon regains his senses, Haruhi has left. As the last day of vacation arrives, Kyon, resigned to the loop repeating itself, goes to bed without finishing his summer homework.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="105133" update="2019-02-01">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-08-14</airdate>
<rating votes="23">4.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">涼宮ハルヒの溜息I</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Sigh of Haruhi Suzumiya I</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les Soupirs de Suzumiya Haruhi 1</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suzumiya Haruhi no Tameiki I</title>
<summary>Upon the start of a new term, North High School is preparing for the annual school Culture Festival. Displeased with the class decision on a questionnaire, Haruhi tells Kyon that the SOS Brigade will do something more interesting. Influenced by a bad film the previous night, Haruhi commits the Brigade for a short independent film with Mikuru and Itsuki as the protagonists, Yuki as the villain, and Kyon doing `menial tasks` including the filming. Kyon and Mikuru accompany Haruhi as she negotiates shop owners for materials, such as an expensive camcorder and airsoft guns for free upon willingness to sponsor the film.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="105134" update="2019-02-01">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-08-21</airdate>
<rating votes="19">6.37</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">涼宮ハルヒの溜息II</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Sigh of Haruhi Suzumiya II</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les Soupirs de Suzumiya Haruhi 2</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suzumiya Haruhi no Tameiki II</title>
<summary>Preparation for the SOS Brigade`s short film continues, with character roles revealed. Mikuru is forced to dress in an embarrassing waitress costume for her role, while Yuki appears as a witch. On the first day of filming, the Brigade film the two commercials to advertise their sponsors, as shown in the episode "The Adventures of Mikuru Asahina Episode 00". They then film several scenes in a park, and Kyon points out that Haruhi did not actually write a script.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="105135" update="2019-02-01">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-08-28</airdate>
<rating votes="18">6.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">涼宮ハルヒの溜息III</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Sigh of Haruhi Suzumiya III</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les Soupirs de Suzumiya Haruhi 3</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suzumiya Haruhi no Tameiki III</title>
<summary>The SOS Brigade continue filming, though Haruhi is displeased with the battle sequence. Haruhi conjures the idea of the "Mikuru Beam" from her blue-contact lens on the left eye. With Haruhi`s powers, the beam turns out to be real and fires dangerous invisible beams. Yuki protects Kyon from the laser shots before tackling Mikuru and removing the contact. While Haruhi changes Mikuru into a bunny girl outfit, the others discuss the situation. After filming for the remainder of the day, Haruhi leaves insisting on a tight filming schedule until the festival, including working on a Sunday. Yuki uses bite-injected nanomachines to counter Haruhi`s effects on Mikuru. The next day, Mikuru shows some unwillingness to resume prompting Haruhi to pick her up. Also, Haruhi adds Taniguchi, Kunikida and Tsuruya to be extras in the film.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="105136" update="2019-02-01">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-09-04</airdate>
<rating votes="21">7.08</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">涼宮ハルヒの溜息IV</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Sigh of Haruhi Suzumiya IV</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les Soupirs de Suzumiya Haruhi 4</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suzumiya Haruhi no Tameiki IV</title>
<summary>As the SOS Brigade continues filming, Haruhi tries to give Mikuru another contact lens, ergo another superpower. Yuki quickly takes action and injects her with more nanomachines before any serious damage could be done. After Mikuru is doused in a lake, Tsuruya offers her place as a movie scene. When Kyon notices Mikuru drugged up for a kiss scene with Itsuki, he gets furious about Haruhi`s poor treatment of Mikuru and almost hits her, forcing Itsuki to stop him. As a result, Haruhi becomes depressed, since she always thought Kyon would support her. After hearing Taniguchi`s rude comments, Kyon realizes he is no better and later talks to Haruhi and reinvigorates her. However, Haruhi becomes a little too encouraged as her powers bloom cherry blossoms out of season.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="105137" update="2019-02-01">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-09-11</airdate>
<rating votes="18">7.17</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">涼宮ハルヒの溜息V</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Sigh of Haruhi Suzumiya V</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Les Soupirs de Suzumiya Haruhi 5</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Suzumiya Haruhi no Tameiki V</title>
<summary>Deciding Yuki needs a familiar for her role, Haruhi picks up a stray cat and names it Shamisen. However, when Haruhi leaves that day, Shamisen starts talking as a result of Haruhi`s powers. The other Brigade members meet up, where Itsuki suggests a reminder to Haruhi that her movie is a work of fiction, before reality incurs further damage. Later on, both Mikuru and Yuki share their independent views about Haruhi. As Haruhi`s powers continue through filming, Itsuki calls out Kyon to hold back Haruhi`s powers. Kyon accomplishes this by convincing Haruhi to add a disclaimer over the credits saying it is a work of fiction. After the filming, Kyon and Haruhi remain at the club room to do the editing. Kyon falls asleep while editing the movie, but wakes up the next day to find the movie had somehow completed itself while he was sleeping. The episode ends with a flashback to May, where Kyon tells Haruhi the truth about the other Brigade members, but she does not believe him.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="105139" update="2019-02-01">
<epno type="1">25</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-09-18</airdate>
<rating votes="15">5.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">朝比奈ミクルの冒険 Episode 00</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Adventures of Mikuru Asahina Episode 00</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Épisode 00 - Les Aventures d`Asahina Mikuru</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Asahina Mikuru no Bouken Episode 00</title>
<summary>The SOS Brigade previews their movie of questionable quality. In the movie, Mikuru Asahina stars as a time-travelling waitress from the future who must engage in fights with Yuki Nagato, who is playing as an alien-magician. Mikuru has sworn to protect a young man, played by Itsuki Koizumi, but a love-triangle ensues with both Mikuru and Yuki striving for Itsuki`s affections. Kyon is the narrator of the movie, while Haruhi Suzumiya is the director. The production of this movie can be found in the episodes, "The Sigh of Haruhi Suzumiya".</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="105140" update="2012-09-25">
<epno type="1">26</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-09-25</airdate>
<rating votes="13">8.54</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ライブアライブ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Live Alive</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Live, Alive</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Live Alive</title>
<summary>On the day of the school`s cultural festival, the members of the SOS Brigade are involved in different activities. Mikuru, along with Tsuruya, and their class open a fried noodles café, Yuki attempts fortune telling, and Itsuki is in a play. Kyon attempts to enjoy a normal day. Kyon goes to the auditorium, where bands are playing for the audience, and falls asleep. When he awakens, he sees Haruhi walking on stage in a bunny girl costume with a guitar hanging from her shoulders, which makes him surprised at the beginning.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="105871" update="2010-12-18">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2009-05-22</airdate>
<rating votes="2">8.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="108585" update="2012-09-25">
<epno type="1">27</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-10-02</airdate>
<rating votes="13">7.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">射手座の日</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Day of Sagittarius</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le Jour du Sagittaire</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Iteza no Hi</title>
<summary>Hoping to reclaim the computer Haruhi extorted from the Computer Research Society earlier in the year, the Computer Research Society President challenges the SOS Brigade to a computer game they created for the cultural festival entitled The Day of Sagittarius III. Haruhi accepts their challenge, but soon finds out that playing the game is much harder than she thought. Yuki is initially mystified by the computer`s operation but catches on quickly, as she will tend to do. Eventually she manages to find out the guys from the Computer Society club are cheating and is able to block and use it against them, thus winning the game and some laptops for the SOS Brigade clubroom.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="108586" update="2012-09-25">
<epno type="1">28</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2009-10-09</airdate>
<rating votes="14">4.73</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">サムデイ イン ザ レイン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Someday in the Rain</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Someday in the Rain</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Someday in the Rain</title>
<summary>The skies are overcast with a chance of rain, and Haruhi instructs Kyon to go pick up a heater. With Kyon gone, Haruhi takes pictures of Mikuru in various costumes for the movie`s DVD cover, Itsuki helps how he can, and Yuki is left alone to read. After Kyon returns, he finds only Yuki in the clubroom and decides to wait for the others, but falls asleep. When he awakens, he finds Haruhi alone with him, waiting for him to wake up so they can leave. It has already started raining, so Haruhi borrows an umbrella from school for them to use. When returning home, Kyon finds a more playful side to Haruhi and in the end, she pulls a playful tongue-out face.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="180511" update="2016-09-25">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Hare Hare Yukai (Ep.00)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="180512" update="2016-09-25">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Koi no Mikuru Densetsu? (Ep.00)</title>
</episode>
<episode id="180513" update="2016-09-25">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">FUNimation Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="180514" update="2016-09-25">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Special Teaser</title>
</episode>
<episode id="180515" update="2016-09-25">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Endless Eight Prologue - Summer - An Audio Slideshow</title>
</episode>
<episode id="180516" update="2016-10-07">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2007-07-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="ja">東中学監視カメラ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Security Camera Feed</title>
<summary>Security camera feed of Haruhi making Kyon paint the hieroglyphs on the school grounds</summary>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
