<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="6783" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>12</episodecount>
<startdate>2010-01-05</startdate>
<enddate>2010-03-23</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Sora no Oto</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">So-Ra-No-Wo-To</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">So・Ra・No・Wo・To</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">ソラノヲト</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">Soranowoto</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">the sound of the sky</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="synonym">Klang des Himmels</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Звуки небес</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="synonym">Odgłos Nieba</title>
<title xml:lang="pl" type="synonym">Dźwięk Nieba</title>
<title xml:lang="ar" type="synonym">صوت السماء</title>
<title xml:lang="lt" type="synonym">Dangaus Garsai</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">So-Ra-No-Wo-To</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="synonym">Sora no Woto</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="synonym">Звуки неба</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hant" type="synonym">天空之音</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">空之音</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="short">ソラヲト</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">snw</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">sorawoto</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">ソ・ラ・ノ・ヲ・ト</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Sound of the Sky</title>
<title xml:lang="de" type="official">Sound of the Sky</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">La mélodie du ciel</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="6257" approval="180" total="316">K-On!</anime>
<anime id="4473" approval="34" total="68">Pumpkin Scissors</anime>
<anime id="271" approval="16" total="34">Haibane Renmei</anime>
<anime id="7307" approval="10" total="24">K-On!!</anime>
<anime id="5970" approval="9" total="18">Strike Witches (2008)</anime>
<anime id="13256" approval="9" total="14">Shoujo Shuumatsu Ryokou</anime>
<anime id="10161" approval="8" total="17">Kantai Collection: KanColle</anime>
<anime id="2659" approval="6" total="22">Aria the Animation</anime>
<anime id="275" approval="3" total="12">Kaze no Tani no Nausicaa</anime>
<anime id="13257" approval="3" total="10">Sora yori mo Tooi Basho</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="16">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="481642">Saving a few highlights, the strengths of this anime, which make this show well-rounded, come out starting episode 10. If you accept a storyline slightly below that standard for the rest of the series, this is a worthwhile watch.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="548718">Intriguing, promising, decent production values; and yet overtly moe, with an absurd choice of characters, and a fundamentally stupid plot.

Would`ve worked well with adult characters, more emphasis on allowing the viewer to understand the universe it portrays, and in a slice-of-life episodic format.

Do say: "reminds me a little of YKK"

Don`t say: "I preferred K-On"

PS: I preferred K-On.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="158874">Found it rather plain but the music was top notch!
Only for fans</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="317829">Stunning animation but not the greatest story. Similar to K-on!, Sora no Woto is a hit or miss depending on the viewer.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="281">Art style is "similar" to K-On! (despite having two completely different teams)... Sorry is definitely unique. Mainly fluffy but showing glimpses of the horrors of war.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="4119">Though called "Military K-On", this anime goes on a very different way compared to K-On, with some good (although not fully developed) drama</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="252758">I`d say, if you`re both into slice-of-life and military you might find it rather good. There`s some underlaying post-apocalyptic theme but it isn`t pursued very far. But the two most notable things in this anime are awesome soundtrack (and not only the already mentioned pleasing arrangement of Amazing Grace) and breathtaking backgrounds animation.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="211502">Contrary to many of the other users, I found the shows pacing spot on. You can`t go into it expecting a story about war. The story actually reminded me more of Haibane Renme than K-ON (as was suggested elsewhere). The daily lives of five girls in a deeply compelling world that`s slowly winding down.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="284037">wouldve been a great anime if it were made shorter or even as a movie. 12 episodes are too much with little to tell</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="481845">WTF?! You liked K-on! and you don`t like this anime?!
K-on! is no match for this!! This anime was fucking underrated! Although it`s not on the level of a masterpiece but why k-on`s rating`s 8 and this anime`s is only 7? I don`t know what u`r thinking. Darn it</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="303369">The setting is rather ridiculous and the show had me looking away from a few things, but other than that it really got my attention, and by the end I realized just how good of a show it actually was and I would gladly recommend it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="479011">immensely underrated and misunderstood; this is a beautiful work with various themes artfully intertwined. highly recommended.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="638909">A good story with nice animation and amazing soundtracks. Plot is kind and heartwarming like K-On but at same time showing "the war reality" side. Absolutely must see.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="432184">In my opinion one the most underrated anime there are, and it is a beautiful story to witness. I don`t really know why there aren`t more "must see" ratings. Everything about this anime is above average for me; plot: multi-layered with much of character past exploration as well as it having an overall deeper "legend", quality: very well made, high quality animation, music: the strongest side, outstanding, gorgeous themes everywhere, somewhat nostalgic and "hopeful" (Kalafina - Hikari no Senritsu and Michiru Oshima - Amazing Grace are just so, SO good), characters: mostly female but not only, rather well made and deep. Shame there was no sequel...</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.sorawoto.com/</url>
<creators>
<name id="1405" type="Direction">Kanbe Mamoru</name>
<name id="3626" type="Music">Ooshima Michiru</name>
<name id="1303" type="Work">A-1 Pictures</name>
<name id="9248" type="Chief Animation Direction">Akai Toshifumi</name>
<name id="9248" type="Character Design">Akai Toshifumi</name>
<name id="4250" type="Series Composition">Yoshino Hiroyuki</name>
</creators>
<description>* Sora no Oto was created as a multimedia mix project and the first entry in Aniplex and TV Tokyo`s http://anidb.net/t5408 [Anime no Chikara] project.
Set in the future on a land that, after being marred by long-lasting wars, has settled into a quiet cycle of decline. http://anidb.net/ch11833 [Sorami Kanata] is a 15-year-old girl who fulfills her dream of enlisting in the army and joins a unit of five girls who protect a fortress that looms over a little village. The girls also play music that reverberates across the skies over towns without people and seas without fish.
Note: This title is reported as using the Spanish city of Cuenca and its nearby Alarcón Fortress as a model for the storyline.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2627">6.55</permanent>
<temporary count="2639">7.32</temporary>
<review count="3">6.82</review>
</ratings>
<picture>41075.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11023</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>8197</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>6802</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4570</identifier>
<identifier>qkgjec</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.sorawoto.com/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.rightstuf.com/rssite/nozomiEntertainment/seriesSites/soundOfTheSky/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>So_Ra_No_Wo_To</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>ソ・ラ・ノ・ヲ・ト</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1797</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>335588</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12223</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>sound-of-the-sky</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="36" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>military</name>
<description>The military, also known as the armed forces, are forces authorized and legally entitled to use deadly force so as to support the interests of the state and its citizens. The task of the military is usually defined as defence of the state and its citizens and the prosecution of war against foreign powers. The military may also have additional functions within a society, including construction, emergency services, social ceremonies, and guarding critical areas.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>212184.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="798" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-04">
<name>moe</name>
<description>Moe is a Japanese slang loanword that refers to feelings of strong affection mainly towards characters in anime, manga, and video games. Moe, however, has also gained usage to refer to feelings of affection towards any subject. Moe can be related to lust; however, pure lust without other feelings is considered outside its scope. The word Moe originated in the late 1980s and early 1990s in Japan and is of uncertain origin, although there are several theories on how it came into use.
At the anime level, the http://anidb.net/t7146 [cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] tag may also apply.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1363" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-21">
<name>breast fondling</name>
<description>Breast fondling is the act of touching, groping, or fondling the breasts of a person, typically female.</description>
<picurl>238325.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2090" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-17">
<name>trauma</name>
<description>Character with emotional or psychological injury, caused by single or multiple events/experiences in the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2831" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-06">
<name>Europe</name>
<description>Europe is a continent located entirely in the Northern Hemisphere and mostly in the Eastern Hemisphere. It is bordered by the Arctic Ocean to the north, the Atlantic Ocean to the west, and the Mediterranean Sea to the south. It comprises the westernmost part of Eurasia.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192044.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2923" parentid="2874" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-06-25">
<name>post-apocalyptic</name>
<description>An anime that takes place on future Earth (or it could be an alternative universe) after a major cataclysm has occurred. World War III, an alien invasion, plague, global warming or some other general disaster are common themes to build a post-apocalyptic world upon, where the effects were severe enough that mankind barely survived.
The time frame may be immediately after the catastrophe, focusing on the travails or psychology of survivors, or considerably later, often including the theme that the existence of pre-catastrophe civilization has been forgotten (or mythologised). Post-apocalyptic stories often take place in an agrarian, non-technological future world, or a world where only scattered elements of technology remain. There is a considerable degree of blurring between post-apocalyptic fiction and that which deals with false utopias or dystopian societies.</description>
<picurl>42081.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2925" parentid="2874" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>war</name>
<description>War is a phenomenon of organized violent conflict, typified by extreme aggression, societal disruption and adaptation, and high mortality. The objective of warfare differs in accord with a group`s role in a conflict: The goals of offensive warfare are typically the submission, assimilation or destruction of another group, while the goals of defensive warfare are simply the repulsion of the offensive force and, often, survival itself. Relative to each other, combatants in warfare are called enemies. The terms military, militant, and militarism each refer to fundamental aspects of war, i.e. the organized group, the combative individual, and the supportive ethos (respectively).
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>56441.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3028" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-17">
<name>real-world location</name>
<description>Places seen in the show exist in reality.
Note: This could be sometime in the future, though names and certain places will still be recognizable.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4299" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-29">
<name>flashback</name>
<description>A flashback is a moment in which someone remembers events from their past. In fiction, flashbacks are used primarily to give insight into a character`s mind or to reveal information which had been previously kept from the audience. They normally consist essentially of new content; in some cases, they may also consist of short snippets of already displayed content, as in http://anidb.net/ch23266 [Okabe Rintarou]`s flashbacks in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate], but even in these cases the flashbacks are used to look into what the character is thinking. As such, they are different from and should not be confused with recaps, which are old content being shown again for no particular purpose other than padding or reminding the audience of the events up to that point. As a rule of thumb, to qualify as a flashback, the scene must advance the show`s content in some way or form; anything else is just a recap.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4333" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-07-06">
<name>predominantly female cast</name>
<description>A show with a predominantly female cast has mostly females as main and secondary cast members while few if any male characters have major roles. This also applies when a male lead is surrounded by females of lesser individual plot relevance, such as in a harem setting.</description>
<picurl>70752.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4480" parentid="6246" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>happy ending</name>
<description>And they lived "happily ever after"... *sniff*.
All issues in the anime have been resolved, the love polygons sorted out, the conflicts resolved, the guy gets the girl (or the other way around), and everyone else lives on blissfully.
(Not very realistic, but then again this is anime.)</description>
<picurl>222185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4521" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-28">
<name>lost technology</name>
<description>Any advanced technology or science-related knowledge that was lost for some reason fits the description. This could be technology from a time before a post-apocalyptic cataclysm, knowledge gained a long time ago but forgotten, or the relics of an old alien civilization only recently discovered.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4565" parentid="2925" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-08-17">
<name>war-zone realities</name>
<description>War is hell. This tag is for when characters experience the hell of war... not just the exciting stuff blowing up part.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5408" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-19">
<name>Anime no Chikara</name>
<description>Anime timeslot on TV Tokyo.
Anime no Chikara (The Strength of Anime) gathers together "spirited" creators to develop original animated stories into a television series.
The project was launched in January 2010 with the airing of http://anidb.net/a6783 [Sora no Oto].</description>
<picurl>4189.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5851" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-01">
<name>female protagonist</name>
<description>The anime has a female protagonist.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5916" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-26">
<name>product placement</name>
<description>Otherwise known as a "plug" or "writing commercials right into a show". The practice of prominently displaying or talking about a recognizable product in a program, in exchange for some consideration from the manufacturer, usually monetary. (Source: TV Tropes)
Particularly notorious example, Pizza Hut for the involvement with Code Geass, Darker than Black and other series.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6246" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-06">
<name>ending</name>
<description>This is a container tag to house meta-like tags relating to how endings of anime play out.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6623" parentid="36" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-04-02">
<name>tank warfare</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="11833" type="main character in" update="2009-09-19">
<rating votes="40">6.88</rating>
<name>Sorami Kanata</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>35862.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9642" picture="56026.jpg">Aikawa Juri</seiyuu>
<seiyuu id="12266" picture="56026.jpg">Kanemoto Hisako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11834" type="main character in" update="2009-09-19">
<rating votes="19">4.65</rating>
<name>Suminoya Kureha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>35865.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="401" picture="223216.jpg">Kitamura Eri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11835" type="main character in" update="2009-09-19">
<rating votes="45">8.57</rating>
<name>Kannagi Noel</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>35866.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1625" picture="226033.jpg">Yuuki Aoi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11836" type="main character in" update="2009-09-19">
<rating votes="24">6.91</rating>
<name>Phylicia Heideman</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>35867.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="424" picture="224027.jpg">Endou Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="11837" type="main character in" update="2009-09-19">
<rating votes="31">7.76</rating>
<name>Kazumiya Rio</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>35863.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="79" picture="228519.jpg">Kobayashi Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12138" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-10-06">
<rating votes="10">6.40</rating>
<name>Yumina</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>36824.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="304" picture="17139.jpg">Fukuen Misato</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12139" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-10-06">
<rating votes="7">4.61</rating>
<name>Klaus</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>36825.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="339" picture="79312.jpg">Ishizuka Unshou</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12140" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-10-06">
<rating votes="5">3.64</rating>
<name>Naomi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>36826.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9864" picture="36832.jpg">Yasokawa Mayuno</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12141" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-10-06">
<rating votes="2">2.22</rating>
<name>Mishio</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>36827.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9038" picture="223492.jpg">Takahashi Mayuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12142" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-10-06">
<rating votes="1">2.31</rating>
<name>Seiya</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>36828.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12352" picture="130106.jpg">Hirata Mana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="12143" type="appears in" update="2009-10-06">
<rating votes="3">6.76</rating>
<name>Shuko</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>36829.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="17807" type="appears in" update="2010-11-29">
<rating votes="4">5.56</rating>
<name>Aisha Aldola</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Aisha is a Roman scout that Kanata and Kureha discover unconscious and injured while on patrol. While in their care, the platoon quickly befriends her despite the language barrier (as she only speaks in her native tongue) and her status as the enemy.</description>
<picture>60018.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2360" picture="228063.jpg">Miyahara Nami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17808" type="appears in" update="2011-04-14">
<rating votes="1">5.06</rating>
<name>Miyaoka Yukiko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69793.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="210" picture="71057.jpg">Ueda Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="17809" type="appears in" update="2010-11-30">
<rating votes="2">6.32</rating>
<name>Iliya Arkadia</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The late first Princess of the Archduke of Arkadia.</description>
<picture>60024.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="594" picture="156858.jpg">Ono Ryouko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29080" type="appears in" update="2011-02-22">
<rating votes="2">5.57</rating>
<name>Maria</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66278.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5" picture="233827.jpg">Tomatsu Haruka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="29082" type="appears in" update="2011-02-22">
<rating votes="1">5.06</rating>
<name>Carl</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66281.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4425" picture="26689.jpg">Sugino Hiroomi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="108535" type="appears in" update="2020-03-01">
<name>Hopkins</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>244721.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="266" picture="17091.jpg">Uchida Naoya</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="111770" update="2010-09-07">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<rating votes="1">2.28</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="111978" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-01-05</airdate>
<rating votes="15">5.05</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">響ク音・払暁ノ街</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Sound That Fills the Air: The City of Dawn</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hibiku Oto - Futsugyou no Machi</title>
<summary>When she was a child, Kanata was rescued by a female soldier while lost in an abandoned building.  The soldier was carrying a shiny gold trumpet. "If I become a soldier, I can play the trumpet!" With this slight misunderstanding in her mind, Kanata joins the army to become a trumpeter. The newly-minted Private Kanata is deployed to the small 1121st Platoon, in the town of Seize.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>538472</identifier>
<identifier>sound-of-the-sky</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="112070" update="2011-02-17">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112418" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-01-12</airdate>
<rating votes="11">5.79</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">初陣・椅子ノ話</title>
<title xml:lang="en">First Battle: A Chair Story</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uijin - Isu no Hanashi</title>
<summary>Kanata`s new life begins in the 1121`s Platoon`s station, Clocktower Fortress. There she meets the kind captain Felicia, her trumpet teacher Rio, the quiet Noel, and the youngest member of the squad, Kureha. Kanata quickly fits in with the relaxed atmosphere of the group. She is then given her first mission - what will it be?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>538538</identifier>
<identifier>sound-of-the-sky</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="112719" update="2010-05-03">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-01-05</airdate>
<rating votes="3">9.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112720" update="2011-02-17">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-01-05</airdate>
<rating votes="1">7.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1a</title>
</episode>
<episode id="112997" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-01-19</airdate>
<rating votes="11">6.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">隊ノ一日・梨旺走ル</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Day with the Squad: Rio Runs</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tai no Ichinichi - Rio Hashiru</title>
<summary>A horrible wake-up call plays to a clear dawn sky. Kanata still isn`t very good at the trumpet, but she`s really fitting in at the squad, and enjoying each day with energy. Then one day she suddenly collapses with a fever...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>538540</identifier>
<identifier>sound-of-the-sky</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="112998" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-01-26</airdate>
<rating votes="11">7.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">梅雨ノ空・玻璃ノ虹</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Rainy Season Sky: Quartz Rainbow</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tsuyu no Sora - Hari no Niji</title>
<summary>Kanata`s mission today is to go to town to get supplies. She takes her shopping list and Noel drives her into town in a jeep. Everything`s new and fresh to her, but Noel gives her answers to all her questions. Even Noel has a problem she can`t solve, however...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>538542</identifier>
<identifier>sound-of-the-sky</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="112999" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-02-02</airdate>
<rating votes="12">5.80</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">山踏ミ・世界ノ果テ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mountain Hiking: The Edge of the Earth</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yamafumi - Sekai no Hate</title>
<summary>Claus delivers several letters to Clocktower Fortress in early summer. When they see who their letters are from, Noël is happy and Kanata is overjoyed. Rio curses, and Kureha looks at them all, a bit sad. The 1121`s Platoon`s members each respond in a different way. And a letter arrives for Filicia. A letter that will change all of their destinies forever, a letter that begins everything
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>538544</identifier>
<identifier>sound-of-the-sky</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="113000" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-02-09</airdate>
<rating votes="11">6.33</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">彼方ノ休日・髪結イ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kanata`s Day Off: Hairdressing</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kanata no Kyuujitsu - Kamiyui</title>
<summary>On her first day off since arriving in Seize, Kanata goes into town with a smile on her face. By chance, it`s the day the town market is being held. Kanata goes from shop to shop with her first paycheck in hand, when she meets Yumina, the nun from the church. She becomes caught up in the search for Mishio, a little girl who ran away from the orphanage. But at the same time, something else is going on at Clocktower Fortress...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>538576</identifier>
<identifier>sound-of-the-sky</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="116348" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-02-16</airdate>
<rating votes="13">8.68</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">蝉時雨・精霊流シ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Song of Cicadas: Spirits Down the River</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Semishigure - Shouryounagashi</title>
<summary>On On a summer day when the crickets chirped, the rest of the squad is worried over a depressed Filicia. Filicia was thinking back to a battle she was once in, where she wandered through a ruined city alone and met the ghost of an ancient soldier. "Is there any meaning to surviving in this world?" he asked her. At the same time, Sieze is approaching the Fiesta des Lumieres, when paper lamps are sent down the river to appease the spirits of the dead.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>538578</identifier>
<identifier>sound-of-the-sky</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="116455" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-02-23</airdate>
<rating votes="11">4.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">電話番・緊急事態ヲ宣言ス</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Phone Duty: We Have an Emergency</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Denwa Ban - Kinkyuujitai o Sengensu</title>
<summary>We open to Kanata fidgeting atop a chair. A broken bottle, wet clothes... Seeing the disarray that the mess hall is in, Kanata cannot help but think thoughts of regret and retrospection. Even doing all that, when she has to put up with it... And yet before her tear-ladened eyes rests a black phone that has yet to ring. Private-second-class Kanata Sorami, currently on the mission to confirm maintenance to the HQ-command line for high-level emergency situations.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>538580</identifier>
<identifier>sound-of-the-sky</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="116500" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-03-02</airdate>
<rating votes="10">7.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">台風一過・虚像ト実像</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Typhoon Passes: Illusion and Reality</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Taifuu Ikka - Kyozou to Jitsuzou</title>
<summary>Kureha admires a man named Claus. He`s a legendary tanker who she says was once called the "Desert Wolf". Claus and the girls are stranded in the fortress due to a typhoon. Kureha is excited to hear his story, but they get word of a missing orphan, named Seiya, from the church. The platoon leaves, in the turbulent storm, to go search for the boy. Will they be able to safely find him...?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>538582</identifier>
<identifier>sound-of-the-sky</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="116501" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-03-09</airdate>
<rating votes="9">6.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">旅立チ・初雪ノ頃</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Departure: The First Snow</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tabidachi - Hatsuyuki no Koro</title>
<summary>Rio had been depressed somehow ever since she opened a certain page in the military almanac. What was it she should do, what was it she could do? Kanata worried about her, but she couldn`t put her thoughts into words. With each of them begin the winter this way, they meet an old woman. The way she lived her life would have a huge effect on Rio.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>538630</identifier>
<identifier>sound-of-the-sky</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="116684" update="2011-02-17">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-01-12</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1b</title>
</episode>
<episode id="116750" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-03-23</airdate>
<rating votes="9">8.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">蒼穹ニ響ケ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fill the Blue Sky</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Soukyuu ni Hibike</title>
<summary>The fortress maidens are accused of treason for hiding an enemy soldier. But even then, they try to follow the path they believe is right. The two nations` armies are in a tense standoff at the border. What will the fortress maidens do to stop the war?
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>538634</identifier>
<identifier>sound-of-the-sky</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="116751" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-03-16</airdate>
<rating votes="9">8.64</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">来訪者・燃ユル雪原</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Visitor: A Burning Field of Snow</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Raihousha - Moyuru Setsugen</title>
<summary>The Fortress receives word that the enemy army is on the move at the eastern border. The group is uneasy, but spends their days happily. Then one day, Kanata and Kureha find a wounded girl on the snowy plains. But the wounded girl was an enemy, a Roman soldier!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>538632</identifier>
<identifier>sound-of-the-sky</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="117085" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-06-23</airdate>
<rating votes="12">6.50</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">番外編 第7.5話「饗宴・砦ノ戦争」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Drinking Party: Fortress Battle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bangai Hen, Dai 7.5 Wa: Kyouen - Toride no Sensou</title>
<summary>The jig is up - Kanata saw Rio coming out of the distillery, and now she won`t rest until she knows what`s going on! Filicia proposes a little game, and if Kanata wins, they`ll tell her everything. But of course, Filicia still has an ace up her sleeve...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>693049</identifier>
<identifier>sound-of-the-sky</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="118141" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2010-09-22</airdate>
<rating votes="9">8.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">番外編 第13話「空の音·夢ノ彼方」</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Sound of the Sky: Dream`s Horizon</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bangai Hen, Dai 13 Wa: Sora no Oto - Yume no Kanata</title>
<summary>Given a letter sent to Rio from the Emperor, Kanata searches the city and ponders a question asked by Mishio of what her dreams of the future are.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>559068</identifier>
<identifier>sound-of-the-sky</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="128222" update="2011-02-17">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Promo 3</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
