<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="7435" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2010-07-06</startdate>
<enddate>2010-09-28</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Seikimatsu Occult Gakuin</title>
<title xml:lang="ru" type="synonym">Оккультная Академия</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="synonym">세기말 오컬트 학원</title>
<title xml:lang="vi" type="synonym">Học Viện Huyền Bí</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="short">オカ学</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">occult</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">okagaku</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">世紀末オカルト学院</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Occult Academy</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="official">世纪末超自然学院</title>
</titles>
<recommendations total="18">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="177436">A good series, but it was a little jarring when it suddenly introduced a whole lot of elements that seem out of place compared to the beginning of the series.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="55416">This anime is quite fun to watch, it has a great mix of comedy and horror in it that I haven`t seen in a long time.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="367753">One word... Wait for iiit, wait for itttt - Legendary!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="598920">Very entertaining show. The ending was a bit cheesy for my liking. Characters are well made and interresting.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="97893">It was worth while to watch it. Pretty funny at times. But, only problem I saw of it was that they ran off on different tangents. Almost every episode was filler, it was like okay can we get back on to the real plot line now?</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="239694">Nice work done here with this Anime. liked to watch it good charakter and a good story :)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="26239">A good anime mixed with humor, action, a little suspense, and of course the OCCULT!  A short but sweet series, enjoyable till the end!  

A RARE original anime story. (not based on a manga, novel, or movie)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="437251">In the beginning it is kind of strange but it has good plot and funny characters!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="443328">An extremely funny horror anime. Though it probably won`t be scary for most viewers. The clean animation and hilarious facial expressions really make this one a gem. Everyone should definitely check it out!</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="16938">Absolutely fantastic.
The animation is god-tier, and the story is great (the side-stories/arcs actually works in with the main plot), it will also surprise you with it`s habit of going a complete different way than what you might have thought of. 
Characters are also some of the best I`ve seen to date, which will make you remember them.
And last but not least: DEM DELICIOUS THIGHS.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.occult-gakuin.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="6186" type="Character Design">Chiba Takahiro</name>
<name id="4344" type="Series Composition">Minakami Seishi</name>
<name id="1303" type="Work">A-1 Pictures</name>
<name id="1303" type="Original Work">A-1 Pictures</name>
<name id="8068" type="Direction">Itou Tomohiko</name>
<name id="6186" type="Chief Animation Direction">Chiba Takahiro</name>
<name id="3894" type="Music">Elements Garden</name>
</creators>
<description>It is the year 1999. In Nagano Matsushiro stands the pyramid of Japan, the private Waldstein Academy.
This place is famous for the repeated occurrences of occult phenomenon within its premises. Hence, it is also called the Occult Academy. The dean is committed to studying the occult, while the students are zealous in their everyday schoolwork.
One day, the dean passes away and his occult-hating daughter, http://anidb.net/ch18062 [Kumashiro Maya], visits the academy. There, she meets a self-proclaimed spoon-bending "time agent" from the year 2012, http://anidb.net/ch18060 [Uchida Fumiaki]. As the two encounters various bizarre phenomenon within the academy, the reason for Fumiaki`s timeslip to 1999 becomes clear.
~ translated and adapted from the official Japanese site by Cranston</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2821">5.51</permanent>
<temporary count="2842">7.06</temporary>
<review count="2">6.66</review>
</ratings>
<picture>221839.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11390</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>9220</identifier>
</externalentity>
<externalentity>
<identifier>6974</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4739</identifier>
<identifier>wfdpwx</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.occult-gakuin.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Occult_Academy</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>世紀末オカルト学院</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1966</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>337119</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12861</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="11">
<externalentity>
<identifier>mediadb/media/2612</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="15">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2010/occultgakuin</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>occult-academy</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="204" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-06-19">
<name>violent</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1802" parentid="2606" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-01-24">
<name>seinen</name>
<description>Seinen, literally "young man", is one of the main demographic classifications applied to manga, and, by extension, to anime, especially manga-based ones. As the name implies, seinen works are marketed primarily to an audience of young men; the age range commonly understood to be the target of such works goes roughly from 17 to somewhere in the 40s.</description>
<picurl>181651.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2202" parentid="2846" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-12">
<name>alien</name>
<description>This entity or creature was born on another world than the main characters.</description>
<picurl>222176.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2420" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-13">
<name>enigmatic</name>
<description>An enigmatic person is someone with a mysterious personality that is difficult to grasp and/or defies description.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2606" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-05">
<name>target audience</name>
<description>Anime, like everything else in the modern world, is targeted towards specific audiences, both implicitly by the creators and overtly by the marketing. While categories are associated with specific sex and age groups, this is not a bar on the anime being enjoyed by people who don`t fit into that band; not only do crossover titles exist, but the categories also have a considerable following outside their main demographic, and a person might as well enjoy anime from all categories. Still, does not invalidate the usefulness of marking a title as one of the categories; the same themes will likely be treated differently in anime geared for different audiences. Only one should not jump the gun and assume that a title will be more or less serious or present content in this or that way due to its target audience, or conversely assume the target audience on the content and its presentation alone. As such, the audience categories help form a broad impression of how a title might work with the announced themes, but offer little to no in-depth information about specific content or its treatment.
The audience categories originate from manga magazines, which group titles of a same intended audience into a magazine that is advertised as belonging to that category, and so manga-based anime will have the category from their parent work. As for anime based on other works, the audience is often debatable, but comparing information such as time slot to the manga-based anime generally helps figure out the most likely possibility.
If the parent material was classified under multiple audiences over time (for example, it was originally shounen, but then as the plot changed and became more mature, it was reclassified as seinen), and the anime adapts parent material time periods covering multiple audiences, we tag all audiences covered by the anime adaptation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2625" parentid="2612" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>past</name>
<description>Anime that takes place in the past or clearly seems to take place in the past in case of an alternative universe. This category should almost always go together with one of its sub-categories, because the past can either be a depiction of a historical event(s) or not, in which case it would be alternative past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2626" parentid="2612" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-15">
<name>future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2637" parentid="7050" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>time travel</name>
<description>In time travel anime characters are transported through time either figuratively or literally to find themselves either in the past or the future</description>
<picurl>210068.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2773" parentid="2094" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-01-18">
<name>magic circles</name>
<description>A magic circle is circle or sphere of space marked out by practitioners of many branches of ritual magic. It may be marked physically, drawn in salt or chalk, for example, or merely visualised.
Traditionally, circles have been used by ritual magicians to form a protective barrier between themselves and what they summoned. Nowadays, circles often have the more benign function of containing and concentrating the energy raised during a ritual. Circles can also be used as barriers for non-magical work such as meditation.
Generally, as with most magical practices, an incantation is recited stating the purpose and nature of the circle, often repeating an assortment of divine and angelic names.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>32800.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2827" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-06">
<name>sudden naked guy appearance</name>
<description>A male specimen previously unknown to the viewer and not dressed in any clothes suddenly appears out of nowhere.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2846" parentid="7050" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-10-04">
<name>science fiction</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from.</description>
<picurl>212180.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2851" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>horror</name>
<description>The horror cinematic genre is characterized by the attempt to make the viewer experience dread, fear, terror, or horror. Often their plots involve the intrusion of an evil force, event or personage, sometimes of supernatural origin, on the mundane world and the consequences thereof.</description>
<picurl>214682.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2869" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>school life</name>
<description>Since a large part of the anime audience still takes part in school life or is visiting college, it is only natural to choose a setting the audience can identify with, be it elementary, middle, or high school. For the older viewers a college setting with more mature real-life problems is appropriate. And since clubs take up so much time in the lives of students, these are obviously also important.</description>
<picurl>210062.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2874" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-05-07">
<name>disaster</name>
<description>A disaster is a large-scale situation that causes great loss of or damage or threat to life, health, property, society, or the environment, irrespective of its source or cause. Disasters have substantial, long-lasting negative repercussions, and great effort must be spent in order to undo or mitigate their effects.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2880" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-01-01">
<name>Christmas</name>
<description>Christmas, also referred to as Christmas Day, is an annual holiday celebrated on December 25 that commemorates the birth of Jesus of Nazareth. The day marks the beginning of the larger season of Christmastide, which lasts twelve days. The nativity of Jesus, which is the basis for the Anno Domini system of dating, is thought to have occurred between 7 and 2 BC. December 25 is not known to be Jesus` actual date of birth, and the date may have been chosen to correspond with either a Roman festival or the winter solstice.
On the Julian calendar, followed by most Orthodox churches, Christmas Day also falls on O.S. December 25th; this corresponds to N.S. January 7th on the Gregorian calendar, followed by Western churches.
Modern customs of the holiday include gift-giving, Church celebrations, and the display of various decorations—including the Christmas tree, lights, mistletoe, nativity scenes, and holly. Santa Claus (also referred to as Father Christmas, although the two figures have different origins) is a popular mythological figure often associated with bringing gifts at Christmas for children. Santa is generally believed to be the result of a syncretization between Saint Nicholas and elements from pagan Nordic and Christian mythology, and his modern appearance is believed to have originated in 19th century media.
Christmas is celebrated throughout the Christian population, but is also celebrated by many non-Christians as a secular, cultural festival. Because gift-giving and several other aspects of the holiday involve heightened economic activity among both Christians and non-Christians, Christmas has become a major event for many retailers.</description>
<picurl>160837.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2888" parentid="2607" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>coming of age</name>
<description>In the strict sense the Coming of age describes a young person`s transition from adolescence to adulthood. In anime the term is used in a more general sense where the protagonists have to face a challenge, make an important decision in their life, take on responsibility, or learn a lesson, and by overcoming these obstacles they reach a higher level of maturity.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2910" parentid="6249" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>parental abandonment</name>
<description>In Japan it is a common custom for parents to leave their children alone at home and embark on a lifelong trip around the world once they hit the tender age of 14, sometimes even earlier.
Of course this is done because the parents believe their children are independent enough to get their act together. But little do they know about the small secrets their offspring has, such as a childhood fiancé(e) or even a forbidden incestuous love between their (often not-blood-related) children.
Of course aside from having a huge house, financial support is provided as well. Usually through the means of MAGICAL MONEY.
In rare cases the parents actually die (shortly) before embarking on their world-trip, which is self-evidently used as an important plot device in the development of the child.</description>
<picurl>38239.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3062" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-02">
<name>unidentified flying object</name>
<description>An unidentified flying object, or UFO, is in its strictest definition any apparent object in the sky that is not identifiable as a known object or phenomenon. However, the term is widely used in popular culture to refer more specifically to supposed observations of craft of extraterrestrial origin.
Most UFOs are later identified as conventional objects or phenomena (e.g., aircraft, weather balloons, clouds). Some of them are not identified, either because of lack of evidence or because no conventional explanation can be found despite extensive evidence. Some people consider the latter cases as possible observations of extraterrestrial space craft.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3233" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-09-13">
<name>cooking curry</name>
<description>Japanese curry, usually eaten as curry rice, and often pickled vegetables, served on the same plate and eaten with a spoon, is one of the most popular dishes in Japan, where people eat it 125 times a year according to a survey made in 2005.
As such Japanese series will often devote a whole episode to the characters cooking and eating curry dishes.</description>
<picurl>160828.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3663" parentid="6347" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-14">
<name>body takeover</name>
<description>A person`s body is taken over by some foreign intelligence. It`s not brainwashing, because they still have control of their own mind — but that`s all they have. Either they`ve been reduced to a spectator in their own body, or their soul has been booted out of their body entirely. Either way, the rest of the cast will soon find he`s not himself.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3843" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-26">
<name>saving the world</name>
<description>While villains love to take over the world or cause the end of the world as we know it, the heroes are most likely motivated by the polar opposite, saving the world. A fairly simple plot/motivation related to for great justice and what not, this trope is pretty broad and very common for many stories not focused on character interaction only.
Source: TV Trope</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3852" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-09">
<name>Bright slap</name>
<description>"You hit me! Not even my father ever hit me!" 
You are the commander of a spaceship, leader of a faction or a team and your best mecha pilot stops fighting and grows increasingly hysterical and angsty, while the enemy could strike you at any time. What are you going to do? 
You slap or punch him, preferably in the face, and back to his senses while delivering a heroic speech that would turn any wimp into a man of destiny.
Named after Bright Noa of Mobile Suit Gundam, a prominent user of this for-sure method.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3898" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-11-11">
<name>science and magic coexist</name>
<description>In this anime science and magic do not exclude each other. Magic here is actually very advanced, artefact- and/or ritual-based science.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3921" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2012-07-04">
<name>occult</name>
<description>Having to do with paranormal or metaphysical activity and/or phenomena. Beyond the range of ordinary knowledge or understanding.
The unseen.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4022" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4199" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2020-02-20">
<name>live-action closing -- TO BE MOVED AND DELETED</name>
<description>This tag is set to be removed. For each tagged anime, please tag the corresponding ending/credits episodes with the http://anidb.net/t6679 [live-action episode] tag (adding them and their relation to the ending songs if necessary) and then remove this tag from it. Please do not apply this credit to the main episode that has the live-action ending, only to the corresponding credits episode. For example, if episode 22 has a live-action ending, and that ending is also credits episode C7, tag episode C7, not episode 22.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4343" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="true" verified="false" update="2009-09-21">
<name>main character dies</name>
<description>At least one of the main characters in the anime dies.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4564" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-06-01">
<name>spirits</name>
<description>Spirits will appear throughout this anime. These will often be depicted as small orbs of glowing light, or transparent images of the deceased.
Not to be mistaken with "I see dead people", these spirits will usually appear at the location of their departure when the characters have gotten close to the truth surrounding their death. Or as plot element, when a spirit will often stay close to a character as a sort of "Guardian Angel". Although they are never actually seen, their presence is sometimes felt.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4584" parentid="2637" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-13">
<name>time machine</name>
<description>A machine (or sometimes a living being) that accomplishes time travel. The details (what travels in which direction in time and how far) vary wildly from anime to anime.</description>
<picurl>214767.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5046" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-19">
<name>out-of-body experience</name>
<description>Out of Body Experience</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5408" parentid="6153" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-19">
<name>Anime no Chikara</name>
<description>Anime timeslot on TV Tokyo.
Anime no Chikara (The Strength of Anime) gathers together "spirited" creators to develop original animated stories into a television series.
The project was launched in January 2010 with the airing of http://anidb.net/a6783 [Sora no Oto].</description>
<picurl>4189.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5781" parentid="2849" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-08-01">
<name>exorcism</name>
<description>Eviction of demons or other spiritual entities from a person or place which they are believed to have possessed.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5952" parentid="2874" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-25">
<name>end of the world</name>
<description>The imminent end of the world may range from the total destruction of the planet Earth, to the destruction of Earth`s surface, or to the point where human life on the planet is no longer possible, aka the end of humanity.
In any case it looks grim, and the protagonists battle to preserve what they can.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5993" parentid="2853" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-08-28">
<name>black humour</name>
<description>Sure, it`s funny, but you really shouldn`t be laughing...
In other words, it`s a comedy that employs situations that nice people should not be laughing about.</description>
<picurl>222688.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6070" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-15">
<name>mystery</name>
<description>The mystery film is a sub-genre of the more general category of crime film. It focuses on the efforts of the detective, private investigator or amateur sleuth to solve the mysterious circumstances of a crime by means of clues, investigation, and clever deduction. (Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6153" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>multi-anime projects</name>
<description>Many anime are created as part of larger projects encompassing many shows without direct relation to one another. Normally, there is a specific idea in mind: for example, the http://anidb.net/t4859 [Young Animator Training Project] aims to stimulate the on-the-job training of next-generation professionals of the anime industry, whereas the http://anidb.net/t3763 [World Masterpiece Theatre] aims to animate classical stories from all over the world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6347" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-17">
<name>body and host</name>
<description>When a foreign entity like that of a symbiote, body snatcher, puppeteer parasite, or even a hacker (when regarding machines like robots and computers) enters/outright hijacks a body, the possessed subject becomes what is usually called: the host.
The basic purpose of the host varies on what the point was for it to have been hijacked in the first place. Sometimes it`s used as a disguise, other times it`s used as a decoy and destraction, even simply being used as a weapon and piece of armor that the possessor uses to cause sheer chaos and destruction, but sometimes... a host can be used for fetish fuel.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="18057" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-09-26">
<rating votes="10">2.80</rating>
<name>JK</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>JK is an occult dowser who specializes in using dowsing rods to locate individuals. Like http://anidb.net/ch18061 [Kozue], he is also an occult manic and often accompanies the other characters when occult-related events occur. He is able to engage in combat using his dowsing rods, but usually calls for http://anidb.net/ch18058 [Smile] when in trouble.</description>
<picture>53546.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18058" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-09-26">
<rating votes="10">4.83</rating>
<name>Smile</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Smile acts as the mechanic for the http://anidb.net/ch20888 [Academy]. He first meets http://anidb.net/ch18062 [Maya] and the others when http://anidb.net/ch18063 [Ami] requested his and http://anidb.net/ch18057 [JK]`s help to find the possessed former principal. Smile is shown to be very adept at physical combat although he often carries an enormous wrench as a weapon. He is usually shown to be with http://anidb.net/ch18057 [JK].</description>
<picture>53547.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="52" picture="19811.jpg">Takahashi Hiroki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18059" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-09-28">
<rating votes="22">7.20</rating>
<name>Nakagawa Mikaze</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nakagawa Mikaze is a cute teenage girl who works at a local diner. Her cooking skills are extremely outstanding, as http://anidb.net/ch18060 [Uchida Fumiaki] eats at her diner everyday. However, despite her cute and cheerful personality, Mikaze is not a normal teenage girl. She is actually a black mage whose main goal is to open Hell`s gate and allow supernatural beings to take over the world. However, despite her demonic powers, Mikaze is not the Nostradamus Key. Mikaze is shown to have a wide range of powers, notably being able to summon creatures to do her bidding.</description>
<picture>53557.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="245" picture="46862.jpg">Chihara Minori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18060" type="main character in" update="2011-03-18">
<rating votes="19">2.57</rating>
<name>Uchida Fumiaki</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Uchida Fumiaki is a time traveler from 2012 who is sent to 1999 to find the key of Nostradamus. He was forced to be #6 after the agent before him, http://anidb.net/ch20898 [#5], was killed. In 1999, Fumiaki was a little boy with special psychic powers. Dubbed "Uchida Bunmei", he appeared on many television shows, demonstrating his psychic powers by bending a spoon. His popularity grew quickly, but it came at a heavy cost. As he became more popular, his mother became obsessed with his fame, to the point that she refuses him a normal social life. Fumiaki eventually loses his psychic powers, and by 2012, he was considered a fake.
Upon arriving in 1999, Fumiaki encounters http://anidb.net/ch18062 [Maya], who at first thought of him as a coward, since all he could do is run in fear. However, he eventually earns some of http://anidb.net/ch18062 [Maya]`s respect, as http://anidb.net/ch18062 [Maya] sees part of his life in a near-death experience and realizes that he, like her, was also a lonely child. He and http://anidb.net/ch18062 [Maya] form a team to find the Nostradamus Key and prevent the alien invasion.</description>
<picture>48518.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="326" picture="17162.jpg">Mizushima Takahiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18061" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-09-26">
<rating votes="21">3.13</rating>
<name>Naruse Kozue</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Naruse Kozue is first shown to be a http://anidb.net/ch18063 [Ami]`s friend and classmate at the http://anidb.net/ch20888 [Academy]. She is deeply embracing of the occult, shown through her endeavors to prove to http://anidb.net/ch18062 [Maya] that the occult is very real as well as agreeing to go through a near death experience for a class demonstration. Kozue is portrayed as a being very clumsy, often being the first to fall victim to demons.</description>
<picture>53545.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="176" picture="192484.jpg">Hanazawa Kana</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18062" type="main character in" update="2011-03-18">
<rating votes="92">8.23</rating>
<name>Kumashiro Maya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kumashiro Maya is a daughter of the Waldstein Academy`s late headmaster, http://anidb.net/ch19562 [Kumashiro Jun`ichirou]. She hates occult despite her good knowledge about it. Her hatred stemmed from her father`s obsession with it which caused a strained relationship between his wife and daughter. After her father`s death, Maya becomes headmistress of the school and vows to destroy the school. But after the arrival of http://anidb.net/ch18060 [Uchida Fumiaki], she teams up with him in order to find the key of Nostradamus which will cause an alien invasion in 1999.</description>
<picture>48517.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1799" picture="156027.jpg">Hikasa Youko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="18063" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-09-26">
<rating votes="16">4.98</rating>
<name>Kuroki Ami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kuroki Ami is http://anidb.net/ch18062 [Maya]`s childhood friend as well as classmate in the Academy. She genuinely cares for http://anidb.net/ch18062 [Maya] and tries to mend http://anidb.net/ch18062 [Maya]`s relationship with the occult. Ami is often seen with http://anidb.net/ch18061 [Kozue], http://anidb.net/ch18057 [JK], and http://anidb.net/ch18058 [Smile].</description>
<picture>53544.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="411" picture="17475.jpg">Takagaki Ayahi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19415" type="secondary cast in" update="2010-09-28">
<rating votes="13">7.31</rating>
<name>Kawashima Chihiro</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kawashima Chihiro serves as the vice-principal for http://anidb.net/ch20888 [Waldstein Gakuin]. She is depicted as a stern woman, although with a penchant for keeping a love diary. She is very much infatuated with http://anidb.net/ch18060 [Bunmei], and develops a hatred for http://anidb.net/ch18059 [Mikaze] because of that. Despite numerous attempts, she was never successful in courting http://anidb.net/ch18060 [Bunmei].
Initially, Chihiro is hinted to be an antagonist, but she is eventually revealed to be a white mage, whose goal was to keep http://anidb.net/ch18062 [Maya] safe under http://anidb.net/ch19562 [Jun`ichirou]`s request. Chihiro is said to be a very strong white mage and her abilities very much reflects this. Being a white mage, she is shown to be more defensive oriented than http://anidb.net/ch18059 [Mikaze], a black mage. She is able to erect barriers, and she is able to materialize beams of light offensively. She has demonstrated healing powers as well; she was able to cure http://anidb.net/ch18060 [Bunmei] who became frozen in time due to http://anidb.net/ch18059 [Mikaze]. While in her untransformed state, she can throw her earrings which can function as flash grenades and displays an impressive amount of physical strength.</description>
<picture>53548.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="79" picture="228519.jpg">Kobayashi Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="19562" type="appears in" update="2010-09-28">
<rating votes="5">5.68</rating>
<name>Kumashiro Jun`ichirou</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kumashiro Jun`ichirou is http://anidb.net/ch18062 [Maya]`s father. He spent his life on occult researches,built and directed the occult academy.
in the first episode,we can see him dead - by heart attack(?)- then a lamie take over his body,but http://anidb.net/ch18062 [Maya] kills him.
however in the last 2 episode it gets revealed,that was just a fake body,and he is yet alive.
also it appears,that he is the commander in the future of the organization,who sent Bunmei back in the past.</description>
<picture>53550.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3388" picture="24415.jpg">Yajima Masaaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20888" type="appears in" update="2010-08-17">
<rating votes="3">7.50</rating>
<name>Waldstein Gakuin</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>53543.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="20898" type="appears in" update="2010-08-17">
<rating votes="2">3.23</rating>
<name>No5</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53552.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="20329" picture="53553.jpg">Sumiyoshiya Tsutomu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20908" type="appears in" update="2010-08-17">
<rating votes="5">3.96</rating>
<name>Bunmei-kun</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53564.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="89" picture="148709.jpg">Yahagi Sayuri</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20909" type="appears in" update="2010-08-17">
<rating votes="7">1.59</rating>
<name>Fumiaki no Hahaoya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53565.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="360" picture="171401.jpg">Hisakawa Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20910" type="appears in" update="2010-08-17">
<rating votes="2">3.23</rating>
<name>Ooya no Oba-chan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Landlady.</description>
<picture>53566.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9659" picture="36043.jpg">Tomoe Seiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20911" type="appears in" update="2010-08-17">
<rating votes="2">3.23</rating>
<name>Teishokuya no Oba-chan</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53567.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9659" picture="36043.jpg">Tomoe Seiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="20913" type="appears in" update="2010-08-17">
<rating votes="4">4.72</rating>
<name>Kuroki Shigeru</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53581.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2823" picture="83143.jpg">Shimaka Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21234" type="appears in" update="2010-08-31">
<rating votes="3">6.85</rating>
<name>Okamoto Akari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54265.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="21013" picture="201781.jpg">Minase Inori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21424" type="appears in" update="2010-09-06">
<rating votes="2">4.99</rating>
<name>Okamoto Kengo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54597.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="316" picture="25472.jpg">Ueda Yuuji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21430" type="appears in" update="2010-09-08">
<rating votes="2">3.23</rating>
<name>Okamoto no Tsuma</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>54677.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12335" picture="41371.jpg">Nohama Tamako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21870" type="appears in" update="2010-09-26">
<rating votes="4">4.72</rating>
<name>Kurofuku</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Nameless subordinate of http://anidb.net/ch19415 [Kawashima Chihiro].</description>
<picture>55459.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="18225" picture="228635.jpg">Egawa Daisuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21871" type="appears in" update="2010-09-26">
<rating votes="7">2.54</rating>
<name>Nakagawa Mikaze</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>55460.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="245" picture="46862.jpg">Chihara Minori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="21872" type="appears in" update="2010-09-26">
<rating votes="10">8.79</rating>
<name>Kawashima Chihiro</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>55463.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="79" picture="228519.jpg">Kobayashi Yuu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="49709" type="appears in" update="2012-10-07">
<rating votes="1">5.08</rating>
<name>Tsucchi</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>126579.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="117590" update="2010-04-09">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">Trailer</title>
</episode>
<episode id="119377" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-07-06</airdate>
<rating votes="20">7.36</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">マヤの予言</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Maya`s Prediction</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maya no Yogen</title>
<summary>The year 1999, seventh month,
From the sky shall emerge a great King of Terror.
Waldstein Academy in Matsushiro, Nagano Prefecture. AKA "Occult Academy." A famous school where you can study spirits, monsters, UMA (Unidentified MYsterious Animals) and every manner of the occult. 
One day, a beautiful girl named Kumashiro Maya comes to the school. She is the only daughter of the school principal. Despite the fact that she`s attending her father`s funeral, she wears a white dress and high heels. In the middle of the funeral, they start to play a message the principal left for the students. Suddenly, the coffin bursts open and the students are attacked by the school president, who is possessed by a dead spirit!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543190</identifier>
<identifier>occult-academy</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="119609" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-07-13</airdate>
<rating votes="20">6.21</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">文明の到来</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Advent of Bunmei</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bunmei no Tourai</title>
<summary>July 1997: everybody on TV is talking about the prophecies of Nostradamus, and the famous spoon bending boy Bunmei.  Maya insists that she hates the occult, and becomes the principal with the intent of disbanding the school.  Then, the shady-looking guy who appeared from the sky, Uchida Fumiaki, appears as a new teacher.  He was a time agent, sent to the past to save the earth!!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543192</identifier>
<identifier>occult-academy</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="119610" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-09-28</airdate>
<rating votes="11">8.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">マヤの文明</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Maya`s Bunmei</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maya no Bunmei</title>
<summary>Mikaze is defeated, but Bunmei finds that the future is still unaltered and that his encounter with his younger self is the real Nostradamus Key
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543218</identifier>
<identifier>occult-academy</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="119611" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-09-21</airdate>
<rating votes="10">8.67</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">千の風, 美の尋めゆき</title>
<title xml:lang="en">A Thousand Wind, The Search for Beauty</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sen no Kaze, Bi no Tomeyuki</title>
<summary>The person who killed Junichiro, tried to kill Maya, and is now trying to open the door to hell, has appeared.  But Bunmei can`t even move.  Mothmen and Chupacabra are unleashed, and townspeople cry "Kill the witch!"  In the sky above the city, magical lights smash into one another.  Ami and the others try to summon Maya`s soul, but an unlikely person appears before them...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543216</identifier>
<identifier>occult-academy</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="119612" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-09-14</airdate>
<rating votes="11">8.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">マヤの死</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Maya`s Death</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maya no Shi</title>
<summary>Bunmei and Maya go to Matsushiro City to look for Nostradamus`s Key.  A legendary mask has been found there. It`s said that when it and its partner meet, Minakamiyama will be destroyed.  During the investigation, Maya eagerly offers ice cream and other treats, but Bunmei is glum.  In his mind he hears again and again the words he`s been told: Maya is the key to open the door to hell.  Bunmei finally makes his decision.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543214</identifier>
<identifier>occult-academy</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="119613" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-09-07</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">暖炉のあかり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Akari of Fireplace</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Danro no Akari</title>
<summary>Maya and the rest find Akari`s father, Okamoto Kengo.  They try to ask him about Akari, but he angrily insists that they leave. On the way home, Maya visits the house where she grew up, which is soon to be torn down. She stares at it sadly. The next day, she`s called to the teacher`s room by Bunmei.  With a uncharacteristically serious expression, he says "I want to know more about you."
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543212</identifier>
<identifier>occult-academy</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="119614" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-08-31</airdate>
<rating votes="9">4.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">雪のあかり</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Akari of Snow</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yuki no Akari</title>
<summary>Maya`s class goes to a special class in spirit summoning.  They try to summon the spirit of Jun`ichiro, but instead a young girl named Akari appears.  "I want to go home," she cries, and Maya and the others decide to help her find her home. 
Bunmei says that he`ll help too, but then instead agrees to meet with Mikaze. 
Bunmei is deeply infatuated with Mikaze, and Maya is more than a little annoyed by this.  Maya and the others take Akari to the city, but...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543210</identifier>
<identifier>occult-academy</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="119615" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-08-24</airdate>
<rating votes="10">5.57</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">まんま亜美~ヤ!</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mamma Ami~ya!</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mamma Ami~ya!</title>
<summary>Maya and Ami had a fight.  The two of them are avoiding each other at school, looking away whenever they meet.  After school, Maya and Fumiaki go to the pasture to look into the cattle mutilations,  where they find that all the cows have been drained of blood.  Later Maya is called by Ami to the grounds of Minakami shrine.  Just as the two are about to speak, they hear Kozue scream!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543208</identifier>
<identifier>occult-academy</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="119616" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-08-17</airdate>
<rating votes="12">3.47</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">マヤの亜美~ゴ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Maya`s Amigo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Maya no Amigo</title>
<summary>Maya meets with Ami`s father, Shige. Shige tells scary stories, like the old days, but Maya isn`t interested or scared. She used to listen to attentively... Shige is worried now that she`s come to hate the occult. The next day Maya and Kozue head to Ami`s house. Ami brings out a school diary from elementary school. Maya gets embarrassed over this as they read it. And then, news of a mystery circle in the outskirts of Matsushiro!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543206</identifier>
<identifier>occult-academy</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="119617" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-08-10</airdate>
<rating votes="14">6.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">文明の道程</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Bunmei`s Distance</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bunmei no Michinori</title>
<summary>fter her near-death experience, Kozue had been acting weirdly.  Maya and Ami show her various occult things, but she doesn`t respond at all.  As a last resort, they make Fumiaki show his spoon bending trick, but it does nothing.  They decide to go to the afterlife to bring her back, and with Smile and JK.`s help, they sneak into the school in the middle of the night!
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543204</identifier>
<identifier>occult-academy</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="119618" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-08-03</airdate>
<rating votes="14">4.35</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">夏のこずえ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Kozue in the Summer</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Natsu no Kozue</title>
<summary>Maya has given up on Bunmei. She decides to stop the prophesy herself and Bunmei is confused about the sudden change in attitude. Meanwhile, Kozue heads down the path towards the occult... Non-rusting spoons, ghost summoning, tsuchinoko, aliens, poltergeists?! Kozue swears to herself she will see these phenomena firsthand someday! Then the near-death monitor shows a candidate...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543202</identifier>
<identifier>occult-academy</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="119619" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-07-27</airdate>
<rating votes="14">4.70</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">文明の崩壊</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Collapse of Bunmei</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bunmei no Houkai</title>
<summary>Maya and Kozue have vanished.  The whole town starts searching for them; Smile and JK with dowsing, and Fumiaki and Mikaze on their own.  Fumiaki and Mikaze follow a witness`s lead and search Minakamiyama; a power spot known as Japan`s pyramid.  As they enter a temple in the center of the mountain, they find a cave that leads deeper in...
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543200</identifier>
<identifier>occult-academy</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="119620" update="2016-11-21">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2010-07-14</airdate>
<rating votes="19">3.60</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">美し風, 吹き抜けて</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Mikaze Blows Through</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Umashi Kaze, Fukinukete</title>
<summary>People are vanishing all around Occult Academy.  Maya hears that a Tengu is behind it, and tells Fumiaki that he needs to investigate, since it may be related to the Key of Nostradamus.  Their goal is to find the key of nostradamus and stop the prophecy.  However, Fumiaki isn`t getting into it.  "Things used to be so good," he whispers at he watches his old self on TV as the spoon-bending boy.
Source: crunchyroll</summary>
<resources>
<resource type="28">
<externalentity>
<identifier>543198</identifier>
<identifier>occult-academy</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
</episode>
<episode id="120117" update="2010-09-30">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-07-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
<episode id="120118" update="2010-09-30">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-07-06</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="122772" update="2011-06-12">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2010-09-22</airdate>
<rating votes="2">5.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">LOVEマシーン</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Love Machine</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Love Machine</title>
</episode>
<episode id="124860" update="2011-11-20">
<epno type="2">S2</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2010-10-27</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">よろしくツッチー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Getting Along With Tsucchi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yoroshiku Tsucchi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="125594" update="2011-06-12">
<epno type="2">S3</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2010-11-24</airdate>
<rating votes="3">4.46</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">なかよしツッチー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Our Good Friend Tsucchi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nakayoshi Tsucchi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="126456" update="2011-06-12">
<epno type="2">S4</epno>
<length>3</length>
<airdate>2010-12-22</airdate>
<rating votes="2">6.13</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">がんばれツッチー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">You Can Do It Tsucchi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Ganbare Tsucchi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="127864" update="2011-06-12">
<epno type="2">S5</epno>
<length>4</length>
<airdate>2011-01-26</airdate>
<rating votes="2">3.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">さよならツッチー</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Farewell Tsucchi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sayonara Tsucchi</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
