<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="8421" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>24</episodecount>
<startdate>2011-07-03</startdate>
<enddate>2011-12-23</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Mawaru Penguindrum</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Penguin Drum</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">回转企鹅罐</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">mpd</title>
<title xml:lang="uk" type="short">Пінгвобарабан</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">輪るピングドラム</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Penguindrum</title>
<title xml:lang="fr" type="official">Mawaru Penguindrum</title>
<title xml:lang="it" type="official">Mawaru Penguindrum</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">돌아가는 핑드럼</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="287" approval="84" total="110">Shoujo Kakumei Utena</anime>
<anime id="10811" approval="29" total="36">Yurikuma Arashi</anime>
<anime id="13869" approval="15" total="15">Sarazanmai</anime>
<anime id="9875" approval="4" total="17">Kill la Kill</anime>
<anime id="6671" approval="3" total="16">Durarara!!</anime>
<anime id="9214" approval="3" total="13">Zetsuen no Tempest: The Civilization Blaster</anime>
<anime id="8742" approval="2" total="11">Kokoro Connect</anime>
<anime id="4889" approval="2" total="8">Tatoe Kimi ga Sekaijuu no Teki ni Natte mo</anime>
<anime id="9499" approval="1" total="5">Bakumatsu Gijinden Roman</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="19">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="360228">Amazing anime. In my opinion 8/10.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="63624">Be warned, this is shoujo...Don`t be fooled by the tags.
Also, starts very well, but soon becomes "static" and boringand the end is awful.
Try it at your own risk.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="1057">If you like Bakemonogatari stylized anime this will probably be for you as it`s quite well animated and most definitely tries to `mind screw you`, but there isn`t a lot of meaning to it besides the intent.

If you`re looking for deep plots, philosophical delving, and symbolism different animes like Kaiba would better serve that. This just seems to be a schizophrenic mess trying to dress itself up in grown up clothes. Quite overrated.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="729755">Anime newcomers may be put off by this anime taking it as deep and artistic. Just enjoying the experience will reveal the real depth of this anime. It`s honestly a phenomenon</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="203901">One of the best shoujo series I`ve seen... from someone who generally doesn`t like the shoujo genre...

If you`ve seen it / gonna see it, I`d definitely recommend reading up on the 1995 Sarin gas attack on the Tokyo subways. ;)</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="207137">Definitly watch worthy. At first I thought it was another crap anime, but the originality of this anime kept me watching it. If this keeps up until the end of the series, the show may be one of the top animes this season.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="75448">When i started with this show, i thought another random shounen anime...but after watching it through from beginning to end i have to say there is a bit of everything, shounen, tragedy, twisted love but most important thing this show had in some twisted way a soul, and it has an end. Watch it and you wont regret it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="494541">One of the best(if not the best)animes from this season. The character development is amazing, the op is amazing(so is the ending), definitely recommend it...</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="2975">Revolutionary Girl Utena meets Evangelion... and Philip Dick.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="281995">This one`s kind of controversial. I really liked it, and it definitely has value in it, but a lot of it just seemed random. I`d say watch it and decide for yourself if you want to love it or hate it.</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="373701">A masterpiece that we have definitely there ! Maybe it isn`t an anime which will be appreciated by the large public but I don`t have other advice except to give his chance to this anime !</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Must See" uid="536019">A rare find, amongst the sea of anime. Very unique. Nice mix of comedy &amp; heartwarming moments. Plus this anime-- when it ends. Very enjoyable, worth a watch. Definitely one of my favorites.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://penguindrum.jp/</url>
<creators>
<name id="982" type="Animation Work">Brain`s Base</name>
<name id="3648" type="Series Composition">Ikuhara Kunihiko</name>
<name id="3648" type="Direction">Ikuhara Kunihiko</name>
<name id="2213" type="Chief Animation Direction">Nishii Terumi</name>
<name id="2213" type="Character Design">Nishii Terumi</name>
<name id="2214" type="Chief Direction">Nakamura Shouko</name>
<name id="3073" type="Music">Hashimoto Yukari</name>
<name id="27350" type="Series Composition">Ikami Takayo</name>
</creators>
<description>The story centres around the lives of three siblings, http://anidb.net/ch33250 [Takakura Kanba], http://anidb.net/ch33251 [Takakura Shouma] and their terminally ill sister http://anidb.net/ch33252 [Takakura Himari]. Himari passes away after going out on a trip with her brothers. She was however, miraculously saved by a spirit thriving in a penguin-shaped hat. In return for her extended life, the twins must search for an item known as the Penguin Drum with the aid of three penguins which are visible only to the siblings.
Source: ANN
Note: The first episode received an advanced screening as part of an event held at Animate`s Yokohama branch on July 3, 2011. The regular television broadcast started on July 8, 2011.</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="2928">7.60</permanent>
<temporary count="2948">7.69</temporary>
<review count="7">6.61</review>
</ratings>
<picture>66485.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>12998</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>10721</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>4937</identifier>
<identifier>xifvht</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://penguindrum.jp/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>http://starchild.fm/special/en/penguindrum</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Mawaru-Penguindrum</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>輪るピングドラム</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>2225</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>339909</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="10">
<externalentity>
<identifier>13625</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>maintenance tags</name>
<description>These tags are used for maintenance.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="55" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-08-11">
<name>awards</name>
</tag>
<tag id="1760" parentid="2608" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-05-23">
<name>bishounen</name>
<description>Young man whose beauty (and sexual appeal) transcends the boundary of gender or sexual orientation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1835" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-12-17">
<name>animal sidekick</name>
<description>Every mahou shoujo anime needs them, the cute little critters that are supposed to help the protagonists but in reality are nothing but useless bystanders most often abused for gags. Kids love them but they can also often turn into an annoyance.</description>
<picurl>227760.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1876" parentid="2794" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>musical band</name>
<description>A musical ensemble also known as a music(al) group or music(al) band is a group of people who perform instrumental or vocal music, typically known by a distinct name.</description>
<picurl>10249.jpeg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="1973" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-22">
<name>cooking</name>
<description>Cooking is the process of preparing food by using heat.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2094" parentid="2849" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-10-25">
<name>magic</name>
<description>Magic is the art of purportedly manipulating aspects of reality either by supernatural means or through knowledge of unknown occult laws.</description>
<picurl>178878.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2608" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-12-04">
<name>fetishes</name>
<description>Everything under fetishes (except for Bishounen and Juujin) is strictly only meant for hentai (18 Restricted) and ecchi anime. In case of ecchi, it must be the main element of the show and not when there`s only some of it, for example, there`s some ecchi in Shinseiki Evangelion, but the fact you get to see Asuka`s pantsu doesn`t warrant it the schoolgirl fetish category. So be careful to which ecchi show you add fetishes; it`s fairly straightforward with hentai, though. Overall, this category tree is to satisfy the needs of people with different fetishes, so they can search for what tingles their tangle; hence why this is restricted to hentai and full ecchi shows. </description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2623" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>super power</name>
<description>Be it an ancient Greek Heracles, a cybernetic muscle-man, or a fourteen year-old girl in a mini-skirted sailor suit. As long as they have super powers, they`re in the show.</description>
<picurl>212182.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2648" parentid="2849" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-11-04">
<name>contemporary fantasy</name>
<description>Contemporary fantasy, also known as modern fantasy or indigenous fantasy, is a sub-genre of fantasy, set in the present day. It is perhaps most popular for its sub-genre, urban fantasy.
These terms are used to describe stories set in the putative real world (often referred to as consensus reality) in contemporary times, in which magic and magical creatures exist, either living in the interstices of our world or leaking over from alternate worlds. It thus has much in common with, and sometimes overlaps with secret history; a work of fantasy in which the magic could not remain secret or does not have any known relationship to known history would not fit into this subgenre. Occasionally certain contemporary fantasy novels will make reference to pop culture.
Novels in which modern characters travel into alternate worlds, and all the magical action takes place there (except for the portal required to transport them), are not considered contemporary fantasy. Thus, C.S. Lewis`s The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, where all fantasy events take place in the land of Narnia which is reached via a magic wardrobe, would not count as contemporary fantasy; on the other hand, the part of The Magician`s Nephew, where the Empress Jadis gets to London, tries to take over the Earth and clashes with police and a crowd of cockneys, would qualify as such.
Contemporary fantasy is also to be distinguished from horror fiction, which also often has contemporary settings. When encountering magical events and creatures, the protagonist of a horror novel is horrified, while the protagonist of a fantasy novel (contemporary or otherwise) is filled with a sense of joy and wonder. Horrifying events may happen, but the fundamental distinction is vital.
In his preface to That Hideous Strength, one of the earlier works falling within this sub-genre, C.S. Lewis explained why, when writing a tale about "magicians, devils, pantomime animals and planetary angels", he chose to start it with a detailed depiction of narrow-minded academic politics at a provincial English university and the schemes of crooked real estate developers: "I am following the traditional fairy-tale. We do not always notice its method, because the cottages, castles, woodcutters and petty kings with which a fairy tale opens have become for us as remote as the witches and ogres to which it proceeds. But they were not remote at all to the men who first made and enjoyed the tales". The same is true for many of the later works in the genre, which often begin with a seemingly normal scene of modern daily life to then disclose supernatural and magical beings and events hidden behind the scenes.
Source: wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2651" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-01-15">
<name>absurdist humour</name>
<description>Surreal humour, also known as absurdist humour, is a form of humour predicated on deliberate violations of causal reasoning, producing events and behaviours that are obviously illogical. Constructions of surreal humour tend to involve bizarre juxtapositions, non-sequiturs, irrational or absurd situations, and expressions of nonsense.
The humour arises from a subversion of audience`s expectations, so that amusement is founded on unpredictability, separate from a logical analysis of the situation. Its appeal stems from the fact that the situation described is exceedingly ridiculous or unlikely.
On an analytical level, all jokes contain a certain amount of incongruity, but while regular jokes carry an incongruity that the audience accepts as compatible with expectations, absurd jokes are characterized by a disproportionate amount of it, with the punch line delivering a situation incompatible with the world as we know it and failing to resolve the matter in the audience`s eyes.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2653" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-04">
<name>slapstick</name>
<description>Slapstick humour is generally recognized by lots of physical abuse, horseplay and practical jokes. Also often seen are impossible situations, using sounds to illustrate impossible stunts that aren`t shown on-screen and to create tension for audience anticipation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2658" parentid="2853" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-07">
<name>toilet humour</name>
<description>Everything leads back to poo.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2729" parentid="2848" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-02">
<name>BDSM</name>
<description>A form of "kinky sex". The acronym BDSM derives from BD (bondage and discipline), DS (dominance and submission) and SM (sadism and masochism). BDSM usually characterizes with one side being superior (active) over the other (passive), with each side being one or more participants. Whips, chains, handcuffs, ropes, blindfolds are common elements of BDSM.</description>
<picurl>233865.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2739" parentid="2842" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-17">
<name>brother-sister incest</name>
<description>Immoral or illegal sexual relations between two siblings of opposite sex.</description>
<picurl>210881.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2746" parentid="2901" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-26">
<name>shibari</name>
<description>Not to be confused with Hojoujutsu (捕縄術) or Nawajutsu (縄術), which is the traditional Japanese martial art of restraining a person using cord or rope.
More commonly known as Kinbaku (緊縛) in Japan, Shibari is the word for "erotic bondage" or Kinbaku-bi which means "beautiful bondage". Kinbaku (also Sokubaku) is a Japanese style of sexual bondage or BDSM which involves tying up the bottom using simple yet visually intricate patterns, usually with several pieces of thin rope usually hemp or jute (generally 6 mm or 8 mm in diameter). The person`s body can also be hanging from the rope while tied to it.
The word Shibari came into common use in the West at some point in the 1990s to describe the bondage art Kinbaku. Shibari (縛り) is a Japanese word that literally means "to tie" or "to bind". It is used in Japan to describe the artful use of twine to tie objects or packages.
In anime/manga, Shibari or Kinbaku is often seen as a tool of rape or torture, rather than intended for a concept of bondage aesthetics.</description>
<picurl>161702.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2749" parentid="2604" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing. The wearing of clothing is exclusively a human characteristic. The amount of clothing worn depends on functional considerations (such as a need for warmth or protection from the elements) and social considerations. In some situations the minimum amount of clothing (i.e. covering of a person`s genitals) may be socially acceptable, while in others much more clothing is expected.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.
People, as individuals and in groups, have varying attitudes towards their own nudity. Some people are relaxed about appearing less than fully clothed in front of others, while others are uncomfortable or inhibited in that regard. People are nude in a variety of situations, and whether they are prepared to disrobe in front of others depends on the social context in which the issue arises. For example, people need to bathe without clothing, some people also sleep in the nude, some prefer to sunbathe in the nude or at least topless, while others are nude in other situations. Some people adopt naturism as a lifestyle.
Though the wearing of clothes is the social norm in most cultures, some cultures, groups and individuals are more relaxed about nudity, though attitudes often depend on context. On the other hand, some people feel uncomfortable in the presence of any nudity, and the presence of a nude person in a public place can give rise to controversy, irrespective of the attitude of the person who is nude. Besides meeting social disapproval, in some places public nudity may constitute a crime of indecent exposure. Many people have strong views on nudity, which to them can involve issues and standards of modesty, decency and morality. Some people have an psychological aversion to nudity, called gymnophobia. Many people regard nudity to be inherently sexual and erotic.
Nudity is to be found in a multitude of media, including art, photography, film and on the Internet. It is a factor in adult entertainment of various types.
Especially gratuitous fanservice anime shows tend to show their (usually female) characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.
Source: wiki</description>
<picurl>60576.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2782" parentid="2858" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-03">
<name>shoujo ai</name>
<description>Shoujo Ai means girls love, and thus explores what happens when two girls (or women) fall in love. This is not to be mistaken for http://anidb.net/t2695 [Yuri] which is (or, at least, how this term is often used by the western audience) used in adult works. This is not; that means there is no graphic sex.
The male version is http://anidb.net/t2783 [Shounen Ai].
http://anidb.net/t7146 [Cute girls doing cute things (CGDCT)] is often mistaken as low level Yuri or Shoujo Ai. If there is no Yuri or Shoujo Ai subtext, i.e. if there is no romantic subtext, only tag CGDCT. Please note: CGDCT and yuri/shoujo ai are not mutually exclusive; it is possible to have an anime tagged both.</description>
<picurl>210060.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2790" parentid="2605" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-01-17">
<name>plot continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2794" parentid="2883" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-23">
<name>music</name>
<description>Music anime generally revolves around people concerned with music in their everyday lives. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competitions, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal. This is not unlike the Sports category.</description>
<picurl>169131.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2821" parentid="2856" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-06">
<name>sudden naked girl appearance</name>
<description>A character or group of characters are simply minding their own business, when suddenly, a naked girl appears. It does not matter how or why, but a naked someone is there. Sometimes the naked girl is not happy about this. 
Usually this is a fanservice element, but not always.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2842" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-09-19">
<name>incest</name>
<description>Incest is human sexual activity between family members or close relatives by consanguinity (blood relations) and sometimes by affinity (marriage or stepfamily), adoption, clan, or lineage. The incest taboo is among the most widespread cultural taboos in present and past societies. Most modern societies have laws regarding incest or social restrictions on closely consanguineous marriages, with first cousins being the closest kin that is often (but not always) considered legally acceptable.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>210769.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2844" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>angst</name>
<description>A feeling of general discomfort and uneasiness is present due to either trivial or more serious reasons, often accompanied by depression.
Warning: may contain copious amounts of brooding and sighing.
Etymology: "Angst" is a German word meaning fear or anxiety.</description>
<picurl>212183.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2848" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-07-15">
<name>pornography</name>
<description>Anime clearly marked as "Restricted 18" material centring on all variations of adult sex, some of which can be considered as quite perverted. To certain extent, some of the elements can be seen on late night TV animations.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2849" parentid="7050" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2005-05-07">
<name>fantasy</name>
<description>Fantasy is a genre of fiction that uses magic and other supernatural phenomena as a primary element of plot, theme, or setting. Many works within the genre take place in fictional worlds where magic is common. Fantasy is generally distinguished from science fiction and horror by the expectation that it steers clear of (pseudo-)scientific and macabre themes, respectively, though there is a great deal of overlap between the three (which are subgenres of speculative fiction).
In popular culture, the genre of fantasy is dominated by its medievalist form, especially since the worldwide success of The Lord of the Rings books by J. R. R. Tolkien. In its broadest sense however, fantasy comprises works by many writers, artists, filmmakers, and musicians, from ancient myths and legends to many recent works embraced by a wide audience today.
Fantasy is a vibrant area of academic study in a number of disciplines (English, cultural studies, comparative literature, history, medieval studies). Work in this area ranges widely, from the structuralist theory of Tzvetan Todorov, which emphasizes the fantastic as a liminal space, to work on the connections (political, historical, literary) between medievalism and popular culture
Source: Wiki</description>
<picurl>68768.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2852" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-11">
<name>thriller</name>
<description>The thriller is a genre of fiction in which tough, resourceful, but essentially ordinary heroes are pitted against villains determined to destroy them, their country, or the stability of the free world. The hero of a typical thriller faces danger alone or in the company of a small band of companions. The protagonist may be a law enforcement agent, a journalist, or a soldier, but typically he or she is cut off from the resources of "their" organization. More often the hero is an ordinary citizen drawn into danger and intrigue by circumstances beyond their control.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>214683.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2854" parentid="2611" weight="300" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-08">
<name>henshin</name>
<description>Japanese for "transformation" (metamorphosis or disguise).
A "henshin anime" is any anime, where the characters or their costumes transform, such as Sailor Moon. The henshin switches on the character`s special powers, and is frequently accompanied by a costume change. Often the change of clothing is the only outward indicator that the character has changed and yet nobody seems to notice the hero`s true self.
Most henshin heroes have a special item which they use to change into their heroic form. These items are usually activated by a command phrase (which is often in Engrish, for some reason), triggering a transformation sequence.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2856" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-05">
<name>ecchi</name>
<description>Fan service is found in many anime, in many forms. When the service has a distinctly sexual slant to it, and it appears to be a major focus of the show, then it`s safe to assume you`re watching ecchi.
The word "ecchi" is used by English-speaking anime fans to refer to refer to soft-core pornographic or sexually suggestive anime and manga. This is a western invention; in Japanese, it is a catch-all term for all things anyhow sexual in nature, not being limited to porn, but also not really considered a "milder" term, as it may also refer to sexual intercourse itself. The term "ecchi" in Japanese comes from the pronunciation of the letter "H" in English, which is rendered into Japanese syllabary as エッチ, which in turn is transliterated in the English alphabet as "ecchi" or "etchi". It is not, as many believe, short for "hentai" -- that, too, seems to be a western invention. It is, however, nearly as misunderstood and misapplied a term as "hentai".
The line between ecchi and hentai, from the western perspective over these terms, can be hard to draw at times; one good rule of thumb is: if it was aired on Japanese public TV at all, it probably wasn`t hentai. Ecchi usually features all the specifics to human anatomy that can only be found in anime, and generally avoids full nudity, instead abusing of panty shots. Hentai, on the other hand, will usually show full frontal nudity in some explicit form, including genitalia, and full, intimate sex scenes. At its mildest, ecchi is composed of double entendres, big misunderstandings, and sexual farce; at its most explicit, it is still in the realm of softcore pornography, with full breast shots, full back nudity and similar content, but no display of genitalia. Another good way to distinguish the two is looking for animated sex scenes; if one is found, you have generally left the genre entirely, though a few borderline exceptions apply here. For AniDB`s purposes, the distinction between explicit ecchi and actual hentai is simple: if it was sold with a 18+ restriction in its country of origin, it is hentai; if it was sold without it, it is ecchi.
Source: TV Tropes</description>
<picurl>32416.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2864" parentid="2607" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>daily life</name>
<description>The antics of the protagonists do not take place in some exotic setting or time, but in everyday life. When not "at the job" this means getting up in the morning, making meals, house cleaning, going shopping or out to eat, visiting the bath house or spa, leisure activities in the spare time, etc. The time "on the job" for students is School Life, for others working in their profession. Daily Life is basically a synonym for everything normal, repetitive, and trivial happening to your average person.</description>
<picurl>210069.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2878" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>conspiracy</name>
<description>The conspiracy thriller (or paranoid thriller) is a sub-genre of the thriller which flourished in the 1970s in the US (and was echoed in other parts of the world) in the wake of a number of high-profile scandals and controversies (most notably Vietnam, the assassination of President Kennedy, Chappaquiddick and Watergate), and which exposed what many people regarded as the clandestine machinations and conspiracies beneath the orderly fabric of political life.
The protagonists of conspiracy thrillers are often journalists or amateur investigators who find themselves (often inadvertently) pulling on a small thread which unravels a vast conspiracy that ultimately goes "all the way to the top".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2883" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-07">
<name>the arts</name>
<description>The arts represent an outlet of human expression, usually influenced by culture, and driven by human creative impulse. Major constituents of the arts include literature – including poetry, novels and short stories, and epics; performing arts – among them music, dance, and theatre; culinary arts such as baking, chocolatiering, and winemaking; media arts like photography and film, and visual arts – including drawing, painting, and sculpting. Some art forms combine a visual element with performance (e.g. film) and the written word (e.g. comics).
From prehistoric cave paintings to modern day films, art serves as a vessel for storytelling and conveying mankind`s relationship with its environment.
Source: Wiki</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2887" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>tragedy</name>
<description>Tragedy is a form of drama characterized by seriousness and dignity, usually involving a conflict between a character and some higher power, such as the law, the gods, fate, or society.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2901" parentid="2729" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-12-09">
<name>bondage</name>
<description>Bondage is the use of restraints for the sexual pleasure of the parties involved. It may be used in its own right, as in the case of rope bondage and breast bondage, or as part of sexual activity or BDSM activity. When a person is sexually aroused by bondage, it may be considered a paraphilia, known as vincilagnia (from Latin vincio, to bind or fetter with chains, and lagneia, lust).
[Source: wiki]</description>
<picurl>42021.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3013" parentid="55" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-10">
<name>Newtype Anime Award</name>
<description>This anime has won 1 or more Newtype Anime Award(s)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3028" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-17">
<name>real-world location</name>
<description>Places seen in the show exist in reality.
Note: This could be sometime in the future, though names and certain places will still be recognizable.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3146" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-04-29">
<name>divorce</name>
<description>The parents depicted in this anime have divorced, usually upsetting the life of their children.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3314" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-10">
<name>fate</name>
<description>Fate — The predestined path of all things. The outcome is inevitable and the consequences predetermined. Whether or not the protagonist ultimately decides to follow this path shall weigh heavily on their soul.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3842" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-10-31">
<name>TV censoring</name>
<description>The TV version is censored and later DVD/BD releases are uncensored, so the money-grubbing capitalists can make a couple more bucks at our expense.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3870" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2016-09-11">
<name>resurrection</name>
<description>At least one character in this anime is brought back from the dead or from a near-death experience. This is achieved by either very advanced technology or simply magic.</description>
<picurl>191152.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="3934" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-04-10">
<name>non-linear</name>
<description>The story is told achronologically.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3992" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-08-17">
<name>nostalgia</name>
<description>A bitter-sweet longing for things, persons, or situations from the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4112" parentid="3842" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-07-14">
<name>excessive censoring</name>
<description>There are basically two cases to which this term can be applied to:
1) creative censorship
The TV station airing the anime does its best to remove most ecchi parts from the show, using various and original methods. Usually, an uncensored BD/DVD is released later. Apart from the publisher`s greed - sometimes the censorship is used intentionally to make a scene look more obscene than it actually is.
2) convenient censorship
Another case of it - more often known under the term of "convenient censoring/ship" - is a blatant substitute for mosaic/steam/etc. over nether regions. This applies both to normal shows with occasional nudity as a normal part of human life (or just occasional flash of fanservice), as well as to heavy ecchi / borderline hentai shows where /literally/ everything is a fair (and far more "obscene" no matter how to look at it) game, except that misinterpreted taboo nonsense coming from §175 of JPC.</description>
<picurl>169459.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4149" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="true" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-10-19">
<name>non-blood-related siblings -- DO NOT USE -- TO BE DELETED</name>
<description>This tag is set to be deleted. Please add char-char relations of the "is family of" type with the http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Content:Characters#is_family_of [appropriate relation comment] to the relevant characters and remove the tag from the corresponding anime. Thank you.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4225" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2011-02-16">
<name>symbolism</name>
<description>Representation of a more complex concept by a simple thing. Like a red flower for love or a flag for a nation.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4251" parentid="6230" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-20">
<name>ensemble cast</name>
<description>A show with an ensemble cast focuses on a larger group of main characters in a single plot narrative; anime containing several segmented plot narratives (such as episodic or arc-based plots) are excluded. As such, it doesn`t really have a "main" or "lead" character; instead, every member of the central main character group plays an important part in the show`s grander scheme; no single character is more important or prominent than the others (equality of importance). Further, subplots (if any) lead by each character in the ensemble have equal weighting in importance (or lack of weight).

* In a show where no single main character is more important or prominent than the others, 4+ main characters is almost always an ensemble cast.
* A show with 3 main characters of equal importance is likely also an ensemble cast; equality of importance must be considered carefully.
* A show with 2 main characters of equal importance is generally not an ensemble cast situation; however, on an exception basis where neither main character is considered an antagonist, a 2-main-character anime may be considered an ensemble (e.g. http://anidb.net/a11829 [Kimi no Na wa.]).

Pictured: http://anidb.net/a9043 [K (anime)]</description>
<picurl>94914.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="4280" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2008-06-02">
<name>surreal</name>
<description>Refers to things or occurrences that are generally bizarre or dreamlike, with the relentless capability of replacing reality through the eyes of the beholder. Surrealism is boundless, limited only by thought itself.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4299" parentid="6148" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-04-29">
<name>flashback</name>
<description>A flashback is a moment in which someone remembers events from their past. In fiction, flashbacks are used primarily to give insight into a character`s mind or to reveal information which had been previously kept from the audience. They normally consist essentially of new content; in some cases, they may also consist of short snippets of already displayed content, as in http://anidb.net/ch23266 [Okabe Rintarou]`s flashbacks in http://anidb.net/a7729 [Steins;Gate], but even in these cases the flashbacks are used to look into what the character is thinking. As such, they are different from and should not be confused with recaps, which are old content being shown again for no particular purpose other than padding or reminding the audience of the events up to that point. As a rule of thumb, to qualify as a flashback, the scene must advance the show`s content in some way or form; anything else is just a recap.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4479" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-02-03">
<name>sense of foreboding</name>
<description>The anime starts off quietly, everything seems to be fine, but from episode to episode the signs that something ominous is about to happen increase. E.g. a typical mystery setting.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4499" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-07-28">
<name>some weird shit goin` on</name>
<description>Scenes of this show point to insanely strange events which seem to be taking place; throughout its episodes, the show may or may not explain what is going on. Either way, many viewers will find that a succinct and accurate way to describe the show is "WTF?", and the show`s explanations (or lack thereof) to the events will often be subject of heated debate.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4522" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-03">
<name>social commentary</name>
<description>Social commentary is the act of rebelling against an individual, or a group of people by rhetorical means. This is most often done with the idea of implementing or promoting change by informing the general populace about a given problem and appealing to people’s sense of justice. (Source: Wikipedia)&#13;
&#13;
Since this is anime, usually, the mores of Japan and the Japanese society are scrutinised, but not restricted to that.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4640" parentid="6149" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-12-14">
<name>social outcast</name>
<description>Someone who has been rejected or excluded from the majority, or all of the social groups in an area (school, work, etc.). A person that does not fit in society.
They typically look slightly high or depressed and they are usually alone most the time. Some are alone because they are too snobbish and see themselves above everyone else. Others are alone because they want to be. 
They are usually the victims of every negative stereotype and rumour. Some might even be called “freaks”.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4753" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2010-03-15">
<name>disturbing</name>
<description>Watching the show may cause the viewer to have unpleasant feelings.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5417" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-22">
<name>mind fuck</name>
<description>A `mind fuck` is a slang term which describes a work that uses literary devices such as nonlinear storytelling and plot twists in order to present convoluted, yet not conflicting, themes.
A creation is usually considered a mind fuck when a casual observer is not able to discern the true meaning of a work without making a serious attempt to unravel the themes presented or when the plot is incredibly difficult to follow.
Special examples of mind fucks involve a single plot twist which completely changes the viewer`s understanding of the events in a film or novel as well as the ideas it presents.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5515" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-06-01">
<name>faceless background characters</name>
<description>Unimportant random/extra characters that appear mostly as part of the background are often drawn without much facial details, normally to save money, effort and manpower for more important parts of the show. Sometimes, they have almost or no facial details, meaning their heads only have indications of the presence of parts such as hair or mouth, or not even that. This can go as far as only drawing an abstracted silhouette of the whole body.</description>
<picurl>233515.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="5697" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-06-02">
<name>randomness</name>
<description>The anime does not follow a predictable storyline. New, strange, obscure, or otherwise unexpected story elements are introduced at a whim.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5768" parentid="6249" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-02-01">
<name>intact family</name>
<description>The main character`s family is a so-called "nuclear family". Wherein both parents are alive and present in his or her life. This is actually relatively rare for anime, where "parental abandonment" is the norm.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5843" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-16">
<name>sibling yin yang</name>
<description>In real life, siblings hardly ever act the same. Fiction sometimes takes this to an extreme.
Enter Sibling Yin Yang, the occurrence of siblings that are nearly polar opposites. If he`s cool and reckless, she`s responsible and thoughtful. If she`s a spiky-haired hooligan, he`s the nerdy wimpy one. If he`s an immature brat, she`s... well, you get the picture.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5865" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-05-22">
<name>manly tears</name>
<description>Somewhere down the line, it became the "norm" that boys don`t cry. The scenario does not matter; shedding tears is the ultimate no-no in terms of what you can and cannot do as a man (at least in the West, anyway). But there comes a time when a man`s emotions do get the better of him, and they pour forth - as prerequisite an impassioned speech may or may not be present - by cascading down his cheeks. These are what we like to call "manly tears". Extremely powerful. Not limited but often used in hot-blooded / super robot shows. Examples include Yuusha Ou GaoGaiGar, Getter Robo and Tengen Toppa Gurren Lagann.
The opposite of manly tears are "girly tears".</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5981" parentid="6232" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2009-10-12">
<name>seeking protagonist</name>
<description>The main character has a main objective that is referenced to through the whole series; he is in search of something, or someone
Should it be treasure, friends, money, power or all of the above nothing will stop our lead character in his quest to find his passion</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6062" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-04-05">
<name>heroic sacrifice</name>
<description>"In order to save the many, the few will need to sacrifice their lives..." or so this character may think. 
In a seemingly hopeless situation, against impossible odds, the character does not choose the path of the coward and run, he or she chooses to bravely face the enemy, fully aware that this will mean death.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6070" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-03-15">
<name>mystery</name>
<description>The mystery film is a sub-genre of the more general category of crime film. It focuses on the efforts of the detective, private investigator or amateur sleuth to solve the mysterious circumstances of a crime by means of clues, investigation, and clever deduction. (Source: Wikipedia)</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6148" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO EPISODE</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to episode tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what episodes they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6149" parentid="30" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>TO BE MOVED TO CHARACTER</name>
<description>Tags under this parent tag are going to be moved to character tags and removed from the anime they`re currently assigned to. They will be blocked from the anime system once that move is complete. Please help with that job if you know what characters they should be assigned to.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6232" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false" update="2014-10-21">
<name>character related tags which need deleting or merging</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6249" parentid="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-31">
<name>family life</name>
</tag>
<tag id="7050" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2019-04-18">
<name>speculative fiction</name>
<description>Speculative fiction is an umbrella genre encompassing fiction with certain elements that do not exist in the real world, often in the context of supernatural, futuristic or other imaginative themes. This includes, but is not limited to, science fiction, fantasy, superhero fiction, horror, utopian and dystopian fiction, fairytale fantasy, supernatural fiction, as well as combinations thereof.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="33249" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-09-23">
<rating votes="31">6.77</rating>
<name>Oginome Ringo</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>A student at Sakuramisono Girls High School. She has a crush on the teacher in charge of Shoma and Kamba`s class. She seems like just another student at the school, but is that really the case...?</description>
<picture>75026.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12598" picture="74984.jpg">Miyake Marie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33250" type="main character in" update="2012-07-22">
<rating votes="25">4.31</rating>
<name>Takakura Kanba</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Shouma`s brother. Unlike his brother, he has lots of romance experience and knows how to handle girls. He cares more than anyone else for his little sister Himari.
It is later revealed that he is not actually related to his siblings, but was adopted by the Takakura family after his http://anidb.net/ch38209 [real father] had died. His real sister is http://anidb.net/ch35027 [Natsume Masako].
He can see and converse with the ghost of the deceased http://anidb.net/ch35166 [Takakura Kenzan] and http://anidb.net/ch36571 [Watase Sanetoshi].</description>
<picture>75025.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="25023" picture="70106.jpg">Kimura Subaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33251" type="main character in" update="2012-07-22">
<rating votes="27">3.49</rating>
<name>Takakura Shouma</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kanba`s brother. He has almost the complete opposite personality when compared to his brother - particularly when it comes to his love life. He takes care of most of the housework for the others.
He is later revealed to be the only biological child of the Takakura family.</description>
<picture>75023.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2225" picture="192115.jpg">Kimura Ryouhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="33252" type="main character in" update="2012-07-22">
<rating votes="24">4.29</rating>
<name>Takakura Himari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Kanba and Shouma`s younger sister. She has been told by doctors that she does not have long to live, and even lost her life once - only to be revived by the mysterious power of a penguin hat.
It is later revealed that she is not actually related to her brothers. The Takakura family adopted her after she was abandoned by her real mother.</description>
<picture>75024.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27221" picture="131964.jpg">Arakawa Miho</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34315" type="main character in" update="2011-11-12">
<rating votes="46">7.87</rating>
<name>Princess of the Crystal</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76992.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27221" picture="131964.jpg">Arakawa Miho</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34667" type="appears in" update="2011-07-15">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Yamashita Yousuke</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>75576.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9955" picture="37029.jpg">Sakamaki Ryousuke</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34668" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-11-12">
<rating votes="10">2.04</rating>
<name>Tabuki Keiju</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76990.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="194" picture="130580.jpg">Ishida Akira</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34669" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-11-12">
<rating votes="5">6.90</rating>
<name>Penguin Ichigou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76997.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="25023" picture="70106.jpg">Kimura Subaru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34670" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-11-12">
<rating votes="8">8.91</rating>
<name>Penguin Nigou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76998.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2225" picture="192115.jpg">Kimura Ryouhei</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34671" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-11-12">
<rating votes="8">8.34</rating>
<name>Penguin Sangou</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76999.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="27221" picture="131964.jpg">Arakawa Miho</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34868" type="appears in" update="2011-11-12">
<rating votes="2">4.43</rating>
<name>Oginome Eriko</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76994.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1509" picture="19311.jpg">Fukami Rika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="34869" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-11-12">
<rating votes="16">5.25</rating>
<name>Tokikago Yuri</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76991.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10" picture="226529.jpg">Noto Mamiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35027" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-11-12">
<rating votes="16">8.18</rating>
<name>Natsume Masako</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76989.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="61" picture="58663.jpg">Horie Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35028" type="appears in" update="2011-11-12">
<rating votes="3">6.89</rating>
<name>Kuhou Asami</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76995.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2296" picture="189623.jpg">Hayami Saori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35166" type="appears in" update="2011-08-04">
<rating votes="3">1.19</rating>
<name>Takakura Kenzan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76457.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35167" type="appears in" update="2011-08-04">
<rating votes="3">2.19</rating>
<name>Takakura Chiemi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76458.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="240" picture="17059.jpg">Inoue Kikuko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35168" type="appears in" update="2011-08-04">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Washizuka Ishi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76459.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="2026" picture="21352.jpg">Yara Yuusaku</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="35725" type="appears in" update="2011-11-12">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Oginome Satoshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76996.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32" picture="16618.jpg">Tachiki Fumihiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36203" type="appears in" update="2011-09-02">
<rating votes="2">6.40</rating>
<name>Aoi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51205.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1614" picture="148394.jpg">Uchida Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36204" type="appears in" update="2011-09-02">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Aoi no Hahaoya</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>51206.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="388" picture="17234.jpg">Suzuki Masami</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36571" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-11-12">
<rating votes="12">6.24</rating>
<name>Watase Sanetoshi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76993.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1510" picture="49914.jpg">Koizumi Yutaka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36572" type="appears in" update="2011-11-21">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Natsume Mario</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>77436.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10080" picture="235712.jpg">Aranami Kazusa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36573" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-09-09">
<rating votes="2">4.43</rating>
<name>Isora Hibari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53856.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="24615" picture="73810.jpg">Watanabe Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36574" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-09-09">
<rating votes="2">4.43</rating>
<name>Utada Hikari</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>53874.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12598" picture="74984.jpg">Miyake Marie</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36575" type="appears in" update="2011-09-09">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Triple H</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>53876.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="36576" type="appears in" update="2011-09-09">
<rating votes="2">6.40</rating>
<name>Double H</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>53877.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="36766" type="appears in" update="2011-09-16">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Natsume Mario</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>55941.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="10080" picture="235712.jpg">Aranami Kazusa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="36767" type="appears in" update="2011-09-16">
<rating votes="2">9.90</rating>
<name>Esmeralda</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>55943.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="61" picture="58663.jpg">Horie Yui</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37542" type="appears in" update="2011-10-08">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Ikebe no Ojisan</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>66412.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1733" picture="25839.jpg">Tanaka Hideyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37750" type="appears in" update="2011-10-14">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Yuuki Tsubasa</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>69070.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="566" picture="25408.jpg">Paku Romi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37916" type="secondary cast in" update="2011-10-21">
<rating votes="3">7.68</rating>
<name>Oginome Momoka</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71151.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1438" picture="69192.jpg">Toyosaki Aki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="37947" type="appears in" update="2011-10-22">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Yuri no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>71739.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="266" picture="17091.jpg">Uchida Naoya</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38207" type="appears in" update="2011-10-28">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Renjaku</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>74852.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="6" picture="171987.jpg">Nakahara Mai</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38208" type="appears in" update="2011-10-28">
<rating votes="1">6.73</rating>
<name>Natsume Sahei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>74857.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3239" picture="225574.jpg">Ito Hiroshi</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38209" type="appears in" update="2011-10-28">
<rating votes="1">3.04</rating>
<name>Masako no Chichi</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>74860.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="60" picture="171602.jpg">Kawada Shinji</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="38639" type="appears in" update="2011-11-11">
<rating votes="2">1.62</rating>
<name>Tabuki no Haha</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>76984.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="360" picture="171401.jpg">Hisakawa Aya</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="131463" update="2011-12-23">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-07-03</airdate>
<rating votes="19">6.91</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">運命のベルが鳴る</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Bell of Fate Rings</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le glas du destin</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Suona la campana del destino</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Unmei no Bell ga Naru</title>
<summary>The Takakura household is made up of Shoma and Kanba, two twin brothers, and their younger sister Himari. Himari has been diagnosed with an incurable disease, and her doctor has determined that she does not have long to live. A few days after hearing this news, Shoma and Kanba decide to take Himari for a visit to one of her favorite places - the local aquarium. But while there, Himari catches a glance of a strange penguin...</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="131466" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-07-29</airdate>
<rating votes="14">6.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">舞い落ちる姫君</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Descension of a Princess</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La princesse s`écroule</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La principessa che discende danzando</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Mai Ochiru Himegimi</title>
<summary>Shoma wakes up earlier than normal to find Ringo standing in his kitchen - she is getting Himari to teach her to make omelets. After she has finished making the omelets, she heads out on her `date` with Tabuki at the park. While Shoma knows this is simply more of her stalking antics, he tags along with her to try and solve the mystery of the Penguindrum.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="131467" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-07-22</airdate>
<rating votes="14">5.58</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">そして華麗に私を食べて...</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Then Devour Me Courageously</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Mange-moi avec délectation</title>
<title xml:lang="it">E poi mangiami curryosamente...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Soshite Karei ni Watashi o Tabete...</title>
<summary>If the Penguindrum is something of Ringo`s, then the most likely place to find it will be in her room, so Kamba and Shoma take the day off school and sneak into Ringo`s room... however they are unable to find the Penguindrum anywhere.
But while they are still looking around, they hear the front door opening - it seems Ringo is home earlier than they expected!</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="131468" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-07-15</airdate>
<rating votes="14">6.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">危険な生存戦略</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Risky Survival Strategy</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une dangereuse stratégie de survie</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Una pericolosa strategia di sopravvivenza</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kiken na Seizon Senryaku</title>
<summary>While under the control of the mysterious penguin hat, Himari tells Kamba and Shoma that if they wish to keep their little sister alive, they need to search for the `Penguindrum` as a part of the survival strategy. Although they have no idea what the Penguindrum is, they have no choice but to follow the orders they are given and catch a specific train. There they find a girl named Ringo Oginome and believe she may have the Penguindrum, so they tail her to try find out more...</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="131643" update="2011-10-27">
<epno type="3">C3</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-07-03</airdate>
<rating votes="1">6.92</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131644" update="2011-07-08">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-07-03</airdate>
<rating votes="1">9.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="131745" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-08-05</airdate>
<rating votes="12">8.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">だから僕はそれをするのさ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">That`s Why I Do That</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">C`est pour ça que je le ferai</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Ecco perché lo faccio</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dakara Boku wa Sore o Suru no sa</title>
<summary>Himari heads back to the hospital for a check-up, and Shoma is glad to find out from the doctor that she seems to be in perfect health. Meanwhile, Kamba is back at the house speaking with his uncle, who is looking into selling the Takakura house. Kamba, on the other hand, is determined to both keep the house and the family together.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="132036" update="2011-07-20">
<epno type="4">T2</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132037" update="2011-07-20">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 1</title>
</episode>
<episode id="132154" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-08-19</airdate>
<rating votes="11">6.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">Mでつながる私とあなた</title>
<title xml:lang="en">You &amp; I Are Connected by M</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Nous sommes reliés par "M", toi et moi</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La "M" che lega te e me</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">M de Tsunagaru Watashi to Anata</title>
<summary>Kanba goes to visit his ex-girlfriend Asami in hospital, but for some reason she has absolutely no memory of ever meeting him. At the same time, Shoma is doing everything he can to be able to borrow Ringo`s diary - which means he is helping her move out of her room.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="132416" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-09-09</airdate>
<rating votes="11">7.66</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">氷の世界</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The World of Ice</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Le monde de glace</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il mondo di ghiaccio</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Koori no Sekai</title>
<summary>While trying to save Ringo, Shoma has been involved in a traffic accident. While that unfolds, Himari is back home peacefully resting - dreaming about the day that she and her brothers went out to the aquarium. In her dream, she seems to be chasing a strange penguin that nobody else can seem to see. While chasing the penguin she eventually finds herself in an elevator which takes her down to a big white library, surrounded by a grove of trees.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="132417" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-09-02</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.83</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">君の恋が嘘でも僕は</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Even If Your Love Is a Lie...</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Même si cet amour est factice, je...</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Anche se il tuo amore è una bugia, io...</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kimi no Koi ga Uso demo Boku wa</title>
<summary>Yuri has become engaged to Tabuki and the two have decided to move into a new apartment - which Ringo only finds out when she finds herself in Tabuki`s empty old house. But she does find the change of address notice that Tabuki gave to Shoma, and decides that she can still make her destiny come true. Meanwhile, Kanba decides that if Shoma fails to get the diary soon, he is going to take it from Ringo by force.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="132418" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-08-26</airdate>
<rating votes="9">5.85</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">タマホマレする女</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Tamahomare Girl</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Une Femme-Tamahomare</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Colei che prepara l`elisir di Ranamore</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tamahomare Suru Onna</title>
<summary>Ringo is still living beneath Tabuki`s house - Shoma can`t believe she is keeping it up, but still comes by to visit her. While Shoma is visiting her, Ringo gets a message on her cellphone from Tabuki, asking her out to go and watch a play with him. Ringo couldn`t be happier - until she finds out that the play`s lead actor is in fact her love rival - Yuri Tokikago.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="132932" update="2012-03-24">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-10-07</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.69</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">僕と君の罪と罰</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Our Crime &amp; Punishment</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Notre crime et notre châtiment</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il nostro delitto e castigo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Boku to Kimi no Tsumi to Batsu</title>
<summary>Although she was revived by the power of the Princess of the Crystal, Himari has once again lost consciousness, and she is in critical condition. Kamba tells the Princess of the Crystal that he will give up of his own life in order to save Himari, but it is simply not enough, and she still falls back into her death bed, leaving Kamba powerless to save her.
Just as all seems lost, a doctor named Sanetoshi Watase appears before Kamba. He tells Kamba not to give up, claiming he has some medicine that can save Himari from her unfortunate fate.
Source: Official Site</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="132933" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-09-30</airdate>
<rating votes="8">8.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">僕たちを巡る輪</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Wheel That Spins Us Round</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Ce cercle qui nous entraîne</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La ruota che gira intorno a noi</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bokutachi o Meguru Wa</title>
<summary>An incident took place sixteen years ago causing many people to lose their lives, including the life of a 10 year old girl named Momoka - Ringo`s sister. The incident was caused by Kanba and Shoma`s parents, who were members of a terrorist organization at the time. Shoma tells Ringo about this, claiming that her sister`s death was their family`s fault.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="132934" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-09-23</airdate>
<rating votes="10">8.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">ようやく君は気がついたのさ</title>
<title xml:lang="en">You Have Finally Realized It</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Tu en as enfin pris conscience</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Finalmente hai capito</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Youyaku Kimi wa Kigatsuita no sa</title>
<summary>Kamba heads to Masako Natsume`s house trying to recover the half of the diary that was taken from Ringo, however Masako says that she needs the diary just as much as he does, and refuses to hand it over.
On the other side of things, Ringo tells Shoma that the dairy was once her sister Momoka`s diary. She believes that because she was born on the day that her sister died, she was born to replace her. Shoma simply tells her that `Ringo is Ringo, and nobody else`.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="132935" update="2011-10-20">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-09-16</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.27</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">だって好きだから</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Because I Love Him</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">C`est parce que je t`aime</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Perché lo amo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Datte Suki Dakara</title>
<summary>When Shoma awakens from his accident he finds himself in a hospital bed. Kanba and Himari have been watching him overnight, and were glad to find out that he only suffered minor injuries from the accident - although just in case they are keeping him in the hospital for some tests. Meanwhile Ringo believes she doesn`t deserve to see Shoma again and is waiting in the corridor outside his room - it was after all her fault that he was involved in the accident.</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="133751" update="2011-11-29">
<epno type="3">C5</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-10-07</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 3</title>
</episode>
<episode id="133766" update="2012-03-24">
<epno type="1">17</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-11-04</airdate>
<rating votes="7">5.14</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">許されざる者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Those Who Cannot Be Forgiven</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Des êtres impardonables</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Chi non può essere perdonato</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Yurusarezaru Mono</title>
<summary>Kamba and Shouma once again go and visit Himari in the hospital. The medicine seems to be working well, as Himari is feeling as healthy as ever, and the doctor says she will be able to leave the hospital soon. Just as the two brothers are starting to relax though, the penguin hat acts up once again, informing them that the survival strategy has not yet come to an end.
If Kamba and Shouma cannot get hold of the Penguindrum soon, they will lose that which is most important to them...
Source: Official Site</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="133767" update="2012-03-24">
<epno type="1">16</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-10-28</airdate>
<rating votes="8">5.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">死なない男</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Immortal Man</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un homme immortel</title>
<title xml:lang="it">L`uomo che non muore</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shinanai Otoko</title>
<summary>Masako disguises herself as a waitress at the hot spring hotel in order to steal Yuri`s half of the diary. However, the half she manages to steal is in fact a fake that Yuri had setup beforehand.
While Masako plans her next move, the trusted maid of the Natsume family, Renjyaku, is secretly watching over Kamba and Himari. She ends up finding Himari wearing the penguin hat, where she is informed about the survival strategy...
Source: Official Site</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="133768" update="2012-03-24">
<epno type="1">15</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-10-21</airdate>
<rating votes="7">8.09</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">世界を救う者</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Saving the World</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La sauveuse du monde</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Colei che salva il mondo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Sekai o Sukuu Mono</title>
<summary>Yuri invites the depressed Ringo to a hot spring hotel to ease the pain of Shouma`s rejection. She also reveals that she was in the same class as Momoka when she was much younger. She claims that Momoka was the only one who ever loved her after finding out who she really was. Yuri approaches Ringo, telling her that she needs Ringo to become Momoka for her...
On the other hand, Shouma is regretting having said such cruel things to Ringo. He receives a message from Ringo, and then calls her to try and apologies, but when she picks up she seems to be saying some rather peculiar things...
Source: Official Site</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="133769" update="2012-03-24">
<epno type="1">14</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-10-14</airdate>
<rating votes="7">6.56</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">嘘つき姫</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Princess of Lies</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La princesse fallacieuse</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La principessa delle menzogne</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Usotsuki Hime</title>
<summary>The medicine Sanetoshi provides manages to save Himari from her death bed, but Shouma still feels guilty for what happened to Ringo`s sister, and tries to avoid her however possible. When Ringo tries to meet with him instead, he tells her that it is probably a good idea for them to not meet anymore.
On the other hand, Kamba is off trying to get the money to pay for the medicine that saves Himari - he manages to do so, but after paying Sanetoshi he asks when Himari can be released from the hospital... only to receive a rather mysterious answer.
Source: Official Site</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="134293" update="2011-11-29">
<epno type="3">C7</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-10-28</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134294" update="2012-02-29">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-10-21</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134759" update="2012-03-24">
<epno type="1">18</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-11-11</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.55</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">だから私のためにいてほしい</title>
<title xml:lang="en">So, I Want You to Be Here for My Sake</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Alors, reste pour moi</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Perciò io vorrei che tu mi stessi vicino</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Dakara Watashi no Tame ni Ite Hoshii</title>
<summary>Ringo and Himari were out shopping when Ringo received a call from Yuri, who invites her and Himari to meet for a meal. But when they arrive for the meeting, they find Tabuki instead of Yuri, and the meeting place is not a restaurant at all - it`s a construction site. Tabuki was the one who told Ringo not to have hard feelings against the Takakura family due to events in the past - but now he seems to be the one seeking revenge.
Tabuki calls Kamba and informs him that his sister has been kidnapped, and unless Kamba brings his father to meet with Tabuki... who knows what will happen is going to happen to her?!
Source: Official Site</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="134858" update="2012-03-24">
<epno type="1">19</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-11-18</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.29</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">私の運命の人</title>
<title xml:lang="en">My Fated Person</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Celui qui m`est destiné</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La mia persona del destino</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Watashi no Unmei no Hito</title>
<summary>Kamba claims that he doesn`t know where his father is, and Tabuki tells him that if he can not find the father, the children will have to pay for his sins instead. However, in the end Tabuki could not bring himself to take Himari`s life.
Soon after the incident, Himari is released from the hospital. Kamba, Shouma and Ringo all hold a little party to celebrate her return home. Himari, however, has a strange feeling about her brothers, and she can`t seem to figure out what is causing it...
Source: Official Site</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="134862" update="2011-11-29">
<epno type="3">C8</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-11-18</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134939" update="2011-11-29">
<epno type="3">C6</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-10-14</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134940" update="2011-11-29">
<epno type="3">C4</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-09-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 2</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134945" update="2012-03-24">
<epno type="1">20</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-11-25</airdate>
<rating votes="8">7.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">選んでくれてありがとう</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Thank You for Choosing Me</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Merci de m`avoir choisie</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Grazie per avermi scelta</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Erandekurete Arigatou</title>
<summary>Masako comes to visit the Takakura home while Shouma and Kanba are out, and prepares to fire a `remembrance` bullet at Himari just as Kanba and Shouma return home to stop her - but the event still causes Himari to begin to remember the truth buried deep inside her memory.
The next morning, the three are once again eating breakfast together as if nothing had happened, but when Himari mentions that Shouma`s miso soup tastes just like their mother`s, the two brothers sink into silence...
Source: Official Site</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="134947" update="2011-11-25">
<epno type="3">C9</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-11-25</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 7</title>
</episode>
<episode id="134967" update="2012-03-24">
<epno type="1">24</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-12-23</airdate>
<rating votes="9">8.03</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">愛してる</title>
<title xml:lang="en">I Love You</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Je t`aime</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Vi amo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aishiteru</title>
<summary>Kamba is attempting to change everything in order to save Himari, however Shouma believes that Kamba`s plans will not save her. The train that will determine their fate has left the station, leaving the two of them to confront each other.
Ringo manages to join them on the train, and she plans to use the spell that Momoka left in her diary in order to save Himari. She knows that if she uses the spell she will pay the price, but even so, she is willing to do whatever it takes to save Himari...
Source: Official Site</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="134968" update="2012-03-24">
<epno type="1">23</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-12-16</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.81</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">運命の至る場所</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Fate`s Destination</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Là où aboutit le destin</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Il capolinea del destino</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Unmei no Itaru Basho</title>
<summary>Himari loses consciousness as Kamba leaves her, and is taken to East Kamome Hospital. When Shouma finds out he rushes to the hospital and is told by the doctor that Himari was mumbling Kamba`s name all the way to the hospital.
Kamba on the other hand is given the chance to see Sanetoshi`s power for himself, and thus starts obeying him to the letter, as he is confident that Sanetoshi can save Himari. But according to the doctor at the hospital, Himari only has a few hours left to live...
Source: Official Site</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="134969" update="2012-03-24">
<epno type="1">22</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-12-09</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.18</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">美しい棺(ひつぎ)</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Beautiful Casket</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">Un joli cercueil</title>
<title xml:lang="it">Uno splendido feretro</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Utsukushii Hitsugi</title>
<summary>Himari has found out that Kamba is working with the remaining members of his father`s organization in order to get the money for her medicine. She swears that she will get him to stop, even if it means giving up her life.
Kamba however has learned that Himari`s medicine is no longer working for her, and so decides to follow Sanetoshi`s plans that he claims will save her. Even with Himari telling him that she is ready to die, Kamba leaves Himari and heads to Ikebukuro station...
Source: Official Site</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="134970" update="2012-03-24">
<epno type="1">21</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2011-12-02</airdate>
<rating votes="6">6.49</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">僕たちが選ぶ運命のドア</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Door of Fate We Choose</title>
<title xml:lang="fr">La porte du destin que nous choisissons</title>
<title xml:lang="it">La porta del destino che scegliamo</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Bokutachi ga Erabu Unmei no Door</title>
<summary>A reporter for a weekly magazine appears before Ringo, claiming he wants to interview the families of those affected by the incident. He also comes out with the fact that the siblings of the Takakura household are in fact not related by blood at all.
The same reporter, then finds his way to Himari. He asks about where the money used to afford her expensive medicine is coming from, which leads Himari to trail Kamba late at night to a certain secret location...
Source: Official Site</summary>
</episode>
<episode id="135184" update="2011-12-05">
<epno type="3">C10</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-12-02</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 8</title>
</episode>
<episode id="135241" update="2011-12-10">
<epno type="3">C11</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-12-09</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 9</title>
</episode>
<episode id="136517" update="2012-01-20">
<epno type="3">C12</epno>
<length>2</length>
<airdate>2011-12-16</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending 10</title>
</episode>
<episode id="143861" update="2012-09-15">
<epno type="4">T6</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 6</title>
</episode>
<episode id="143862" update="2012-09-15">
<epno type="4">T5</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 5</title>
</episode>
<episode id="143863" update="2012-09-15">
<epno type="4">T4</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 4</title>
</episode>
<episode id="143864" update="2012-09-15">
<epno type="4">T3</epno>
<length>1</length>
<title xml:lang="en">CM 3</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
