<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><anime id="9493" restricted="false">
<type>OVA</type>
<episodecount>1</episodecount>
<startdate>2013-05-26</startdate>
<enddate>2013-05-26</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Kick-Heart</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">キックハート</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="synonym">キック・ハート</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">KICK-HEART</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Kick-Heart</title>
</titles>
<similaranime>
<anime id="2900" approval="3" total="5">Ichi Pound no Fukuin</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="1">
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="314076">Two words: Yuasa Masaaki. If you like Kaiba etc., then you should also like this one.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.production-ig.co.jp/works/kickheart</url>
<creators>
<name id="721" type="Animation Work">Production I.G</name>
<name id="1670" type="Character Design">Mihara Michio</name>
<name id="49" type="Direction">Yuasa Masaaki</name>
<name id="47794" type="Music">Oorutaichi</name>
</creators>
<description>Kick-Heart is a love story between Romeo, a successful pro-wrestler, and Juliet, a nun who lives a secret double-life as a female pro-wrestler. Romeo`s secret is that he enjoys taking a beating in the ring, while Juliet feels invigorated when facing her opponents as a wrestler. When the two meet in the ring, the fireworks fly. Their story is set in the colourful backdrop of the professional wrestling world. Will Juliet reveal her true identity to the one she loves? Will Romeo be able to share his secret to the world?
Note: This production was funded by people donating money via Kickstarter</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="529">4.62</permanent>
<temporary count="531">5.86</temporary>
<review count="1">7.16</review>
</ratings>
<picture>140855.jpg</picture>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>15034</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>16149</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.production-ig.co.jp/works/kickheart</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="5">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.kickstarter.com/projects/production-ig/masaaki-yuasas-kick-heart</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Kick-Heart</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>キックハート</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>346069</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="32">
<externalentity>
<identifier>B014X138AA</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="1482" parentid="2751" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2010-09-08">
<name>wrestling</name>
<description>Wrestling is a fight between two people without weapons, in which each person tries to beat their opponent. Wrestlers use clinching, holding, locking, and leverage. It resembles ritual fighting as it avoids things that will likely lead to serious injury. It is similar to military hand-to-hand combat or self-defence systems.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2604" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>content indicators</name>
<description>The content indicators branch is intended to be a less geographically specific tool than the `age rating` used by convention, for warning about things that might cause offence. Obviously there is still a degree of subjectivity involved, but hopefully it will prove useful for parents with delicate children, or children with delicate parents.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-28">
<name>dynamic</name>
<description>Some of the central structural elements in anime are: 
Plot Continuity 
How does the plot or several plots unfold. Are they a strictly linear retelling of one big continuing story, a serial, possibly with several side stories, or is the content chopped into a set of unconnected episodes, only sharing the same setting and characters?
Stereotype Characters
Then there is the question of the character set presentation. Is it completely original, or is it your usual stereotypical character cast. Both choices have their merit, for example it would not really make much sense to reinvent the wheel for a harem anime. Fans of that genre come to expect their favourite stereotype protagonists.
Plot Twists
Finally there is the question of how complex the plot / the story unfolds. Are there side-plots that merge into the main plot leading to unexpected plot twists, or is the anime quite predictable? The latter would not be appropriate for detective stories. In harem anime on the other hand a foreseeable outcome is actually something the fans will come to expect.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2607" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-29">
<name>themes</name>
<description>Themes describe the very central elements important to the anime stories. They set the backdrop against which the protagonists must face their challenges. Be it School Life, present Daily Life, Military action, Cyberpunk, Law and Order detective work, Sports, or the Underworld. These are only but a few of the more typical backgrounds for anime plots. Add to that a Conspiracy setting with a possible tragic outcome, the Themes span most of the imaginable subject matter relevant to anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2609" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-09-01">
<name>original work</name>
<description>What the anime is based on! This is given as the original work credit in the OP. Mostly of academic interest, but a useful bit of info, hinting at the possible depth of story.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-04-22">
<name>setting</name>
<description>The setting describes in what time and place an anime takes place. To a certain extent it describes what you can expect from the world in the anime.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-08">
<name>elements</name>
<description>Next to Themes setting the backdrop for the protagonists in anime, there are the more detailed plot Elements that centre on character interactions: "What do characters do to each other or what is done to them?". Is it violent Action, an awe-inspiring Adventure in a foreign place, the gripping life of a Detective, a slapstick Comedy, an Ecchi Harem anime, a SciFi epic, or some Fantasy travelling adventure?</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2612" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>time</name>
<description>This placeholder lists different epochs in human history and more vague but important timelines such as the future, the present and the past.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2613" parentid="2610" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-09-04">
<name>place</name>
<description>The places the anime can take place in. Includes more specific places such as a country on Earth, as well as more general places such as a dystopia or a mirror world.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2624" parentid="2612" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-20">
<name>present</name>
<description>Somewhere between past and future.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2630" parentid="2613" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2012-10-13">
<name>Earth</name>
<description>The Earth is the third planet from the Sun, and the densest and fifth-largest of the eight planets in the Solar System. It is in effect a ball of hot mud, but on the surface it`s cold enough, so most of us live on it (or are supposed to). It is circa 4.5 billion years old, and, unless we humans succeed in destroying it over the next couple of centuries, it is expected to last for quite another while, though the changes in the Sun`s emissions due to its aging will likely cause the extinction of everything; the species of earthlings are guaranteed to die, even if we fail to kill them -- unless, of course, we find ourselves another planet and figure out a way to take everything there. Our little planet on a corner of this galaxy may mean nothing in the grand scheme of things, but to its inhabitants it is their home, so, as a species, we cherish it dearly, to the point many cultures even to this day deify it. Being the home to the human civilizations, the Earth is the main setting of most fiction, be it anime or otherwise, but not only are many titles set in other places, such as unrelated fantasy worlds, in a considerable number of fictional titles the Earth is actually destroyed by aggressive alien invaders.</description>
<picurl>126792.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2672" parentid="2834" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-03-05">
<name>Japan</name>
<description>Japan is a sovereign island nation in East Asia. Located in the Pacific Ocean, it lies off the eastern coast of the Asian mainland and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and China in the southwest.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>65689.png</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2750" parentid="2604" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-11-08">
<name>violence</name>
<description>Violence is the use of physical force against oneself or another entity, compelling action against one`s will on pain of being hurt.
Note: Refer to further guidance on http://wiki.anidb.net/w/Categories:Content_Indicators [the Wiki page] for how to apply tag weights for content indicators.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2751" parentid="2881" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-02-27">
<name>combat</name>
<description>Combat involves a violent conflict with the goal to establish dominance over an opponent.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2791" parentid="6230" weight="200" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-12-25">
<name>stereotypes</name>
<description>This show presents stereotypes, which are generalizations about a group of people. Examples would be saying that people from a certain country or with a certain hair color are stupid. If the show deals with comedy, the stereotypes are likely to be played on for laughs; if the show is a parody, the stereotypes will be exaggerated to have their flaws exposed and may be used as a form of social commentary.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2797" parentid="2609" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2009-05-18">
<name>new</name>
<description>Not based on anything, the story is a new work, usually made up by the people involved in creating the anime. Generally if an original work (原作) credit is given, it will be to the studio, or director, or other members of the production team.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2834" parentid="2630" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-10-04">
<name>Asia</name>
<description>Asia is Earth`s largest and most populous continent, located primarily in the eastern and northern hemispheres and sharing the continental landmass of Eurasia with the continent of Europe. Asia covers an area of 44,579,000 square kilometers, about 30% of Earth`s total land area and 8.7% of the Earth`s total surface area. The continent, which has long been home to the majority of the human population, was the site of many of the first civilizations. Asia is notable for not only its overall large size and population, but also dense and large settlements as well as vast barely populated regions within the continent of 4.4 billion people.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
<picurl>192245.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2841" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="400" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-26">
<name>action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting.</description>
<picurl>211261.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2853" parentid="2611" infobox="true" weight="500" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-02-13">
<name>comedy</name>
<description>Anime whose central struggle causes hilarious results. These stories are built upon funny characters, situations and events. A comedy anime is laced with humour and sets out to provoke laughter from the audience.
Japanese humour can be a bit strange to westerners, so if you`re new to this type of humour, just bear with it; it`ll most likely grow on you if you`re a fan of other kinds of comedy.</description>
<picurl>198104.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2858" parentid="2611" weight="100" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2017-12-01">
<name>romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
<picurl>210061.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2881" parentid="2607" infobox="true" weight="600" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2018-01-21">
<name>sports</name>
<description>Sports anime revolves around a recreational physical activity or skill. In addition they often adhere to certain genre conventions, the emphasis on training and practice in preparation for competition, characters desire for self improvement, and pursuit of a specific goal.</description>
<picurl>212185.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-12-04">
<name>unsorted</name>
<description>a bunch of tags that still need to be either deleted or moved into proper places.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3546" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2013-01-08">
<name>experimental animation</name>
<description>This anime uses distinct, alternative animation — much unlike other contemporary anime — either throughout or in individual episodes/sequences.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3718" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true">
<name>love between enemies</name>
</tag>
<tag id="3863" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2008-07-05">
<name>competition</name>
<description>Some sort of confrontation occurs in this show. The protagonists "duke it out" via various competitions.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4431" parentid="2858" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-04-06">
<name>love at first sight</name>
<description>Plot device: When two characters meet for the first time, at least one party, supposedly, immediately falls in love with the other party, and from then on tries to get to know that party better.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="4664" parentid="6151" infobox="true" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-05-18">
<name>short movie</name>
<description>Typically used when an OVA only has one part and is less than the usual 20 to 25 minutes in length.
So instead of calling it a `short episode`, the `short movie` tag is more appropriate.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="5257" parentid="2931" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="false">
<name>psychedelic</name>
</tag>
<tag id="5935" parentid="6233" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2011-07-06">
<name>ass-kicking girls</name>
<description>The female characters in the anime are very proficient in some form of martial arts, swordplay, or gunfights. They may also have super powers.</description>
<picurl>71307.jpg</picurl>
</tag>
<tag id="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-09-10">
<name>technical aspects</name>
<description>It may sometimes be useful to know about technical aspects of a show, such as information about its broadcasting or censorship. Such information can be found here.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6230" parentid="2605" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2014-10-20">
<name>cast</name>
</tag>
<tag id="6233" parentid="2611" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2015-08-11">
<name>tropes</name>
<description>A trope is a commonly recurring literary and rhetorical devices, motifs or clichés in creative works. This use is a broader redefining of a literary trope, the use of figurative language, via word, phrase, or even an image, for artistic effect, such as using a figure of speech.
Source: Wikipedia</description>
</tag>
<tag id="6358" parentid="6151" weight="0" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" verified="true" update="2016-03-18">
<name>crowdfunded</name>
<description>This anime was funded, at least partially, through a campaign on a crowdfunding website (e.g. Kickstarter, Makuake).</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="58426" type="main character in" update="2013-08-03">
<rating votes="2">7.15</rating>
<name>Maskman M</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>140844.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="644" picture="205640.jpg">Suzuki Tatsuhisa</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58427" type="main character in" update="2013-08-03">
<rating votes="2">6.10</rating>
<name>Lady S</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>140845.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="442" picture="187043.jpg">Honda Takako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58428" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-03">
<rating votes="1">3.70</rating>
<name>Father</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>140846.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="335" picture="64826.jpg">Takagi Wataru</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58429" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-03">
<rating votes="1">5.68</rating>
<name>Sister</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>140847.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="5639" picture="212814.jpg">Nitta Makiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58430" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-03">
<rating votes="1">5.68</rating>
<name>Devil Chicken</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>140848.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="9164" picture="69944.jpg">Matsumoto Shinobu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58431" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-03">
<rating votes="1">2.26</rating>
<name>Boss</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>140849.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="32782" picture="223624.jpg">Kanuka Mitsuaki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58432" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-03">
<rating votes="1">2.06</rating>
<name>Vacuum Fat</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>140850.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="28794" picture="223534.jpg">Satou Miyuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58433" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-03">
<rating votes="1">7.74</rating>
<name>Juliet</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>140851.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="442" picture="187043.jpg">Honda Takako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="58434" type="secondary cast in" update="2013-08-03">
<rating votes="1">5.68</rating>
<name>Maki Romeo</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>140852.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="644" picture="205640.jpg">Suzuki Tatsuhisa</seiyuu>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="150858" update="2013-11-05">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>15</length>
<airdate>2013-05-26</airdate>
<rating votes="4">4.38</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">OVA</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152170" update="2013-07-28">
<epno type="4">T1</epno>
<length>2</length>
<title xml:lang="en">PV 30s</title>
</episode>
<episode id="154331" update="2013-11-05">
<epno type="2">S1</epno>
<length>30</length>
<airdate>2013-06-27</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Making of Kick-Heart</title>
</episode>
<episode id="168304" update="2015-05-06">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>1</length>
<airdate>2013-05-26</airdate>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
